<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1704560425"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1704560425"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.<br/><br/>-----------------------------------<br/><br/>Something you want to say? <br/>Email us: <a href="mailto:hello@secondfacesoftware.com">hello@secondfacesoftware.com</a><br/>Support: <a href="mailto:support@secondfacesoftware.com">support@secondfacesoftware.com</a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Memories</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495450/Winter_Memories/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1704773760"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Header_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter-Memories-Cards_GIF.gif?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Trading_Others_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_1-EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/>After the unforgettable summer memories you’ve made half a year ago, Yui, Rio, and Miyuki are back. With the change of seasons and the cold falling snow, a new page to your story is about to begin. <br/><br/>Revisit the peaceful, seaside town, and spend time catching up with your family and friends.<br/><br/>What new memories will you make this winter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_3-EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Miyuki_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Rio_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_4-EN.png?t=1704773760"><br/><strong>A Relaxing, Adventure RPG<strong><br/><br/><strong>Explore the Beautiful, Seaside Town<strong><br/><br/><strong>Manage How You Spend Your TIme<strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Godfather Origin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739460/Esports_Godfather_Origin/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/游戏简介英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>"Esport Godfather" is a management simulation card game that revolves around the theme of MOBA esports. In this game, you will assume the role of a coach in an esports club and personally build your own team! Starting from scratch, what kind of playstyle will you devise for your team? In a constantly evolving meta, can you derive a unique understanding of what it takes to win? How will you unlock the potential of your handpicked athletes and mold them into superstars?<br/><br/>Ultimately, will you be able to become a legendary figure in the esports industry, crafting your own esports story and lifting the championship trophy?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/选手培养英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>Each athlete is unique! They all have their own strengths and weaknesses.<br/>If an athlete's efficiency in earning money increases over time, they are undoubtedly a skilled late-game specialist.<br/>Successful ambushes can unlock hidden potential, propelling some athletes onto the path of godlike.<br/>As a coach, it's your responsibility to analyze each athlete's characteristics, devise training plans tailored to their needs, and guide them on their journey to becoming superstars!<br/><br/>· Every athlete possesses distinct abilities that will impact their performance on the battlefield!<br/>· An athlete's hero pool is crucial for Ban &amp; Pick strategies!<br/>· The tactic cards utilized by athletes in matches serve as the foundation of all strategies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/版本变更英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>The meta environment is ever-changing!<br/>Changes in the equipment pool, the structure of economic income, and the source of decisive advantages, even slight alterations to the rules can drastically shift the priorities of Ban &amp; Pick and alter the strategic approach!<br/><br/>· Equipment will be added or removed as the versions change!<br/>· The timing of crucial team fights will shift with each version update, making team composition crucial!<br/>· Does harassment grant more gold? Do kills damage towers? Each gameplay rule brings a fresh experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/指挥战斗英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>You have the power to command the battlefield, with athletes attentively listening to your orders.<br/>Should you play it safe and focus on farming under the towers, or launch aggressive assaults and initiate attacks?<br/>Perfect team composition requires perfect leadership! The game is ever-changing, and you must face your opponents head-on!<br/><br/>· Each hero and athlete possesses their own tactic cards. It is through creative combinations and strategic application that they become unstoppable!<br/>· Offense or defense? Aggression or caution? The outcome rests in your hands. Formulate strategies and implement tactics!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/其他内容英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>· Over 50 unique heroes in the starting lineup, each with their own special abilities!<br/>· 200+ tactic cards, granting you control over the battlefield!<br/>· Diverse athlete training options! As a mentor, it's important to tailor your teachings to each individual!<br/>· Unearth young talents and cultivate new forces in the youth training camp!<br/>· Choose sponsors, a top-tier club deserves the support of top-tier sponsors!<br/>· Trash-talking sessions, asserting dominance is a must before crucial matches!<br/>· Abundance of events, includes unexpected occurrences, athlete communication, team pep talks!<br/>· Training match plans, knowing your opponents inside out ensures victory after victory!<br/>· Regular season, playoffs, transfer periods—different decisions await you at different times!<br/>· When athletes reach their limits, you must help them break through and reach new heights!<br/>· Create a custom team logo for your club!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/工作室LOGO英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones: NWO Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2487350/Alex_Jones_NWO_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the OFFICIAL Alex Jones video game! Save the world from the evil globalists’ plot to turn everyone into bug-eating pod-dwelling libtards! STAY TUNED FOR FUTURE BONUS LEVELS AND CHARACTERS.<br/><br/><strong>Classic Run-and-Gun Gameplay</strong>: Enjoy fast-paced action, intricate animations, and detailed environments as you blast your way through waves of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Unique Levels</strong>: Battle in various environments like secret underground bases, globalist conferences, and mind control facilities, all inspired by real events. Stay tuned for future levels.<br/><br/><strong>Challenging Boss Fights</strong>: Face off against the elite henchmen of the New World Order, including lizard overlords, secret society leaders, and genetically modified creatures.<br/><br/><strong>Dynamic Voice Lines</strong>: Featuring iconic and often humorous catchphrases from Alex Jones himself, adding flavor to every combat scenario. Special guest vocals by Ryan Katsu Rivera.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_06.png?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">JOIN ALEX AND HIS ALLIES </h2><br/>Every day the deep state sues, lies, defames, and KILLS law-abiding patriots who threaten their power!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_05.png?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">DEFEAT BIG TECH CUCKS and MORE</h2><br/>And other anti-American communist bosses throughout this adrenaline-inducing adventure!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_04.png?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">PLAY AS ALEX!</h2><br/>For the first time in history, experience the world through Infowars leader Alex Jones’ eyes and see the WAR he fights!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/new_screenshot_03.jpg?t=1704518222"><h2 class="bb_tag">SAVE THE BABIES</h2><br/>It’s no secret the NWO REPTILES are after our children. Play NWO Wars now to help save these innocent victims from these MONSTERS!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_02.png?t=1704518222"><br/><br/>“They’re turning the friggin frogs gay!”<br/><br/>Only Alex Jones can stop this madness and restore balance in the Brain Force!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2487350/extras/screenshot_01.png?t=1704518222"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milo and the Christmas Gift</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716140/Milo_and_the_Christmas_Gift/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							After his adventure in Milo and the Magpies, Milo is looking forward to spending a cosy Christmas at home. But a Christmas gift is about to upset his holiday celebrations, especially when said gift disappears after a little misunderstanding! Can you help Milo bring home the lost Gift and save Christmas for Marleen… and himself?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_playing_1.gif?t=1704473114"> <br/><br/>Milo and the Christmas Gift is a free-to-play short and atmospheric point-and-click adventure game created by artist Johan Scherft. The game is a spin-off story following the events in Milo and the Magpies. The game has 5 chapters and a gameplay time of around 30 minutes!<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/>■ Relaxing yet stimulating game-play<br/>Join Milo in his home and revisit some of the neighbouring gardens, but this time in a wintery Christmas wonderland! Interact with the festive environment and solve small point-and-click / hidden-object puzzles.<br/><br/>■ Captivating artistic atmosphere<br/>Each hand-painted, interior and snowy garden Milo has to search through has its unique personality, reflecting that of Milo’s owners and next-door neighbours respectively.<br/><br/>■ Atmospheric soundtrack<br/>Each chapter has its own festive theme song composed by Victor Butzelaar.<br/><br/>■ Average playtime: 15-30 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2716140/extras/Milo_Toby_snow_1.gif?t=1704473114"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704471185"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704471185"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704471185"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704471185"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704471185"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1703493452"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1703493452"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1703493452"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Expanse: A Telltale Series</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1708010/The_Expanse_A_Telltale_Series/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1708010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the exciting universe of The Expanse like never before in Telltale’s latest adventure, The Expanse: A Telltale Series. Take on the role of Camina Drummer and explore the dangerous and uncharted edges of the Belt aboard the Artemis. From scavenging wrecked ships in a zero-g environment, to surviving a mutiny, to combating fearsome pirates, you make the difficult choices and reveal Camina Drummer’s resolve in this latest Telltale adventure.<br/><br/><strong>A TELLTALE STORY LIKE NO OTHER</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the role of Camina Drummer, the Executive Officer aboard the Artemis, a scavenging ship hunting for a big score in the outer regions of the Belt. You must corral a crew rife with tense relationships and powerful personalities, and make tough decisions that will decide everyone’s fate.<br/><br/><strong>EXPLORE THE BELT IN ZERO-G</strong><br/><br/>Scour shipwrecks, use mag boots to walk on walls and ceilings, and utilize zero-g thrusters to float through the void. As you fly through sections of ships and the open expanse of space, interact with objects in the world and converse with members of the crew in the largest and most immersive exploration of any Telltale game to date.<br/><br/><strong>DIFFICULT CHOICES, GRAVE CONSEQUENCES</strong><br/><br/>Contend with the unforgiving brutality of space, the politics of a corrupt solar system, the animosities of your crew, and Drummer’s own conflicting responsibilities to the people she cares about and the Belt she has sworn to protect. There is no right or wrong path - only your choices and the consequences they unleash.<br/><br/><strong>INCLUDES ALL 5 EPISODES</strong><br/><br/>Episode 1: Archer's Paradox<br/>Episode 2: Hunting Grounds<br/>Episode 3: First Ones<br/>Episode 4: Impossible Objects<br/>Episode 5: Europa's Folly						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1704392583"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1702747783"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1703278835"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Get in the groove –</strong> featuring 90+ minutes of catchy and electrifying original music by <i>Minecraft</i> composer Aaron Cherof!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1703278835"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1702633213"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1702633213"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1702633213"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Frontiers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/814730/Rogue_Frontiers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/814730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/814730/extras/RF_Fight_350_small_feather.gif?t=1704771856"><br/>Embark on a bone-chilling journey of survival and terror with your comrades, as you traverse a perilous realm filled with unfathomable horrors lurking in every corner. Brace yourself for heart-pumping battles against bloodthirsty beasts, honing your skills and mastering your craft to emerge victorious in the face of insurmountable odds.<br/><br/>With every step you take, you'll encounter diverse locales, each more treacherous than the last, and daunting obstacles that will test your mettle to the core. But you'll have no choice but to press on, constructing an unbreachable fortress to shield you from the darkness that threatens to consume you.<br/><br/>And yet, even your fortress may not be enough to withstand the unrelenting onslaught of your foes. You must hone your tactics, refine your strategy, and outwit the most cunning of enemies if you hope to survive.<br/><br/>In Rogue Frontiers, there is no room for error. Every decision you make could mean the difference between life and death. But with each victory, you'll grow stronger, more resilient, and better equipped to face the next challenge.<br/><br/>And with frequent updates featuring bug fixes, balance adjustments, and fresh content drops, Rogue Frontiers is an ever-evolving nightmare, where your feedback and input will help shape the future of the game. So join the fray now, and leave your mark on the annals of horror gaming forever. But be warned: once you enter, there may be no escape.<br/><br/><strong>EXPLORE THE WORLD</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/814730/extras/RF_Temple_Orc_350.gif?t=1704771856"><br/>Unleash your sense of adventure and step into a world steeped in mystery and intrigue. Explore a vast and varied landscape, brimming with dangerous foes to conquer, precious resources to gather, and hidden secrets to uncover.<br/><br/>Prepare to battle bloodthirsty monsters at every turn, as you journey through treacherous terrain, encountering unique adversaries with their own deadly abilities and cunning tactics. Only the bravest and most skilled adventurers will survive the perils that lie ahead.<br/><br/>But the greatest rewards await those who dare to venture into the most perilous dungeons, facing the most challenging creatures in their quest for glory. These ancient, labyrinthine tombs are filled with untold riches, rare artifacts, and coveted crafting recipes, but they are also home to the deadliest monsters in the land.<br/><br/>Surviving these harrowing encounters will require every ounce of skill and strategy you possess, as you adapt to ever-changing circumstances and employ every weapon in your arsenal. Only those with the courage and fortitude to persevere will emerge victorious, earning their place among the greatest adventurers of all time.<br/><br/>So prepare to immerse yourself in a world of endless possibility, where danger and reward go hand in hand. Gather your wits, arm yourself to the teeth, and embark on a journey unlike any other. The fate of the realm rests in your hands.<br/><br/><strong>DEFEND YOUR STRONGHOLD</strong><br/>Forge unbreakable fortresses, the last bastion of hope in a world teeming with danger and chaos. With a comprehensive building system, you can personalize both the interior and exterior of your structures, creating a safe haven from the perils that lie ahead.<br/><br/>But it won't be easy. As you advance through building tiers, enhancing and expanding your stronghold, you'll have to stay one step ahead of the hostile Horde, who launch regular assaults on your base.<br/><br/>To fend off these relentless attackers, you'll need to construct traps and defensive structures that will keep them at bay. Every decision you make could mean the difference between life and death, so you'll need to employ all your ingenuity and strategic thinking to survive.<br/><br/>But the rewards are worth the risk. With every upgrade to your fortress, you'll become stronger, more resilient, and better able to withstand the onslaught of your enemies. And as you progress through the game, you'll unlock new and more powerful building options, allowing you to customize your stronghold to suit your playstyle.<br/><br/>So gather your materials, fire up your imagination, and set to work building the ultimate fortress. The Horde may be relentless, but with the right combination of traps and defensive structures, you can hold them off indefinitely. Do you have what it takes to survive in this hostile world? The fate of your fortress, and your survival, rests in your hands.<br/><br/><strong>GATHER, CRAFT AND SURVIVE</strong><br/>Survival is the name of the game in this harsh and unforgiving world, and you'll need all your wits and resourcefulness to make it through each day. Collect materials from the environment and fashion them into weapons, armor, tools, and defenses that will help you stay alive and fend off the dangers that lurk around every corner.<br/><br/>But survival isn't just about brute strength and firepower. You'll need to be able to cultivate crops and vegetables, cook food, concoct drinks and potions, and upgrade your living space to create a safe and comfortable haven in this hostile world.<br/><br/>As you progress through the game, you'll face more formidable foes, and you'll need to discover new items to craft in order to stay ahead of the game. With each new challenge you overcome, you'll gain experience and become more skilled at gathering, crafting, and surviving.<br/><br/>But be warned: the challenges will be many, and the stakes will be high. You'll need to be able to adapt quickly to changing circumstances and make split-second decisions that could mean the difference between life and death.<br/><br/>So strap on your boots, grab your tools, and get ready for an unparalleled experience of gathering, crafting, and survival. This world is unforgiving, but with the right combination of skill, luck, and determination, you just might make it out alive.<br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Venture forth into an enormous, meticulously crafted world where every locale boasts a distinct ambience, unique foes, and resources.<br/></li><li>Embark on your odyssey solo or team up with up to 32 players on player-hosted servers and brace yourself for scaling enemy difficulty.<br/></li><li>Explore extraordinary biomes, each offering its own special ingredients to gather, monsters to battle, and dungeons to delve into.<br/></li><li>Indulge in a highly detailed crafting system where you can hone your skills and create hundreds of items, unlocking endless possibilities.<br/></li><li>Choose from dozens of weapons and armor types, progressing through various tiers as you journey through the world.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in stamina-based combat that rewards preparation and skill. Utilize weapon types with unique attacks, different blocking styles, ranged combat, dodges, and parries to combat your enemies.<br/></li><li>Fuel your adventure with a rewarding food system where you gain health, stamina, and regeneration buffs depending on the foods you consume.<br/></li><li>Experience a flexible building system that takes structural integrity into account, allowing you to create anything from a small shelter to an entire village, claim abandoned buildings as your own, and customize them to your liking.<br/></li><li>Protect your base from the Horde, who will launch attacks on all your bases. Or, make sacrifices to them beforehand and they will skip an attack, adding a whole new level of strategic gameplay. Get ready for the ultimate survival adventure!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Party 丧尸派对</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2507630/Zombie_Party/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Zombie Party" is an anti-superhero-themed strategy game. You need to play the role of a chaotic ability user GRAVEDIGGER, and use your super power to summon the zombie army to destroy the land that is governed by the government and the PARLIAMENT OF FIVE, The established order of power.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/小标题文字1_EN.png?t=1704765698"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/1.gif?t=1704765698"><br/>You can use your superpowers to summon thousands of zombies and form an army of the living dead loyal to you. But be aware that once summoned, most of them will tend to act according to their bloodthirsty instincts. At this time, you need to summon more powerful special infected. They will perform their respective duties and become an important aid for you to fight against the enemy.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/小标题文字2_EN.png?t=1704765698"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/2.gif?t=1704765698"><br/>Using your powerful Chaos abilities on the battlefield, whether it is to amplify friendly troops or let them self-destruct and damage enemies, will have a vital impact on the entire battle situation.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/小标题文字3_EN.png?t=1704765698"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/3.gif?t=1704765698"><br/>In a secret corner where no one is watching, you will build a refuge for those with super powers. Configure upgrade modules for various instruments and buildings to make your abilities more powerful<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/小标题文字4_EN.png?t=1704765698"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2507630/extras/4.gif?t=1704765698"><br/>The conflict and hatred could no longer be suppressed. He embarked on the road of revenge and fought fiercely with more than a dozen heroes. Become a [gravedigger] to destroy all this hypocrisy and injustice, and sound the death knell for the sanctimonious superhero.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primateria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1397130/Primateria/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1397130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1397130/extras/FUSION_EDIT.gif?t=1704762501"><br/><br/>Embark on an epic journey in Primateria, a game redefining the roguelike deckbuilder with a nod to classic Yu-Gi-Oh! experience. Fuse cards, battle divine beings, and navigate through a universe teeming with challenges and surprises. Embrace the thrill of endless combinations and tactical depths.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Revolutionary Infinite Fusion:</strong> Primateria redefines deck-building with its innovative infinite fusion system. You can infinitely merge cards to create more potent tokens, breaking free from the confines of traditional turn-based mechanics. This system, while drawing inspiration from classics like Yu-Gi-Oh!, introduces a distinct and innovative twist.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Unleash High Attack Combos: </strong>Primateria empowers you to unleash powerful combo attacks through the unique abilities of each card, providing a thrilling and satisfying gameplay experience that captures the essence of the most dramatic moments in card battle games.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Strategic Fusion Summoning:</strong> Elevate your summoning tactics by perfectly matching levels for fusion. Every decision you make, every move you plan, becomes a crucial part of your strategic journey, demanding your tactical foresight and mastery.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Balanced Risk and Reward with Card Devolution:</strong> Face the unique challenge where high-level cards, upon defeat, transform back into their original forms rather than being destroyed. This balanced risk-reward system keeps your strategic play dynamic and engaging, constantly calling for your tactical adaptability.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Adaptive Mana Pool System:</strong> Primateria introduces a unique mana pool system tied to the fusion mechanic. This system doesn’t just govern card play but also powers up your special abilities, adding an additional layer of strategy to your gameplay.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>“Dual Graveyard” Dynamics: </strong>Primateria introduces a dual graveyard system – the "Damage Pile" and "Discard Pile," adding complexity to the management of defeated and discarded cards and introducing a new strategic element to the gameplay.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Protection &amp; Repositioning Mechanic: </strong>The game's design incorporates frontline and backline battle dynamics, forcing you to think critically about card placement and repositioning strategies, enhancing the depth of tactical play.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Rich, Expansive Universe: </strong>Set in a beautifully crafted world, Primateria offers a narrative-rich experience. Players, as "Polupus," embark on a journey filled with divine entities and mythical challenges, making each playthrough not just a game but a story unfolding.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Roguelike Elements for Endless Replayability: </strong>With a variety of relics, consumables, and ever-changing maps, the game offers you immense replayability, ensuring that no two playthroughs are the same.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Almighty Legendary Cards:</strong> To make playing cards even more exciting, new legendary cards can be summoned by fulfilling very specific conditions and challenges during a run. These incredibly powerful cards have amazing new art and represent the divine characters in the game.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1397130/extras/legendary_cards.png?t=1704762501"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here's some of the new and exciting things you can expect on the full game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A complete story mode with 9 unique quests, a thrilling story and a bunch of characters!<br/></li><li>100+ cards, with hundreds of effects, mechanics and endless combos!<br/></li><li>43 Steam achievements for you to challenge yourselves and unlock!<br/></li><li>12 unique pre-built decks with specific archetypes for you to explore, including a Random Deck for experienced players to challenge their might!<br/></li><li>20+ special items that can be found and used in runs to enhance your chances of reaching the surface!<br/></li><li>10+ challenging nodes for exploration!<br/></li><li>A new and improved Endless Mode with challenging bosses, enemy encounters, exploration and much more!<br/></li><li>A gallery system that serves as a compendium for all cards, items and unlockables in the game so you can track your progress!<br/></li><li>A meta-progression system that allows you to gain experience, level up, and unlock all sorts of magical items and cards for your Primateria journey!<br/></li><li>And much, much more!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before The Sun Rises</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2648370/Before_The_Sun_Rises/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2648370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Before the Sun Rises is a 3D exploration and platform game about connection with nature and others. You play as a water drop, born from the misty dew of dawn. Can you restore the forest of your birth before the sun rises?<br>
<br>
In single player, explore the landscape to find and collect the water that you need to bloom trees and move onto the next area. In multiplayer, connect with friends or strangers online, help each other find water sources, and work together to restore the forest! <br>
<br>
NOTE: The current version of Before the Sun Rises is a demo and work in progress. While multiplayer is available, it is still being tested and is currently in beta.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH ALL - FLIES</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2749720/SEARCH_ALL__FLIES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2749720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SEARCH ALL - FLIES</h2> is a hidden object game in which you need to find all the flies in a large location. The flies will be located in a variety of places, from the most prominent to barely noticeable places. The entire game location looks lively because of the animation elements. Find all the flies! Don't let them go unnoticed :)<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/>- Animation elements on location;<br/>- 100 flies to find;<br/>- Pleasant soundtrack;<br/>- The gameplay can be interrupted at any time, and the game will automatically save the result;<br/>- Implemented hints! If you find it difficult to find an item, use the hint!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching For Rest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2338240/Searching_For_Rest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							When you died your body could not be found, a funeral was held and an empty casket was lowered into your grave. Many years later your soul has brought you back from death to finally find eternal rest.<br/><br/><strong>50+ Unlocks</strong><br/>Advance your Necropolis and unlock game altering upgrades as you play. Discover Curses that influence your gameplay in different ways.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338240/extras/NecropolisGIF.gif?t=1704751296"><br/><br/><strong>Strategic Gameplay</strong><br/>Fight fearsome foes and gain unique abilities each time you venture through the cemetery. Uncover the mystery of your unending search and fight powerful bosses in the Catacombs.<br/><br/><strong>Deckbuilding and Upgrades</strong><br/>Create the perfect graveyard and obtain powerful upgrades on your search for rest. Mix and match different upgrades each time you play to create unstoppable builds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338240/extras/UpgradeGIFSFR.gif?t=1704751296"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat Guess Games</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2523390/Chat_Guess_Games/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2523390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Chat Guess Games is a community game for Twitch Streamers. A game for your community to battle it out and see who truly knows the most about video games!<br/><br/>Screenshots, artwork, genres, release year and more are displayed on screen and chat races to guess the correct game first!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Rounds can be started with chat commands, from within the game, or users can use their channel points to redeem a round.</li><li>Autoplay mode where the rounds keep coming, perfect for engaging viewers during breaks.</li><li>Channel Leaderboards to encourage competition in your community and Global Leaderboards to compete against other channels and see which community is best at game trivia.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien Slayer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2663260/Alien_Slayer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A top-down rogue-like shooter. Customize your weapons with looted upgrades to stay alive as long as possible. Freely combine different upgrades to make use of their synergy and craft your own unique way of playing.<br>
Each round your face of against and ever increasing numbers of enemies that become stronger as the game progresses.<br>
Collect valuable upgrades and different guns along the way that help you survive.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Office Nightmare Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2657220/Office_Nightmare_Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2657220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are working as an office worker and you just finished your work late when everyone left except you, then when you try to leave you realize that your boss trapped you in your office so you need to find a way out by solving puzzles, exploring the place, fight monsters, finding keys, reveal the truth about the place to world and destroy it, stop the evil plans of the owner behind the plans, this game is constantly updated by continuing the story, fixing bugs, making the game look better visually						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running Through The Beat</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2607960/Running_Through_The_Beat/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Make one with the music and Run Through The Beat!<br/><br/>This fast paced parkour game is scattered with obstacles, some of them move with the tempo of the music. Run, slide, glide on the walls and reach the beam of the end.<h2 class="bb_tag">The obstacles</h2><strong>- Blue walls stop you.</strong><br/><strong>- White is the ground.<br/>- Yellow and Orange walls can be run on.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607960/extras/yellowResized.gif?t=1704746894"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607960/extras/orangeResized.gif?t=1704746894"><br/><strong>- Purple makes you faster when you slide on them.</strong><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607960/extras/purpleResized.gif?t=1704746894"><br/><strong>- Red is moving on the Beat.</strong><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607960/extras/redResized.gif?t=1704746894"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crystal Guardians Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2744890/Crystal_Guardians_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2322090" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2322090</a><br/><br/><strong>The prologue will be a small slice of the full game</strong><br/><br/>Crystal guardians is a rogue-like tower defense game where you need to defend your base crystal on an expanding procedural generated battlefield. Gain a strategic advantage using the many towers + crystal combinations and unique item combinations stored in those towers. Make use of the expanding battlefield by placing towers on strategic position for maximal damage to the enemies.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features of the prologue</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Enjoy the first 40 waves in the prologue version<br/></li><li> Procedural generated levels, every run is different <br/></li><li> Upgrade towers using items<br/></li><li> Currently over 50 items available<br/></li><li> 25 tower combinations<br/></li><li> Extensive meta progression<br/></li><li> Loads of different enemies</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Procedural expansion</h2><br/>Keep expanding the battlefield while fighting off relentless waves of enemies. Use the newly gained grounds to gain an advantage on the enemies or find the lands secrets.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744890/extras/progression-showcase-final-optimized.gif?t=1704740899"><h2 class="bb_tag">A roguelike system</h2><br/>Buy and use items on your towers to create the optimal strategy for you. With currently over 50 items to choose from.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744890/extras/roguelike-showcase-final-optimized.gif?t=1704740899"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unique Bosses</h2><br/>Adapt your strategy to the unique boss waves<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2744890/extras/boss-showcase-final-optimized.gif?t=1704740899"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quadruzzle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2533410/Quadruzzle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Puzzle difficulty squared!  Quadruzzle is an exciting brain teasing logic, spatial, and word puzzle all wrapped into one.  Each day you will be tasked with solving a new puzzle.  Each puzzle consists of 3 four letter words, and 1 three letter word scrambled in a 4x4 tile box.  Solve the puzzle by guessing each of the four color coded words and moving their corresponding letter tiles into the proper place.  If you have ever played the popular 15 logic puzzle then this game will be very intuitive.  Solving these word puzzles will tax your problem solving and spatial skills to the max.  Don't let the four letter words and the ever popular three letter word fool you.  Solving these words will put your vocabulary knowledge to the test.  And even if you do know each word, lining up their corresponding letters in the proper locations to form the word (ups the challenge level of this puzzle) is another level of difficulty.  Put your problem solving, word knowledge, spatial skills to work with Quadruzzle.<br/><br/><strong>The Word Clues</strong><br/>There are 4 words to solve in the puzzle, and there are clues to solving each word.  The Word Clues are in colored boxes to the left of the play field.  Each clue corresponds to the row and color of the word to be solved.  The colors are Yellow for the word on the first row, Blue for the word on the second row, Red for the word on the third row, and Green for the final 3 letter word on the bottom row. If the text is too small, the player can tap the clue box to enlarge it for easier viewing. <br/><br/><strong>The Playfield</strong><br/>The playfield consists of a 4 x 4 grid of 16 spaces, 15 of which are taken up by lettered tiles leaving one open space.  The player can move the 15 lettered tiles by tapping or dragging them into an adjacent empty space.<br/><br/><strong>Solving Words</strong><br/>All letter tiles are grey at the start of the game.  When you move a tile to its proper location it will change colors to match the word color and its clue box to the left of the playfield.  If a tile is moved from its proper location it will turn back to grey.  When all of the letter tiles for a word are placed in their proper location, you will know immediately as they will all be the correct color, play a special animation, and make a special sound.<br/><br/><strong>Solving The Puzzle</strong><br/>Only when <strong>ALL</strong> of the tiles for all 4 words are in their proper location will the puzzle be considered solved.  When this happens all four words in the puzzle will animate and make a puzzle complete sound.  This will denote the puzzle as solved.  After this you will have to wait until the next day's puzzle is released to play again.<br/><br/><strong>Colorblind Players</strong><br/>Since the game uses a lot of color coding, we have added the ColorADD system to the game.  This system will let those with any form of colorblindness play the game as each word tile, clue box, and any associated colored objects in game will have a special color code.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trippy's Disc Golf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2477030/Trippys_Disc_Golf/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2477030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Trippy's Disc Golf, an open world disc golf experience where you can explore a map and throw discs from wherever to wherever you like!<br>
<br>
In Trippy's Disc Golf, you'll be able to explore several maps as they are built out and added to the game, seeing vastly different maps, ranging from a casual little forest with a cute village nearby, or play disc golf around an active volcano! Maps are still being made and will be included at no charge to people who have purchased the game!<br>
<br>
As with maps, you will have a variety of discs to choose from, with more coming out after release for free to the user!<br>
<br>
With dynamic weather, a sun that moves based on your real time, and lanterns that light up at appropriate hours, we hope that this game is a little immersive, so that you can enjoy the sights to behold in the environment, as beautiful god-rays pierce the clouds and shadows are cast by the trees.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popmoji</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2746220/Popmoji/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							🤩 In Popmoji you combine two of the same emojis to create bigger emojis until the cycle is finished. But the bigger they get...the less space you'll have to place them!<br>
<br>
😲 Strategically drop emojis in the box to match and create bigger ones!<br>
<br>
🥶 Use abilities to create crazier scenarios, and increase your chances of survival!<br>
<br>
🤺 Fight for the best spot on the leaderboard!<br>
<br/>
Includes 11 different emojis in the cycle and 15 different abilities!<br/>
<br/>
Inspired by the viral Suika Game; now with a new coat of paint, and abilities to make it feel like the next weird mixed-genre Vampire Survivors!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Town Idle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2207490/Factory_Town_Idle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2207490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Factory Town Idle is a unique town builder that takes place entirely within a massive living spreadsheet. At the start, simple clicks will harvest resources, create housing &amp; production buildings, and assign workers to craft items. You'll choose which items to sell at the markets, and which to refine into better items. As you gain experience, you'll acquire tools that help automatically manage your growing town - which you will need in order to manage its increasing demands.<br/><br/>Eventually you will gain the ability to expand into exotic biomes, unlocking valuable resources &amp; recipes exclusive to those regions. All along, you'll need to invest your earnings back into research and upgrades so that your town can earn you increasingly large piles of coins.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A huge variety of items to craft &amp; sell, including gourmet food, tailored clothing, steam-powered tech, jewelry, and potions<br/></li><li>Discover new recipes as your production skills increase<br/></li><li>Cultivate crops and prospect for ores to boost natural resources<br/></li><li>Huge list of quests which unlock powerful perks when completed<br/></li><li>Discover aqueducts, water wheels, steam power, electricity, machinery, and also magical powers that let you add enchantments to items<br/></li><li>Several different Biomes with unique resources, as well as advantages &amp; weaknesses to work around<br/></li><li>Exchange goods between multiple towns to maximize the benefit of local specialties<br/></li><li>Detailed production stats let you know where your bottlenecks are so you can keep your supply chain flowing<br/></li><li>Set production limits and priorities to precisely allocate your resources<br/></li><li>While away from the game, you earn Time Tokens you can use to fast-forward the simulation when you're ready to play again</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Human: GO!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717630/The_Last_Human_GO/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717630/extras/aboutgame.jpg?t=1704736531"><br/>The Last Human: GO! It is a third person Adventure parkour game. Our main character, Lizz, is interested in science. He develops a device in his room, the purpose of which is to make micro-little creatures grow a little bigger. On Lizz's first attempt, something goes wrong and wreaks havoc on the universe. Its neighbors have disappeared and there is no one in the world except animals, various creatures and plants. It is unknown whether Lizz got smaller or everything in the world got bigger. Lizz quickly looks for ways to go to her room. When she reaches her room, the device is damaged and its parts are scattered to different points of the universe. Lizz goes on an adventure to solve this situation and starts looking for the missing pieces.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2719950/Unveiling/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You drive a car when a UFO crosses the road. You get abducted, but what comes next is not what you expect.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719950/extras/1.gif?t=1704734394"><br/><br/>It's an enigmatic trip of your mind towards the mind of the Other. It has something to say to you. Will you listen? Will you understand?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719950/extras/2.gif?t=1704734394"><br/><br/>The gameplay of "Unveiling" is simple and the puzzles are unobtrusive. You move through mind-bending environments, wrapped in striking visuals, and interact with pieces of the story.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719950/extras/Unveiling_PuzzleResized.gif?t=1704734394"><br/><br/>This 30-minute experience is inspired by the love of sci-fi and the resurgence of UFO/UAP in the modern psyche. It explores a moment of contact and the possible motives of Non-Human Intelligence.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2719950/extras/Unveiling_Gif_01.gif?t=1704734394"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Flame: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517810/The_Last_Flame_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_1.png?t=1704771070"><br/>The Last Flame is a roguelike auto-battler which focuses on build creation, strategy and decision making. Recruit special heroes, fight deadly encounters, loot and craft powerful gear, discover and create unique synergetic builds! Every run, you will need to create powerful builds that will take down your foes!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_A3.gif?t=1704771070"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_2.png?t=1704771070"><br/>The Last Flame offers an incredible amount of build diversity. Combine heroes, items, relics and origins together to create amazing builds! Hero and team building have been designed with flexibility and freedom at their core which allows you to discover and create unique synergetic builds every single run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Builds.gif?t=1704771070"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_3.png?t=1704771070"><br/>In between the automated combats, you will have to cleverly guide your heroes through the adventure by making the smart decisions! Manage your resources, choose the optimal path in the map, make powerful builds, and strategically position and plan the combat phase!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Tactical.gif?t=1704771070"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/comingToFullVersion.png?t=1704771070"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get access to a lot more stuff! Make amazing builds with over 250 items, 55 heroes, 120 relics and 55 origins.<br/></li><li>Continue the adventure in the third act, and meet the final boss in a special act!<br/></li><li>Face 30 challenging enemies and 10 bosses!<br/></li><li>Progress through 5 difficulties which will challenge your knowledge and strategy!<br/></li><li>Push your builds to their limit in the endless mode, a mode where you try to reach the highest floor!<br/></li><li>Experience the game in diverse and fun new ways with the challenge modes!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_ENDLESS.gif?t=1704771070"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Search In The Wild West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2631580/Cat_Search_In_The_Wild_West/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2631580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2631580/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__17_.gif?t=1704732331"><br/><strong>Yee ha!</strong><br/><br/>The cats are hiding all over this western town! Can you find the all? Some cats are more hidden than others. Some rest on the rooftops, others inside buildings, while others in plain view. Keep an eye out for the hidden wanted posters, maybe the cat outlaws are lurking nearby!<br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🐱100 Hidden cats</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🤠5 Hidden cat outlaws</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>📜5 Hidden wanted posters</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🔎10 Hints</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🏜️Hand-Drawn western town</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>😸A lot of meowing sound effects</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🏆100 Achievements!</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supernormal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2532430/Supernormal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2532430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>For the last two years, I've had the honour of developing the spiritual successor to Allison Road, with the blessing of its original creator. It's designed and optimized for both old and next-gen hardware. This has been a solo journey for me, and I like to think of it as <i>Allison Road, Reimagined</i>. I've put my heart and soul into this project, and I truly hope you enjoy it. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2532430/extras/Gif_01_V2.gif?t=1704730003"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><h2 class="bb_tag">SOLVE THE CASE</h2>Your detective skills shape the story, leading to one of two different endings. It all depends on the number of clues you discover and how observant you are. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><h2 class="bb_tag">VOICE RECOGNITION</h2>Communicate with the paranormal entities using your microphone. Will they offer crucial clues or mislead you into dead ends?</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><h2 class="bb_tag">MICROPHONE DETECTION</h2>Engage with the paranormal, but remember this crucial rule: if they unveil their presence and hear you, STAY QUIET and DON'T MOVE, or risk altering the game's ominous outcome.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><h2 class="bb_tag">PHOTOSCANNED GRAPHICS</h2>Using Unreal Engine 5, the game is set in a hyper-realistic environment. It also uses photo scanned graphics to enhance every tiny detail, including the horror!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><h2 class="bb_tag">RANDOMIZED PARANORMAL EVENTS</h2>Introduces unpredictable, spine-chilling encounters that are randomly generated throughout the gameplay. No two scares are alike, intensifying the terror and replayability.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">SUPERNORMAL OFFERS ABOUT 2 HOURS OF GAMEPLAY AND COMBINES DETECTIVE WORK WITH PUZZLE-SOLVING IN A HORROR SETTING. EXPECT TO SEARCH FOR CLUES AND SOLVE PUZZLES TO PROGRESS THROUGH THE GAME.</h2> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path of Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2293130/Path_of_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2293130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Path of Survivors</strong> is a <strong>multi-class auto-battler survival</strong> game with <strong>roguelite</strong> elements. <br/><strong>Demo save data will carry over to the full version!</strong><br/><br/>You can have <strong>up to six playable characters</strong> on your team auto-battling their way through <strong>hundreds of mobs</strong> on the screen<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2293130/extras/Movie_0422023-06-09662x250.gif?t=1704730853"><br/><br/>Plan your path in the 1000+ nodes passive tree<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2293130/extras/Movie_0572023-06-09662x250.gif?t=1704730853"><br/><br/>Pick <strong>ability altering rewards</strong> to spice up the run after defeating bosses<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2293130/extras/Movie_0582023-06-09662x250.gif?t=1704730853"><br/><br/>Craft gear to help your battlers survive in this fast paced world<br/>Earn <strong>experience and loot</strong> to help you prepare for the next run.<br/><strong>Various playing modes</strong> available to suit your needs (fully auto, all manual, or a mix)						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drilbert</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2338630/Drilbert/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FRWtg6RCqqG" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338630/extras/gif_spin.gif?t=1704711666"/></a><br/>Help Drilbert the drill boy recover his stolen gold! <br/>Drilbert is a short puzzle game with a unique digging mechanic, made by a solo developer. I hope you like it! Music by Nicole Marie T.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Unlimited undo<br/></li><li> Super moddable: comes with level editor and source code<br/></li><li> Steam workshop support for custom map packs<br/></li><li> Full controller support<br/></li><li> Tight, focused puzzles</li></ul><br/>Drill Dirt! <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338630/extras/gif_eat_dirt.gif?t=1704711666"><br/><br/>Bomb Rocks! <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338630/extras/gif_many_bomb.gif?t=1704711666"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Retro BoxBot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709060/Super_Retro_BoxBot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A modern take on 1990's puzzle classics with a retro aesthetic! As Boxy the robot, your task is to traverse puzzle rooms while cleverly rearranging boxes to reach the exit. Some are locked, providing additional mental workouts as you work to retrieve keys before making your way to the exit. Elevators provide further challenges navigating rooms as you progress. Are you prepared to take on the challenge?<br/><br/>Key Features<br/>- Explore and solve 66 challenging levels (50 main levels + 16 bonus levels to unlock)<br/>- Steam achievements<br/>- Modern smooth grid-based movement<br/>- Optional classic control scheme for traditional grid-based movement<br/>- Full controller support (Note: While PS4/PS5 controllers will work, the on-screen guide correlates to Xbox controls)<br/>- You can set a rewind point during a level and restore if you make a mistake<br/>- Create your own challenges with the included level editor<br/>- Enjoy the game on PC, Linux or Steamdeck with cross-platform cloud saving<br/><br/><strong>Share custom levels with your friends and the community at ModDB</strong><br/><a href="https://www.moddb.com/games/super-retro-boxbot" rel="" target="_blank">https://www.moddb.com/games/super-retro-boxbot</a><br/><br/>Special thanks to Mr. William Soleau, founder of Soleau Software, for graciously providing me permission to take inspiration from his DOS games Loader Larry and Block-man!<br/><br/>Look for keys in levels with locked doors:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709060/extras/SRBB_Key.gif?t=1704709860"><br/><br/>An elevator automatically transports you to another elevator.  You can avoid taking an elevator by carrying a box or you can block an elevator with a box to disable the second elevator:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709060/extras/SRBB_Elevator.gif?t=1704709860"><br/><br/>Use the "Rewind Point" feature to save or restore your progress mid-level:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709060/extras/SRBB_Rewind.gif?t=1704709860"><br/><br/>With the included level editor, you can create your own custom levels.  You can also export and share levels on ModDB:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709060/extras/SRBB_Editor.gif?t=1704709860"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Climpy's Warfair</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2050980/Tim_Climpys_Warfair/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2050980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A word from Tim Climpy</h2><br/>Hi, I'm Tim Climpy and welcome to my PvP FPS Warfair game.  As an expert in military warfare, i decided to collaborate with Common Blob on a first person shooter.  I was thrilled to lend my expertise to them. Unfortunately, they seemed to have ignored a lot of what I said, which is disappointing. I dont recall ever using a flamethrower with a grappling hook while parachuting ever. Not in my approximately 40 years experience! Anyway, i digress, I did lend my knowledge, whether they used it or not.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2050980/extras/timclimpsig.png?t=1704710375"><br/><br/>Battle your friends (and enemies?) on 12 maps across the world to see who comes top of the leader board.<br/><br/>Featuring<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 280 character customisation options<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2050980/extras/characters.png?t=1704710375"><br/></img></li><li>27+ Weapons - Assault Rifles, Pistols, Snipers, SMGs, Minigun, Shotguns, Grenades<br/></li><li>12 Maps<br/></li><li>Modify your weapons to include different Muzzles, Scopes, Grips, Camos<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2050980/extras/attachbefore.png?t=1704710375"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2050980/extras/attachafter.png?t=1704710375"><br/></img></img></li><li>Integration with Ready Player Me<br/></li><li>Parachute!<br/></li><li>Lay prone and dive!<br/></li><li>Ziplines<br/></li><li>Limb removal!<br/></li><li>Set the time and weather for night time conflict, or in the middle of a thunderstorm<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2050980/extras/weather.gif?t=1704710375"><br/></img></li><li>An audio engine to model geometry to calculate audio occlusion, reverb and dampening effects, creating a more realistic audio experience<br/></li><li>Many Gamemodes<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Classic Free-For-All mode<br/></li><li>Another classic Team Deathmatch<br/></li><li>Yet another classic Capture the Flag<br/></li><li>HODL mode where you need to hold the point<br/></li><li>Gunrace, get a kill with a gun to move onto the next weapon. <br/></li><li>Kill Confirmed - pickup the bag to confirm the kill and gain the point</li></ul><br/></li><li>Modify each game mode with game mods:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li>Chunk - After every kill you get bigger and stronger, there is no end to how much you can grow<br/> </li><li>Big Head Mode - Big heads all round. Surely more headshots?<br/> </li><li>Bouncy-Bouncy - Bouncing platforms are scattered across the maps<br/> </li><li>Hardcore - Lose the minimap, health bars and ammo count and rely on your instincts<br/> </li><li>Paintball - Half damage, paint splats, larger bullet drop, exaggerated ragdolling</li></ul></li><li>Drivable vehicles<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Cars<br/></li><li>Tanks<br/></li><li>Planes<br/></li><li>Helicopters</li></ul></li><li>Bots, for when noone else is around!<br/></li><li>Level up and unlock new items, skins, weapons, attachments, camos<br/></li><li>Some destructible environments</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send It: The Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2410370/Send_It_The_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2410370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Send It! Ordnance Delivery Services<br>
<br>
Keep Calm<br>
<br>
And<br>
<br>
Send It!<br/>
<br/>
Ever wanted to know what it's like to shoot a mortar?  Ever wanted to just destroy stuff? Ever wanted to save Duke's Pond from an imminent Slime invasion?  This is your chance<br/>
<br/>
Will you choose to carefully select your targets and take them out with precision, or overwhelm your enemies and flatten them with firepower? Oil depots, radio towers, tanks, high altitude surveillance balloons, destroy them all, fend off the imminent invasion, and save Duke's Pond!<br/>
<br/>
The best mortar firing experience around, guaranteed! Your mission, if you choose to accept it, is to... Send It!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GymFistprint</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2711680/GymFistprint/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2711680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this <strong>gym</strong> we love to train a lot and have sparring with people from all over the world, here old <strong>Martín</strong>, former professional boxer, will be the one who trains you to get the best out of you, you will test your agility, reflexes, concentration, coordination, patience, perseverance in The 3 machines that the gym offers so far include the punching bag, the speedbag and the dodgeball. Improve your stats like your <strong>strength</strong>, <strong>critical hits</strong>, <strong>aim</strong>, <strong>guard</strong>, and reflex while <strong>dodging</strong> blows to see them in action in combat. Your teammates will always give you good advice to raise your spirits and improve as a fighter and person, try to talk to them when they are taking a break.<br/><br/>Old Martín will turn you into a diamond, the only thing he asks is <strong>that you trust yourself</strong>.<br/><br/>Some advices:<br/>-The game has <strong>autosave</strong> (local on PC)<br/>-Training too much before a fight will cause your fighter's <strong>fatigue</strong> to affect his recovery in combat.<br/>-Before a fight, the <strong>3 best results</strong> of each machine in the gym are averaged, to consider your <strong>statistics</strong> in combat.<br/>-After each fight the fighter eliminates his highest statistic and also eliminates his fatigue (if he does not abandon the fight) and can retrain for his next sparring.<br/><br/><strong>Do not give up!</strong><br/><br/><br/>(I will be making future improvements, stay tuned for <strong>updates</strong>, this will only get better) Francisco Canales						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Fund Tycoon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2310900/Hedge_Fund_Tycoon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2310900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the cutthroat world of high finance with this tycoon-simulation game. The goal is to become the richest hedge fund in the world. In a market where the stakes are high and the competition is fierce, you'll need to be strategic, aggressive, and willing to take risks to come out on top.<h2 class="bb_tag">Buy and Sell</h2>You'll have access to a wide range of financial tools to help you make the most of every opportunity. From stocks and bonds to derivatives and options, you'll have the tools you need to make smart investments and maximize your returns.<h2 class="bb_tag">Manage multi-billion Corporations</h2>But simply having access to the right tools isn't enough. In order to succeed in this game, you'll need to be willing to manage billion-dollar corporations, take calculated risks, and be aggressive in your pursuit of wealth. <br/>As you build your empire, you'll need to manage your assets and make strategic decisions to ensure your continued success. You'll have to keep an eye on the markets, track your profits and losses, and adjust your strategy as necessary.<br/>Whether you're looking to dominate a particular market or diversify your portfolio, you'll need to be constantly on the lookout for new opportunities and be ready to act when they arise.<h2 class="bb_tag">Use power and corruption</h2>And when the going gets tough, you'll need to be willing to use your power and influence to bend the rules in your favor. Whether you're engaging in insider trading, manipulating the market, or using your connections to gain an edge, you'll need to be bold and unafraid to push the boundaries of what's legal if you want to make it to the top.<h2 class="bb_tag">Be ruthless</h2>But be careful, your opponents will also be doing everything they can to outsmart you. So you'll need to stay one step ahead, be always informed, and make the right decisions at the right time. As you amass wealth and influence, you will be able to engage in corrupt deals and backroom negotiations to gain an unfair advantage over your rivals. But be careful, as these actions will also come with consequences.<br/><br/>With realistic market simulations, engaging gameplay, and endless opportunities for wealth and power, this game will keep you hooked for hours on end. The competition is fierce, but with the right strategy and a bit of luck, you can become the wealthiest hedge fund manager in the world.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>minitechno</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2680080/minitechno/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Developed with teachers and educators, minitechno is for toddlers and kids of all ages to learn, develop and play safely across 5 activities at launch.<br>
<br>
No ads. No subscription. No additional purchases. No account necessary. No internet connection required. No tracking. AND FREE UPDATES!<br>
<br>
Launching with:<br>
+ Techno ABC, to learn the ABCs with tech rhymes and illustrations<br>
+ FlashTap, for the development of reflexes and coordination<br/>
+ Vocakey, to help with the association of letters and numbers on a keyboard<br/>
+ Sandbox, to explore physics and construction<br/>
+ Piano, a single and dual multi-sound musical keyboard<br/>
<br/>
A complete guide with recommendations for both little ones and bigger ones is available for parents in the app.<br/>
<br/>
The entire app is bilingual and switchable instantaneously with an always available switch that can be disabled.<br/>
<br/>
Supports touch, mouse and keyboard. Controller support coming soon!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTRAL TALE-星界神話</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2591210/ASTRAL_TALE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FKczTvnAY6v" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2591210/extras/Steam_discord.png?t=1704687724"/></a><br/>Classic Japanese MMORPG "ASTRAL TALE" is making its official release!. Embark on cute adventures under the starry sky, heal your soul, become a one-of-a-kind adventurer, journey with familiar companions into a new chapter, explore the beautiful starry world freely, and shape your destiny to create legends!<h2 class="bb_tag">【Explore the Astral Realm, Forge Adventures】</h2>Embark on a journey of free exploration in a vast fantasy world, uncover hidden treasures, immerse yourself in adventures and legends unknown, and join hands with your fellow adventurers as you head towards the horizons of the sky and the sea!<h2 class="bb_tag">【Freedom to Change Class, Your Mastery at the Helm】</h2>Switch between multiple Class at will, allowing your mood or tactical needs to change roles whenever necessary. In the Astral Realm, you can always find your unique style, returning to the initial excitement of role-playing!<h2 class="bb_tag">【With You in Battle, Stellar Companions】</h2>Powerful companions from the stars have descended at this moment. From the first encounter to building deep connections, they grow alongside you. Each stellarian has their unique story and charm, becoming an indispensable part of your adventures!<h2 class="bb_tag">【Explore Hidden Worlds With your own personal Mobile Cottage】</h2>Wherever the mobile cottage goes, it takes you there! With its unique three-level design and customizable interior, along with a rich array of life systems including greenhouse gardening, alchemy in the basement, cooking, tailoring, and more, you can create a one-of-a-kind space that's truly your own!<h2 class="bb_tag">【Rich Wardrobe, Unique Appearance】</h2>Obtain a wealth of free outfits appearance, allowing you to create versatile character images without extra money. From classical elegance to cyber-future, become the cutest adventurer with charm that touches the heart!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KARAKURI Colosseum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2673370/KARAKURI_Colosseum/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2673370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							KARAKURI Colosseum is an enthralling VR sword-fighting journey, blending the mystic allure of Japanese samurai warfare with the epic scale of an ancient Roman amphitheater.<br/><br/>Embark on a winner-takes-all duel in the legendary arena, where robot adversaries escalate in power with each conquest, and mastery over the elegant Japanese swords becomes your key to survival.<br/><br/>Unique swords, each whispering tales of ancient powers and secrets, are strategically placed throughout the stage, awaiting warriors astute enough to unveil and harness their latent energies.<h2 class="bb_tag">How to Use Japanese Swords:</h2><br/>In a world where every blade tells a story, your survival hinges on skillful interaction and strategic management of your sword’s potent abilities.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unsheathe your destiny: Draw the sword, enveloping yourself in its mystical aura, and unlock abilities by keeping it sheathed until the crucial moment.<br/></li><li>Rarity in power: Remember, only select swords harbor hidden, formidable powers waiting to tip the scales of battle in your favor.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Getting Started with Your Sword:</h2><br/>Navigating the ethereal world of KARAKURI Colosseum demands fluidity in your swordplay and an intuitive connection with your blade.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Grabbing the Sword: Approach the handle closely with your hand to grip the sword.<br/></li><li>Drawing the Sword: Lift it ever so slightly and reaffirm your grip to unsheathe.<br/></li><li>Sheathing the Sword: Align the blade with the scabbard’s opening to sheathe, preserving its aura and potential.</li></ul><br/>Experience a breathtaking confluence of history and futurism, engaging in visceral swordplay against relentless mechanical samurai within a monumental arena, where victory breathes life into steel, and defeat beckons the eternal echoes of the colosseum.<br/><br/>Join us in the KARAKURI Colosseum, where every strike etches a tale of survival in the hallowed grounds once graced by warriors of epochs past.<br/><br/>Your destiny awaits, warrior. Will your name resonate through the annals of the KARAKURI Colosseum? May your sword guide you to eternal glory amidst the spectral echoes of the ancient arena.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2426960/Summoners_War/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2426960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>▶Features</strong><br/><strong>[Tactical RPG play]</strong><br/>Witness the dazzling display of each monster 's unique skills.<br/>23 different Rune sets to pick and choose additional abilities for your monsters!<br/>Come up with the best strategy to win battles in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[Endless Fun]</strong><br/>Decorate your Village, battle other summoners , explore dungeons , fight in PvP battles , expand your collection, train monsters , and more.<br/><br/><strong>[The Key of Colletion RPG : Massive Collection]</strong><br/>Fire, Water, Wind, Light and Dark!<br/>5 different attributes, and 1500 different monsters!<br/>Collect as many monsters as you can and win battles with your own decks .<br/><br/><strong>[Real-time Raid]</strong><br/>Battle as a team with your greatest monsters !<br/>A real-time battle with 3 users!<br/>Defeat the boss with your fellow Summoners using various tactics.<br/><br/><strong>[Homunculus]</strong><br/>The Forbidden Summoning Magic has finally been revealed!<br/>You can Evolve the skill of your choice with this special monster.<br/>Summon Homunculus and show off your strategy in the Sky Arena .<br/><br/><strong>[All about Turn-Based RPG : World Arena]</strong><br/>Enjoy a real-time battle with Summoners worldwide!<br/>Experience a breathtaking battle that starts from Pick &amp; Ban.<br/>Reveal your unique strategy to the world and win battles .<br/><br/><strong>[Guild Content]</strong><br/>A sensational Guild PvP battle in the Isle of Conquest!<br/>Explore the Tartarus' Labyrinth and dungeons with Guild Members.<br/>Make your Guild the greatest of all.<br/><br/><strong>[Dimension Hole]</strong><br/>Fight against the ancient power emerged from a new dimension!<br/>Defeat the Ancient Guardians and meet the powerful monsters with new awakening power.<br/><br/><strong>[Artifact]</strong><br/>Artifacts are now dropped with MAX power-up levels!<br/>Summoners , fight against the powerful bosses and acquire Artifacts!<br/>Enhance your monsters with various sub properties of Artifacts.<br/><br/><strong>[Progression and Farming Structure Revamp]</strong><br/>Summoner progression structure renewed and content reward greatly improved!<br/>Dive into Summoners War and experience the enhanced progression system!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic of Tarot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687140/Epic_of_Tarot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Role-playing game, turn-based genre, where you will play as the heir of an ancient sage, and face off once again against the demon king who was sealed a thousand years ago</strong>.<br/>As a first-born Sage, your magical power is not enough to immediately fight against the Demon King and his hordes.<br/>In order to restore the power to its peak, <h2 class="bb_tag">you must:</h2><br/> <h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Find the time wormhole in the continent and explore</strong></h2> As the seal of the Demon Realm is lifted, the Demon King uses his power to open countless wormholes across the continent of Tarot. The wormholes link to the magic world, and dangerous magical creatures have come to the Tarot world from the wormholes.<br/>In order to close these wormholes, you need to actively enter the wormholes to find the source of power in the wormholes to defeat him and close the wormholes.<br/>  When you enter the magic world, you will encounter many dangers unknown to mankind, but you can also find magic items (relics &amp; potions) that can help you survive in this magic world.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Monster Soul Power</strong></h2>  When a monster in the Demon Realm is defeated, its soul does not dissipate. The ancient sages made a prop, The Crystal Ball, that attracts and gathers the scattered monster souls in this crystal ball. You can make a deal with the Crystal Ball to gain the monster's power.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Law of Equipment Attraction</strong></h2>Weapons and clothes in the magic world have a very magical characteristic, when two identical pieces of equipment are close to overlapping, the two props will attract and fuse with each other like magnets and spawn even more powerful weapon props.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Rune Wheel</strong></h2> When you enter the abyss, you will collect the unique Mystic Dust in the abyss, and inject the Mystic Dust into the Rune Wheel to strengthen your own magic.<br/><br/>There are many more magical things and objects in this continent, and more surprises are waiting for you to embark on the journey.<br/><br/>For more information, please join the official discussion group: 729691834						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2727700/Real/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2727700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Real" is a unique psychological puzzle game offering the player an in—depth immersion into the moral aspects of human nature through exciting levels. In this abstract world, each level represents a separate moral quality, reflected in words and phrases that become the key to the solution.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2727700/extras/gif.gif?t=1704775966"><h2 class="bb_tag">Moral challenges:</h2><br/>Each level offers a unique moral challenge, ranging from loneliness to compassion and determination. Your decisions affect the course of the game and are reflected in changing phrases that comment on your emotional path.<h2 class="bb_tag">Minimalism and abstraction:</h2><br/>"Real" is visually designed in a minimalist style, providing players with a simple and clean visual experience. The graphics and sound complement the unique atmosphere of the levels<br/><br/>Is not just a game, it is a guide to the world of human feelings and moral dilemmas, where your every decision leaves a mark in this abstract landscape. Immerse yourself in a mind-blowing adventure of self-discovery.<br/><br/><i>Background Music: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Ffreesound.org%2Fpeople%2FUNIVERSFIELD%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank">UNIVERSFIELD</a> </i><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><i>Notes: Don't expect exciting gameplay, wow effects and high-budget stunts here. This is not the case when drastic changes in game development become the new norm. The purpose of this project has never been to hurt anyone's feelings, offend any of you</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubyte</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2593410/Cubyte/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Cubyte. A 2D game made of shapes. </i></strong><br/>Beginning as a lab escapee with your friends detained, you must figure the way out. Prepare to face numerous enemies, each wanting to bring you down! Your objective is to get to a portal that will help teleport you to the next area. Green Bois (ICues) will help guide you through your journey. <br/><br/><br/><strong>Skills Required</strong><br/><br/><i>Dodging.</i> Otherwise, you'd probably die.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593410/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif.gif?t=1704671943"><br/><br/><i>Brain.</i> Can't play the game without it!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593410/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif__1_.gif?t=1704671943"><br/><br/><i>Aim.</i> How else do you expect to defeat your enemies?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2593410/extras/ezgif.com-crop.gif?t=1704671943"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>15 levels </li><li>3 different styled environments </li><li>3 unique bosses </li><li>in-game currency </li><li>player-leveling experience </li><li>2 difficulty options </li><li><strong>FIRE</strong> music </li><li>Green bois </li><li><i>Secrets</i> </li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ragdoll Wreckage: Zombie Farts</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733200/Ragdoll_Wreckage_Zombie_Farts/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ragdoll Wreckage offers a whimsical and entertaining experience—a delightful side-scrolling game where you creatively employ both your flatulence and the structures around you to skillfully maneuver towards victory by collecting coins. Moreover, with each progressing level, the game unfolds into extended challenges, ensuring endless enjoyment and excitement for players.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733200/extras/mp4togif__1_.gif?t=1704666458"><br/><br/>Employ both your flatulence and structures around you to collect points for victory!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2733200/extras/0001-0272.gif?t=1704666458"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yokai City</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2725430/Yokai_City/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2725430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Yokai City</strong> is a character-driven visual novel in the style of Japanese anime of the 1980s, set against a backdrop of uneasy social tensions between humans and yokai who are forced to live together in a part of Tokyo.<br/><br/>The year is 1988. After millennia of conflict with humans, all remaining yokai were at last convinced to relocate to the centre of Sumida: one of the capital’s 23 wards. Only oni and Inari remain now, all the other species of yokai that once played such an important part in Japan’s history and folklore are now reduced to existing solely in literature and cinema. <br/><br/>Enter the shoes of a half-man, half-oni regulator (a law enforcement official tasked with keeping the peace between humans and non-humans) and see how you and your team deal with daily life in 80s Tokyo all the while trying to stop criminals and violent fanatics from both sides who seem hell-bent on tearing the city apart.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring...</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>A Personalised Protagonist</strong></li></ul>Name your character and choose what they say or do, impacting those who you meet along the way and affecting how they see and treat you. This also helps to flesh out your character instead of having them be just a bland cut-out who watches everyone else do all the talking.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Numerous Choices</strong></li></ul>This 5-hour story has over 200 dialogue choices available which will not only affect your relationship with your fellow regulators but also lead you to see different scenes and multiple endings, adding to its replayability.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
