<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Collapse: Code Name Bakery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1127700/Reverse_Collapse_Code_Name_Bakery/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Reverse Collapse: Code Name Bakery faithfully recreates MICA Team’s Codename: Bakery Girl (2013) with revamped graphics, new gameplay mechanics, and expanded narrative.<br/><br/>30 years after the events of Girls’ Frontline, Antarctic Union (AU) special agent Mendo goes on an important mission in the heart of the North Caucasus. Unexpectedly ambushed by the forces of the Union of Rossatrism Nations Coalitions (URNC), his situation takes a dramatic turn with the appearance of Jefuty, the mysterious silver-haired “Bakery Girl.” Together, they traverse hostile terrains, unraveling the dark secrets shrouded within the GRAVIRUL Project.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Game Features</strong></h2>Classic Tactical RPG: command a diverse roster of characters, each with unique skills and abilities. Masterfully orchestrate tactical maneuvers and leverage a vast arsenal of advanced weapons and crafted items to navigate through and triumph over challenging situations.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/zhanyi.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>60+ Campaign Stages: navigate through a variety of intricate missions while balancing strategic elements such as stealth, unique stage mechanisms, and varied terrains. Overcome these challenges to achieve the coveted S-rank status<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/qianxing.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>Immersive storytelling: vibrant illustrations and 2D animations work together to deliver every encounter with heightened intensity and emotional impact.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/shaonvcg.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/新小人cg.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>The Original Saga Retold: with a script exceeding over 300,000 words, the expanded narrative goes beyond recreating the intense battle over two days. Stay alert for hidden depths and untold stories that bring new dimensions to the saga. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/fenweigai.png?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>Stay Connected:<br/>Twitter (X): @Re_Collapse_EN<br/>Discord: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FDXfNGu8QXR" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.com/invite/DXfNGu8QXR</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054970/Dragons_Dogma_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Note: There are other sets that include this item.<br/><br/>Set forth on your grand adventure, Arisen!<br/><br/>Dragon’s Dogma is a single player, narrative driven action-RPG series that challenges the players to choose their own experience – from the appearance of their Arisen, their vocation, their party, how to approach different situations and more. Now, in this long-awaited sequel, the deep, explorable fantasy world of Dragon’s Dogma 2 awaits.<br/><br/>On your journey, you’ll be joined by Pawns, mysterious otherworldly beings, in an adventure so unique you will feel as if accompanied by other players while on your own adventure.<br/><br/>All of these elements are elevated further through physics technology, artificial intelligence (AI) and the latest in graphics, to create a truly immersive fantasy world in Dragon’s Dogma 2.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Action that challenges your creativity </u></strong> <br/><br/>Wield swords, bows, and chant magick.<br/>The vocations in Dragon's Dogma 2 give you the ability to approach combat the way you want.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_01.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Company in your single-player experience </u></strong> <br/><br/>Players can customize their own main Pawn, who will always accompany your Arisen, <br/>and enter a covenant with up to 2 additional Pawns from other players through the network. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_02.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Facing the monsters in this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Beyond the town borders, you will encounter diverse monsters that inhabit the lands. <br/>You will need to decide between engaging in battles or finding alternatives; <br/>so be aware of your party’s setup, the terrain around you, and the monsters you face.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_03.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Inhabitants of this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Travelers, merchants, soldiers and other folk go about their daily lives. <br/>Preoccupied by their own objectives and motives, they all exhibit different emotions.<br/>At times, they may lead you to a quest by approaching you and asking for a favor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_04.gif?t=1711067553"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cureocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2612680/Cureocity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							We are "Bread On Board," a collective of independent game developers spread across four countries, united by our passion and meeting during a GameJam. <br/>Our game demo was born in the "BOOOM CHALLENGE", a GameJam by GCORES. With only 21 days, we created a game based on a given theme. After the competition, we even won the "Most Popular Game" award at an Online Game Trial Event.<br/>The full playthrough of our game will take about an hour. We hope to give you a short, but super heartwarming and loving adventure❤️.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/1.奇幻而治愈（英文）.png?t=1711092805"><br/>A rookie adventurer fresh on the scene and a former mercenary who was transferred into an adventurer due to injury. Two protagonists with contrasting personalities will embark on an adventure of fantasy and healing together. In the mysterious ruins of an underground dungeon that lies in the depth of a jungle, what awaits them will be...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1711092805"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/2.两位冒险者（英文）.png?t=1711092805"><br/>According to the tavern's adventurer logs, the team heading into the dungeon features a rookie adventurer and an ex-mercenary who is now working as a healer. The adventurer looks as charming as a doll, and the enthusiasm never disappears; the healer is cool and a bit traditional, acting as a guiding figure for their adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1711092805"><br/><br/>What stories have unfolded between these two contrasting characters, and what challenges will they face together in this adventure? The continuation of this adventurous story is yours to discover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/3.注重手法的回合制解谜（英文）.png?t=1711092805"><br/>"People think battles need powerful weapons, but strategy at hand is key." <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1711092805"><br/><br/>In "Cureocity," the power of your strategy is materialized as the numerical values of your hands in combat. You can swap different weapons or items held in your left and right hands to alter your character's attack and defense stats. You may also change "gestures" to focus attacks or land heavy blows on specific enemies.As you delve deeper into the dungeon, you will take the unique traits of monsters into consideration and discuss strategies with your allies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/4.你的选择决定冒险归途（英文）.png?t=1711092805"><br/>In this adventure, you'll discover not only the secrets hidden within the dungeon, but also the truths about the world and the  characters themselves. When faced with contaminated monsters, you can choose to either fight them or attempt to purify them. Of course, you also have the option to let things take their own course.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1711092805"><br/><br/>With each decision,the fate of the protagonists may change. The end of this adventure... is yours to decide.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Publisher</h2>GCORES PUBLISHING is an independent game publishing venture formed by GCORES, committed to bringing you more outstanding indie games from the BOOOM CHALLENGE.<br/>Feel free to follow our <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/44750639" rel="" target="_blank">publisher webpage</a> for future updates.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/915810/Midnight_Ghost_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/915810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>MIDNIGHT GHOST HUNT IS A <i>PETRIFYING</i> PROP HAUNT GAME TO PLAY WITH PALS! </strong><br/><br/>Lying in wait across a series of cursed locations, relentless spirits stalk the halls. Assigned to eliminate them are the Ghost Hunters, armed to the teeth with the ghoul-busting tech to banish them to another realm! Play both Ghost and Hunter in a chaotic 4v4 struggle between the living and the dead.<br/><br/><strong>TONGUE-IN-CHEEK HIDE-AND-SEEK</strong><br/>As a Ghost, conceal yourself inside seemingly harmless pieces of furniture to evade preying Hunters… but when their backs are turned, turn the environment against them with telekinetic bombardment. No chair, lamp, or grandfather clock is innocent in this hijinks-heavy frenzy.<br/><br/><strong>MIDNIGHT MAYHEM</strong><br/>The fun isn’t over yet...when the clock strikes twelve, the witching hour begins, and the Hunters become the Hunted. The tables turn and Ghosts become supercharged, giving Hunters a limited amount of time to survive their vengeful wrath.<br/><br/><strong>MURDEROUS 4v4 MULTIPLAYER</strong><br/>Play together and communicate with your team and ensure a triumphant victory, giving each other pointers on the paths enemies tend to tread. Create synergies with your team's abilities to outthink and outwit your opponents.<br/><br/><strong>HARNESS SUPERNATURAL ABILITIES</strong><br/>The restrictions of reality don’t apply to Ghosts, of course. Claim your supernatural powers, which include turning invisible, causing furniture to float, and conjuring a dangerous Ghostly miasma. Ghosts can even hide in plain sight by masquerading as a Hunter’s doppelgänger!<br/><br/>Ghostly Perks include dramatically increasing your weight, extending your possessing range, the ability to see nearby Hunters through walls, and much more. <br/><br/><strong>ARMED AND READY</strong><br/>Hunters must choose their weapons from a full range of hi-tech gadgets designed to cast out Ghosts from our plane of existence. Detect ghostly presences with the Spectrophone, Radar and Pathfinder, capture them with a Trap, and suck up their spectral remains with the Vacuum – or just blast them to smithereens with the Spectral Cannon, sledgehammers, harpoons, salt-spewing shotguns, and more.<br/><br/>Hunters can also select Perks to give them a special boost. Choose from an extra burst of speed, health-replenishing capabilities and a host of other powers to get ahead of the game.<br/><br/><strong>A BEVY OF BLOOD-CURDLING MAPS </strong><br/>Explore ten unsettling locations, including an abandoned theatre, eerie mansion and cursed carnival. Each map brings with it different tactical considerations and items to throw about… as well as plenty of opportunities to play tricks on the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>FRIGHTENING NEW FEATURES</strong> <br/>As it crept through Steam Early Access, Midnight Ghost Hunt picked up a gaggle of game-changing features, built on the feedback of its community of Ghosts and Hunters.<br/><br/>Dedicated servers and host migration support make setting up matches a breeze, while the Progression Tier and Challenge systems bring added competition to the hunt. Looking for less of the silly and more of the scary? The Experimental Darkness game mode lends a chill to the chaos. Not to mention crossplay, full controller support, and even the GhostMaster minigame to pass the time during the van ride to your next match!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711032993"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1710945887"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1710945887"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1710945887"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw Metal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2279600/Raw_Metal/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2279600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Raw Metal is a sci-fi stealth-action dungeon crawler with a focus on smooth, stylish gameplay.<br/><br/>You are a lone scavenger on the distant, barren exoplanet Charybdis. In search of gear and supplies, you infiltrate the depths of Katabase 6, a massive mining facility run by a corrupt megacorporation known as Orpheus Tech. Sneak through the mines undetected, cleverly utilizing various gadgets and equipment to your advantage, but beware; if you're caught, you'll need to rely on your combat skills for a fighting chance to escape.<h2 class="bb_tag">High-Stakes Stealth</h2><br/>Use taser darts, noisemakers, improvised concussion grenades, and more to slip past and isolate guards. The shadows are your domain; manipulate your environment and your enemies well enough and they'll never see you coming.<h2 class="bb_tag">Breakneck Combat</h2><br/>Combat in Raw Metal is fast and punishing. The guards stationed at Katabase 6 are stronger and more heavily armored than you, so fighting them head on will take skill, cunning, and a great degree of risk. However, mastering combos and using your environment will allow you to come out on top, and yield far greater rewards. Depending on whether it is initiated through a clever ambush or a stealth slip-up, combat can range from a calculated risk to a desperate fight for survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Blend of top-down stealth and third-person beat 'em up combat<br/></li><li>Freeform combo system that rewards aggression, improvisation, and precise timing and positioning<br/></li><li>50+ unique gear pieces to find and upgrade<br/></li><li>Distinct visuals for each gear piece to customize the look of your character<br/></li><li>Risk vs. reward extraction system that grants you the choice of cashing out your loot, or pushing deeper into the facility<br/></li><li>3 memorable and challenging boss fights, each with their own fighting styles, twists, and story development<br/></li><li>9 hand-crafted levels to infiltrate, with a few variants each to mix up your approach each time<br/></li><li>Environmental hazards and enemy variants to keep you on your toes as the game progresses<br/></li><li>5 deployable gadgets to utilize to your advantage in stealth and combat alike</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479320/Pesticide_Not_Required/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pesticide Not Required combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1710830410"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1710830410"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1710830410"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Customizable home interior and backyard garden area<br/></li><li>Season-themed map variations with 16 difficulty levels<br/></li><li>20+ unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>100+ achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Compendium with unique fish for each season<br/></li><li>Mouse-only gameplay support<br/></li><li>Gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast - A New Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1013140/Outcast__A_New_Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							20 years after the award-winning action adventure hit, Outcast, pioneered the genre of non-linear open-world games, the long-awaited sequel sees Cutter Slade return to the spectacular alien world of Adelpha. Resurrected by the almighty Yods, he has returned to find the Talans enslaved, the world stripped of its natural resources, and his own past intertwining with the invading robot forces. It's up to him to go on a mission and save the planet again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/flight_8mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/><br/>The original team behind Outcast 1 has reunited to create this fascinating world, full of dangerous creatures and home to the Talan people – an ancient culture whose fate has become inextricably linked with earth since the events of the first game. You play as Cutter Slade, ex-Navy SEAL, sporting the same dry wit he had back in the 90s – however, the world around him has changed and eventually, so will he.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat01_6mb.gif?t=1710511218"><br/> <br/>To save Adelpha, you will … <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>use your jetpack to jump, air-dash, glide, and quickly traverse the fantastic in-game open world <br/></li><li>combine dozens of different modules to create your own personal weapon for taking down the robot invaders <br/></li><li>have total control to approach the story at your own pace in this non-linear world <br/></li><li>explore the world without boundaries, discover hidden temples and dangerous wildlife <br/></li><li>get familiar with the Talan culture while helping them free their villages and gain access to ancient Talan powers that use forces of nature to destroy your enemies <br/></li><li>experience a beautiful, hand-crafted world accompanied by an epic soundtrack by Outcast's original composer, Lennie Moore </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1013140/extras/combat02.gif?t=1710511218"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skelethrone: The Prey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2139870/Skelethrone_The_Prey/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Wishlist_Follow_ENG.gif?t=1710431377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/About_the_Game_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>You're in for a great adventure inspired by games like Castlevania and Dark Souls.  Bloodthirsty monsters, divine creatures and epic boss battles. The game’s story is shaped by  choices that will define your journey.<br/><br/><strong>PROLOGUE KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Metroidvania</strong> - Unlock unique upgrades for movement and combat to expand the world. Maintaining the game's progression requires you to use different relics, items and abilities.<br/></li><li><strong>Challenging bosses</strong> - Test your skills against multiple bosses and other creatures from the Dark Ages. The game will constantly test your patience as you face challenging battles that require their own unique approach..<br/></li><li><strong>Exploration</strong> - The game features a huge world represented by a variety of hand-crafted levels. From fog-shrouded ruins, where undead corpses cling to any living being passing by, and shambling figures emerge. To the Sun-city that hides in the labyrinthine of an ancient tomb where an unspeakable evil lingers, long forgotten by mankind.</li></ul><br/><strong>AVAILABLE IN FULL GAME:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Weapons and Equipment</strong> – Your character can be armed with bows, scythes, longswords, whips, pistols, rifles, and many more traditional weapons. More exotic weapons will also be available to you, so use any means to achieve success.<br/></li><li><strong>Multiple Endings</strong> – Make key decisions along the way to determine Ericona's fate as you progress through the story.<br/></li><li><strong>Non-linear exploration</strong> – Play through levels and bosses, discover side areas with more secrets and enemies to defeat.<br/></li><li><strong>Combat galore</strong> - You must use an ever-expanding arsenal of weapons and equipment to repel  a wide variety of enemies. Put your courage, skills, and resolve on display for them.</li></ul><br/>"Skelethrone: The Prey" is a free prequel to the main game, setting the stage for the events that will unfold throughout Skelethrone's main campaign.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Story_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>The story takes place a few decades before the events of the game's main campaign. Assume the role of Derek Ericona, a lord who escaped the persecution is now trying to get to the borders of the neighboring kingdom to resist the tyranny of Queen Aurora, but he is being chased and faces an uphill battle. Prepare all your skills to overcome all the obstacles and difficulties prepared for our hero. And now the hunt is on!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F89UKE37PuC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/join_the_comunity_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710955211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710955211"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rental</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796550/Rental/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/extras/Gif_Final__2___1_.gif?t=1709834139"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Great Deal!</strong></h2><br/><i>Perfect cabin for a family of four. Close to the beach with great vibes!<br/>For more information about this rental, contact the caretaker!</i><br/><br/>For summer vacation, Umi's family rents a cabin near the beach. However, Umi soon realizes that the offer was not as grand as promised...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Explore the summer cabin in this short game reminiscent of classic survival horror games.<br/></li><li> Meet and talk to a quirky cast of characters as you try to piece together the secrets of the cabin. <br/></li><li> Find items that will help you advance and find out what is wrong with this place. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Arrows or WASD to move<br/></li><li> Space to interact</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1711043620"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1711043620"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1711043620"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy: The Soldier</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2870470/Troy_The_Soldier/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2870470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Game Description: </strong><br/><br/><i>Play as the young enlisted Michael as he goes through odd location to odd location looking for why he's stuck in a 40 year time loop. Meet odd fellows, weird looking Oddities, people doing their low entry jobs, and talking piles of ash as you embark on your very odd quest. </i><br/><br/><u>Purchase skills and give them to the RIGHT party members</u><br/><br/><u>Enjoy the 75+ theme soundtrack with new songs for each room (<i>almost</i>)</u><br/><br/><u>Purchase items to upgrade health and other stats</u><br/><br/><u>Look through the stylistic monochromatic game based around limited color pallet handheld games</u><br/><br/><u>Equip different types of gear to each of your party members (anyone can equip any armor, except a few)</u><br/><br/><u>Go through seven different areas (<i>or eight if you can find it</i>) all with their own different colors, unique enemies, unique bosses, and tracks</u><br/><br/><u>And be sure to be sparing of your items, you never know when you might need them.</u><br/><br/>The game's around four hours or more, give or take with the main file size coming from all the music (<u>All of which are open to listen to in the files, so be weary of spoilers.</u>)<br/><br/>RPG MAKER VX ACE's Run Time Package (RTP) is needed to play this game.<br/><br/>(Thank you Galv Scripts for creating the scripts used for this game, and thank you to yanfly as well.)						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss Neko: Pirates</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695270/Miss_Neko_Pirates/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In "Miss Neko: Pirates," players take on the role of the captain of the "Lucky Coin," overseeing the protagonist's adventures on a pirate-infested island from a top-down perspective. Strengthen your character to survive in this hostile world.<br/><br/>Thrown into the sea by a mutinous crew, the captain of the "Lucky Coin" was left for dead.Yet, some mysterious force allows you to survive from death, surviving the depths as the crew believes they've killed their captain. Stripped of everything, can you seek revenge with formidable combat skills, reclaim your pirate ship, seize the island's treasures, and punish the mutineering crew?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695270/extras/jadeshop-min.gif?t=1711106345"><br/><br/>Game Features:<br/><br/>Pirate-themed storyline and adventure<br/>Diverse and characterful beast-girl crew members<br/>Explore rich RPG maps<br/>Engage in challenging top-down battles and equipment growth<br/>Own your pirate ship, collect crew members to accompany you on board						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. What &amp; Detective Son</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2855580/Dr_What__Detective_Son/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an epic adventure with Dr. What and Detective Son in this captivating logic game available on Steam! Dive into a world where each level presents a unique challenge, requiring you to flex your mental muscles and employ cunning strategies to unravel mysteries and solve puzzles.<br>
<br>
With a whopping 100 mind-bending puzzles awaiting your expertise, the journey promises hours of immersive gameplay. Join forces with the ingenious Dr. What and his intrepid sidekick Detective Son as you navigate through a labyrinth of enigmas and conundrums. From deciphering cryptic codes to unraveling perplexing riddles, each puzzle offers a fresh test of your deductive reasoning and problem-solving prowess.<br>
<br>
This game is a standalone adaptation of an online browser-based game called "Mysterious Pron," where you had to guess the URL of the next level. Hints were hidden in various places—sometimes beyond the game itself. In this game, you have to do exactly the same: solve the case using various hints and type the solution to proceed to the next case. You will have to type in your guess to find out if you solved the case or maybe if you have found hint(s).<br>
If you struggle too much, feel free to seek hints in the dedicated Discord channel ;)						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost In Failures</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2813250/Lost_In_Failures/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2813250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Lost In Failures is an <strong>action</strong>, <strong>survival</strong> and <strong>adventure</strong> game set in a <strong>living</strong>, <strong>rich</strong> and <strong>challenging</strong> open world. In the work you control <strong>David</strong>, a character who had a normal life, but suddenly woke up on an unknown beach surrounded by a dense forest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2813250/extras/FirstGif.gif?t=1711103012"><br/><br/>The region has many <strong>mysteries</strong> and <strong>enemies</strong> that will do whatever is necessary to kill you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2813250/extras/SecondGif.gif?t=1711103012"><br/><br/>His goal is to regain his <strong>normal life</strong>, for this, he will have the help of <strong>Hades</strong>, a strange man who claims to have the answers to the problems David is facing.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2813250/extras/HistoryGif.gif?t=1711103012"><br/><br/>The player will need to understand what is happening to the world around them, <strong>explore</strong> and <strong>fight</strong> with all their might to save your life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2813250/extras/ThirdGif.gif?t=1711103012"><br/><br/>The world of the work allows you to <strong>craft</strong> items and equipments, <strong>hunt</strong> various species of wild animals, <strong>explore</strong> caves and structures, <strong>invade</strong> enemy occupations, <strong>evolve</strong> the character's skills and much more.<br/><br/><strong><u>Game mechanics:</u></strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Management of life, stamina, hunger and thirst;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Manufacture of items and equipment;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fun and challenging combat;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Use and domestication of horses;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Animal hunting;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Construction of structures for the camp;</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Evolution of skills.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL ESTATE Simulator - FROM BUM TO MILLIONAIRE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738900/REAL_ESTATE_Simulator__FROM_BUM_TO_MILLIONAIRE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an exhilarating journey to build your real estate empire in "Real Estate Simulator," a deep and dynamic business simulation game. Begin as a small-time property investor and strategize your way to become a tycoon in the cutthroat world of real estate. Navigate market trends, negotiate deals, and outsmart competitors in this immersive simulation experience.<br/><br/>⛺️ From Broke to Rich: Embark on a journey from Broke to Rich, developing skills and overcoming challenges with unwavering determination.<br/>Start with a tent as your first home.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738900/extras/12.gif?t=1711101068"><br/><br/>🤝 Interactive NPC Negotiations: Engage with a range of NPC clients, from cautious first-time buyers to wealthy investors. Understand their needs, negotiate terms, and close deals that shape your path to success.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738900/extras/06.gif?t=1711101068"><br/><br/>🏗️ Property Development and Management: Purchase, renovate, and sell properties across the city. From cheap living areas to luxury skyscrapers, each property brings unique challenges and opportunities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738900/extras/05.gif?t=1711101068"><br/><br/>🎮 Intuitive Controls and UI: Whether you're a seasoned tycoon or new to business sims, intuitive controls and a clear user interface make managing your empire accessible and enjoyable.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738900/extras/02.gif?t=1711101068"><br/><br/>🌟 Unique Challenges and Achievements: From market crashes to VIP clients, face unique challenges that test your strategic prowess. Unlock achievements and make your mark in the world of real estate.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swing By</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2698600/Swing_By/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Start your space expedition with Swing by - a game that will test your skills and reflexes! Become a master of spaceship control as you race through endless space. Your task is simple but challenging: collect valuable gems and win prizes while skillfully maneuvering through space.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698600/extras/intro.gif?t=1711099099"><br/><br/><br/>🎮 <strong>Simple controls</strong><br/>use gamepad, keyboard or mouse to rotate the ship around the planet and thrust forward to far reaches of unexplored space. Practice your reflexes as you spin around the planet and collect valuable rewards and prove you're the best.<br/><br/>🚀 <strong>2D and 3D Game view</strong><br/>Choose your gaming style between 2D and 3D perspectives. Experience the game in the way that suits you best.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698600/extras/SwingBy_SP3D_1-e.gif?t=1711099099"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698600/extras/SwingBy_SP2D_1.gif?t=1711099099"><br/><br/>💎 <strong>Gems and Ranks</strong><br/>Collect gems to unlock new levels and spaceships. Each level brings new challenges and exciting rewards for you to discover.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698600/extras/RankUpPanel_small.gif?t=1711099099"><br/><br/>🚢 <strong>Various Spaceships</strong><br/>Unlock different spaceships to customize your gaming experience. Each ship has its own special characteristics.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698600/extras/SwingBy_ShipShop.gif?t=1711099099"><br/><br/>🏆 <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/>Compare your score to fellow space travelers around the universe<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698600/extras/Leaderboards.gif?t=1711099099"><br/><br/>🌐<strong>Multiplayer</strong><br/>Join friends or challenge players around the world in exciting multiplayer battles. Show your skills and win galactic leadership!<br/><br/>Multiplayer is supported, only in local split screen mode up to 4 players can play together.<br/>Note: Online multiplayer mode will be implemented in a future update.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698600/extras/SwingBy_MP3D.gif?t=1711099099"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698600/extras/MP_ChooseScena.gif?t=1711099099"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Descent from Arkov's tower Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688600/Descent_from_Arkovs_tower_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Warning contains 8-bit-ish Retro!</h2><strong>Caution!</strong> This is a retro pixel art roguelike which might bring back memories you didn't even know you had. A flickering, humming CRT screen in your living room or bedroom back in the '90s after a day at school. What do you mean you weren't even born back then?<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>This roguelike puts you in the shoes of an unnamed adventurer who just woke up on the top level of Arkov's Tower. Try to fight your way down and escape it - or die trying.<br/><br/>Move your player trough numerous procedural generated levels. Fight numerous enemies including some unique bosses. The turn based combat system allows you to take your time and plan every move carefully. Upgrade your character with all sorts of items found in chests or dropped by enemies. In rare occasions you might find a wishing well, which allows you to upgrade your base stats. Can you make it to the bottom of the mysterious Tower?<br/><br/>Please be aware that this is a prologue, so more levels and bosses will be added in planned content Upgrades.<h2 class="bb_tag">Modding</h2> This game is highly customizable for people with pixel art and/or programming experience. Just have a look at the included manual and the Mod Manager in the main menu. Maybe you want to create your own story? Use this game as a roguelike engine and make it happen!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten World:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827510/The_Forgotten_WorldPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FVuKggh6WYN" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/dss.png?t=1711106032"/></a><br/><br/><strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 8 in the official version.<br/>Chapters: 2 prologues, 6 official versions</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/111.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>This is about Alice after Wonderland.<br/>Oblivion is the vilest of spells. As an adult, Alice also experiences a less fairytale-like life and stops dreaming, which also means that everything about Wonderland is slowly disappearing. The people of Wonderland have even forgotten why they exist, and before everything dissipates, the Cheshire Cat casts a phantom spell to try to find Alice in the hope that she can save Wonderland once more.<br/>But the Cheshire Cat can't remember the spell either, and the wrong spell sends it traveling to a parallel world, a world where Alice has no idea that Wonderland even exists.<br/>In order to keep Wonderland from being forgotten, the Cheshire Cat brings Alice from each parallel world back to Wonderland, trying to awaken people's memories, and despite failures after failures, the Cheshire Cat still believes that he will find the right Alice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Play as different Alice and utilize different abilities and decks to defeat your enemies, each Alice has her own story! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Spellbound "monsters" are not real monsters, so defeat them to break the spell and discover their true nature! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Playing cards, which seem to be everywhere, will become your biggest fighting force at this moment! Poker soldiers can get different runes to increase combat power! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Arrange Poker Pawns of the same number of points or color to get a reinforcement effect, they don't have emotions but are very good at fighting! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Kawaii Ninja</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700220/Super_Kawaii_Ninja/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700220/extras/center.png?t=1711096685"><br/><br/><br/><strong>The great slime king and his army attacking japan, the country is on high alert and only one person can save it, the kawaii ninja.</strong><br/><br/><br/>Super kawaii ninja is a single player arena fps.<br/><br/>In each level you will have to save the peoples of the city within a given time while fighting the ordes of slimes.<br/><br/><br/>During the game you will earn money to increase your abilities.<br/><br/>As you advance in game you will unlock new levels and game modes.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Game Called Paako</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2382580/A_Game_Called_Paako/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2382580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2382580/extras/About_the_game_english.png?t=1711097551"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2382580/extras/About_the_game.gif?t=1711097551"><br/><br/>A Game Called Paako is a pixel-art 2D platformer metagame that tells the story of a game major graduate student making his thesis game project: A Game Called Paako.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2382580/extras/Gameplay_english.png?t=1711097551"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2382580/extras/Gameplay.gif?t=1711097551"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Quality-certified double jump and wall jump mechanics. (Very old-school)<br/></li><li>A fishing minigame. (Of course)<br/></li><li>Watch a talk show. (Why?)<br/></li><li>Find a job. (Or at least try to)<br/></li><li>Listen to your own echo. (No, I don’t have one)</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2382580/extras/Development_english.png?t=1711097551"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2382580/extras/Development.gif?t=1711097551"><br/><br/>A Game Called Paako is initially an MFA thesis project at the University of Southern California created by Chaoran Huang, developed with help of Team Paako. For more information, please visit our publisher page. To learn more about the USC Games program, the #1 Games Program in the world, check out the USC Games website.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emil: A Hero's Journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2259130/Emil_A_Heros_Journey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2259130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2259130/extras/Emil_Trailer_Gif.gif?t=1711094935"><h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2>After Nazi forces take his father away, 11-year-old Emil must use the only two things he has left—creativity and imagination—as he embarks on a perilous journey to find his father. Inspired by the true coming-of-age story of a Holocaust survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2><strong>Emil: A Hero's Journey</strong> is a Cinematic 2.5D Puzzle-Platformer that combines intense action, stealth elements and creative puzzle-solving.<br/>Play as Emil and Interact with the world to creatively solve puzzles and overcome obstacles. Time your actions such as pulling, pushing, climbing, crawling, hiding and much more to avoid danger and find Olek, Emil's father.<h2 class="bb_tag">A personal note </h2>During the midst of Covid, I remember being locked up in my apartment, playing Playdead's masterpiece <i>INSIDE</i> and being blown away by it's art, atmosphere and of course puzzles. After finishing it, I felt a burning inspiration to do something related, but with my personal twist. For some reason, INSIDE's dystopic world, combined with a young boy surviving all on his own, reminded me of something... I didn't know what it was at first but then I understood - It was the survival story of my grandfather, Avraham Hartzook, as a young boy surviving all alone in Europe during WW2, hiding and running from place to place to find shelter.<br/>At first, I thought I would be good at creating video games if I was good at playing them. But after a year as a "one man band" and being part of my finals project at Tel-Aviv University, after doing code, animation and level design my self, I understood it would take me years to create something amazing and dealing with all this alone was very hard emotionally and technically.<br/><br/>From there, I luckily and happily paired with <strong>Afik Yaari</strong> (our Producer), <strong>Or Hadir</strong> (our Animator/3D artist) and later on <strong>Nadav Litver</strong> (our Technical Director) who we not only worked together but became close friends and a first circle for learning, guidance and more important, support group when times were tough (and they were).<br/>Looking back at the creation process of <i>Emil</i> I can definitely say there were many decisions (game design, production, animation) that could have been done different, and yes there's always place to learn and improve. However, I think, that for our first serious game, I am so proud of us and wouldn't do anything differently if I would go through this journey again.<br/><br/>Eventually, <i>Emil: A Hero's Journey</i> the child of a unique mixture of almost two and a half years of sensitive-intensive question asking, the love or video games as a medium for storytelling, thorough research and entrepreneurship. As this is currently a short version of the game, I hope that in the future we will gather all together again to create more emotional-compelling games or even a full length version.<br/>I truly hope this game (and maybe this little letter of confession) has touched you in some kind of way and I hope you will all be lucky as I was to pursue your dreams actively with the support of special friends and family.<br/><br/>If you read all of this,<br/>thank you.<br/>Ohad.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Soil to Bottle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2873190/From_Soil_to_Bottle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2873190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Soil to Bottle is a sandbox winemaking simulator that blends cozy charm with unparalleled realism. In this captivating game, you'll immerse yourself in the art and science of winemaking, where every decision shapes the character and quality of your wines.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Delve into the intricate details of viticulture and oenology. Experience the entire winemaking journey From Soil to Bottle.<br/></li><li>Embrace the freedom to experiment and explore, as there's no fixed formula for crafting the perfect wine. Just like in life, there's no exact correct answer.<br/></li><li>Discover the joy of blending different grape varieties, mastering the art of balance and complexity. <br/></li><li>Navigate the challenges of the winemaking world, from unpredictable weather to demanding clients, as you strive to build your winery's reputation and success.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Record Retriever</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2119580/Golden_Record_Retriever/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2119580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2119580/extras/GIF_Gameplay.gif?t=1711091464"><br/><br/><strong>Golden Record Retriever (GRR) introduces <u>dice</u> instead of cards to the roguelike deck-building genre, creating a new genre of <i>Roguelike Dice Building</i>. Collect and upgrade unique dice that contribute to your team in their own way, and <u>grow from victim to conqueror</u> of luck and chance!</strong><br/><br/>On Earth, a golden retriever named <strong>River</strong> had an owner named "Paul".  An inventor, Paul's fascination with space and aliens led him to spend his life savings on building a spaceship.<br/>Soon, the ship is off into space, loaded with golden records of friendly greetings.<br/><br/>Shortly thereafter, Paul falls ill and dies. Lonely and alone in the empty house, River one day receives unexpected visitors who say,<br/><i>"The golden records your friend shot out have caused trouble throughout the universe.  You will now travel to the planets and retrieve the Golden Record".</i><br/><br/>With an enormous mission to save the universe, River sets out on a journey.<br/><br/>...But for River, who has only ever lived on Earth, life in space won't be easy - it's more like a <strong>puzzle</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">Engine Building for Puzzle Solving</h2><br/>Each time, River is given a new mission and destination, and he must overcome a series of challenges as he builds his team to complete the journey.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2119580/extras/GIF_ThreeTerry_Eng_0322.gif?t=1711091464"><br/><br/>However, the situations he faces are far from typical combat. Instead, they're more like puzzles that require thought and deliberation.<br/>You'll need to place colored orbs called "auras" on the board to use Action Cards to resolve the situation. It's your <u>teammates</u> that create these auras, and it's up to you to <u>place your teammates in the right places</u> to solve the puzzle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2119580/extras/GIF_CrewInfo_Eng.gif?t=1711091464"><br/><br/><i>Almost</i> every teammate has the skill to create auras. But they don't always do what you want them to do, because skills are represented by dice sides and abilities. If you want a blue aura and roll a die that shows blue on three of the 6 sides and red on the other three, you have a 50% chance of getting your wish.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2119580/extras/Capture_Upgrade_Eng.png?t=1711091464"><br/><br/>But don't worry, there are ways to control the <strong>luck and odds</strong>. As you work your way through situations, you'll have the opportunity to "upgrade" your teammates by changing the composition of the dice sides, or enhancing their effects and abilities to produce more auras or be more <i>reliable</i>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2119580/extras/Capture_Shop_Eng.png?t=1711091464"><br/><br/>There is another way to upgrade your teammates: Gear. You can equip one piece of gear per teammate, and you can earn gear in a variety of ways, including shop purchases, situation resolution rewards, and planet scouting. With the right combination of gear, your teammates will be even more powerful than when you first met them!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2119580/extras/GIF_Antique_Eng.gif?t=1711091464"><br/><br/>Then collect "Antiques," the equivalent of the relics in the traditional deck-building genre. When their requirements are met, they provide you with the means to overcome an unfavorable situation, by generating bonus auras, healing your teammates' injuries, and so on.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2119580/extras/Capture_Briefing_resized_Eng.png?t=1711091464"><br/><br/>It's up to you how you build your team, with which teammates and items, but ultimately your team's goal is to succeed in the mission, so you don't want to stray too far from the direction the mission requires.<br/>Each new mission will determine the <strong>theme</strong> of the run. Just as you would adjust your deck build based on who the final boss is, your team build should be different each time based on where the mission takes you.<h2 class="bb_tag">Inspired by Legacy Board Games</h2><br/>GRR is heavily inspired by the legacy board game genre. Each mission follows the roguelike format, but the choices and actions you make will ultimately affect the universe. So, when visiting a planet to resolve a situation, it's good to go for an easy and quick option. But try to consider other options if they can buy you the planet's favor. Then the planet will remember your warm heart and repay you someday.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2119580/extras/GIF_RiverLike_Eng_0322.gif?t=1711091464"><br/><br/>Furthermore, the planets you helped and those you didn't will meet different fates in the great vortex created by the factions of the universe. To make matters worse, as the number of decaying planets increases, your mission may become more difficult to complete.<br/><br/><strong>But don't limit your imagination before you play GRR, because it also includes:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 80+ characteristic teammates<br/></li><li> 3 destinations<br/></li><li> 200+ visitable planets and countless routes<br/></li><li> 120+ gear items<br/></li><li> Antiques(Relics) and story cards</li></ul><br/>☉ <i>All names and stories in this game are fictional and have nothing to do with actual events or history.</i> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momo and the Mine</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2542550/Momo_and_the_Mine/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542550/extras/01.gif?t=1711091565"><br/><br/>Help this charismatic mole collect matchsticks in a haunted mine in this challenging platform game!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Easy-to-learn gameplay and tight controls.<br/><br/></li><li> Beautiful graphics in pixel art that refer to the most nostalgic games of the 8bit era.<br/><br/></li><li> An optional retro filter that will increase the nostalgia even more.<br/><br/></li><li> The best of chiptune in an immersive and memorable soundtrack.<br/><br/></li><li> Play 40 levels including boss battles.<br/><br/></li><li> Cute characters and enemies.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542550/extras/02.gif?t=1711091565"><br/><br/>You're not going to let this adorable mole get cold, are you?						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2797350/Dea/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2797350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A classic turn-based RPG that takes in a world full of charismatic characters and interesting stories. "A self-proclaimed goddess asks a boy and his friends to protect Lastia, the last piece of land remaining in their world... but why them?"<br>
Join them in this adventure made with RPG Maker for fans of old school RPGs.						</br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cozy Room Decorator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2615130/Cozy_Room_Decorator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/room.gif?t=1711090820"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/about.png?t=1711090820"><br/><strong>Step into the world of Cozy Room Decorator </strong>where you’re the chief curator of cozy and it’s up to <i>you</i> to define what cozy means. Whether that means a lived-in kitchen space filled with sweets, or a tech-laden game room, the combinations are waiting to be explored. Dive into a world of boundless imagination and creativity with a treasure trove of thousands of items, each brimming with endless possibilities. Equipped with your very own room, this whimsical isometric room design game invites you to unleash your inner interior decorator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>What Is It?</strong></h2>Cozy Room Decorator is a casual room decorating game that offers players an opportunity to unleash their creativity. Gameplay is as simple as drag and drop what you want into the space. Players are given a room template that has a fixed isometric view, so two walls and a floor are the “shell” of the room. At game start up, players are given a catalog full of items to use in their rooms. There will be a variety of items to choose from so the player can decide what style of room they want. Some examples of items are bedroom furniture, kitchen appliances, and bathroom items. We’ve also done away with item collision restrictions, so players can merge items together to create “new items”. There is no overarching plot to the game, nor are there any side quests or prerequisites that may hinder one from decorating within gameplay. There is no in-game currency system that forces a player to “buy” furniture for their rooms. The objective of Cozy Room Decorator is simply to decorate. This game is especially for those that want to put together an aesthetic room, but perhaps don’t want to deal with the hassle and headache of learning a 3D modeling program. The integrated online community gallery will also help lend a hand in offering inspiration as players will be able to upload their rooms for others to view as well as download rooms for their own uses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/features.png?t=1711090820"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/scenes.gif?t=1711090820"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cozy Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Decorate your room to show your unique style.<br/></li><li>Choose from thousands of items!<br/></li><li>Decorate Inside and Outside.<br/></li><li>Change the walls, floors or background of your room.<br/></li><li>Select from different lighting options, time of day or weather patterns.<br/></li><li>Pick different art options for different photo frames that you decorate with.<br/></li><li>Change the ambient noise sound effects to set the mood of your environment.<br/></li><li>Change the location of your room for a change of scenery!<br/></li><li>Upload Rooms to Community Gallery.<br/></li><li>Browse other player's rooms online to gain Inspiration.<br/></li><li>Backup and restore rooms from our online platform.<br/></li><li>Future versions of the game will have cross save enabled. <br/></li><li>Collision is disabled to allow merging items so players can be very creative!<br/></li><li>A sandbox game. There is no story. Just decorating at your own pace.<br/></li><li>Turn the grid on or off, there is no grid-snapping by design. <br/></li><li>A truly unique and beautiful soundtrack, hand crafted by the Lucky Roll team!<br/></li><li>Enjoy our wallpaper mode. Hide the interface and use your room as a desktop wallpaper!</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/outside.gif?t=1711090820"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/community.png?t=1711090820"><br/><br/>Cozy Room Decorator has online features that take the game to the next level! <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fluckyrollstudio.com%2Fsignup" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Sign up</a> for a Lucky Roll account and you'll be able view other players rooms in the <strong>Community Gallery</strong>. Once a day there are new featured rooms on the home page! You can always explore more rooms to see the newest rooms and most popular rooms in real time! Show support by favoriting your favorite rooms or search for something special using our search features. Every room uploaded to the community gallery can be loaded and viewed just like your own rooms! The community gallery was designed to bring players together in a space to gain inspiration and to show off all the hard work put in to each and every room.<h2 class="bb_tag">Online Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Back-up and save your rooms.<br/></li><li>Restore your game data from your online save.<br/></li><li>Explore the community gallery to gain inspiration for your next design!<br/></li><li>Have your rooms featured and displayed in the gallery for other players to view.<br/></li><li>Cross Save is enabled. In the future you'll be able to bring your rooms to any platform.<br/></li><li>View, download and edit your own rooms in the community gallery. <br/></li><li>Found a room you liked? Load the room and view it to see more detail.<br/></li><li>Don't worry, you can only edit your own rooms in the community gallery.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/online.gif?t=1711090820"><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FBHkBQH7Udh" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/discord.png?t=1711090820"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FBHkBQH7Udh" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our amazing and growing community over at Discord!</a> We post patch notes, road maps and game updates for all of our games in our discord! For Cozy Room Decorator in specific we have a place to share your rooms with other decorators, a place to request features and of course many rooms to chat about the game. Meet other like-minded people and become a part of the Lucky Roll community. We'll be waiting! <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/follow.png?t=1711090820"><br/>Follow Lucky Roll Studio on Social Media! As a new studio we're really just starting to grow. Every follow and repost helps us tremendously. <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.tiktok.com%2F%40luckyrollstudio" rel="noopener" target="_blank">TikTok</a><br/></li><li><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fluckyrollstudio" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Instagram</a><br/></li><li><a href="https://twitter.com/luckyrollstudio" rel="" target="_blank">Twitter/X</a><br/></li><li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@luckyrollstudio" rel="" target="_blank">Youtube</a><br/></li><li><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitch.tv%2Fluckyrollstudio" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Twitch</a><br/></li><li><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fluckyrollstudio" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Facebook</a><br/></li><li><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.threads.net%2F%40luckyrollstudio" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Threads</a><br/></li><li><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.linkedin.com%2Fcompany%2Fluckyrollstudio" rel="noopener" target="_blank">LinkedIn</a></li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fluckyrollstudio.com%2Fmailing-list" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615130/extras/mail.gif?t=1711090820"/></a><br/>Discord and social media isn't really your thing? We get it. Please join our <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fluckyrollstudio.com%2Fmailing-list" rel="noopener" target="_blank">mailing list</a> if you want updates on Cozy Room Decorator and future games by Lucky Roll Studio.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow of Engimor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840140/Shadow_of_Engimor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840140/extras/Снимок.PNG?t=1711088736"><br/><strong>Glory to the Kingdom of Engimor!</strong><br/>Ah the Kingdom of Engimor A majestic place unfortunately with the unfortunate fate of being consumed by darkness. There seems to be no hope, but then out of nowhere he appears. The Guardian of Kings is a beacon of hope in this world who is ready to help the kingdom and his king survive.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840140/extras/Снимо2к.PNG?t=1711088736"><br/><strong>Explore.</strong> Kingdom of Engimor is not only the beauty of the castle, but also beautiful fields and forests, as well as abandoned mines and secret passages<br/><strong>Enemies.</strong>The Darkness is gaining strength and throwing its forces against the Guardian of Kings. Will he be able to overcome them and reach his goal?<br/><strong>Story.</strong> Get a closer look at the story of the Guardian of Kings' mission and his ally.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840140/extras/Сни3мок.PNG?t=1711088736"><br/>But that's just the beginning! We aim not only to create an engaging gameplay but also to support you throughout your journey. Get ready for endless adventures, because we promise regular free updates that will expand your experience and introduce new possibilities into our world.<br/>New levels, characters, and much more await you in future updates. We believe every player deserves full access to content, so our updates will be absolutely free. Our team is committed to creating the best gaming experience, and we invite you to be part of our amazing journey.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eye see fun</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2773460/Eye_see_fun/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2773460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Eye See Fun" is an adventure and puzzle game that offers a rich combination of elements. In this game, players take control of an eye to interact with various objects in the scenes, unravel complex puzzles, and progressively unlock different environments. Adding to the excitement, players have the opportunity to assist non-playable characters (NPCs) in fulfilling their wishes within these diverse settings. It's not just a game; it's the tangible realization of the author's unique and imaginative ideas.<br>
The game's design philosophy emphasizes a relaxed and enjoyable gaming experience, completely devoid of any violent or explicit content. It is suitable for players of all ages to unwind and immerse themselves in the delightful atmosphere.						</br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kakuriyo Village ~Moratorium of Adolescence~</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2326590/Kakuriyo_Village_Moratorium_of_Adolescence/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/故事_EN_.png?t=1711077657"><br/><br/><strong>As they mature, will they be together forever?</strong><br/><br/>Summer<br/>Emerald, green plants growing everywhere.<br/>Sparkling white dirt shimmered on the gravel road from sunlight.<br/>The storm clouds resemble the intimidating gates of a grand castle.<br/>Most importantly, is the strange and endless blue sky.<br/><br/>Summer<br/>The landscape filled with primitive colors looked so blindingly bright.<br/>The climate ravages the flesh and revives memories of the past.<br/>The shifting mirage reflects the fullness of being homesick.<br/><br/>Summer<br/>The most special season for children.<br/>The most ordinary season for adults.<br/><br/>Summer<br/>The past that can't be revived.<br/><br/>6 months later a couple of childhood friends Ao &amp; Hinori met again during the New Year.<br/>Escaping from a boring family party, their friendship sways between maturity and youthfulness...<br/>Unexpectedly, on the way home, they accidentally broke into a village called "Kakuriyo Village".<br/><br/>They didn't realize that it was a sexist village where men and women had unequal statuses.<br/>Because of Hinori's boyish appearance, the villagers mistaken her as a boy.<br/>So, until they find a way to escape from the village, they must figure out how to hide that Hinori is a girl...<br/><br/>There's only one rule in this village that can not be broken, and that is " You can not disguise your physical gender".<br/>Rumor has it, whoever breaks this rule will be punished horribly…<br/><br/>Can they successfully escape from the village?<br/>It's all left to the players to decide.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/奇諾理_英語.jpg?t=1711077657"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/遊戲特色_EN_.png?t=1711077657"><br/><br/><strong>They experienced young love that sways between youthfulness and maturity.</strong><br/><br/>"Even if you're destined to love--And even if the gods wish you to love each other--<br/>but you can't be together because of fate,<br/>to fight against this fate, <br/>the god summoned his people here. To give happiness to the world--"<br/><br/>Hinori &amp; Ao asked for help from the Shrine Maiden to escape but learned a shocking truth instead.<br/><br/>"If they return to their world, their paths will never cross again──"<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/在房間互動.gif?t=1711077657"><br/><br/>The two of them will spend a year here.<br/>They love each other forever in this constantly cyclical world that does not age or die,<br/>or they find the courage to overcome their separation and look towards the future.<br/>Their fate is all decide by "You" the player.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/四季.jpg?t=1711077657"><br/><br/><strong>Explore the open village!</strong><br/><br/>From morning to night, there are countless events in the village that are waiting for you to explore.<br/>Let's explore &amp; discover all 4 seasons of this beautiful village with Ao and Hinori!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/幽_英語.jpg?t=1711077657"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/戀川流歌_英語.jpg?t=1711077657"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/紗那_英語.jpg?t=1711077657"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/理紗_英語.jpg?t=1711077657"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/扇町華繪_英語.jpg?t=1711077657"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/梅川美琴_英語.jpg?t=1711077657"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/文野亞子_英語.jpg?t=1711077657"><br/><br/>More than 20 fully-voiced supporting characters!<br/>Enjoy interacting with all the residents!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Basic CG 80 pics (color)<br/></li><li>Total of 200 scenes<br/></li><li>All scenes are voiced<br/></li><li>Expected playing time over 20 hours</li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Ftv4k6jFHKu" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/discord_link.gif?t=1711077657"/></a> <a href="https://twitter.com/bokibokigames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2326590/extras/twitter.gif?t=1711077657"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room -Random Dungeon-</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2847000/Room_Random_Dungeon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2847000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							When I woke up, I was in a small room. <br/>Escape through the endless rooms.<br/><br/><u>Explore the room using light while running away from threats.<br/><br/>Solve the mystery and escape from the room</u><h2 class="bb_tag">【concept】</h2>・A haunted house that you can play over and over again<br/>・A story that progresses each time you escape from 6 rooms<br/>・Each time you play, you will experience a different room and may arrive at a different ending.<h2 class="bb_tag">【flashlight】</h2>The room is pitch black and you can only see your surroundings.<br/>A flashlight allows you to explore a room more efficiently.<br/>Unravel the mysteries of the room by relying on the light.<br/><br/>Using a flashlight will increase your visibility and may make it easier to recognize and deal with "threats."<br/>"Threat" is not good at light. You may be able to counter it by shining a light on it.<br/><br/>If you continue to use a flashlight, the battery will drain. When you turn it off, the battery will continue to charge.<br/>Just turning the flashlight on will drain the battery, so be careful when switching it on and off quickly.<br/><br/>※This game is a horror action game inspired by Backrooms, The Witch's House, The Exit 8, etc.<h2 class="bb_tag">【guide】</h2>Move：arrow key<br/>Flashlight : keyboard[A] or pad[X]<br/>Fix the angle : keyboard[S] or pad[A]						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Collapse: Code Name Bakery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1127700/Reverse_Collapse_Code_Name_Bakery/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Reverse Collapse: Code Name Bakery faithfully recreates MICA Team’s Codename: Bakery Girl (2013) with revamped graphics, new gameplay mechanics, and expanded narrative.<br/><br/>30 years after the events of Girls’ Frontline, Antarctic Union (AU) special agent Mendo goes on an important mission in the heart of the North Caucasus. Unexpectedly ambushed by the forces of the Union of Rossatrism Nations Coalitions (URNC), his situation takes a dramatic turn with the appearance of Jefuty, the mysterious silver-haired “Bakery Girl.” Together, they traverse hostile terrains, unraveling the dark secrets shrouded within the GRAVIRUL Project.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Game Features</strong></h2>Classic Tactical RPG: command a diverse roster of characters, each with unique skills and abilities. Masterfully orchestrate tactical maneuvers and leverage a vast arsenal of advanced weapons and crafted items to navigate through and triumph over challenging situations.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/zhanyi.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>60+ Campaign Stages: navigate through a variety of intricate missions while balancing strategic elements such as stealth, unique stage mechanisms, and varied terrains. Overcome these challenges to achieve the coveted S-rank status<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/qianxing.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>Immersive storytelling: vibrant illustrations and 2D animations work together to deliver every encounter with heightened intensity and emotional impact.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/shaonvcg.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/新小人cg.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>The Original Saga Retold: with a script exceeding over 300,000 words, the expanded narrative goes beyond recreating the intense battle over two days. Stay alert for hidden depths and untold stories that bring new dimensions to the saga. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/fenweigai.png?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>Stay Connected:<br/>Twitter (X): @Re_Collapse_EN<br/>Discord: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FDXfNGu8QXR" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.com/invite/DXfNGu8QXR</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Collapse: Code Name Bakery</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1127700/Reverse_Collapse_Code_Name_Bakery/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Reverse Collapse: Code Name Bakery faithfully recreates MICA Team’s Codename: Bakery Girl (2013) with revamped graphics, new gameplay mechanics, and expanded narrative.<br/><br/>30 years after the events of Girls’ Frontline, Antarctic Union (AU) special agent Mendo goes on an important mission in the heart of the North Caucasus. Unexpectedly ambushed by the forces of the Union of Rossatrism Nations Coalitions (URNC), his situation takes a dramatic turn with the appearance of Jefuty, the mysterious silver-haired “Bakery Girl.” Together, they traverse hostile terrains, unraveling the dark secrets shrouded within the GRAVIRUL Project.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Game Features</strong></h2>Classic Tactical RPG: command a diverse roster of characters, each with unique skills and abilities. Masterfully orchestrate tactical maneuvers and leverage a vast arsenal of advanced weapons and crafted items to navigate through and triumph over challenging situations.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/zhanyi.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>60+ Campaign Stages: navigate through a variety of intricate missions while balancing strategic elements such as stealth, unique stage mechanisms, and varied terrains. Overcome these challenges to achieve the coveted S-rank status<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/qianxing.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>Immersive storytelling: vibrant illustrations and 2D animations work together to deliver every encounter with heightened intensity and emotional impact.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/shaonvcg.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/新小人cg.gif?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>The Original Saga Retold: with a script exceeding over 300,000 words, the expanded narrative goes beyond recreating the intense battle over two days. Stay alert for hidden depths and untold stories that bring new dimensions to the saga. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1127700/extras/fenweigai.png?t=1711108567"><br/><br/>Stay Connected:<br/>Twitter (X): @Re_Collapse_EN<br/>Discord: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FDXfNGu8QXR" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.com/invite/DXfNGu8QXR</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI.Cybercraft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2429630/AICybercraft/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>THIS GAME OFFERS THREE IMMERSIVE MODES: SPACHESHIPS BATTLES, TOWER DEFENSE,  &amp; FIRST-PERSON SHOOTER</strong><br/> -  39 Levels of Spaceships battles<br/> -  10 Levels of Tower Defense<br/> -  7  Levels of Battles against AI Bosses<br/> -  3 Levels of Endless Space Battles<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/SPACESHIP-BATTLES.GIF?t=1711074222"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/ships.gif?t=1711074222"><br/>Prepare for high-stakes Spaceship Battles where strategy meets adrenaline-pumping action. Throughout the campaign, unlock a diverse array of spacecraft to navigate cosmic conflicts. Each mission pits you against relentless waves of enemies—from AI robots and drones to formidable mini-Bosses and epic end-level Bosses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/GamePlay.gif?t=1711074222"><br/>Each vessel boasts unique attributes and customizable load-outs, allowing you to tailor your approach to the battles at hand. Before each mission, meticulous planning in the lobby involves purchasing and upgrading tactical missiles, destructive warheads, squad reinforcements, Super weapons, Health boosts, Shields, and more. Mastering these tools is key to navigating the chaos, outmaneuvering foes, and emerging triumphant in the thrilling expanse of space combat.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/Steam_Achievements_Gif.gif?t=1711074222"><br/><strong>Steam Achievements</strong><br/>Test your mettle and prove your mastery in AI.Cybercraft through an array of Steam Achievements. From conquering challenging missions to unlocking hidden story segments, these achievements provide an additional layer of motivation. Showcase your dedication as a defender of Ulara and a beacon of hope for humanity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/Story.gif?t=1711074222"><br/><strong>THE STORY</strong><br/>"AI.Cybercraft" thrusts players into a gripping futuristic scenario where humanity fights for survival against invading AI robots that decimated Earth in 2068. As battles spill into the galaxies, humans stake their claim on new planets like Ulara, seeking refuge and a chance to strike back.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/TOWER-DEFENCE-MODE.gif?t=1711074222"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/Gif-3.gif?t=1711074222"><br/>Engage in Tower Defense Mode, where your critical task is to fortify defenses by tactically placing an array of ground and air defenses. The relentless AI adversaries launch calculated assaults from strategic points encircling your base, requiring astute management of defenses while safeguarding key elements: energy reserves, technological advancements, and the central machine gun tower - the linchpin of your defense strategy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/Gif-5.gif?t=1711074222"><br/>the dynamic battlefield demands swift action. When the situation escalates, seamlessly transition to a first-person perspective. As you switch to FPS mode, assume the frontline defender role, wielding the potent Machine Gun Tower. Your accuracy and reflexes become pivotal in repelling successive enemy waves and preventing breaches that could compromise your mission or base integrity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/FPS.GIF?t=1711074222"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/Gif-2.gif?t=1711074222"><br/>In the adrenaline-fueled First-Person Shooter mode, you're the critical support for your defenses under siege. Operating the potent machine gun emplacement at your base's core, your task is to fend off relentless assaults. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/Gif-4.gif?t=1711074222"><br/>Alongside the machine gun, an anti-air guided missile system stands ready to intercept drones and stray satellites hurtling towards your stronghold. Your precision and speed are paramount as you thwart aerial threats and prevent breaches that could jeopardize your mission.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429630/extras/Gif-6.gif?t=1711074222"><br/>Amidst the chaos, the Tech Center sends crucial drops containing ammunition and raw materials. Your sharpshooting skills come into play as you shoot down these supplies, securing resources vital for maintaining your defense. Balancing offense with defense, your role as the frontline defender is pivotal.<br/><br/>Throughout the game, players experience thrilling combat, delve into strategic planning, and engage in high-stakes battles against powerful AI adversaries. With its diverse modes and challenging gameplay, "AI.Cybercraft" offers an immersive and adrenaline-pumping experience set in a captivating futuristic universe.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REMINGTON, the A.I.</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2836260/REMINGTON_the_AI/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2836260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disclaimer: The story plot of REMINGTON, the A.I. is entirely fictional. None of it is based on real-life events, NOR is it meant to predict the future. It is simply a story meant to entertain. (end of disclaimer)<br/><br/>REMINGTON, the A.I. is a kinetic (linear) visual novel set in the year 3000. Human society has reached super-civilization, and A.I.s and robots are part of our daily life.<br/><br/>At the forefront of the A.I. industry stand two giants -- the US government and a private European company called ENTROPY. <br/><br/>The US government created REMINGTON, a scientific-research A.I. <br/><br/>ENTROPY created Waverly, a socializing humanoid. <br/><br/>Until 2 weeks ago, REMINGTON was the undisputed NO.1 artificial technology in the world. Now his competition WAVERLY threatens to overtake him with a mega-upgrade. <br/><br/>Who will win the International Artificial Technologies Award this year? The American scientist REMINGTON, or the European socialite WAVERLY?<br/><br/>Join REMINGTON as he prepares for fierce competition with WAVERLY, and discover a global conflict far bigger than themselves...<h2 class="bb_tag">What to Expect?</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> NOTE: Even though the gameplay trailer video has no sound, the actual game does have background music<br/></li><li> There are a total of 6 episodes<br/></li><li> Each episode is set in a different place. For example, one episode is set in a party, the next episode is set in a military compound<br/></li><li> Each episode has many new characters. The main characters will appear in every episode, but each episode will have somewhere between 2 to 6, or 8 new side characters who are just there for the one episode. This is to keep the story feeling fresh and something new always coming-in<br/></li><li> Very few, if at all any deaths. This is NOT a game where everyone dies. The story is focused on competition and growing as a person, rather than death and grief<br/></li><li> The first episode will be released FAR BEFORE the other episodes. This means there will be a time gap between the first episode's release and the other episodes. The purpose of this is to gather feedback and see if any changes need to be made to the future episodes, as well as dealing with any code bugs and other coding issues.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Want Notifications When the Game Comes Out?</h2>Add this game to your Wishlist and ALSO click the "follow" button on this store page. <br/>When the game is out, notifications will be sent to your Steam inbox<h2 class="bb_tag"> Mac and Linux Users Please Read </h2>This game was originally planned to be released on all platforms (Mac, Linux and Windows). Due to many factors, the Windows version will be released first. Whether the game will be released for Mac and Linux remains to be seen. <br/><br/>If you like this game, add it to your Wishlist + Click 'Follow' on the Store Page. All followers will get a notification if a Mac/Linux version is announced<h2 class="bb_tag"> Credits </h2>All the writing, coding and artwork of this game is done by CM Pictures. NO A.I.s were used for ANY part of the game. <br/><br/>All the soundtrack used in Episode 1 is made by Infraction (inAudio): <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Finaudio.org%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://inaudio.org/</a>.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep The House Warm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2865890/Keep_The_House_Warm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2865890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Keep the house warm as long as possible in this endless survival against the winter!<br>
The outside temperature lowers every day!<br>
<br>
If the inside temperature goes below 10°C the pipes will freeze!<br>
<br>
Keep filling the heater with woodchips while also managing your hunger.<br>
If the ashes overfill the inside temperature starts to drop.<br/>
<br/>
Set the heat, order more woodchips and upgrade the house insulation from the control panel<br/>
<br/>
Finding bread or fish automatically gives you money and relieves your hunger. <br/>
<br/>
Ways to earn money:<br/>
Every day you get money based on the inside temperature!<br/>
Finding bread from the woodchips gives a random amount of money!<br/>
Ice fishing gives money based on fishing experience! <br/>
After day 18 you can start investing in the stock market!<br/>
<br/>
Power-ups:<br/>
When you reach day 10 and 20, you get to choose 1 of 5 power-ups.<br/>
Fishing speed - Boosts your fishing speed<br/>
Pickup speed - Move woodchips  and clean the ashes faster <br/>
Bread % - Boosts your chance to find bread<br/>
$2000 - instant +$2000<br/>
Daily money - Boosts the amount of money you get based on the inside temperature<br/>
<br/>
Choose your power-ups wisely, manage your resources and time to survive as long as possible!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VirtualBuster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2839320/VirtualBuster/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2839320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							welcome! “VirtualBuster” is a new level of action-adventure that brings the legendary arcade gun game to the realistic virtual reality (VR) world. Using both hands, you can enjoy a unique combat experience where you can slash enemies with a sword in one hand, block and deflect bullets, and hold a gun in the other hand to acquire items and switch to a special gun to kill robot criminals.<br>
<br>
characteristic:<br>
<br>
1. Combat experience in virtual reality: Using VR technology, players can become so immersed that it is difficult to distinguish it from reality. The thrilling battles that take place in various environments provide a sense of reality.<br>
<br>
2. Missions and challenges of varying difficulty: While responding to various crime incidents occurring in each area of the city, players can improve their mission performance by performing missions of varying difficulty from easy to difficult.<br/>
<br/>
3. Two-handed play: The player can cut enemies with a sword in one hand, block and deflect bullets, and use the other hand to kill enemies by switching between the basic gun and a special weapon that appears mid-play.<br/>
<br/>
4. Special Weapons: In addition to basic knives and guns, acquire a variety of special weapons to gain the upper hand in the battle against robot criminals. Overwhelm powerful enemies with special abilities and tactical choices.<br/>
<br/>
“VirtualBuster” provides an exciting experience that combines reality and virtuality. Become the city's hero against the darkness of crime!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sneaky Snacks - Hidden Object Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2823190/Sneaky_Snacks__Hidden_Object_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the role of a chef who has been given the task to cook the kings royal feast. There is only one problem... the snacks are missing! <br/><br/>Embark on a hidden object journey where you must find over 40 different snacks &amp; objects across 20 unique medieval style levels. Once completed you will unlock 10 challenging bonus levels to really test your skills.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823190/extras/smallmenupic1.png?t=1711069396"><br/><br/>You will have to beat the clock but don't worry as you'll have time bonuses and even mini games to earn extra hints along your journey!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823190/extras/smallmenupic2.png?t=1711069396"><br/><br/>Search high and low as you may never know where those pesky snacks are hiding.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2823190/extras/smallmenupic3.png?t=1711069396"><br/><br/>Sneaky Snacks is a simple but relaxing game which should take roughly 1 hour to complete for intermediate players of this genre.<br/><br/>Best of luck!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HappyFunland</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/642910/HappyFunland/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/642910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You had never heard of Happyfunland theme park, or it's tragic tale, when you agreed to meet a total stranger, named Larry, in the middle of a South Florida swamp. Perhaps if you would have known about the grisly events that happened there, you wouldn't have agreed to the job!<br>
<br>
Explore the abandoned remains and uncover the dark secrets of Mort Grisly's HappyFunland theme park, Home of Randy Rodent!<br>
<br>
Ride rides such as the piratey boat ride "Marauders of the Tropic Isles''!<br>
<br>
Get spooked by grisly ghosts in the "Grisly Manor" spookhouse attraction!<br>
<br/>
Get nuttier than squirrel droppings on "Feral Squirrel's Nutty Excursion" dark ride!<br/>
<br/>
Experience happiness overboard on "It's a Happy Little Grisly World ''!<br/>
<br/>
Those and many more unique and exciting attractions await you at HappyFunland! South Florida's happiest and funnest themed park!<br/>
<br/>
No lines! No Waiting! No Escape!<br/>
<br/>
Warning! This is a high speed turbulent insane VR thrill ride that may cause motion sickness in certain users. <br/>
<br/>
VR motion controllers required. Supports Vive and Valve Index controllers, as well as Quest 2 via Oculus Link						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craft Lands</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2797570/Craft_Lands/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2797570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Let's develop the village!<br>
Craft Lands is a development simulation game where you plant trees in a vast empty space and develop a village.<br>
Defend your village from enemies, plant trees and get resources. Use the resources to build houses and increase the number of residents.<br>
However, residents' satisfaction remains low with just building houses. It would be better to build a lookout tower, prepare a park, and plant some trees.<br>
What kind of village you create is entirely up to you.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054970/Dragons_Dogma_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Note: There are other sets that include this item.<br/><br/>Set forth on your grand adventure, Arisen!<br/><br/>Dragon’s Dogma is a single player, narrative driven action-RPG series that challenges the players to choose their own experience – from the appearance of their Arisen, their vocation, their party, how to approach different situations and more. Now, in this long-awaited sequel, the deep, explorable fantasy world of Dragon’s Dogma 2 awaits.<br/><br/>On your journey, you’ll be joined by Pawns, mysterious otherworldly beings, in an adventure so unique you will feel as if accompanied by other players while on your own adventure.<br/><br/>All of these elements are elevated further through physics technology, artificial intelligence (AI) and the latest in graphics, to create a truly immersive fantasy world in Dragon’s Dogma 2.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Action that challenges your creativity </u></strong> <br/><br/>Wield swords, bows, and chant magick.<br/>The vocations in Dragon's Dogma 2 give you the ability to approach combat the way you want.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_01.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Company in your single-player experience </u></strong> <br/><br/>Players can customize their own main Pawn, who will always accompany your Arisen, <br/>and enter a covenant with up to 2 additional Pawns from other players through the network. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_02.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Facing the monsters in this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Beyond the town borders, you will encounter diverse monsters that inhabit the lands. <br/>You will need to decide between engaging in battles or finding alternatives; <br/>so be aware of your party’s setup, the terrain around you, and the monsters you face.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_03.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Inhabitants of this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Travelers, merchants, soldiers and other folk go about their daily lives. <br/>Preoccupied by their own objectives and motives, they all exhibit different emotions.<br/>At times, they may lead you to a quest by approaching you and asking for a favor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_04.gif?t=1711067553"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildlands Resurgence</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2599310/Wildlands_Resurgence/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2599310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							section for a game where players need to survive from wildlife, mine resources, craft items and structures,<br>
<br>
 Tribes of the Wildlands Resurgence" is an epic open-world survival game that thrusts you into a rugged wilderness teeming with danger and adventure. Your sole objective? Survive at all costs.<br>
<br>
In this immersive world, you must fend off not only the unforgiving elements of nature but also rival players who are vying for dominance in this untamed land. Hunt or be hunted, it's your choice.<br>
<br>
Explore, Gather, Craft:<br/>
Venture into the sprawling wilderness and mine trees, rocks, and iron ore to gather essential resources. These resources are the building blocks of your survival, allowing you to craft weapons, tools, and structures. Will you construct a towering fortress to defend against intruders or create hidden shelters to avoid detection?<br/>
<br/>
Survive the Wild:<br/>
The wilderness is alive with a diverse range of wildlife, each with its own unique behaviors. Be prepared to face off against ferocious predators, or utilize your skills to become a master of the hunt.<br/>
<br/>
Conflict and Strategy:<br/>
As you interact with other players, engage in intense conflicts, negotiate trades, and form uneasy truces. Will you choose to attack rival tribes to plunder their resources or opt for diplomacy in the pursuit of peaceful coexistence?<br/>
<br/>
"Wildlands Resurgence: Tribes of the Wilderness" challenges your survival instincts, strategic prowess, and creativity as you navigate a treacherous world filled with surprises and perils. Will you thrive as a solitary survivor or rise to lead a thriving tribe in the midst of this unforgiving wilderness? The choice is yours. Begin your journey today!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anime Thighs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2838450/Anime_Thighs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2838450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Who doesn't like some Anime Thighs?<h2 class="bb_tag">The game</h2>Anime Thighs is a puzzle game with 3 unique puzzle formulas that switch up every 4 levels, so be ready for a challenge, as with every level the game gets a bit harder!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/>- Enjoy 12 unique levels with 3 different puzzle modes for you to complete.<br/><br/>- Visit the Gallery, revealing our girls artwork for each level you completed.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Days</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2856570/Dark_Days/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2856570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Dark Days</strong>, a supernatural Thriller, was our team’s former project, back in 2016, initially designed for VR mobile headsets and now remastered for PC gaming.<br/><br/>🔶 <strong>A Psychological Creepy Horror Game</strong><br/>🔶 <strong>A first person point'n’click adventure</strong><br/>🔶 <strong>An atmospheric and haunted escape room game</strong><br/>🔶 <strong>4h+ of gameplay with 20 secret tapes to find and randomized puzzles</strong><br/>🔶 <strong>2 different endings</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2856570/extras/DD_SpecialImg_01.png?t=1711103030"><br/>Inspired by <i>Twin Peaks</i> and <i>The X-­Files</i>, <strong>Dark Days</strong> stands as an adventure horror game of its own. From an eerie motel to a haunted desert, solve puzzles and progress towards a disturbing truth. Dive in an American nightmare, immerse yourself in cinematographic environments, but be careful and think smart! Something is hunting you. There's only one rule: if you look at it, this nightmare kills.<br/><br/><strong>◈ An emotional, story heavy supernatural investigation</strong><br/><strong>◈ Accessible gameplay and randomized puzzles</strong><br/><strong>◈ You're the prey, so be smart or be ready to scream!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2856570/extras/DD_SpecialImg_03.png?t=1711103030"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>+1x2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2876140/1x2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2876140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>+1x2</strong> is a super simple clicker game. Just click anywhre to get profit. You can use these money to improve your power by one or multiply it by two. Plus one is temporary upgrade, multiplication by two is permanent. The second upgrade works like a prestige. It resets all money and plus upgrades.<br/><br/>Your goal is to reach the quadrillion value. And +1 or x2 are the only options you have. Good luck!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Nice gameplay<br/></li><li>Nice graphics<br/></li><li>Completable goals<br/></li><li>Three achievements<br/></li><li>11 languages support<br/></li><li>Refund friendly (please don't)</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neanderthal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2267790/Neanderthal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2267790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Humanity's evolution as a species has accelerated over the last 30,000-40,000 years in a manner unparalleled in the evolution of life on Earth. What triggered this change? Genetic mutation? Probably not. Our brains and anatomy have remained relatively unchanged for 4 million years. An encounter with different hominid species? Perhaps...<br/><br/>Play solo against AI, with others locally or against other players online. This digital version of the board game Neanderthal also includes an introductory tutorial to the game which will make it easier to learn Neanderthal. Useful both for playing the app and for when you want to play the physical version of the game.<br/><br/>This is a thematic game where you as a player, will play through the critical epoch during which this change occurred. After millions of years of an uninterrupted, modest nomadic existence, we suddenly developed complex language, began forming tribes and building villages. You play as one of the human species existing at that time. The game system enables you to follow your tribe's evolution as well as that of the environment in which you live. The three players you can represent are the Archaic Man (Player Green), Neanderthal (Player Yellow), and Cro-Magnon (Player Red) species fighting to survive in Europe during the last glacial maximum from 45,000 to 35,000 years ago. You begin the game vocal (i.e. words for speech but not ideas) and with a sexuality (promiscuous, harem, or pair bonding).<h2 class="bb_tag"> NEANDERTHAL SEQUENCE OF PLAY </h2>(six phases per turn)[<br/><br/>1. EVENT &amp; CULTURE AUCTION. <br/>Reveal a daughter card to begin the turn. This indicates the first player and the turn’s event icons applied top to bottom to all players. <br/>2. HUNTER ASSIGNMENT. All players assign their unassigned tribesmen to hunt biomes, become Elders, or perform courtships.<br/>3. NEGOTIATIONS, ATTACKS, &amp; GATHERING. <br/><i>Bribes. </i>As long as one of the negotiators has a Chief, players can bribe others to peacefully withdraw Hunters from contested biomes, including marrying them to their daughters (F1). <br/><i>Attack Roll. </i>Players must use their Hunters to attack other Hunters on the same card (F2).<br/><i>Gathering species</i> add one Baby for each gathering biome (F3) they occupy. <br/>4. ROLL FOR HUNT. All players make hunt rolls, rolling one dice for each of their assigned Hunters.<br/>5. DOMESTIC ANIMALS. Each mature in your tableau gives you the Babies and frees the disks specified.<br/>6. SPECIES ACTIONS. You may perform one action:<br/>Portal Action (vocal only) adds one portal disk from your vocabulary to your brain map. <br/>Neolexia Action (vocal only) frees one dedicated disk to your vocabulary.<br/>Elder Action (tribal only). To perform an Elder Action, you need an Elder of the proper rank. <br/><br/><strong>Category:</strong> Card Game, Economic, Prehistoric<br/><strong>Main mechanism</strong> Auction/Bidding, Dice Rolling, Events, Negotiation, Simulation, Worker Placement						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2243220/Greenland/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2243220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The four players in Greenland represent the Tunit (Player Green), Norse (Player Red), Sea Sámi (Player Blue), and Thule (Player Yellow) tribes inhabiting Greenland from the 11th to the 15th centuries.<br/><br/>Play solo against AI, with others locally or against other players online. Also included in this digital version of Greenland is a introductory tutorial to the game which will make it easier to learn board game. Useful both for playing the app and for when you want to play the physical version of the game.<br/><br/>In this thematic game you as a tribe, attempt to secure food, resources, and technology to increase the size of your tribe and support children, elders, and livestock while also wiping out competing species or gathering resources to collect victory points. You must work around the weather and the extinction of natural resources as well as negotiate deals to protect your wives while you decide between monotheism or polytheism. In this tableau-building game, you'll send your population out to hunt native species of Greenland and even explore the North American coast lands — but some might not come back. (Historically, the climate turned frigid and all but the Thule (Inuit) died out.)<br/><br/>In the game, play takes place over six phases; all players complete each phase in turn order, then the next phase starts. Each turn is one generation. The game ends after 10 turns.<h2 class="bb_tag">GREENLAND SEQUENCE OF PLAY</h2><strong>Resolve events:</strong> Reveal an Event Card to begin the turn. Examples include elder deaths, animal migrations, feuds, or global cooling. If a trade ship arrives, an auction is held for its wares.<br/><strong>Assign hunters:</strong>  Hunters are assigned to hunting grounds, resource gathering, colonizing the New World, raiding other tribes for wives or animals, or promotion to an elder.<br/><strong>Negotiate:</strong> Players can bribe others to peacefully withdraw hunters, including marrying them to their daughters. Players with a War Chief Elder can use hunters to attack others on the same card. The New World turns hostile if there are too many colonists.<br/><strong>Resolve hunting: </strong> Each hunter provide a die-roll modified by technologies and marriage advantages. Success can result in gaining new hunters, resources, hand cards, wives, and/or technologies. Beware, as some animals can be confused by the prey-predator relationship and your hunters might not return. Some successes let your take cards from the central play area into your hand if within hand limit.<br/><strong>Maintain livestock:</strong>  Pay to keep the animals you've already domesticated.<br/><strong>Take elder actions: </strong> Examples include invention, domestication, proselytization, and witch-burning. If you have no elders, you can convert to monotheism.<br/>Depending on each player's ending theistic worldview, he has a variable scoring based on successful hunts (polytheism) or resource gathering (monotheism). Most points in the end wins.<br/><br/><strong>Category:</strong> Card Game, Economic, Prehistoric<br/><strong>Main mechanism</strong> Auction/Bidding, Dice Rolling, Events, Negotiation, Simulation, Worker Placement						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
