<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Seeker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2510720/Artifact_Seeker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FtHwzEeUwBW" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/DS.png?t=1711367082"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/11y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>The unique “Artifacts sharing code function” allows you to share the Artifacts you collect with your friends! !<br/>Artifact Seeker is a 3D Roguelike Survivor RPG game. A game of gods, with Aurorium as the board, And all the mortals as their pawns and swords. You can obtain artifacts by slaying corrupted enemies, collecting gold to exchange it for artifacts at mysterious merchants. How to use the power of artifacts, to play the game of gods? to end the game of gods or to become a god yourself. Artifact Seeker, Your choice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/1z.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Dozens of evolvable skills, extreme sprint dash, and the ultimate special skill to slay enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/2y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/gif1.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Intense paced battles, you can buy artifacts to boost your power after each battle! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/3y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of different artifacts with matching skills to create a wide variety of bond Synergy, and utilize the power of the synergy to challenge higher level enemies! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/4y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>RPG like Events, diverse choices, adventuring dungeons, exploring magical worlds, befriend different heroes and unlock new characters! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/5y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Hundreds of affixes and attributes, dozens of different meta-progressions, weapon unlocking and strengthening, and sharing your own unique artifacts with your pals! There's new contents to experience after every run! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.png?t=1711367082"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2510720/extras/6y.gif?t=1711367082"><br/><strong>Explore the world and discover the hidden secrets behind the story! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living With Sister: Monochrome Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2429860/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1711168850"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_1__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>Living in a fantasy world, it's always been your dream to grow up to be a famous adventurer just like your father. Reality proves to be more boring than fiction, however, as your days are mostly spent doing odd jobs for the villagers. With your friends by your side, you enter the Tournament of the Eights and strive for something greater: the chance to become the top guild in the country. Will you realize your ambitions, or will your hopes slip through your fingers and doom you to a life of monochrome monotony?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_2__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/>As a member of your town's Adventurers' Guild, it's your job to protect the townsfolk. Go on hunts, kill dangerous beasts, and hone your abilities to better tackle whatever challenges tomorrow brings.<br/><br/>Once you get home from work, you'll have your sister to attend to. She's a very sickly girl who needs a lot of help. Manage your household finances well, build up your relationship with your sister, and who knows, perhaps you might even be able to solve the mystery behind her illness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_3__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Big_Brother_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Little_Sister_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kana_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Kasumi_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Yukari_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_Akatsuki_EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2429860/extras/Living_With_Sister_Monochrome_Fantasy_Description_4__EN.png?t=1711168850"><br/><strong>Hand-Drawn Monochrome Art</strong><br/>Though it may lack color, this game's world is anything but colorless! The stunning black-and-white art is chock-full of personality and is sure to leave you with plenty of marvelous monochrome memories!<br/><br/><strong>Unique Combat System</strong><br/>With tons of bizarre and ferocious monsters to fight and dozens of unique skills to unlock, your adventures are sure to be full of challenge and excitement!<br/><br/><strong>Charming Characters</strong><br/>Build up your relationships with your guildmates and your sister to learn about what makes them tick and unlock character-specific abilities to further assist you in your quest to become the top guild in the country!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Chilla's Art] Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793370/Chillas_Art_Shinkansen_0___0/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shinkansen 0 | 新幹線 0号 is a game set in Japan where players are tasked with finding anomalies in the Shinkansen. (Japanese bullet train)<br/><br/><i><strong>Supporter content can be turned on and off at the title screen. (It is on by default) </strong></i><br/><br/><i><strong>Motion Blur and Headbob is turned off by default.</strong></i><br/><br/><strong>Controls:<br/><br/>WASD - Move<br/>Left Click - Interact　<br/>Right Click - Zoom<br/>Shift - Run<br/>ESC - Options</strong><br/><br/>Easy mode - There is an easy mode in the mainmenu available for everyone to enjoy<br/><br/>Auto-save: auto-save for each chapter<br/><br/>Endings: There are two endings<br/><br/><strong><i>If you encounter any technical issues, do the following:<br/><br/>-Update GPU driver<br/>-Lower the Graphics settings/Screen resolution<br/>-Update Windows OS<br/>-Check if your anti-virus software is blocking the game or its save data. (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Delete save, then try again (Save Data location: C:\Users\[YOURUSERNAME]\AppData\LocalLow\Chilla's Art, LLC\Shinkansen0)<br/>-Check if your PC meets the system requirements</i></strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears In Space</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1309620/Bears_In_Space/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FG6w3Zxbp8W" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Steam_CTAbutton_Discord.png?t=1711123009"/></a><br/>Get ready to unleash your inner bear in Bears in Space, the over-the-top<br/>bullet-hell FPS that's bound to have you ROARING with excitement! Dive headfirst into hordes of oil-thirsty robots as you embody Maxwell Atoms, a Spacetronaut turned extraterrestrial castaway, whose DNA has been merged with Beartana, the She-Bear. <br/>Embark on a zany and humorous out-of-this-world adventure that'll have you blasting your way across exciting and varied locations, from wastelands to space carnivals to ancient hidden temples and more as you quest to find your way back to earth and if there’s time, save your crew.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fast-paced Mayhem</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BulletHell_acid2.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Bears In Space offers non-stop, high-energy gameplay. Fight your way through waves of fiendish robots using an arsenal of outrageous weaponry and gadgets. Double jump, dash, and dodge enemy attacks in the tradition of the best old-school shooters.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Mighty As A Bear</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/BearMode.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Consume elusive honey pots and unleash your Ursine rage, transforming into a bear!  <br/>Use your unique DNA fusion to your advantage, carving up robot enemies with your mighty bear powers and masterful knowledge of the ancient art of Bear Fu and the fabled Kuma No Ken.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Upgrade Your Arsenal</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/UpgradeRadial.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Complete challenges and break open loot crates to purchase guns, choosing from a diverse range of over 25 weapons!<br/>Most weapons upgrade, with each kill gaining your equipped weapon XP until it evolves into its next evolution tier! So, get out there and let the lasers fly!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Varied Gameplay</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1309620/extras/Varied_Gameplay_BasketCube.gif?t=1711123009"><br/>Venture beyond the ordinary FPS experience and discover Substories, secrets and collectibles across every level!<br/>Learn how to bake a cake, investigate a crime scene, battle a Rock God, play a round of Basketcube and even bust some ghosts! All while meeting a colourful cast of characters with their own quirks and stories to tell.<br/>Completing these exciting optional encounters brings with it a hefty loot pay off, making these encounters even more rewarding to search out as you save up for your next weapon!<br/><br/>Choose your difficulty and play the game your way!<br/>Modify your difficulty with independent sliders for incoming and outgoing damage. You can also engage our Platform Helper mode, making all platforming segments of our game significantly easier to conquer! Perfect for kids or gamers new to the FPS genre!<br/><br/><br/>Whether you're a seasoned gamer looking for a blast from the past or a casual player seeking a fun-filled adventure, Bears in Space promises a fun and absurd, action packed time. Get ready to shoot, chuckle, and unleash your inner bear in this one-of-a-kind bullet-hell FPS adventure that’s truly out of this world!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4D Golf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2147950/4D_Golf/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>4D Golf</strong> is a mind-bending golf game unlike any other because it's set entirely in a 4-dimensional space. Complete fun and unique golfing challenges as you gain hands-on experience of the 4th dimension and beyond!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2147950/extras/SteamGIF_1.gif?t=1711121562"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 120 levels and 7 vibrant themed worlds<br/></li><li>Tons of visualization options to master 4D space<br/></li><li>Build your own 4D courses in the level editor<br/></li><li>Race the clock in Marble Platforming Mode<br/></li><li>Navigate hidden paths, moving platforms, shifting gravity, speed boosts, and more!<br/></li><li>Unlock custom accessories by completing challenges</li></ul><br/>Now open your third eye and unleash your full potential!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten World:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827510/The_Forgotten_WorldPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FVuKggh6WYN" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/dss.png?t=1711106032"/></a><br/><br/><strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 8 in the official version.<br/>Chapters: 2 prologues, 6 official versions</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/111.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>This is about Alice after Wonderland.<br/>Oblivion is the vilest of spells. As an adult, Alice also experiences a less fairytale-like life and stops dreaming, which also means that everything about Wonderland is slowly disappearing. The people of Wonderland have even forgotten why they exist, and before everything dissipates, the Cheshire Cat casts a phantom spell to try to find Alice in the hope that she can save Wonderland once more.<br/>But the Cheshire Cat can't remember the spell either, and the wrong spell sends it traveling to a parallel world, a world where Alice has no idea that Wonderland even exists.<br/>In order to keep Wonderland from being forgotten, the Cheshire Cat brings Alice from each parallel world back to Wonderland, trying to awaken people's memories, and despite failures after failures, the Cheshire Cat still believes that he will find the right Alice. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/1.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Play as different Alice and utilize different abilities and decks to defeat your enemies, each Alice has her own story! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/2.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Spellbound "monsters" are not real monsters, so defeat them to break the spell and discover their true nature! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/3.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Playing cards, which seem to be everywhere, will become your biggest fighting force at this moment! Poker soldiers can get different runes to increase combat power! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4y.png?t=1711106032"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827510/extras/4.gif?t=1711106032"><br/><strong>Arrange Poker Pawns of the same number of points or color to get a reinforcement effect, they don't have emotions but are very good at fighting! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2054970/Dragons_Dogma_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Note: There are other sets that include this item.<br/><br/>Set forth on your grand adventure, Arisen!<br/><br/>Dragon’s Dogma is a single player, narrative driven action-RPG series that challenges the players to choose their own experience – from the appearance of their Arisen, their vocation, their party, how to approach different situations and more. Now, in this long-awaited sequel, the deep, explorable fantasy world of Dragon’s Dogma 2 awaits.<br/><br/>On your journey, you’ll be joined by Pawns, mysterious otherworldly beings, in an adventure so unique you will feel as if accompanied by other players while on your own adventure.<br/><br/>All of these elements are elevated further through physics technology, artificial intelligence (AI) and the latest in graphics, to create a truly immersive fantasy world in Dragon’s Dogma 2.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Action that challenges your creativity </u></strong> <br/><br/>Wield swords, bows, and chant magick.<br/>The vocations in Dragon's Dogma 2 give you the ability to approach combat the way you want.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_01.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Company in your single-player experience </u></strong> <br/><br/>Players can customize their own main Pawn, who will always accompany your Arisen, <br/>and enter a covenant with up to 2 additional Pawns from other players through the network. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_02.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Facing the monsters in this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Beyond the town borders, you will encounter diverse monsters that inhabit the lands. <br/>You will need to decide between engaging in battles or finding alternatives; <br/>so be aware of your party’s setup, the terrain around you, and the monsters you face.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_03.gif?t=1711067553"><br/><br/><strong><u>Inhabitants of this world </u></strong> <br/><br/>Travelers, merchants, soldiers and other folk go about their daily lives. <br/>Preoccupied by their own objectives and motives, they all exhibit different emotions.<br/>At times, they may lead you to a quest by approaching you and asking for a favor. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2054970/extras/13_GL_DD2_custom_Gif_04.gif?t=1711067553"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cureocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2612680/Cureocity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							We are "Bread On Board," a collective of independent game developers spread across four countries, united by our passion and meeting during a GameJam. <br/>Our game demo was born in the "BOOOM CHALLENGE", a GameJam by GCORES. With only 21 days, we created a game based on a given theme. After the competition, we even won the "Most Popular Game" award at an Online Game Trial Event.<br/>The full playthrough of our game will take about an hour. We hope to give you a short, but super heartwarming and loving adventure❤️.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/1.奇幻而治愈（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>A rookie adventurer fresh on the scene and a former mercenary who was transferred into an adventurer due to injury. Two protagonists with contrasting personalities will embark on an adventure of fantasy and healing together. In the mysterious ruins of an underground dungeon that lies in the depth of a jungle, what awaits them will be...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/2.两位冒险者（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>According to the tavern's adventurer logs, the team heading into the dungeon features a rookie adventurer and an ex-mercenary who is now working as a healer. The adventurer looks as charming as a doll, and the enthusiasm never disappears; the healer is cool and a bit traditional, acting as a guiding figure for their adventure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>What stories have unfolded between these two contrasting characters, and what challenges will they face together in this adventure? The continuation of this adventurous story is yours to discover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/3.注重手法的回合制解谜（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>"People think battles need powerful weapons, but strategy at hand is key." <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_3_en.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>In "Cureocity," the power of your strategy is materialized as the numerical values of your hands in combat. You can swap different weapons or items held in your left and right hands to alter your character's attack and defense stats. You may also change "gestures" to focus attacks or land heavy blows on specific enemies.As you delve deeper into the dungeon, you will take the unique traits of monsters into consideration and discuss strategies with your allies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/4.你的选择决定冒险归途（英文）.png?t=1711172050"><br/>In this adventure, you'll discover not only the secrets hidden within the dungeon, but also the truths about the world and the  characters themselves. When faced with contaminated monsters, you can choose to either fight them or attempt to purify them. Of course, you also have the option to let things take their own course.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2612680/extras/GIF_4_en.gif?t=1711172050"><br/><br/>With each decision,the fate of the protagonists may change. The end of this adventure... is yours to decide.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Publisher</h2>GCORES PUBLISHING is an independent game publishing venture formed by GCORES, committed to bringing you more outstanding indie games from the BOOOM CHALLENGE.<br/>Feel free to follow our <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/44750639" rel="" target="_blank">publisher webpage</a> for future updates.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Ghost Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/915810/Midnight_Ghost_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/915810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>MIDNIGHT GHOST HUNT IS A <i>PETRIFYING</i> PROP HAUNT GAME TO PLAY WITH PALS! </strong><br/><br/>Lying in wait across a series of cursed locations, relentless spirits stalk the halls. Assigned to eliminate them are the Ghost Hunters, armed to the teeth with the ghoul-busting tech to banish them to another realm! Play both Ghost and Hunter in a chaotic 4v4 struggle between the living and the dead.<br/><br/><strong>TONGUE-IN-CHEEK HIDE-AND-SEEK</strong><br/>As a Ghost, conceal yourself inside seemingly harmless pieces of furniture to evade preying Hunters… but when their backs are turned, turn the environment against them with telekinetic bombardment. No chair, lamp, or grandfather clock is innocent in this hijinks-heavy frenzy.<br/><br/><strong>MIDNIGHT MAYHEM</strong><br/>The fun isn’t over yet...when the clock strikes twelve, the witching hour begins, and the Hunters become the Hunted. The tables turn and Ghosts become supercharged, giving Hunters a limited amount of time to survive their vengeful wrath.<br/><br/><strong>MURDEROUS 4v4 MULTIPLAYER</strong><br/>Play together and communicate with your team and ensure a triumphant victory, giving each other pointers on the paths enemies tend to tread. Create synergies with your team's abilities to outthink and outwit your opponents.<br/><br/><strong>HARNESS SUPERNATURAL ABILITIES</strong><br/>The restrictions of reality don’t apply to Ghosts, of course. Claim your supernatural powers, which include turning invisible, causing furniture to float, and conjuring a dangerous Ghostly miasma. Ghosts can even hide in plain sight by masquerading as a Hunter’s doppelgänger!<br/><br/>Ghostly Perks include dramatically increasing your weight, extending your possessing range, the ability to see nearby Hunters through walls, and much more. <br/><br/><strong>ARMED AND READY</strong><br/>Hunters must choose their weapons from a full range of hi-tech gadgets designed to cast out Ghosts from our plane of existence. Detect ghostly presences with the Spectrophone, Radar and Pathfinder, capture them with a Trap, and suck up their spectral remains with the Vacuum – or just blast them to smithereens with the Spectral Cannon, sledgehammers, harpoons, salt-spewing shotguns, and more.<br/><br/>Hunters can also select Perks to give them a special boost. Choose from an extra burst of speed, health-replenishing capabilities and a host of other powers to get ahead of the game.<br/><br/><strong>A BEVY OF BLOOD-CURDLING MAPS </strong><br/>Explore ten unsettling locations, including an abandoned theatre, eerie mansion and cursed carnival. Each map brings with it different tactical considerations and items to throw about… as well as plenty of opportunities to play tricks on the enemy.<br/><br/><strong>FRIGHTENING NEW FEATURES</strong> <br/>As it crept through Steam Early Access, Midnight Ghost Hunt picked up a gaggle of game-changing features, built on the feedback of its community of Ghosts and Hunters.<br/><br/>Dedicated servers and host migration support make setting up matches a breeze, while the Progression Tier and Challenge systems bring added competition to the hunt. Looking for less of the silly and more of the scary? The Experimental Darkness game mode lends a chill to the chaos. Not to mention crossplay, full controller support, and even the GhostMaster minigame to pass the time during the van ride to your next match!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711032993"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1711356992"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1711356992"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1711356992"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw Metal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2279600/Raw_Metal/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2279600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Raw Metal is a sci-fi stealth-action dungeon crawler with a focus on smooth, stylish gameplay.<br/><br/>You are a lone scavenger on the distant, barren exoplanet Charybdis. In search of gear and supplies, you infiltrate the depths of Katabase 6, a massive mining facility run by a corrupt megacorporation known as Orpheus Tech. Sneak through the mines undetected, cleverly utilizing various gadgets and equipment to your advantage, but beware; if you're caught, you'll need to rely on your combat skills for a fighting chance to escape.<h2 class="bb_tag">High-Stakes Stealth</h2><br/>Use taser darts, noisemakers, improvised concussion grenades, and more to slip past and isolate guards. The shadows are your domain; manipulate your environment and your enemies well enough and they'll never see you coming.<h2 class="bb_tag">Breakneck Combat</h2><br/>Combat in Raw Metal is fast and punishing. The guards stationed at Katabase 6 are stronger and more heavily armored than you, so fighting them head on will take skill, cunning, and a great degree of risk. However, mastering combos and using your environment will allow you to come out on top, and yield far greater rewards. Depending on whether it is initiated through a clever ambush or a stealth slip-up, combat can range from a calculated risk to a desperate fight for survival.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Blend of top-down stealth and third-person beat 'em up combat<br/></li><li>Freeform combo system that rewards aggression, improvisation, and precise timing and positioning<br/></li><li>50+ unique gear pieces to find and upgrade<br/></li><li>Distinct visuals for each gear piece to customize the look of your character<br/></li><li>Risk vs. reward extraction system that grants you the choice of cashing out your loot, or pushing deeper into the facility<br/></li><li>3 memorable and challenging boss fights, each with their own fighting styles, twists, and story development<br/></li><li>9 hand-crafted levels to infiltrate, with a few variants each to mix up your approach each time<br/></li><li>Environmental hazards and enemy variants to keep you on your toes as the game progresses<br/></li><li>5 deployable gadgets to utilize to your advantage in stealth and combat alike</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479320/Pesticide_Not_Required/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pesticide Not Required combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1710830410"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1710830410"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479320/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1710830410"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Customizable home interior and backyard garden area<br/></li><li>Season-themed map variations with 16 difficulty levels<br/></li><li>20+ unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>100+ achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Compendium with unique fish for each season<br/></li><li>Mouse-only gameplay support<br/></li><li>Gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museum Mystery: Deckbuilding Card Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717450/Museum_Mystery_Deckbuilding_Card_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Museum Mystery</strong> is a fusion between deckbuilding rogulite game and narrative adventure with intriguing secrets waiting for you to uncover.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/extras/MM_steam_battle.gif?t=1710453320"><br/><br/>Your first night as a museum security guard takes a disastrous turn.<br/>Animated exhibits, awakened gods, and total chaos. And it’s your job to restore order until dawn.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Explore Various Eras</strong></h2>Museum halls are portals into history. Literally. Walk through each era, from Ancient Egypt to the 19th century, to find the roots of what’s happening.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/extras/MM_steam_lvl_run.gif?t=1710453320"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Battle With Unique Enemies</strong></h2>Museum exhibits have come to life. And most of them are mad. Try to calm down this amazing pieces of art.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/extras/MM_steam_enemies.gif?t=1710453320"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Master Hundreds of Cards</strong></h2>Find cards of ancient artifacts or practices. Combine them, unlock new mechanics and craft your perfect hand.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717450/extras/MM_steam_cards_eng.gif?t=1710453320"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Adventure Through History and Art</strong></h2>Talk with historical figures, complete side-quests and help legendary characters!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>4 historical eras to explore<br/></li><li>150+ cards to create the best deck possible<br/></li><li>Unique relics that give unprecedented power</li></ul><br/><strong>Can you solve this Mystery?</strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dune: Imperium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1689500/Dune_Imperium/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Header.png?t=1710955211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body0_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Experience the ultimate blend of strategy and intrigue as you navigate the treacherous landscapes of Arrakis in the award-winning board game <i>Dune: Imperium</i>!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Battle online, locally with AI, or against the formidable House Hagal.<br/></li><li>Earn Achievements that showcase your prowess as a leader.<br/></li><li>Embark on more than a dozen Challenges that will test your wit and cunning.<br/></li><li>Compete for badges in the rotating Skirmish Mode where no two games are the same!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body1_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>Arrakis. Dune. Desert Planet. Raise your banner above the vast wasteland before you. As the Great Houses of the Landsraad marshal their forces and their spies, whom will you influence, and whom will you betray? A tyrannical Emperor. The secretive Bene Gesserit. The shrewd Spacing Guild. The ferocious Fremen of the Deep Desert. The power of the Imperium can be yours, but war is not the only way to claim it.<br/><br/><i>Dune: Imperium</i> blends deck-building and worker placement in a deeply thematic new strategy game where the fate of the Empire hangs on your decisions. Will you seek political allies or rely upon military might? Economic strength or subtle intrigues? A council seat… or a sharpened blade? The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Body2_2.png?t=1710955211"><br/>In <i>Dune: Imperium</i>, you'll step into the role of one of the leaders of the Great Houses of the Imperium in a struggle to control the planet Arrakis and the invaluable Spice it provides.<br/><br/>The game plays out in a series of ten rounds, each of which is defined by a new Conflict on the surface of the planet; some award critical resources, and some provide Victory Points that will propel you to dominance. But choose your battles wisely: spread your forces too thin, and you'll find your enemies growing too strong to oppose.<br/><br/>Each round, you'll draw a hand of five cards from your deck, which will get stronger over the course of the game as you acquire new cards. Each card can be played in one of two ways: To send an Agent out into the Imperium to gather resources, or to Reveal at the end of the round to purchase new powerful cards. You must maintain a careful balance to get the most of the resources available to you. How will you find your path?<br/><br/>As your game progresses, you'll vie for Influence with four factions of the Imperium: The Emperor, the economically powerful Spacing Guild, the mysterious Bene Gesserit, and the ferocious Fremen of the deep deserts. Earning Influence among the various groups helps you to earn the Victory Points you need...but will you compete with your rivals for their favor, or abandon alliances to pursue other opportunities?<br/><br/>Many strategies are at your disposal, and many paths to victory. The cards are dealt. The choice is yours. The Imperium awaits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1689500/extras/WORM_Steam_AboutSection_Footer.png?t=1710955211"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rental</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796550/Rental/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/extras/Gif_Final__2___1_.gif?t=1709834139"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Great Deal!</strong></h2><br/><i>Perfect cabin for a family of four. Close to the beach with great vibes!<br/>For more information about this rental, contact the caretaker!</i><br/><br/>For summer vacation, Umi's family rents a cabin near the beach. However, Umi soon realizes that the offer was not as grand as promised...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Explore the summer cabin in this short game reminiscent of classic survival horror games.<br/></li><li> Meet and talk to a quirky cast of characters as you try to piece together the secrets of the cabin. <br/></li><li> Find items that will help you advance and find out what is wrong with this place. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Arrows or WASD to move<br/></li><li> Space to interact</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's Something In The Ice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810580/Theres_Something_In_The_Ice/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><u>There's Something In The Ice</u></strong> is a first-person horror game.<br/><br/><strong>Plot:</strong><br/>In 2015, three scientists at the Antarctic research station Zarya drilled into the ice to a depth of 2 kilometers and took samples to study...<br/>As they were returning to base, a severe snowstorm began.<br/>Arriving at the base, the scientists went down to the old bunker, as the security protocol told them, to wait it out...<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There is not a single note in the game. The plot is presented through dialogues with characters.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Realistic graphics.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Advanced lighting system LUMEN (Unreal Engine 5).</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Atmosphere inspired by the movie "The Thing" and other sci-fi films and games.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LakeSide</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1552220/LakeSide/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1552220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1552220/extras/ls_3.gif?t=1711383079"><br/><br/>LakeSide is a cozy city builder where you can build the perfect calm town by the lake side or a sprawling city state with wonders that the world has never seen.<br/><br/>With 2d side-scrolling pixel vistas, each game run offers a different set of building combinations, unlocking unique buildings or epic world wonders that offer sprawling growth to your city state<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1552220/extras/ls_img_desc_1.png?t=1711383079"><br/><br/>Build your own city with your own custom architectural and cultural changes. <br/>Unlocking more buildings and expanding your palace gives you with powerful rewards to keep growing your city.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1552220/extras/ls_img_desc_2.gif?t=1711383079"><br/><br/>Feature List<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> More than 60 building variations<br/></li><li> 5 different wonders and counting!<br/></li><li> 3 different background scenarios to start from<br/></li><li> Each game run offers a different set of available buildings<br/></li><li> Manage your resources carefully and keep your citizens alive</li></ul><br/>Development is still in alpha so expect new things to come!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bounties of Babylon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2712650/Bounties_of_Babylon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/lineBreak.png?t=1711382489"><br/><br/><i>Conquer Babylon by progressing through rounds with your ships to complete a run.<br/>Not enough victory points or too much damage taken, means your reign as Admiral will come to an end.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/tiles.png?t=1711382489"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/tiles_2.gif?t=1711382489"><br/>The tile stack procedurally pairs rivers with bounties to create a tile. Pick two from a choice of three to place in the level. Decide based on the physical connection for where you want to go, and what bounty type has for bounty harvesting. You can also discard tiles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/travel.png?t=1711382489"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/rollAndMove_2.gif?t=1711382489"><br/>Each turn, roll one die per ship. The result is how many connected tiles the ship can travel.<br/>A six allows for teleportation to a settlement. Consider dividing ship responsibilities between harvesting, attacking, and trading.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/tradeTreasure.png?t=1711382489"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/tradeTreasure_2.gif?t=1711382489"><br/>Settlements house merchants to trade with. They rotate in and out with various trade requirements during play, so don't dawdle! Landing on treasure chests will often reward you with an artifact. These are high-value items that can be traded. Can you discover all of them in the game?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/quests.png?t=1711382489"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/quests_2.gif?t=1711382489"><br/>Every round you are given two quests you can complete for victory points. They vary in their nature bringing a new sense of mission to your rounds. For example, <i>Harvest Season</i> requires the player to have a yield of a certain size, whilst <i>Treasure Hunter</i> wants the player to collect treasures.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/combat.png?t=1711382489"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/combat_2.gif?t=1711382489"><br/>The opponent can block your path, so land on them to take them out. Receive one victory point and a proportion of their bounties for combat. If they attack you, you lose some bounties and a life. Acquire more lives throughout play.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZwxwmvZebs" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/discord.png?t=1711382489"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2712650/extras/lineBreak.png?t=1711382489"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bass Invaders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738680/Bass_Invaders/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/bi_logo_text_horizontal_616x49.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Bass Invaders is a rhythmic fusion of classic shoot 'em up and live audio analysis.<br/><br/>Battle to the other side of the galaxy on a mission to save the Earth in a campaign mode with a genre-spanning soundtrack, or load <i>literally any song</i> and experience your favourite music in a new way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/shoot_hold_rotate_L06.gif?t=1711382140"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/UNLIMITED_MUSIC_LIBRARY.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Play using any song you like, loading from your own files or using online video. Any track, any time. No limits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/BEAT_THE_BEST.png?t=1711382140"><br/>High scores and ranked leaderboards for every song. Fill your ship energy levels to unleash power mode. Nail that perfect run and show your skill.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/FIND_YOUR_FLOW.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Five difficulty levels so you can just enjoy the music or really challenge your skills.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/SAVE_THE_WORLD.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Launch into a galaxy spanning campaign mode as Ace and PZO-116 battle to save the world from alien invaders. Enjoy every level with its own custom song from a genre-spanning soundtrack.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/FUN_WITH_FRIENDS.png?t=1711382140"><br/>Two-player local co-op in every game mode (requires at least one controller). Battle through the campaign with your best friend. Play winner-stays-on with your mates and your favourite music. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/2P_powermode_L06_video.gif?t=1711382140"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738680/extras/ACCESSIBILITY.png?t=1711382140"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Custom colours<br/></li><li>Colourblind modes<br/></li><li>Simplified backgrounds<br/></li><li>Enemy outlines<br/></li><li>Gameplay assists<br/></li><li>Button hints<br/></li><li>Key rebinding</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmer's Father: Save the Innocence</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1905980/Farmers_Father_Save_the_Innocence/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/header_alt_assets_18.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"The first casualty of war is innocence"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/extras/Gif0.gif?t=1711382049"><br/><br/>War breeds heroes you've never heard of. You are the ordinary person holding a huge burden of protecting what's most precious and innocent. Fight with hunger, wounds, cold, disease, and enemy cruelty. Defend your family and survive the war!<br/><br/>Imagine waking up in the middle of the snowy night to the sounds of a falling sky. Explosions, fire, chaos, the frightened whimper of your child. It’s your turn: now or never, slip away from your enemies before it's too late…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/extras/Gif1.gif?t=1711382049"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FEW OF MAIN FEATURES IN THE GAME</strong></h2><br/>🕊️ Building - animal homestead, baby cradle, trough, and more<br/>🕊️ Crafting - create something useful out of junk<br/>🕊️ Cooking - prepare all kinds of food out of what you can find<br/>🕊️ Sneaking - move quietly then you'll survive<br/>🕊️ Hunting - use guns and provide needed food<br/>🕊️ Exploring - strange sounds, enemies, unknown territories<br/>🕊️ Taking care of family - making family safe, fed, and warm<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>PROTECT YOUR FAMILY</strong></h2>As a father, since the first breath of your child, you’ve always known the responsibility relies on your shoulders… but the stakes were never that high. Do what you must to keep your wife and son alive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/extras/Gif2.gif?t=1711382049"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>FARM, HUNT, IMPROVISE</strong></h2>Nothing can be taken for granted now. You will have to earn every meal and bargain for each piece of comfort for you and your family using extreme measures. Hunt for wild animals, make forest recipes, and, as a farmer, use your skills to create a new home during the occupation…<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1905980/extras/Gif3.gif?t=1711382049"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE</strong></h2>Sneak, wait for your moment, and ATTACK! Every. Second. Counts. Your enemies are cunning and trained. Can you handle that while being "just" a farmer? Your everyday abilities may come in handy so don’t underestimate yourself and keep trying!<br/><br/><strong>After all, you’ve got nothing to lose and everything to gain.</strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beach Club Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2335810/Beach_Club_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Beach Club Simulator" is an exciting open-world simulation game where players manage a beach club. In the game, you construct, operate, and develop a beach club located next to a beautiful beach. However, the game is not limited to just the beach club; it also offers the opportunity to explore and complete missions in other areas of the island.<br>
<br>
The game begins with a character named Kevin Mathews coming to Nevermind Island to find a job. Kevin initially settles in a campsite and seeks solutions to meet his basic needs.<br>
<br>
In addition to building your beach club, you can interact with other important buildings on the island. You'll encounter different tasks such as driver training at the driving school and assisting with municipal services at the town hall. There are also a hotel, hospital, and other commercial establishments on the island.<br>
<br>
Completing missions adds richness and diversity to the game. By interacting with people, you can elevate your career, and career points can later be used for improvements. You can also hire staff for your beach club. Efforts are made to meet guests' needs, organize the beach area, and host fun events.<br/>
<br/>
Beach Club is also a life simulation game. Among your goals is to buy better homes and vehicles. If you're not using your old car, you can even rent it as a taxi, and similarly, you can rent out your homes.<br/>
<br/>
One notable detail in Beach Club Simulator is the emotions the game evokes. We worked hard to create a refreshing, relaxing, and enjoyable gaming experience. For example, you'll see people dancing wildly as the sun sets; sometimes, you might forget you're playing a game and just enjoy the atmosphere.<br/>
<br/>
"Toilet Management Simulator" is our previous game, and Beach Club is, in fact, a sequel to it. All the characters you encounter at the camp are reimagined versions of characters who went on vacation at the end of Toilet Management Simulator.<br/>
<br/>
The goal of the game is to expand and improve your beach club, turning it into a profitable business. Beach Club Simulator offers an enjoyable experience with impressive graphics, detailed management options, and a rich game content. Exploring the broader world of the game, including other buildings and missions on the island, allows you to enjoy unforgettable experiences in your adventure with Kevin on the island.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstract Code</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732630/Abstract_Code/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on a unique gaming experience that delves into thought-provoking themes... this SHMUP/Visual Novel hybrid offers a compelling narrative interspersed with addictive arcade gameplay.<br/><br/>Play through the captivating <strong>Story Mode</strong>, immersing yourself in a journey that combines engaging storytelling with arcade excitement. <br/><br/>Alternatively, challenge your skills in the pure <strong>Arcade Mode</strong>, a score attack mode featuring 6 levels of intense action.<br/><br/>Explore CODE KNIGHT's personal space within the game, an<strong> Apartment</strong> where you can enjoy a Juke Box, Gallery, and more additional <strong>FREE CONTENT</strong><br/><br/><br/>In the digital world of Abstract Code, assume the role of CODE KNIGHT and embark on a mission to rectify the errors made by those less accountable than yourself. Engage in thrilling battles against the FINK incursion into humanities' knowledge center, CODENAME D1, and uncover the truth behind the enigmatic character known as Katie.<br/><br/>Please note that the game contains content that may be triggering, as it explores various sensitive topics such as social masking, and transhuman identity.<br/><br/>Stay connected with us on our Insta page @_ruok2000_						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridge Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2879260/Bridge_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2879260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In "Bridge Maker," step into the shoes of an ingenious engineer entrusted with a crucial mission: guiding a car across treacherous chasms. The twist? The car is in constant motion, adding a thrilling element of urgency to your task. Armed with a limited arsenal of materials, your challenge is to construct a sturdy bridge capable of withstanding the vehicle's weight. <br>
<br>
Flex your problem-solving prowess as you strategically arrange bridge components to ensure stability and safety. Each level presents a fresh puzzle, testing your creativity and engineering acumen. Can you craft a bridge robust enough to carry the car to its destination without faltering?<br>
<br>
Key features of "Bridge Maker" include:<br>
<br>
1. **Dynamic Bridge Building**: Exercise your architectural ingenuity by constructing bridges on-the-fly to accommodate a moving car.<br/>
<br/>
2. **Infinite Levels**: Embark on an endless journey of bridge-building challenges, with each level offering a unique configuration to conquer.<br/>
<br/>
3. **Personal Records**: Set your own benchmarks as you strive for perfection, aiming to surpass previous feats and establish new records for bridge strength and efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
Whether you're a seasoned problem-solver or a newcomer to engineering, "Bridge Maker" promises an exhilarating experience that will put your skills to the ultimate test. Can you engineer your way to victory and lead the car safely across every daunting gap?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Kong City Destroyer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2879250/King_Kong_City_Destroyer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2879250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the thrilling world of King Kong City Destroyer, players are thrust into a heart-pounding simulator where the forces of nature clash with humanity's hubris. Take on the role of an enormous and enraged primate, King Kong himself, as you embark on a rampage of destruction through urban landscapes. <br>
<br>
Your mission is clear: fulfill King Kong's relentless desires as he wreaks havoc upon everything in his path. With no one able to stand against his might, it's up to you to carry out his will. But amidst the chaos, a question lingers: will nature ultimately reclaim its dominion over the concrete jungle, or is King Kong's reign merely a fleeting whim?<br>
<br>
Featuring 10 adrenaline-fueled levels, players will experience the visceral thrill of demolishing buildings, crushing cars, and even confronting civilians in their quest for dominance. With each mission lasting a tense 3 minutes, every second counts as you unleash destruction upon the cityscape.<br>
<br>
King Kong City Destroyer isn't just a game—it's an electrifying journey into the primal power of nature unleashed. Are you ready to answer the call of the wild and leave a trail of destruction in your wake?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Golf</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2872150/Only_Golf/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2872150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Only Golf is a challenging golf game that puts players' skills to the test. <br>
<br>
The game features a series of increasingly difficult levels, each with its own unique set of challenges and obstacles. In Only Golf, the objective is simple: hit the ball into the hole. However, the game is not that simple, as player must take into account the direction of the wind and adjust their shot accordingly. If the wind is blowing in the wrong direction, the ball may go too far or too slowly, making it difficult to hit the hole. <br>
<br>
Only Golf is the perfect game for anyone who loves golf or enjoys a good challenge. With its intuitive gameplay, challenging levels, and stunning visuals, this game is sure to provide hours of entertainment for players of all ages. So, grab your clubs, adjust for the wind, and get ready to become a golfing master in Only Golf!<br>
<br>
Game Features :<br/>
- Golf rules<br/>
- Showed wind direction<br/>
- 5 strokes per attempt<br/>
- Multiple levels						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets Killer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2879240/Jets_Killer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2879240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Jets Killer is an action-packed game where you are in charge of defending your military base from enemy helicopters that are attacking. <br>
<br>
You will have to choose one of the three powerful bazookas available and use it to the fullest to eliminate the threat. With realistic sound effects and animations, you will feel like you are in the heat of the battle. <br>
<br>
The gameplay is simple, yet challenging. You will have to aim carefully and calculate the trajectory of the missile to hit the moving targets. As you progress through the game, the difficulty level increases, and you will have to be quick on your feet to dodge enemy fire while taking down their helicopters.<br>
With its engaging gameplay and exciting action, Jets Killer is a game that will keep you on the edge of your seat. <br>
<br/>
Whether you are a casual gamer or a hardcore fan of action games, this one is sure to keep you entertained for hours on end.<br/>
<br/>
Game features :<br/>
- 3 types of bazookas<br/>
- Battle against waves of enemy jets<br/>
- Military camp attacked<br/>
- Limited time						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Hunt</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2451010/Project_Hunt/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This semi-realistic hunting experience lets you explore and hunt in large-world environments. Discover true-to-life animals in beautiful natural habitats and handle various detailed and realistic weapons.<br/><br/>Create your own Hunting experience. With a wide range of options, stretching from rifles to handguns, each with different types of ammunition and suited for different-sized animals, it's up to you to find your favorites and regularly practice your aim as you account for wind and bullet drop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451010/extras/3.png?t=1711379101"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451010/extras/6.png?t=1711379101"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451010/extras/4.png?t=1711379101"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451010/extras/2.png?t=1711379101"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451010/extras/1.png?t=1711379101"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451010/extras/5.png?t=1711379101"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FURRY BACKROOMS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2689230/FURRY_BACKROOMS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689230/extras/600xdance.gif?t=1711378418"><br/><br/><strong>FURRY BACKROOMS is a cooperative horror game for 1-8 players, as well as a single-player mode.<br/><br/>The PLAYER попадает into an unknown anomaly and is transferred to creepy and atmospheric rooms - the BACKROOMS. Here you will be met by a terrible and dangerous FURRY who can do something bad to you! I do not recommend meeting him... Or do I?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689230/extras/600x.gif?t=1711378418"><br/><br/>Gather your friends to go through these terribly tense rooms together and meet the FURRY!</img></strong><h2 class="bb_tag">What to expect from the game?</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Minimalistic interface, realistic graphics and oppressive atmosphere will provide a complete immersion in the world of FURRY BACKROOMS.<br/></li><li>Cooperative mode will allow you and your friends to fully experience the atmosphere. Try to escape from the FURRY!<br/></li><li>BACKROOMS are fraught with danger. Various liminal spaces will break your brain.<br/></li><li>Regular updates - adding new locations and mechanics.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic of Brave</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692750/Epic_of_Brave/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692750/extras/5_description.png?t=1711377636"><br/><br/><strong>Epic of Brave</strong> is a <strong>multiplayer online battle arena (MOBA)</strong> adventure where the players can create strategical tactics, craft exceptional weapons, combine powerful spells and experience ultimate battles.<br/><br/>Enhanced with real-time multiplayer experience, flawless controls and beautiful graphics the players can join different matches, collect rare and exceptional materials, customise their heroes and team up against powerful enemies.<br/><br/><strong>Join the battle between Sentinels and Resistance!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692750/extras/3_description.png?t=1711377636"><h2 class="bb_tag">Battle or Campaign</h2><strong>Matches</strong> are intense, quick-fire engagements where you face off against other players or AI-controlled opponents. Victories in Matches earn you a variety of Resources such as currency, experience points, and specific match-related loot. The more challenging the Match, the greater the rewards. Additionally, exceptional performances may grant bonus Resources, encouraging players to push their limits and strive for excellence in every engagement.<br/><br/><strong>Campaigns</strong>, on the other hand, are more extended, story-driven missions that are solo endeavors. These offer a different set of challenges and opportunities. Successful completion of Campaign objectives yields not only substantial Resources but also rare and unique Materials that are crucial for crafting advanced weaponry and armor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Meet the Metropolis of Champions</h2>Choose any of the four Champions - <strong>the Paladin Tyriel</strong>, <strong>the Warrior Barath'Dur</strong>, <strong>the Archer Alessia</strong> or <strong>the Mage Rachel</strong>. Every one of them is gifted with different set of skills and expertise, making them unique and invaluable allies in the face of any challenge. Each champion possesses unique strengths and abilities that can be utilized to strategically overcome any obstacle.<h2 class="bb_tag">Climb the Ranking</h2>Every <strong>Match</strong> and <strong>Campaign</strong> gives you the chance to prove your battle expertise and brings you closer to one of the five exceptional <strong>Ranks</strong>:<br/>- <strong>Apprentice</strong> 1-6 Level<br/>- <strong>Champion</strong> 6-12 Level<br/>- <strong>High Lord</strong> 12-18 Level<br/>- <strong>Manipulator</strong> 18-24 Level<br/>- <strong>Illuminati</strong> 25 Level<h2 class="bb_tag">Craft Epic Weapons and Armors</h2>The participation in <strong>Matches</strong> and <strong>Campaigns</strong> grants you <strong>Resources</strong> and <strong>Materials</strong>, which you can exchange or use to build unmatched Weapons and Armors. As you engage in the thrilling <strong>Matches</strong> and challenging <strong>Campaigns</strong> that await you, you will amass an abundance of Resources and Materials. These valuable resources are the key to crafting the ultimate weapons and armor, empowering the Look of your Champions.<h2 class="bb_tag">Accomplish Quests and Achievements</h2>The Excellence in Battle is recognised and collected in the form of <strong>Achievements</strong>. They enhance your <strong>Visual Representation</strong> and serve as a testament to your prowess on the battlefield. <strong>Achievements</strong> are badges of honor, earned through skill, strategy, and valor. As you accumulate these accolades, your <strong>Visual Representation</strong> undergoes a transformation, reflecting the milestones you've achieved in your journey.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timing Blocks</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2864320/Timing_Blocks/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2864320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Timing Blocks is a logic puzzle game suitable for PC, with simple operation and relaxed atmosphere. You can freely match your choices and control small block to reach the finish line.<br/>2D graphics, logical reasoning, highly challenging puzzles, enjoy the process of solving problems<h2 class="bb_tag"> Gameplay Introduction </h2>By controlling the up, down, left, right arrows or WSAD keys to control your block, the block will automatically choose the planned route to move and avoid obstacles, in order to ultimately reach the finish line and achieve ultimate victory						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Runners</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2573230/Suicide_Runners/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2573230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Classic 2D shoot em up with updated graphics. Dodge a storm of bullets as you blast through space shooting hordes of enemies. Collect powerups to survive against fearsome bosses.  Pilot a suicide runner as you fight to unravel the mystery of what is destroying the universe.<br/><br/>Collect Powerups To Even The Odds<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2573230/extras/PowerupGif.gif?t=1711375569"><br/><br/>Fight Enemies of all Sizes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2573230/extras/NewSateliteGif.gif?t=1711375569"><br/><br/>Dodge Bullets To Survive<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2573230/extras/TurretShotDodge.gif?t=1711375569"><br/><br/>Bosses<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2573230/extras/NewSawBossGif.gif?t=1711375569"><br/><br/>Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul> Choose your own difficulty from 3 lives to 99 lives<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul>8 Handcrafted levels to master<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul>Multiple bosses to overcome and destroy<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li></li></ul>All sorts of powerups to collect from cannons to rockets						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between Horizons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1921980/Between_Horizons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fassemble-entertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/SteamPageLink_Discord.png?t=1711378795"/></a><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmailchi.mp%2Fassembleteam%2Fassemble-newsletter" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/SteamPageLink_Newsletter.png?t=1711378795"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/AssembleEntertainment" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/SteamPageLink_Steam.png?t=1711378795"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/between-horizons-gif-investigate-new.gif?t=1711378795"><h2 class="bb_tag">ABOUT THE GAME</h2><br/>Between Horizons is set aboard the Zephyr, humanity's first generation ship en route to another star. You assume the role of Stella, who was born on the ship 24 years ago and recently inherited her father's post as Chief of Security. Dive into the conspiracy behind the incident that threatens to disrupt the Zephyr's social order and foil its mission.<br/><br/>Between Horizons is a modern 2.5D pixel art adventure that brings a branching narrative into a semi-open world. The team at DigiTales has applied numerous lessons from their first game Lacuna and proven solutions to detective game design problems to maximize player agency in the investigation process – all the while maintaining the tight pacing of a meaningful story that will ask you to reevaluate your moral compass and make increasingly tough decisions as the situation aboard the ship spirals out of control.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/between-horizons-gif-show-evidence-new.gif?t=1711378795"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>A New Kind of Experience:</strong> Between Horizons merges investigative-style gameplay with a branching sci-fi story in an ever-expanding Metroidvania-style environment.<br/></li><li><strong>Solving Cases for Yourself:</strong> The flexible evidence system lets players assign clues to cases, confront ship denizens about them, and submit any case with evidence players have connected to it. Everything found on the ship is connected, but figuring out how — that’s the challenge.<br/></li><li><strong>At What Cost?:</strong> Underneath the game's exciting and plausible sci-fi plot lies a number of thought-provoking problems inviting players to weigh intergenerational responsibility against personal freedom.<br/></li><li><strong>Getting New Perspective:</strong> Timeless pixel art mixed with 3D environments and compelling visual effects come together in Between Horizons, creating a unique, beautiful art style.<br/></li><li><strong>Failure is Very Much an Option:</strong> There are no second chances — submitting wrong solutions means the story will go on and players live with the consequences. A new and improved auto-save system will make sure there is no going back, as the story branches and endings are based on player decisions, none of which can be taken back.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1921980/extras/between-horizons-gif-walk.gif?t=1711378795"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1921980/Between_Horizons/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1921980/Between_Horizons/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUCK's most terrible day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1980700/DUCKs_most_terrible_day/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1980700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Follow the story of DUCK, a feathered protagonist whose serene pond life is jolted into disarray when a group of misfits abduct her friends and left her without the ability to fly. She does have the unique ability to decelerate time momentarily, allowing for precise jumps, dodges, and attacks, turning imminent failures into triumphant successes.<br/><br/>The story, told in 5 colors and <i>well over</i> <strong>100 pixels</strong> per scanline, guides the player through 3 worlds and 20+ levels. Join DUCK in an adventure where every pixel counts!<h2 class="bb_tag">Rescue your friends!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1980700/extras/rescue-friends-scaled.gif?t=1711372027"><br/>Your friends have been captured and are imprisoned within cages scattered throughout the game. Leap on top the cages to destroy them and set your friends free!<h2 class="bb_tag">Timewarp</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1980700/extras/timewarp-tutorial-scaled.gif?t=1711372027"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1980700/extras/timewarp-ingame-scaled.gif?t=1711372027"><br/>Save-up warp pellets and enable timewarp to dodge enemy attacks or surprise your enemies with a burst of rapid-fire bullets. You can find these pellets throughout the levels and enemies will usually drop some when they're destroyed.<h2 class="bb_tag">Enemies</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1980700/extras/enemies.gif?t=1711372027"><br/>You'll encounter a diverse array of adversaries, each presenting unique challenges. There are some that soar through the skies, others that slither close to the ground and attack at a moments notice. And some simply.. walk.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOVE girls</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2440400/LOVE_girls/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2440400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							LOVE GRILS is a relaxing puzzle game. <br>
Features:<br>
♥ Beautiful 25 artworks<br>
♥ "Space" key to quickly complete the current level<br>
♥ Nice music						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters of Mican</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745660/Monsters_of_Mican/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Mican! Explore hand crafted dungeons, fight or befriend tons of zany monsters, and discover the ancient truth behind the origin of monsters!<br/><br/>Monsters of Mican is a first person, party based dungeon crawler RPG, often known as a Blobber. The game was heavily inspired by classic PC RPGs such as Might and Magic and Wizardry, with plenty of modern flair and heaps of QOL features.<br/><br/>Features include:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hundreds of unique, whimsical, and sometimes terrifying monsters<br/></li><li>Dozens of unique monster traits that drastically change what monsters are capable of in battle<br/></li><li>A highly robust character creator with 14 character classes to choose from<br/></li><li>Hundreds of abilities/spells, including one unique ability exclusive to each class<br/></li><li>Dozens of passive skills, each with 5 possible rank upgrades<br/></li><li>Over 10 large, hand-crafted dungeons<br/></li><li>Hand crafted NPCs with unique personalities and stories<br/></li><li>Boss fights with wildly different mechanics<br/></li><li>Randomly generated loot (and unique named artifacts) with tons of different enchantments and abilities<br/></li><li>Monster Buddies, a system that allows you to befriend monsters and then visit or summon them to fight for you<br/></li><li>6 post-game challenge dungeons with specific themed rules and conditions<br/></li><li>Monster Rush Challenge: fight every monster in the game, sequentially.<br/></li><li>Boss Rush Challenge: fight every boss in the game... ALL AT ONCE!<br/></li><li>An original soundtrack featuring over 20 unique compositions made in the style of classic 90s CRPGs<br/></li><li>A robust list of difficulty options and video settings<br/></li><li>An in-game cheat vendor that will trade you powerful wands for various cheat codes<br/></li><li>Full gamepad controls </li></ul><br/>The game takes place on Mican, a world turned upside down long ago by an event called "The Amalgam Anomaly" which birthed hundreds if not thousands of different types of monsters, creatures, half-breed amalgams and other nightmares into the world. The game has you venturing into a mountain at the heart of Spiny Island to discover what the monsters in the caves are up to... and discovering other mysterious secrets about the world in the process.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mines and Magic</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/884640/Mines_and_Magic/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/884640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Multiplayer tower defense auto battler with a strategic economics component.<br>
<br>
Units have various magical abilities. Combine units' complementary strengths.<br>
<br>
There are more than 150 different units currently in the game, every one of which has a unique ability and fights differently.<br>
<br>
Also you can cast spells to help your army.<br>
<br/>
Expand your territory and build mines and farms to gather different resources randomly scattered around the map.<br/>
<br/>
Resource management, strategic thinking and planning ahead would help to win.<br/>
<br/>
Defending the castle is still the main priority. In case of a defense breach, you can upgrade your castle.<br/>
<br/>
Singleplayer campaign has 20 levels. Each has about 25-35 waves of enemies.<br/>
<br/>
1v1 pvp mode is currently available. 2v2 and 4v4 are being developed.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYZD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2857900/NYZD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2857900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							NYZD is a Third person zombie shooter featuring up to 4 players local and online co-op.  <br>
You have to battle swarms of mutants in order to survive. You can choose 4 different characters and buy new weapons from the trader buy earning money killing zombies or collecting the gold bars scattered around the maps. There are 8 different maps for you to choose and play with your friends by LAN. <br>
<br>
<br>
Everything started after meteorite hit New York and scientists found a living virus after examining the meteorite. Government tried to turn this virus into a bioweapon by infecting worms with the virus and genetically altering them but it ended up with a catastrophe soon the whole world was devastated. Only couple cities were left those who survived walled off their cities in order to protect themselves from hoards of mutants. You are one of the few NYZD infection control units  who somehow managed to survive the hordes of mutants. Your duty is to clean up the designated areas near New York City to help expand the city.<br>
<br>
<br/>
And before you say bro it's just another zombie shooter game.<br/>
 Well..... you may be right lol but give it a try this time there's more explosions and cool maps to consooom. <br/>
<br/>
And one more thing if you end up stuck in backrooms Developer does NOT take any responsibilities whatsoever you gotta noclip yourself back to reality <br/>
(alt f4 might help)						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEARTS OF COLD - REDEMPTION</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2592320/HEARTS_OF_COLD__REDEMPTION/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2592320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>STORY</strong><br/>The year is 2070. The Earth has become unstable and can no longer provide for all our needs. Twenty years ago the World Council ordered that another planet be found that could sustain our population. Father had been assigned as Commander of the survey mission which would take him away for a very long time. I was six years old. I remember waving goodbye the day he left. I never saw him again. So it was that Homo2 was discovered<br/><br/>Things have changed a lot since then and so have I. Homo2 has been made ready to receive our people and I was appointed Commander of a ship in the Orion Fleet which was to be the first making the journey. The Controllers have taken over on Homo2. They would have the planet for themselves and have ordered that further incoming traffic from Earth be intercepted and destroyed. <br/><br/><strong>MISSION</strong><br/>Go immediately to the nearest military Battle Port and board the first available ship leaving for Homo2. Your mission is clear - you must take back Homo2 from the Controllers and allow the colonization to proceed. <strong>You will not be allowed to fail</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>LEVELS</strong><br/>27 Game Levels<br/><br/><strong>PLAYER</strong><br/>First and Third Person. Walk, Run, Crouch, Jump, Prone, Strafe, Peek, Swim, Climb Ladder. Drive Terrestrial Vehicles, Pilot Airborne Vehicles.<br/><br/><strong>CHARACTERS</strong><br/>Large number of Characters<br/><strong>FRIENDS</strong><br/>Allies, Friendly Helpers, Passive Civilians<br/><strong>ENEMIES</strong><br/>Military, Civilian, Zombies, Vehicles, Animals<br/><br/><strong>WEAPONS</strong><br/>Knife, Pistol, Shotgun, SMG, Auto Rifle, Sniper Rifle, Dual Pistols, Rocket Launcher, Rail Gun, Quasar, Sentry Gun, Grenade, Placeable Mine<br/><br/><strong>COLLECTABLES</strong><br/>Weapons, Ammo, Health<br/><br/><strong>VEHICLES</strong><br/>Truck, Car, Helicopter, Train, Boat, Spacecraft, Moon Buggy<br/><br/><strong>OTHER</strong><br/>Explosive Objects						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path to Nothing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2861570/Path_to_Nothing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2861570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Path of nothing is a quick game made in spare time with pixel game maker mv, <br>
Defeat enemies that wil stand in your way, fight and find your way trough the path to nothing <br>
and try to get as many coins to recieve upgrades for your character.<br>
<br>
There wil be obstacles, puzzles and bosses on your way trough, some of them have weak spots you'll have to figure out.<br>
<br>
Can you become strong enough to make it trough?						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draw Physics Line</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2101740/Draw_Physics_Line/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2101740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Its a physics puzzle game.You can draw any shape you want and they are all followed by physics rules when you draw your first line or polygon.<br>
Your goal is to use this physics line or polygon to push the ball to the same color cup.<br>
When the physics ball drop into the correct color cup,the level is finished!<br>
Its a nice brain-training game.Hope you can learn physics from the game.<br>
Have fun.More levels is coming!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WizUp!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2864500/WizUp/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2864500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							WizUp! is a wizard idle / incremental / resource management game: kill enemies, collect resources, purchase upgrades, prestige, and repeat!<br>
<br>
Start slow and grow stronger, and play at your own pace!  Discover over 45 different resources, upgrades, and items with unique mechanics.  Here are some of the mechanics you will discover along the way:<br>
<br>
-Awaken to earn Paradox Anchors, which can be shattered to obtain Mirrors of Sight, which can be shattered to obtain Mirrors of Remembrance to boost your Global Storage!<br>
<br>
-Balance the allocation of your Orbs of Power in order to increase your Rune Drop Chance, your Damage, your XP Gain, and your Chaotic Essence Production!<br>
<br/>
-Upgrade over 10 unique Rings, such as the Ring of Stars ("The Stars send you aid"), which gives you 1 Star Seed every time your Wizard dies!<br/>
<br/>
Plus much more!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH ALL - BALLS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2880070/SEARCH_ALL__BALLS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2880070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SEARCH ALL - BALLS</h2> is a hidden object game in which you need to find all the balls in a large location. Balls will be located in a variety of places, from the most prominent to barely noticeable places. The entire game location looks lively because of the animation elements. Find all the balls! Don't let them go unnoticed :)<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/>- Animation elements on location;<br/>- 100 balls to find;<br/>- Pleasant soundtrack;<br/>- The gameplay can be interrupted at any time, and the game will automatically save the result;<br/>- Implemented hints! If you find it difficult to find an item, use the hint!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Time Attack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684100/Real_Time_Attack/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Race to victory in this speedrunning extravaganza! Control the lovable Rucky Anguish as he tries to defeat Do Good Natas and avenge his rat dad. With 16 levels of insane platforming action and built-in timer function, this is one real time adventure you'll LOVE attacking continuously! With full controller support, achievements, and most importantly <strong>SPEEDRUNNING LEADERBOARDS</strong>, you'll be fluttering with Rucky 24/7/365!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forbidden Art</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1166140/Forbidden_Art/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1166140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Forbidden Art is a VR escape room puzzle game where you escape from a killer's secret lair.<br/>Start in the dungeon and work your way through secret passages, studies, morgues, vents, chapel, and more to escape without being seen by the killer.<br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>::MAIN FEATURES::</strong><br/><br/>🔹 <strong>REALISTIC GRAPHICS</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1166140/extras/Main1.gif?t=1711354696"><br/>The beauty of VR is that it allows players to be fully immersed in the environment. We created the backgrounds with a focus on reality to give players the ultimate immersion experience. Feel the killer's lair in VR, a converted abandoned chapel in a remote village in South Korea.<br/><br/><br/>🔹 <strong>ROTATION &amp; HEIGHT ADJUSTMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1166140/extras/rotation_optimized.gif?t=1711354696"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1166140/extras/height_optimized.gif?t=1711354696"><br/><br/>This feature was added for players who play seated or are unable to stand for long periods of time due to health reasons.<br/>The rotation function provides instant and smooth rotation and allows players to choose the way they want to play.<br/>Height adjustment offers crouching, standing, and a hybrid mode that allows players to operate both modes with a single button.<br/>Sit back, relax, and enjoy Forbidden Art!<br/><br/><br/>🔹 <strong>LIGHT SOURCE</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1166140/extras/light_source_final.gif?t=1711354696"><br/>Some areas in the game are very dark, to the point where you can't proceed without a light source. You can use a lighter or flashlight to help you see better in these areas. <br/><br/><br/>🔹 <strong>WRITABLE DIARY</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1166140/extras/note_Final.gif?t=1711354696"><br/>While it is possible to solve all puzzles without taking notes, we have added note-taking to speed up some sections and for overall player enjoyment and convenience.<br/><br/><br/>🔹 <strong>6m X 6m ROOMSCALE MODE</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1166140/extras/6X6.gif?t=1711354696"><br/>"Forbidden Art" is a VR game that supports "6m X 6m Roomscale Mode".<br/>The entire map of the game is built to fit a 6m X 6m real-world space, and players can actually walk around and play in all the spaces in the game instead of just pressing buttons on the controller.<br/>If players have access to a 6m X 6m play area, we highly recommend playing in the "6m X 6m Roomscale Mode". <br/><br/>Of course, we realize that not all players have access to a 6m by 6m space. <br/>Therefore, we also offer the "Controller Movement Mode", which allows players who do not have the space to enjoy "Forbidden Art" in VR without any restrictions.<br/><br/><br/>🔹 <strong>HUNDREDS OF OBJECTS TO INTERACT WITH</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1166140/extras/Object.gif?t=1711354696"><br/>You can grap and interact almost every object in the game, and some of them have special interactions.<br/><br/><br/><br/>🔸 There are no in-game hints to help you escape.<br/>Some of the puzzles can be quite challenging. However, all the clues are in the space you're trapped in. Use the items you have in your inventory, observe the space carefully, and look for ways to escape.<br/>Use all your abilities to escape the dangerous and terrifying hideout created by a psychopathic killer!<br/><br/><br/><br/>::C A U T I O N::<br/>Before first starting the game, make sure there is enough cleared space surrounding you,<br/>with no furniture or any other items around, which may cause injury whilst wearing the headset.<br/>Ensure all motion controllers are fully charged.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSEI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2482150/TENSEI/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2482150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Tensei" is an ultra-casual endless action game.<br/><br/>Leap and fall over and over in the style of a brush flowing across paper,<br/>and go on a relaxed journey into the sky. Leave the hectic routine of life behind<br/>for a chance to enjoy this deeply immersive experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">Playstyle</h2><strong>[Unique Low-Gravity Floating]</strong><br/>Project yourself into the game, relax, and let yourself become immersed in gameplay.<br/><br/><strong>[Purifying Worldly Desires]</strong><br/>You can purify damage zones by dropping (rapidly falling) onto them.<br/>Focus and master the tricks of aiming as you make your way into the skies, avoiding damage as you go.<br/><br/><strong>[Become a Majestic Dragon]</strong><br/>Use triple jumps to navigate from platform to platform while collecting Orbs (ink droplets). Orbs can grant you Boost Mode, letting you turn into a dragon and giving you dynamic flight abilities to navigate new areas.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2482150/extras/web_image01.png?t=1711358985"><br/>Game livestreams and videos may be distributed freely<br/>for this title subject to confirmation of and compliance<br/>with the following guidelines.<br/><br/>We do not issue separate software licenses. Your understanding is appreciated.<br/><br/><strong>・Please display the following copyright notice.</strong><br/>　©2023 NEURON･AGE Co., Ltd.<br/><br/><strong>・Creation of content including the following is not permitted.</strong><br/>　　- Content encouraging discrimination based on race, sex, etc.<br/>　　- Sexually abusive or explicit content<br/>　　- Content encouraging injurious, anti-social, illegal, or criminal actions<br/>　　- Content that contravenes social morality or other offensive videos<br/><br/>　We may delete or request deletion of any content that we find<br/>　to be inappropriate or undesirable, at our own discretion.<br/><br/><strong>・Extraction of individual images, music, soundtrack and other<br/>　elements of the game for posting or distribution is not permitted.<br/>　(Such as extracting only the soundtrack for a stream, etc.)</strong><br/><br/><strong>・We are not liable for any issues experienced by streamers or<br/>　audience members arising from streaming or posting of videos.</strong> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid Entry</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2770300/Liquid_Entry/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2770300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>liquid entry </strong><br/><i>Let's transform into slime, collect clean droplets and purify the polluted world </i><br/><br/>#2.5D #Adventure #Side-scrolling game_Platform #Story_Puzzle<br/>Exploring through puzzles, the number of water droplets collected and users actions taken determine the endings.<br/>Let's gather water droplets using the ability to transform into liquid.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2770300/extras/screen_english_0000_screen0.jpg?t=1711350251"><br/><br/>A future where the world's water is polluted and almost no life can live...<br/>An experimental body was created to solve this situation...<br/><br/><i>But he runs away...! </i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2770300/extras/screen_english_0002_screen2.jpg?t=1711350251"><br/><br/>A boy who turns into slime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2770300/extras/screen_english_0001_screen1.jpg?t=1711350251"><br/><br/>Where will he end up heading?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2770300/extras/screen_english_0007_screen7.jpg?t=1711350251"><br/><br/>People everywhere......what are they?<br/><br/><strong>The ending changes only through your choice...! </strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Hat</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2805210/Space_Hat/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2805210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Space Hat is a Fast FPS Platformer, set in a futuristic Sci-Fi world where you play as Vega, a space bounty hunter hired by an organization to execute a contract.<br/>She's one of the most experienced and deadliest mercenary in the galaxy. Better known by the name ''Space Hat'', her mission is to dismantle a space cartel that has become too powerful.<br/><br/>Vega has a range of different moves and attacks including jumps, dash, slides, two fire modes and a powerful punch. The core of the game is about mixing differents combat or parkour moves with her teleporting Hat. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2805210/extras/0306-ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter.gif?t=1711350179"><br/><br/>The game has parkour phases, asking for dexterity and combat arena phases in which the player have to eliminate all the enemies. The player's goal is to master the various mechanics to finish the levels as quickly as possible. <br/><br/>Embark on 2 adrenaline-packed levels that offer a unique solo experience : Fast and bloody combats and precise platform phases.  <br/>Execute the target and remember the clock is ticking.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2805210/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter.gif?t=1711350179"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Kill ennemies with style</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Teleport everywhere</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Move at lightspeed</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Set the best time</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street Cleaner Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2856100/Street_Cleaner_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2856100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Every morning he gets into his car and goes out to restore order on the streets of his hometown. He has several rules and one of them is that he will never leave leaving the territory dirty. Whether it’s a bottle left behind after drinking or someone’s forgotten refrigerator, the street cleaner will get rid of everything.<br>
Have you ever dreamed of cleaning the streets? This game is for you<br>
Features:<br>
-Various locations for cleaning<br>
-Atmospheric<br>
-A puzzle game where at each level you will find 7 hidden objects that need to be removed (taken to the car). Items can be either just bottles or refrigerators.<br>
-Achievements						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jump Malcolm Jump</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2461570/Jump_Malcolm_Jump/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2461570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Leap into Action in the World of Jump Malcolm Jump<br>
<br>
Embark on a jump-filled odyssey in this captivating 3D platformer that seamlessly blends arcade excitement with daring dashes. As Malcolm, your charismatic hero, you’ll soar through imaginative low poly environments, mastering the art of jumping and dashing to collect precious Energy Orbs scattered across diverse realms. Here’s what makes this game an exhilarating adventure:<br>
<br>
* Diverse Realms: Explore a variety of landscapes, each with its own unique challenges. From the fiery depths of the Volcanic World to the bustling urban sprawl of City Scape, every world presents a fresh adventure waiting to be conquered.<br>
<br>
* Dash to Victory: It’s not just about jumping; harness the power of the dash to blaze through obstacles and navigate treacherous terrain. Strategize your moves and execute flawless combinations to maximize your progress.<br>
<br/>
* Arcade Thrills: Capture the essence of classic arcade games as you dodge hazards and race against the clock. Feel the adrenaline rush as you leap and dash your way to victory.<br/>
<br/>
* Global Leaderboards: Compete against players worldwide! Climb the ranks and prove your jumping prowess by earning a spot on the global leaderboards. Can you reach the top?<br/>
<br/>
* Casual Adventure: Whether you’re a seasoned gamer or just looking for a quick gaming fix, this game offers excitement that suits every player. Dive into this captivating 3D platformer and experience the perfect blend of fast-paced action, precise jumping, and cunning strategy.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightist</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2817020/Lightist/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is an interesting physics puzzle game.<br/>You need to draw creative shapes to linkage with light.<br/>The floowing are the main features of this game:<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817020/extras/SubDescription_physics_english.png?t=1711344553"><br/>Everyting you draw will turn into physical entity(objects).<br/>These objects will follow physical laws like gravity, friction, leverage, conservation of momentum…<br/>Don't worry if you're not good at physics. Using your common sense will be enough.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817020/extras/SubDescription_mathematics_english.png?t=1711344553"><br/>To make the objects you create meet expectation, drawing process needs to be precise.<br/>Perhaps you cannot draw that accurately right away, but you have countless opportunities to try, and trying is the charm of mathematics.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817020/extras/SubDescription_imagination_english.png?t=1711344553"><br/>Sometimes you may at a loss of what to do next. <br/>Well, just jump out of the box. Things look impossible or ridiculous may turn out to be the right answer finally.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817020/extras/SubDescription_logic_english.png?t=1711344553"><br/>Through logical reasoning, you can predict what will happen after you create one object.<br/>As the game progresses, you will encounter more complex scenes, but on the other hand, unlock more features.<br/>Enjoy the process of thinking and you will gain a lot.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do A Barrel Roll??</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2766620/Do_A_Barrel_Roll/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Do A Barrel Roll??</strong> provides a challenging and punishing platforming experience. Despite the punishing level design that may undo a lot of progress with a mistake. There is no time for being sad because the hesitation will only increase the damage. With a combination of skill and level knowledge. Taking appropriate action in the right time can minimize the damage. Providing a punishing yet fair gameplay experience. Exploring more potential save or route when progressing through the level. Providing a unique and satisfying experience. Climb the mountain or not, it's up to you. This is a journey only belongs to you. So may it be meaningful.<br/><br/>Each area presents different themes and Characters. Apart from the first area, each later area will also introduce a new level mechanic to keep the gameplay fresh. The first area act as the training area. Introducing most tricks from basic mechanic. Ability of preforming these tricks will be truly put to the test in the later areas.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay:</h2>- Unique Control Scheme<br/>The barrel is fully controlled by the cursor. Where Moving the cursor around the barrel to spin it. And clicking on the ground to jump toward the opposite direction. Player will needs to adjusting the momentum of the barrel and aiming for the jump at the same time. Which the two controls directly affecting each other. Demanding a constant attention to the barrel and the level at the same time.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766620/extras/DoABarrelRoll_Gif00.gif?t=1711342910"><br/><br/>- Exploring and Observing the Level<br/>The barrel won't stop moving since it is rounded. But it doesn't mean no resting is allowed. You can press [esc] to stand up when on a flat ground and being almost still. Sometime taking a break can have you better prepare for the future. When standing up, you can look further. Identifying potential speed run route or saving method from a mistake.<br/><br/>- Recover from Mistake<br/>Human makes mistake, we all do. It is ok to make mistake, but there is no time to feel bad. As you will have to minimize the damage the mistake does to you. It do make a huge different. Since it is possible to undo all the progress if you do nothing and just watch it fall. Therefore, identify potential danger and saving method will be a big deal.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766620/extras/DoABarrelRoll_Gif01.gif?t=1711342910"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766620/extras/DoABarrelRoll_Gif02.gif?t=1711342910"><br/><br/>- Creative Use of Mechanics<br/>The control may looks simple. But there is probably a lot deeper than you think. Apart from how well can you control it to do platforming. It is almost also a puzzle game for the way of progressing through level with the mechanics you have on your hand.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2766620/extras/DoABarrelRoll_Gif03.gif?t=1711342910"><br/><br/>Credit:<br/>Featuring Music by Matthew Pablo<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.matthewpablo.com" rel="noopener" target="_blank">http://www.matthewpablo.com</a><br/><br/>Featuring Music by The Cynic Project<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fcynicmusic.com%2F" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://cynicmusic.com/</a> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
