<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708589225"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708589225"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708589225"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yohane the Parhelion - NUMAZU in the MIRAGE -</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2459750/Yohane_the_Parhelion__NUMAZU_in_the_MIRAGE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A deckbuilding roguelite played using magical cards!<br/>Another Yohane story is here!!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/InGame_EN_02.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■『Yohane the Parhelion - NUMAZU in the MIRAGE -』<br/>Yohane the Parhelion is an official spin-off of ""Love Live! Sunshine"". 『Yohane the Parhelion - NUMAZU in the MIRAGE -』 is a deckbuilding roguelite set in that world.<br/><br/>While working as a fortune teller in Numazu, Yohane spends her days with her friends.<br/>By chance, she comes into possession of an old mirror.<br/><br/>Worried that her fortune-telling isn't accurate, Yohane decides to perform ""Magic Mirror Fortune-Telling"" using it.<br/>Suddenly, the mirror begins glowing, and sucks Yohane in!<br/><br/>What she finds in the mirror is ""Reverse-Numazu,"" which is a reversed replica of the real Numazu!<br/>Moreover, in that mysterious world, magic could be used with the power of cards.<br/>At the same time, strange things begin happening to her friends in the real world, one after another.<br/>In order to save them, Yohane must go through ""Reverse-Numazu""!<br/>What awaits her?<br/><br/>A mysterious mirror world that changes each time it's entered.<br/>After countless choices, what future will Yohane choose?<br/>A new story begins in the other Numazu!<br/><br/>■Deckbuilding and card battles in ""Reverse-Numazu"" where magic can be used!<br/>Adventure through Numazu in the mirror.<br/>Aim for the deepest level of the ""Reverse-Numazu"" by making full use of the cards you have obtained!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Head_EN.jpg?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■A wide range of deck construction with more than 150 types of cards!<br/>Collect cards as you adventure through ""Reverse-Numazu"" and build powerful decks of your own creation!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Select_1_card_EN_02.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Summon your trusty friends with Summon Cards!<br/>You can summon powerful friends in ""Reverse-Numazu"".<br/>Summon Yohane's friends to help you out in a pinch!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Summon.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Prepare for your next adventure at the Fortune-Telling Shack!<br/>By completing quests in your adventures, you can power up Yohane!<br/>Also, in the 'Closet', you can change into various costumes. <br/>By changing initial cards and charms this way, you can acquire abilities that are different from your usual outfit!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Closet_EN.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Endlessly replayable layout-changing maps! There's infinite strategies!?<br/>Once cleared, the map changes its layout every time you enter.<br/>A bargain system that lets you play forever!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/MAP_Mix.jpg?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Charms to make you stronger than the strongest! Create your strength with Cards x Charms!<br/>""Charms"" are items with powerful effects.<br/>Combine them with your cards to become more powerful than the strongest!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/22222自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/444444史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/666666传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1708542869"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1708534852"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1708534852"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1708534852"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandle Tale: A League of Legends Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1759380/Bandle_Tale_A_League_of_Legends_Story/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							One little Yordle, one humongous problem.<br/><br/>From Lazy Bear, the studio that brought you Graveyard Keeper, comes Bandle Tale: A League of Legends Story™. Jump into this delightful crafting RPG set in the magical world of Bandle City, home of the furry and fun-loving yordles.<br/><br/>You are a shy yordle living in Yarnville, a cozy but isolated island obsessed with all things knitting. When your 101-year-long apprenticeship ends, you want nothing more than to see what lies beyond the portals that connect the rest of Bandle City. But when a party you attend goes horribly wrong, the portals collapse and everything is thrown into chaos!<br/><br/>With your unique knitting magic and unflappable spirit, enlist the help of new friends, restore the portals, and reunite Bandle City once more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Steam-Breaker-Image-616x100.jpg?t=1708535596"><br/><br/>BEYOND THE BANDLEWOODS<br/>In Bandle Tale, experience a never-before-seen look at life beyond the bandlewoods. Encounter curious critters, gather materials to make impossible crafts, and awaken magical portals as you move between five unforgettable new islands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Exploration.gif?t=1708535596"><br/><br/>PARTY ON, BANDLE CITY!<br/>A good life in Bandle City hinges on one thing: beet soup! Wait, no, having fun! Throw festivals to ensure that your fellow yordles are happy and entertained. Cultivate your green thumb and cook farm-to-table dishes for your guests, or flex your engineering prowess and build gadgets to delight them.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Party.gif?t=1708535596"><br/><br/>MEET THE CHAMPIONS<br/>Befriend colorful characters and make League of Legends Champions your allies as you unravel the mysteries around you and mend your community, one magical stitch at a time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Champs.gif?t=1708535596"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator: Dark Fate - Defiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1839950/Terminator_Dark_Fate__Defiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif1.gif?t=1708527822"><br/><strong>Terminator: Dark Fate – Defiance</strong> is a <strong>real-time strategy game</strong> based on the Terminator: Dark Fate universe that follows the war between humanity and Legion's synthetic intelligent machine network.<br/><br/>In the<strong> single-player campaign</strong>, you take the role of a commander in the Founders, a force made up of the remnants of the US military and guide your army in an attempt to foil Legion's plan to exterminate the last remnants of humanity. In skirmish and multiplayer modes, play as three very diverse factions: Founders, Movement and Legion.<br/><br/>Take control of an army carried over from mission to mission on a series of large strategic maps. Make decisions about unit placement, battle tactics and abilities so that you don’t just survive but can become the leader of the resistance against the machines. Hone your skills and military expertise by replaying and achieving the best possible outcomes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic battlefields: realistic tactics and consequences</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif2.gif?t=1708527822"><br/>Engage in complex, realistic battles where your <strong>tactical decisions</strong> are vital to your survival and ultimate victory. Use a variety of military equipment, vehicles and ammunition types in your battles against the enemy. Recruit and train new units, assign new skills and acquire new weapons and equipment to continue the resistance.<br/><br/>Encounter tense battles. Your battlefield tactics and choices have deep consequences that will impact through the campaign, with other factions and characters either joining you or fighting against you, and with certain missions being available or not depending on your actions. <br/><br/><strong>Your resources are limited</strong> and you must protect your army. Weapons of war receive damage through a modular component damage system where armour characteristics, component malfunctions and hull structure all affect if your troops survive.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the survival of mankind</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif3.gif?t=1708527822"><br/>Recruit others to your cause and <strong>grow your army</strong>. Mix and match the composition of your troops to fit your preferred battle tactics. Use infantry units, heavy armoured military vehicles, plasma cannon technology, drones and other flying units and even human skirmishers to achieve victory.<br/><br/>Use the battlefield to your advantage! <strong>Physics-based building demolition</strong> lets you generate a realistic set of tactical consequences, especially in urban areas.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem: Skirmish and Online Battles</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif4.gif?t=1708527822"><br/>The excitement amplifies in <strong>skirmish and multiplayer modes</strong>, where <strong>you can play as three distinct factions</strong>: Founders, Movement, and Legion. <br/><br/>Engage in epic battles across vast strategic landscapes, testing your skills and military expertise. Every decision matters, impacting alliances, missions, and the overall survival of mankind.<br/><br/>Challenge your skills in skirmish and online multiplayer matches, facing off against AI or real-life human opponents in intense 1v1 and 2v2 battles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penny’s Big Breakaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1955230/Pennys_Big_Breakaway/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ready. Set. YO! - Join Penny &amp; Yo-Yo in a kinetic 3D-platformer bursting with innovative gameplay! Showcase your catalog of tricks and chain impressive combos to deliver Penny &amp; Yo-Yo's perfect breakout performance. Take the stage with this vibrant pair in Penny’s Big Breakaway.<br/><br/>Penny is a street performer with big dreams; she has her own spin on what it takes to be a star! When Eddie the Emperor calls for new Palace Court Performers, Penny gets herself tangled in an audition she’ll never forget. A strange encounter with a Cosmic String transforms Penny’s Yo-Yo into a living creature with an appetite for snacks— and mayhem! Use Yo-Yo to help Penny clear her name, outrun the Emperor’s penguin army, and unravel the mystery of the Cosmic String. <br/><br/>Burst onto the scene in the fluorescent world of Macaroon, home to this over-and-under escape! Discover your true star power in this easy-to-play, difficult-to-master challenge. Penny’s Big Breakaway is the debut title from Evening Star.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-01-Supertitles.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Key Features: <br/><br/>Walk the Dog: Yo-Yo’s big appetite will earn an even bigger reward with snack power-ups! Use these tasty treats to temporarily transform Yo-Yo, granting it the abilities to improve movement speed, protect Penny from harm, and much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-02-WalktheDog.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Around the World: Flee from Eddie the Emperor’s massive penguin army as they chase you clear across the planet! These clumsy flightless birds patrol the halls, come bursting through walls, and will stop at nothing to seize you! Help out friendly denizens along the way and make use of your spectacular surroundings to evade your capturers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-03-AroundTheWorld.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Encore Stage: Play your way with multiple game modes! Show off your skills as you chain awesome combos and rack up multipliers in Story Mode. Take on the ultimate speedrunning challenge and dominate the leaderboard in Time Attack Mode. Redeem coins for bonus items, secret stages, and more unlockable extras.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-04-EncoreStage.gif?t=1708524042"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slave Zero X</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1903910/Slave_Zero_X/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/01_Intro_Banner.png?t=1708520359"><br/><br/>From the top of Megacity S1-9, the Sovereign Khan rules with fists of iron and flesh. Beneath the city’s rotting foundations, a vengeful warrior embarks on a journey to murder him. 4 years prior to the events of Slave Zero, Slave Zero X brings new life to a world where horrific, living machines known as Slaves are primed to become the latest tools of war in humanity’s long and bloody history. A secret band of warriors known as The Guardians hope to stop these biomecha from being unleashed upon the world, but one swordsman among their ranks has a different idea: use the enemy’s own weapon against them. By merging with a stolen Slave Unit Prototype, Shou will become a furious Devil in pursuit of killing a false God.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/02_Features_Banner.png?t=1708520359"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/03_Killer-Combos.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>KILLER COMBOS:</strong> Use swift swordplay, explosive ordnance, and stylish combos against an army of meat and metal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/05_Death-From-Above.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>DEATH FROM ABOVE:</strong> Air juggling, dashes, and frequent target switching allow for you to take down foes of any size while wall-jumping and platforming can help you outmaneuver your enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/Graffiti_row_01.png?t=1708520359"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/07_Fight-For-Your-Life.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>FIGHT FOR YOUR LIFE:</strong> Conquer mini-bosses, set pieces, and climactic 1-on-1 encounters that offer intense challenges against unforgettable villains.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/09_Strength-is-Nothing.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>STRENGTH IS NOTHING WITHOUT CONTROL:</strong> Use the Training Room to hone precise and powerful moves to string together devastating attack sequences.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/Graffitti_Row_02.png?t=1708520359"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/11_Battle-to-the-Beat.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>BATTLE TO THE BEAT:</strong> A 90s-inspired soundtrack features heavy Drum’n’Bass and funky industrial music that adds to the thrill of combat.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/13_Feast-Your-Eyes.gif?t=1708520359"><br/><strong>FEAST YOUR EYES:</strong> A unique visual aesthetic combines nostalgic 2D sprites with an advanced lighting system and stylized 3D environments.<br/><br/><strong>THE END IS NEVER THE END:</strong> After completing the campaign, further challenges await in an expansive and frenetic ‘Crimson Citadel’ procedural challenge tower with an online high score leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1903910/extras/15_Footer_Banner.png?t=1708520359"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1708529708"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1708529708"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1708529708"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1708529708"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1708529708"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1708529708"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1708529708"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossilfuel 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2299660/Fossilfuel_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/extras/wishlist_now.gif?t=1708542820"><br/><strong>Dinosaur-themed survival horror set in a flooded underground base. </strong><br/><br/><strong>Wishlist today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>In this thrilling first-person horror shooter, you will play Jack Allen, as he investigates the mysterious Alaskan Sierra Research Facility, now flooded with water, which has been overrun by deadly dinosaurs. You will have to put your skills to the test as you embark on a heart-pumping, 12-hour journey through flooded tunnels, puzzle-filled bunkers, and dark corners filled with jump scares. The base has a dynamic sandbox layout where players can revisit areas, get upgrades to their weapons, and clear sections to create safe zones by draining water in the flooded sections. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/extras/RaptorHeadShot.gif?t=1708542820"><br/><br/>Use a massive arsenal of deadly weapons to bring the pain! Blast dinos apart in glorious gory detail all powered by Unreal Engine 5. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/extras/AnglerFish.gif?t=1708542820"><br/><br/>Much of the game takes place in flooded hallways and rooms. You will have to put on scuba gear and face off against monsters of the deep. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2299660/extras/lock.gif?t=1708542820"><br/><br/><i>Fossilfuel 2</i> is filled with many puzzles to keep you on your feet. Explore the vast nonlinear base of the flooded Sierra Research Facility and face off against not only Dinosaurs but the environment as well.<h2 class="bb_tag">Overview</h2><br/><i>Fossilfuel 2</i> is the highly-anticipated sequel to the indie game <i>Fossilfuel</i>, and it promises to deliver an experience like no other. With improved Unreal Engine 5 graphics, advanced AI, and a range of new weapons, you will have to use all your ingenuity and skill to survive in this Dino-infested facility.<h2 class="bb_tag">Rich Lore</h2>The Sierra Research Facility in Alaska was once a beacon of cutting-edge research and development, but the dinosaurs in the base escaped, and the base has been cut off from the mainland. Much of the base has been flooded with seawater. Jack Allen is part of an expedition sent out to investigate the Sierra disaster. But when their boat gets attacked by a Megalodon, the crew becomes shipwrecked on the shores of Sierra and must find a way to escape. <br/><br/>As a member of this team, you will delve into the dark secrets of the facility and uncover the truth behind the Dino outbreak. With a gripping narrative and heart-pumping action, <i>Fossilfuel 2</i> will keep you on the edge of your seat from start to finish. The game has a heavy focus on underwater horror and has a massive cast of dinosaurs including Utahraptor and Spinosaurus.<h2 class="bb_tag">Nonlinear Replay Value:</h2>With a wide range of weapons and challenging AI, each encounter with the Dinosaurs will be unique. In <i>Fossilfuel 2</i>, no two playthroughs are the same. The game features <strong>multiple endings</strong> and <strong>player choices</strong> that change the course of the game. And with 12 hours of intense horror action, you will want to come back and play again and again to experience all the thrills this game has to offer. Get ready for a pulse-pounding adventure and uncover the truth at the Sierra Research Facility.<h2 class="bb_tag">Sandbox Mode:</h2>A Garrys mod-like sandbox can be unlocked for players to brandish their creativity. Spawn NPCs and watch them fight, or make a house with the block spawner, the possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><strong>ADD TO YOUR WISHLIST TODAY AND DON'T MISS OUT!</strong><br/><br/>You are encouraged to join the discord or leave comments in the community forum. Your feedback will be taken into consideration!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2645580/Free_Stars_The_UrQuan_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">You are the captain</h2><i>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</i>® is a classic space game that captures the charm of retro science-fiction, space combat, and high adventure. Your story begins as the captain of the last human starship, with Earth trapped under a hostile forcefield. You are the last hope for humanity in a fight for control of the galaxy, as you explore thousands of unknown worlds and get dozens of quirky aliens to help.<h2 class="bb_tag">Meet fascinating alien characters</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_alien_dialog_optimized-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>​The galaxy is thriving with alien species, each with unique mysteries and motives. Meet an eclectic cast of characters, brought to life with full English voiceover. Ask sharp questions, make new friends, and exchange colorful insults.<h2 class="bb_tag">Adventure through HyperSpace</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_explore_hyperspace.gif_scaled-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>Discover a vibrant galaxy filled with wonder, terror, and absurdity. Explore thousands of uncharted worlds across hundreds of stars, and gather important resources and technology.<h2 class="bb_tag">Battle your rivals in starship combat</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_super_melee_scaled-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>Build your fleet and battle enemy starships, facing off against friends or the computer-controlled AI. Play action-packed Super Melee as its own mode, or as part of the single-player adventure – or choose automated combat to stay focused on the story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Experience a sci-fi classic – for free!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_precursors_intro.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>As a celebrated piece of gaming history, <i>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</i>® has also received wide acclaim for its story, characters, and setting. It was created as a love letter to classic science fiction like Douglas Adams, David Brin, and Jack Vance. In turn, its setting inspired a new wave of game creators, including the visionaries behind <i>Mass Effect</i>, <i>No Man’s Sky</i>, <i>Subnautica</i>, <i>Starfield</i>, <i>Fallout</i>, and <i>Stellaris</i> – to name just a few.<br/><br/>In 2002, the game was released under an open source license thanks to the generosity of Paul Reiche and Fred Ford. It continues to be available to play as a free download, for game historians and fans to enjoy.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience an open-world adventure, venturing through space to defeat the invading Ur-Quan and its hierarchy of battle thralls.<br/></li><li>Travel through extra-dimensional HyperSpace and discover nearly 500 unknown star systems filled with alien worlds.<br/></li><li>Fight enemies in fast-paced space battles with 25 different starships, each with its own unique attacks and powers.<br/></li><li>Befriend, threaten, or fight a diverse cast of aliens with unique personalities, from scary, to funny, to just plain weird.<br/></li><li>Explore thousands of planets, collecting resources and technology to upgrade your flagship and grow your fleet.<br/></li><li>Play standalone Super Melee to practice space combat against AI opponents or to duel against a friend.<br/></li><li>Mod and tinker with freely available, open-source code and content.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708440801"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708005696"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708005696"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/768200/Smalland_Survive_the_Wilds/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Before the time of the giants, we lived freely under the Sun and Moon. Centuries have passed, but those stories of the surface world have been passed down through the generations. Now the giants are gone, and you, Vanguard, must venture out into the wilds once more, on an urgent mission. Be brave, and do not falter…"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/TreeLookingup.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the vast “Land of the Small" </h2>Traverse lake sized puddles, scale skyscraper sized trees, scramble through cavernous cracks in roads, as you experience a huge open world from a new perspective. Explore dense forests, hazardous swamps and strange ruins left over from the time before. Uncover lore and knowledge from hidden NPCs scattered throughout the world and learn to survive in this vast wilderness. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Land_of_Small.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tame and ride creatures</h2>Uncover recipes that will let you tame and ride an array of critters. Leap huge distances on the back of a Grasshopper, zoom around on a Damselfly, scurry from place-to-place on a Spider. This world and its inhabitants are yours to conquer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Mounts.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive together</h2>Play alongside friends with support for up to 10 players in multiplayer. Explore together, fight together, build together and survive the wilds as a team.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Together.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build encampments on the ground or amongst the trees</h2>Scavenge or refine resources to build your encampment with multiple material tiers, from leaves and twigs to sturdy stone. Pick your favourite spot in the world and build, or scale vast trees and claim your own settlement at the top.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Housing.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Craft powerful armour sets</h2>Collect powerful armours that provide you with resistances and abilities and mix them up to personalise your appearance. Glide through the skies in winged armour, swing from tree to tree with the grappling hook and many more. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Armors.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Wilds</h2>Most of the creatures you encounter will see you as lower on the food chain – Ants, Cockroaches, Beetles, Wasps, and Spiders all view you as a potential meal. Weather conditions and seasons are in constant flux so if you want to survive for another day, preparation is key.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Survive_the_Wilds.gif?t=1708514975"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islands of Insight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2071500/Islands_of_Insight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Islands of Insight: a sublime shared-world puzzle game set in a fantasy realm of ancient wonders and natural beauty. Brimming with mysterious puzzles to solve, secrets to uncover, and vibrant landscapes to explore, this peaceful world of floating islands is the perfect place to unwind. Embark on a puzzle adventure of your choice, all at your own pace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_1-Title-Journey_EN.png?t=1708109878">‎‎‏‏‎<br/>Play as a Seeker on a peaceful journey rich in exploration and puzzle-solving. Embark on the Path of Discovery and let your curiosity guide you through a breathtaking open world where the answer is always in sight.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Journey_HD.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_2-Title-Puzzles_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Seek out and solve an unparalleled collection of over 10,000 puzzles divided across 24 puzzle types. Every corner of the world holds a new eureka moment for you to discover. From enigmas of perspective to logic problems, environmental challenges and more, the puzzles you’ll encounter vary in difficulty and have been crafted by some of the best minds in puzzle design to create an engaging experience for both newcomers and seasoned puzzle fans.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Puzzles_HD.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_3-Title-Exploration_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Freely explore the main island’s expansive open world where most of the puzzles and secrets are found. Wander the vibrant landscapes and architecture of its 5 distinct biomes or spread your wings to glide above them. Navigate the environment’s verticality and take your game to new heights. Unlock puzzle types and new areas in the campaign by completing 20+ Enclaves housing curated puzzle challenges. Go where you want. Solve what you want. The only path here is the one you make.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/3.IOI_Steam_Gif_Exploration___Discovery_2.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_5-Title-Experience_EN.png?t=1708109878"><br/>Customize your character. Increase your puzzle masteries to level them up while earning sparks to unlock new abilities. Complete daily quests. Seamlessly interact with other players in our shared world to gain or offer a bit of guidance, or choose to figure things out entirely on your own. With puzzles that refresh over time, a new discovery awaits with every visit to the islands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/4.IOI_Steam_Gif_An_Evergreen_Experience_2.gif?t=1708109878"><br/><br/>Age restrictions may apply to access this game.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultros</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2386310/Ultros/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You wake up stranded, after seemingly crashing your ship on The Sarcophagus — a giant, space-drifting, cosmic uterus holding an ancient demonic being known as ULTROS. Trapped in the eternal loop of a black hole, you will have to explore The Sarcophagus and meet its inhabitants to understand the part you play. <br/><br/>Are you the gruesome breaker of this cycle, or can you become a link from destruction to rebirth? <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat1.png?t=1708088745"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat1.gif?t=1708088745"><br/>ULTROS is set in a multifaceted realm - a vast alien landscape teeming with life. Grounded in science fiction, ULTROS comes wrapped in an eccentric art style and a mystical soundtrack from the visionary El Huervo, renowned for his work on Hotline Miami. ULTROS explores meta-themes of mental health, life, death, and karmic cycles through deep lore and environmental storytelling.       <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat2.png?t=1708088745"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat2.gif?t=1708088745"><br/>Experience brutal, intimate, close-quarter combat with cosmic lifeforms, driven by a sense of urgency – where precision is paramount and every cut of your blade counts. Yet this intense combat is juxtaposed with cultivating the greenery and tending to plant life in The Sarcophagus, providing precious moments of contemplation and peace. In turn, this grants deeper access to obscured paths.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat3.png?t=1708088745"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat3.gif?t=1708088745"><br/>The rich world of ULTROS holds many secrets for those curious enough — and fearless enough — to seek them out. A unique loop-based mechanic will allow you to start over at key moments in the story, providing opportunities to unfold such secrets, unlock different areas of the world and new abilities on a branching skill tree. Experiment with and master your own specific fighting style as you explore the world of ULTROS. Each loop brings you closer to the truth...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1708080818"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1708080818"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1708080818"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1708080818"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1707811616"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1708570368"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1708570368"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1708570368"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1708570368"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1708570368"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1708570368"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1708570368"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1708570368"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1708570368"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1708570368"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1708570368"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1708570368"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDERDOGS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2441700/UNDERDOGS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Title.gif?t=1708438791"><br/><br/>Wrap yourself in 5 tons of metal and go smashing through a dark scene of UNDERGROUND MECH FIGHTS! Bash, crush, maul and rip apart enemy bots and mechs.<br/><br/><u><strong>IT’S FULL-ON METAL-ON-METAL VIOLENCE IN THIS PHYSICS-BASED MECH BRAWLER!</strong></u><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Smooch.gif?t=1708438791"><br/><br/>But rampaging through the pits ain’t all - <u><strong>THIS IS A ROGUELIKE.</strong></u><br/>Gear up with 120+ items including power tools to customize your mech, meet 30+ characters, hire hackers and saboteurs, hustle and deal with the gangsters and psychos who run these streets as you claw your way up the food chain.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_DF_Pan.gif?t=1708438791"><br/><br/>This city is a dog-eat-dog shit show, but luckily you ain't alone.<br/>Your little bruv King is in your corner - calling out threats and giving you lip while you fight like a wild animal, smashing car sized pit bots that wanna kill you dead to the deafening roars of the blood thirsty crowds.<br/><br/><strong>This is New Brakka - The Mech Fighting Capital of the World.<br/>This is UNDERDOGS.<br/><br/>Welcome to the jungle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441700/extras/UNDERDOGS_-_Dem_Clean.gif?t=1708438791"/></strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRASH MATH</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2828060/CRASH_MATH/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2828060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							CRASH MATH<br>
<br>
You must solve math problems while trying to drive a car and avoid traps.<br>
<br>
This driving game has a lot of possibilities. The physics engine simulates every component of a vehicle in real-time, resulting in a funny behavior. While creating the excitement of solving math problems.<br>
<br>
There are also Several Traps ALL around the City that will destroy Your Car as You try to solve math problems.<br/>
<br/>
Use cool Camera effects like Bullet-Time, so, You can see every detail of the destruction.<br/>
<br/>
Several different car types like Sedan, SUV, Hatchback, SuperCar, and Motorcycles with many different paint jobs.<br/>
<br/>
Can You solve math problems and drive at the same time?<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
FEATURES:<br/>
<br/>
Advanced Driveable car system including physics, damage and deformation, drift, enter/exit, and much more!<br/>
<br/>
Fire Damage<br/>
Full Damage &amp; Explosion<br/>
Flat Tire feature<br/>
Character Ragdoll<br/>
Automatic transmission<br/>
Deformation<br/>
Breakable pieces and glass<br/>
Enter and Exit car<br/>
Full car explosion and destruction<br/>
Many Car Types (SUV, Sedan, Hatchback, SuperCar, and Motorcycles)<br/>
Also Police Cars and Taxis<br/>
Procedurally damaged car paint<br/>
Toggleable Lights (and Sirens)<br/>
Change camera (inside – outside of car)<br/>
Camera zoom and orbit (outside)<br/>
Smoke, dust, impact particle systems<br/>
Drift, and surface impact<br/>
A.I. Traffic (in the Freeway Area)<br/>
Math Problems to solve while You drive<br/>
Some Buildings have Interiors You can Explore<br/>
{I wonder if there are any 'Easter Eggs' hiding in any of those ???} ;)<br/>
<br/>
. . . Oh, and the City is being attacked by Crazy Clowns, so, Mow those guys down, will ya?<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
. . . . and much more!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tipping Point</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1749030/The_Tipping_Point/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1749030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">THE ICE IS COLLAPSING!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1749030/extras/CassRunning.gif?t=1708600744"><br/>You play as <strong>Cass</strong>, an arctic climate researcher. You must get off the ice sheet before it collapses. On your way, you will gather and analyze data about the ice.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1749030/extras/ClimbReadData.gif?t=1708600744"><br/>Make your way over the collapsing ice sheet by jumping, sliding, and climbing. Reach abandoned research stations and gather data in a series of mini-games. Analyze the data and uncover what is happening to the climate.<h2 class="bb_tag">INVESTIGATE AND LEARN</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1749030/extras/AccessTerminal.gif?t=1708600744"><br/><i>The Tipping Point</i> is a 3D side-scroller developed in collaboration with real world researchers in an interdisciplinary effort (physicists, biologists, chemists, statisticians, and more). The things you do in The Tipping Point are based on what researchers do in the arctic in real life.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1749030/extras/RetrieveIce.gif?t=1708600744"><br/>As researchers do, you will compare the data you collect to previous data sets and investigate changes in the climate.<h2 class="bb_tag">UNCOVER WHAT IS HAPPENING TO THE ICE</h2>Solve the mystery of the tipping point and why the ice sheet is suddenly collapsing.<h2 class="bb_tag">THANKS TO</h2>Funded by <strong>EU Horizon 2020</strong>, <strong>The Novo Nordisk Foundation</strong>, and <strong>NordForsk</strong>, <i>The Tipping Point</i> is and will forever be available for free.<br/><br/>The research groups that contributed to the development of <i>The Tipping Point</i> are:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>TiPES</strong> is a large scientific collaboration with the aim to enhance the understanding of tipping points in the earth system. 18 partner institutions work together in more than 10 countries. The project is funded by EU Horizon 2020. <br/></li><li><strong>Narwhal NordForsk</strong> project, consisting of Aarhus University, Chalmers University, Greenland Institute of Natural Resources, and more. The project is funded by NordForsk.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">INFO</h2>The game is free, without any in-app-purchases.<br/>Gameplay time is about 2 to 3 hours.<br/>Best enjoyed with a controller!<h2 class="bb_tag">DISCLAIMER</h2>The exact numbers in the game are not based on real findings. Only the scientific concepts behind the educational content are based on real research.<br/>The game takes liberty to dramatisize the covered science.<br/>We emplore you to think critically about the conveyed information and educate yourself via other sources. You can find correct information via the links above to the collaborating scientific organisations and institutions.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pogo Pogo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2825400/Pogo_Pogo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2825400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I put together this game to upset a certain kind of individual.<br>
<br>
Pogo Pogo is punishing climbing game. you'll be able to jump, climb and fly across a collection of levels designed to challenge you.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider Threat</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796460/Insider_Threat/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><u>About This</u>:</strong><br/><br/>Insider threat is a first-person survival horror game. The game takes place in a scientific complex located somewhere lost in the universe. The plot tells the story of one of the patients who has survived the latest events that occurred in the complex. After waking up alone and disoriented, you will soon discover the terrible experiments that were being carried out in this strange place.<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in an environment full of danger and constant tension while you meet objectives that will allow you to escape threats.<br/><br/>Helpless and disoriented, you will have to manage to obtain the necessary resources to be able to explore the other parts of the scientific complex and try to get out alive.<br/><br/><br/><strong><u>Important note</u>:</strong><br/><br/>This game focuses on exploration and achieving certain objectives. During its course you must solve the enigma that will allow you to complete the story. Your mission will be to overcome all the obstacles that come your way until you escape from the place. Be careful because its constant tension will favor a more realistic and deeper experience for the player.<br/><br/><br/><strong><i>Insider Threat</i>is a first-person survival horror game</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Environment</strong><br/><br/>The game takes place inside a scientific complex located in an unknown location. Under a dark and sinister atmosphere you must explore each of the different sections of the complex without ever neglecting your back, it could be that something is stalking you.<br/><br/><strong>The theme of the game</strong><br/><br/>The game tells the events that occurred in a scientific complex lost in the universe. Its protagonist is a patient who wakes up disoriented and has to discover what has happened in this place. Throughout the game, you will have to be very focused on your surroundings since you may not be the only inhabitant of the complex.<br/><br/><strong><u>Developer comment: </u></strong><br/>This game may not harm you fisically, but it can harm your psychology. It is our recommendation for people who have fear of the dark, heart problems and fear of being alone to play with caution.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon No Dungeon: Tyrant's Endgame</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2449080/Dungeon_No_Dungeon_Tyrants_Endgame/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>"Command a battle on the chessboard. Abandon grand civilization themes and focus on a single combat; that's what we excel at."</strong></h2>This is a casual strategy game based on match-3 gameplay, incorporating the world of the flagship title "Dungeon No Dungeon" and introducing a completely new storyline and game mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/extras/xueqishi.png?t=1708596373"><br/><br/>In the game, you can gradually experience the relatively hardcore deck-building gameplay through the understanding of match-3 and synthesis mechanics, which are simple to understand and easy to operate. After numerous attempts, you can develop your unique game rhythm and strategic thinking, leading to more and more satisfying battle experiences.<br/><br/>Therefore, we warmly welcome everyone to engage in discussions and share their gameplay strategies within the community, allowing for collisions and sparks that may generate unexpected combinations of gameplay elements (even for ourselves).<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/extras/fengexian4.png?t=1708596373"><h2 class="bb_tag">In "Dungeon No Dungeon: Tyrant's Endgame," there is no single correct approach, only the most suitable one.</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/extras/xueqishiPKsishen.png?t=1708596373"><h2 class="bb_tag">In the game, you will assume the role of a follower of the gods, strategizing and manipulating the battlefield on the chessboard.</h2><br/>Allocate resources wisely and use supplies, construct buildings, and build your deck to increase the ability of your own faction. <br/>Plan your layout, be prepared, and defeat the enemies when they reach the battlefield, emerging as the victorious one who laughs last.<br/><br/>Your means include:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Units Movement: Move matching units together to merge them and acquire powerful units or more resources. A single move can trigger multiple merges and yield greater rewards, so every move has the potential to turn the tide of battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/extras/xiaobing_xueqishi.png?t=1708596373"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/extras/xiaobing_sishen.png?t=1708596373"><br/><br/></img></img></li><li>Use of Supplies: Consume gold resources to utilize supplies with diverse effects, providing continuous assistance to your army. Proper use of supplies often leads to unexpected victories.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/extras/buji.png?t=1708596373"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Building Construction: Consume wood resources to construct buildings of various forms on the chessboard. Each building has different effects and activation ranges, and they cannot be moved. Therefore, proper city planning is crucial to determining the outcome of battles.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/extras/jianzhu.png?t=1708596373"><br/><br/></img></li><li>Deck-building Effects: Consume steel resources to select various powerful combat effects. Choosing the right effects often leads to synergy, where the whole is greater than the sum of its parts. Some special combinations can even achieve remarkable results. It's time to showcase your strategic prowess!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/extras/fengexian4.png?t=1708596373"><br/><br/>In the future, we plan to develop more exciting game modes to enrich the gameplay. <br/>(This list may expand over time or with the increase in game sales.)<h2 class="bb_tag">Journey of Chess</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An enjoyable and laid-back story experience <br/></li><li>Relatively fixed unit/building/deck combinations</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Wild Brawl</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An intense and thrilling mental challenge <br/></li><li>Freedom to choose unit/building/deck combinations</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Incarnation of Heroes</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A thrilling and satisfying hack and slash <br/></li><li>Playing as an RPG villain boss with nurturing gameplay</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2449080/extras/logoen.png?t=1708596373"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUNKUNKUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2791570/KUNKUNKUN/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>《KUNKUNKUN》Is a first person horror adventure puzzle game!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791570/extras/kshow01.png?t=1708593778"><br/><strong>Why are abandoned old schools so angry? What the hell happened here?<br/>To investigate the spirit KUNKUNKUN, everything is waiting for you to discover for yourself.<br/>Everything in the game has nothing to do with reality, and any resemblance is purely coincidental.<br/>The game contains a variety of scare elements. If you lack courage, please turn off the lights!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>What will I experience?</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791570/extras/kshow02.png?t=1708593778"><br/><strong>Yes, it's another horror story. On a strange night of thunder and lightning,<br/>KUNKUNKUN is everything you need to know!<br/>Two and a half years in the making!<br/>Trying to give you two and a half hours of extraordinary experience!<br/>And you, will be a real brave MAN!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>What's the play of this game?</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791570/extras/kshow03.png?t=1708593778"><br/><strong>KUNKUNKUNIt's everything you need to know！！<br/>KUNKUNKUNIt's everything you need to know！！<br/>KUNKUNKUNIt's everything you need to know！！<h2 class="bb_tag">TIPS</h2>WASD：move<br/>Shift：run<br/>E：interact<br/>Left mouse：Next sentence</strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>About basketball, about chickens, about affection, about dreams!</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791570/extras/kshow04.png?t=1708593778"><br/><strong>This is a moving and scary story!<br/>This is a little-known show!<br/>It's been a bizarre journey!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2791570/extras/MAN40.jpg?t=1708593778"><br/><br/><i><strong><u>*Everything in the game has nothing to do with reality, and any resemblance is purely coincidental.<br/>The game contains a variety of scare elements. If you lack courage, please turn off the lights!</u></strong></i> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2806830/Welcome_to_Ukraine/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2806830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I've come to the realization that there's so much about my own country that I don't know. In light of this, I've developed a game to share my journey of discovering Ukraine. It's Jigsaws with lot of useful features. Through this interactive experience, I hope to offer insights into the rich culture, history, and beauty of our country. I hope it will be interesting not only for jigsaw puzzle lovers;)<br/><br/>I want to keep this game free and I will update it from time to time with new pictures and features<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><br/></li><li>Multiple puzzle pieces selection<br/></li><li>3 different Cutouts shapes<br/></li><li>Rotation and Sorting features<br/></li><li>Useful Zoom and Magnifier tool<br/></li><li>Customizable background color<br/></li><li>Wide cutout range</li></ul><br/>I used CC0, self generated content or pictures I have permission from the author. <br/>I will try to deal with local photographers to provide more quality pictures and facts of my country.<br/><br/>Also, you can check my other puzzle game (which uses the same engine)  <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1538750/Master_of_Pieces__Jigsaw_Puzzle/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1538750/Master_of_Pieces__Jigsaw_Puzzle/</a><br/><br/>Enjoy game and share your thoughts! Peace!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garden Life: A Cozy Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1915380/Garden_Life_A_Cozy_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/MASTER_GIF.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE1_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF1.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>Plant and nurture your dream garden using gardening techniques based in real life and adapted for everyone to enjoy:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Plant seeds, leaving them enough space to thrive<br/></li><li> Water, fertilize, and clip your plants to enhance their natural beauty and nurture them to health<br/></li><li> Discover different colourful varieties and unlock the full potential of each plant<br/></li><li> Pull out all weeds or choose to leave some to protect plants from pests<br/></li><li> Admire your plants in full bloom even through the changing seasons : in Garden Life, all plants thrive no matter the time of year!<br/></li><li> Play the story mode or the creative mode</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE2_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>You are in charge of an abandoned community garden and decide to roll up your sleeves to restore it to its former glory. Complete tasks given to you by your neighbours to earn rewards, unlock new tools, seeds, ornaments and areas of the garden, and learn more about what lies behind this secluded spot.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE3_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF3.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>Instantly unlock every corner of your garden, including all the seeds and ornaments, and give free rein to your creativity: in this restriction-free mode, you can bring your dream designs to life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE4_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF4.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>Procedural growth simulation developed specifically for the game ensures each plant grows in its own way! Each and every plant grows procedurally, and some even adapt to their environment by climbing if planted close to certain objects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE5_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF5.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>In Garden Life, you are not restricted by a grid: place plants and objects freely to create your designs!  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE6_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF6.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>Head to the village square to sell flowers and bouquets at your stall and use the earnings to buy new seeds, ornaments and tools in the shop. You can also donates flowers to help create huge floral sculptures in the pavilion and win adorable prizes! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE7_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF7.gif?t=1708592520"><br/><br/>Add Garden Life to your wishlist, follow us, and join our discord community so you don't miss out on any news!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garden Life: A Cozy Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1915380/Garden_Life_A_Cozy_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/MASTER_GIF.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE1_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF1.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>Plant and nurture your dream garden using gardening techniques based in real life and adapted for everyone to enjoy:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Plant seeds, leaving them enough space to thrive<br/></li><li> Water, fertilize, and clip your plants to enhance their natural beauty and nurture them to health<br/></li><li> Discover different colourful varieties and unlock the full potential of each plant<br/></li><li> Pull out all weeds or choose to leave some to protect plants from pests<br/></li><li> Admire your plants in full bloom even through the changing seasons : in Garden Life, all plants thrive no matter the time of year!<br/></li><li> Play the story mode or the creative mode</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE2_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>You are in charge of an abandoned community garden and decide to roll up your sleeves to restore it to its former glory. Complete tasks given to you by your neighbours to earn rewards, unlock new tools, seeds, ornaments and areas of the garden, and learn more about what lies behind this secluded spot.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE3_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF3.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>Instantly unlock every corner of your garden, including all the seeds and ornaments, and give free rein to your creativity: in this restriction-free mode, you can bring your dream designs to life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE4_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF4.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>Procedural growth simulation developed specifically for the game ensures each plant grows in its own way! Each and every plant grows procedurally, and some even adapt to their environment by climbing if planted close to certain objects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE5_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF5.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>In Garden Life, you are not restricted by a grid: place plants and objects freely to create your designs!  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE6_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF6.gif?t=1708592520"><br/> <br/>Head to the village square to sell flowers and bouquets at your stall and use the earnings to buy new seeds, ornaments and tools in the shop. You can also donates flowers to help create huge floral sculptures in the pavilion and win adorable prizes! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE7_EN.gif?t=1708592520"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF7.gif?t=1708592520"><br/><br/>Add Garden Life to your wishlist, follow us, and join our discord community so you don't miss out on any news!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rail Route</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1124180/Rail_Route/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/header_alt_assets_7.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ever dreamed of designing your own railway network? Building it from scratch, adding more stations, taking on more contracts, watching your small network grow into a complex, thriving rail system? Rail Route makes this dream a reality!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/june23_gif1.gif?t=1708594591"><h2 class="bb_tag">Master the art of automation</h2>Start with a few stations, design your first railway lines, and experience the joy of your first train completing its route. Take on contracts to earn money and upgrade points, unlocking new technologies that introduce more trains and automation tools into your network. With each added station and contract, the complexity grows, but so does your mastery. Experience the thrill of watching your railway network evolve from a few simple lines to a bustling, automated operation. Automation in Rail Route isn't just a feature - it's a complex, rewarding challenge. As your strategy unfurls, every signal placement and contract planning decision adds another gear in the intricate machine of your network. And when the trains glide smoothly through the tracks, operating flawlessly on their own, you'll feel that unparalleled satisfaction - not just of a job well done, but of mastering a world of your own creation.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/june23_gif2.gif?t=1708594591"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unleash complexity in simplicity</h2>Navigate the charming minimalism of the design, reflecting the familiar screen of a train dispatcher yet imbued with a unique twist. It presents an intuitive interface at a glance - a system that can be understood in minutes. However, beneath this simple surface, a world of intricate mechanics awaits, revealing itself as more stations are added and more contracts are undertaken. Each new layer of complexity maintains the design's authenticity, capturing the essence of real-world rail management.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/june23_gif3.gif?t=1708594591"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your network, your rules</h2>The freedom is yours: build from scratch, gradually unlocking technologies and resources to create your ultimate rail network across real-world city maps. Experience the satisfaction of perfect scheduling, ensuring a smooth and efficient flow of trains that reflects your strategic acumen. Or maybe the thrill of high-pressure, time-sensitive scenarios calls to you, where quick decision-making is key and wave after wave of challenges keep you on your toes.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/june23_gif5.gif?t=1708594591"><h2 class="bb_tag">Join a world of creators and enthusiasts</h2>Join a vibrant community that contributes to an ever-expanding universe of maps.  A community of creators and railway enthusiasts, coming together to design, share, and explore maps that span the globe. Each addition is a new adventure, a new challenge to conquer.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1124180/extras/Maps.gif?t=1708594591"><br/><br/><strong>So, what are you waiting for? Embrace your inner train enthusiast and plunge into the world of Rail Route – make the traffic flow and the network grow!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trolley Path to Gold</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2819210/Trolley_Path_to_Gold/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Puzzle game, build your way to the gold mine by collecting all the tools that come along the way.<br/><br/>Build a railway, help the trolley get to its cherished goal. On your way you will encounter both easy and difficult tasks that will have to be solved in order to find the treasured route. Use your mouse and your head to prove that you can build a railroad.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819210/extras/Trolley.gif?t=1708591839"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819210/extras/Trolley_2.gif?t=1708591839"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708589225"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708589225"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708589225"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golf Monday</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2675400/Golf_Monday/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A Golf Game Like No Other</h2>Welcome to the national amateur golf tournament at Oakvale Meadows!<br/><br/>Avoid the sand traps and water hazards, score birdies and eagles, make new friends, and win the day. Enjoy a golf experience where you not only need to aim your shots, but also keep your social relations finely tuned. Luckily everybody is well rested and in their best mood.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fully featured course with 18 holes of varying difficulty!<br/></li><li>Enjoy interacting with fellow golfers!<br/></li><li>Drive golf carts if you're in a hurry!<br/></li><li>Customise your golfer!<br/></li><li>Chill and no-stress gameplay!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1708586421"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1708586421"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1708586421"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1708586421"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1708586421"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1708586421"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1708586421"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR Dinosaur Village</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2516750/VR_Dinosaur_Village/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is an exciting VR casual game that allows players to experience the fun of dinosaur breeding in person. In this virtual real world, you will become a dinosaur farmeter to cultivate huge dinosaurs and earn money by planting plants and fishing and feeding dinosaurs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516750/extras/1.jpg?t=1708583365"><br/> <br/>The core gameplay of the game is planting and feeding dinosaurs. You will have a piece of land, and you can plant various plants on it. You can choose different seeds, such as vegetables, fruits and grass. You can also use fishing rods for fishing. Different types of dinosaurs have different food habits. Therefore, you need to choose proper feed according to the dinosaur's dietary habits. When sowing seeds, you also need to water and fertilize them to ensure that they grow up healthy and rapid.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516750/extras/2.jpg?t=1708583365"><br/> <br/>Breeding grassy dinosaurs need to be fed with planting plants. When your plant grows mature, you can pick them and feed them to dinosaurs. To feed meat dinosaurs, you need to use a fishing rod to capture fish in the lake and feed dinosaurs.<br/>When you successfully raise dinosaurs, you can sell them and get money rewards. Money is the key to unlock more seeds, props and dinosaur seedlings. You can buy new seeds in the store through money, plant more varieties of plants, and further enrich your farm experience.<br/>In short, this game brings the fun of dinosaur breeding to your fingertips through exquisite graphics and real virtual reality experience. You can not only relax your body and mind, but also cultivate your own planting skills, and feel the sense of accomplishment of becoming a dinosaur farmers. Come and join this fun and creative farm world and start your unique dinosaur breeding journey!<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2516750/extras/3.jpg?t=1708583365"><br/><br/>Operation method:<br/>Feed herbivorous dinosaurs with plants<br/>Feed carnivorous dinosaurs with fish Caught in lake<br/>Walk         left handle up/down/left/right<br/>Turn          right handle left/right<br/>Use ltem      right handle trigger<br/>Cancel        right handle grip<br/>Reset Position  left handle grip<br/>Show/Hide Hud  left/right handle menu						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taoist Survivor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2812310/Taoist_Survivor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In ancient times, there was a mountain known as "Yaoshan" The highest peak on this mountain is called the "Tianjie" You will venture to this mountain to gather rare treasures, face the tribulations of thunder, encounter numerous opportunities, wield powerful artifacts, learn countless immortal techniques, display divine skills, vanquish cunning demons, defeat mighty demon lords, and acquire celestial treasures and artifacts!<br>
<br>
Beginner Tips:<br>
<br>
Killing demons grants immediate experience for leveling up, which provides skill or attribute selections.<br>
Consume peaches and lingzhi mushrooms to increase cultivation, rapidly advancing your realm. Each advancement brings a significant opportunity (a unique enhancement).<br>
Pay attention to your shield bar; it only protects against physical damage, not magical or true damage.<br/>
Being struck by lightning on the Heavenly Tribulation Peak can swiftly increase cultivation but also inflicts considerable magical damage.<br/>
When stuck, consider cliff jumping, which only consumes 25% of your health and teleports you to a random location.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yohane the Parhelion - NUMAZU in the MIRAGE -</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2459750/Yohane_the_Parhelion__NUMAZU_in_the_MIRAGE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A deckbuilding roguelite played using magical cards!<br/>Another Yohane story is here!!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/InGame_EN_02.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■『Yohane the Parhelion - NUMAZU in the MIRAGE -』<br/>Yohane the Parhelion is an official spin-off of ""Love Live! Sunshine"". 『Yohane the Parhelion - NUMAZU in the MIRAGE -』 is a deckbuilding roguelite set in that world.<br/><br/>While working as a fortune teller in Numazu, Yohane spends her days with her friends.<br/>By chance, she comes into possession of an old mirror.<br/><br/>Worried that her fortune-telling isn't accurate, Yohane decides to perform ""Magic Mirror Fortune-Telling"" using it.<br/>Suddenly, the mirror begins glowing, and sucks Yohane in!<br/><br/>What she finds in the mirror is ""Reverse-Numazu,"" which is a reversed replica of the real Numazu!<br/>Moreover, in that mysterious world, magic could be used with the power of cards.<br/>At the same time, strange things begin happening to her friends in the real world, one after another.<br/>In order to save them, Yohane must go through ""Reverse-Numazu""!<br/>What awaits her?<br/><br/>A mysterious mirror world that changes each time it's entered.<br/>After countless choices, what future will Yohane choose?<br/>A new story begins in the other Numazu!<br/><br/>■Deckbuilding and card battles in ""Reverse-Numazu"" where magic can be used!<br/>Adventure through Numazu in the mirror.<br/>Aim for the deepest level of the ""Reverse-Numazu"" by making full use of the cards you have obtained!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Head_EN.jpg?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■A wide range of deck construction with more than 150 types of cards!<br/>Collect cards as you adventure through ""Reverse-Numazu"" and build powerful decks of your own creation!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Select_1_card_EN_02.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Summon your trusty friends with Summon Cards!<br/>You can summon powerful friends in ""Reverse-Numazu"".<br/>Summon Yohane's friends to help you out in a pinch!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Summon.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Prepare for your next adventure at the Fortune-Telling Shack!<br/>By completing quests in your adventures, you can power up Yohane!<br/>Also, in the 'Closet', you can change into various costumes. <br/>By changing initial cards and charms this way, you can acquire abilities that are different from your usual outfit!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/Closet_EN.gif?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Endlessly replayable layout-changing maps! There's infinite strategies!?<br/>Once cleared, the map changes its layout every time you enter.<br/>A bargain system that lets you play forever!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459750/extras/MAP_Mix.jpg?t=1708578030"><br/><br/>■Charms to make you stronger than the strongest! Create your strength with Cards x Charms!<br/>""Charms"" are items with powerful effects.<br/>Combine them with your cards to become more powerful than the strongest!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chambers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2734150/Chambers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2734150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slay monsters! Overcome obstacles! Recover your stolen gold!<br/>'Chambers' is an epic adventure, a thrilling puzzle platformer that puts you on a quest to reclaim your gold!<br/><br/><strong>GAMEPLAY:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You will embark on an adventure through 15 treacherous dungeons, each packed with hidden chambers, deadly traps, and fierce monsters!<br/></li><li>You will encounter legendary weapons, each endowed with a unique and potent power-up!<br/></li><li>Find scattered gold coins, they may just save your life! Also, your high score at the end will be determined by the gold coins you collect!<br/></li><li>Pay your way by giving the Reaper a bag of gold! Getting the bag of gold to the exit however, may often leave you scratching your head!<br/></li><li>Stay on your guard though! if you drop the bag of gold the Gnome will attempt to steal it within 20 seconds and return it to the chest!<br/></li><li>And best be warned: navigating with a bag of gold comes with restrictions—no attacking, jumping, or running! Good Luck!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extraordinary: Monster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2746360/Extraordinary_Monster/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Extraordinary: Monster" is a point-and-click puzzle game created by TeatimeWorkshop<br>
The story begins with E.I. senior investigator Karena tracking down a tragic murder case. The investigation in the abandoned Alberto laboratory made Karena feel that this was no ordinary murder case. Rare equipment, scratches on the wall, purple... Liquids, twisted animal cages... everything gradually points to the suspect-Professor Selon<br>
<br>
Game features:<br>
The operation and gameplay of the game are simple and easy to understand. Even if you have never played point-and-click puzzle games, you can easily get started.<br>
The story in the game is presented in a unique picture book style, which will make you unable to put it down.<br>
The puzzle design is rigorous and varied, supplemented by a variety of mini-games, making logic and fun coexist.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Train Models - JR Kyushu Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2780590/Japan_Train_Models__JR_Kyushu_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2780590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Japan Train Models, the game where you can enjoy trains in its entirety, is now available with trains of JR Kyushu!<br>
<br>
There are three modes to play: Pazzle mode, Layout mode, and Encyclopedia mode!<br>
You can enjoy the fascination of trains as much as you want.<br>
<br>
Puzzle Mode<br>
This is a game mode in which players create pazzle by attaching train parts at puzzle intervals.<br>
All vehicles appearing in the game are officially licensed!<br/>
You can assemble these finely detailed vehicles as many times as you like.<br/>
<br/>
And the vehicles are not the only pazzle you can build.<br/>
At the end of each stage, you can create a diorama of the scenery where the cars run.<br/>
<br/>
Layout Mode<br/>
The layout base featured in this work is the new layout from old edition of "Japan Train Models", the new layout base included in this work is the new layout from the old version!<br/>
Let's create a new cityscape different from the old version.<br/>
<br/>
You can place buildings and other structures on the layout to create your one and only original layout!<br/>
You can also take cool pictures by running the cars you built in the Pazzle mode!<br/>
By selecting morning, evening, or night time, you can enjoy the changes in scenery depending on the time of day.<br/>
There are also a variety of shooting modes, such as scenery from a train window or from the viewpoint of a cameraman placed on the layout!<br/>
In addition, you can move the placed cameraman. Take the best shot from your favorite place and angle!<br/>
<br/>
Encyclopedia Mode<br/>
You can check detailed data and 3D models of the vehicles!<br/>
Enjoy your favorite cars by enlarging and rotating them.<br/>
You can switch the internal camera and move to the carriages to feel as if you are on the train.<br/>
You can also see the detailed descriptions of the cars supervised by JR Kyushu.<br/>
<br/>
Equipped with a train car.<br/>
Japan Train Models - JR Kyushu Edition features the following 3 cars.<br/>
813-1100 Series<br/>
811-0 Series<br/>
Kiha 66 /67<br/>
<br/>
Here is your own railway space to create!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turlock Holmes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2142160/Turlock_Holmes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/关于《海龟蘑菇汤》_EN.png?t=1708567239"><br/><br/>Have you heard of Turtle Soup? It is a kind of Lateral Thinking Puzzlers popular in the East, and the name of Albatross Soup is more well known in the West.<br/><br/>In short, Turtle Soup is a collection of puzzles that at first seem unlikely or illogical. The quizmaster offers a surprise ending (puzzler), and players deduce what leads to the ending (answer). This game contains 64 mind benders from easy to hard created by 15 authors, with an AI quizmaster for a single-player experience.<br/><br/>Just remember: when it comes to this puzzle type, it's important to think way out of the box!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/Th_600x337_Word_Guess.gif?t=1708567239"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/主线故事_EN.png?t=1708567239"><br/><br/>A girl found herself stuck in an underground mall, with a body and some turtle soup lying around. She seemed to be caught in a mysterious loop. Could you help her get out and solve the mysteries?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/图片1_EN.jpg?t=1708567239"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/脑洞大开的故事_EN.png?t=1708567239"><br/><br/>A boy lies dead on a sidewalk, with only his underwear and an umbrella in his hands. What happened?<br/><br/>A stewardess helped splint the pilot’s broken legs, and brought him fresh seafood every day. However, it seems the pilot is very scared of the stewardess. Why?<br/><br/>A big chunk of Turtle Soup are suspenders and thrillers with some dark styles, and others are fun, humorous. Rest assured they do not contain any revolting, unpleasing content, and you can skip if you don’t like one.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/图片2_EN.jpg?t=1708567239"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/游戏玩法_EN.png?t=1708567239"><br/><br/>When you play the game alone, you need to think, reason, and even imagine to reveal the answers to the seemingly illogical, impossible puzzlers.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Enter keywords. Synonyms are also OK!<br/></li><li>Ask AI if the keywords are relevant.<br/></li><li>Hit a dead end? Spend coins to get correct keywords immediately.</li></ul><br/>As you find keywords and hints, the story will gradually become more and more clear visually. Is the answer at all how you had pictured? <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/Th_600x337_single_guss.gif?t=1708567239"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/Th_600x337_Question.gif?t=1708567239"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/Th_600x337_Hint.gif?t=1708567239"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/收藏品_EN.png?t=1708567239"><br/><br/>Get a collectible for every completed puzzler/story, and they can be worn by our little Turtle. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2142160/extras/图片3_EN.jpg?t=1708567239"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">FOLLOW US</h2></strong><br/>Discord: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F3j2huWsj" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Turlock Holmes</a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2142160/_/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2142160/_/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Party Time 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788460/Party_Party_Time_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Introducing an all-new party game for everyone to pick up, play, and enjoy!<br/><br/>Streamlined, enhanced, and intuitive controls make every play session unlimited and easy fun!<br/>Compete with friends and family and let the fun times roll!<br/><br/>[Free Mode]<br/>Pick your favorite game and play right away!<br/>Enjoy an additional selection of co-op games where you must work together to succeed!<br/><br/>[Party Mode]<br/>Choose games to play in succession and compete to be the Party Champion!<br/><br/>Design your own characters and invite them to the party to play along!<br/><br/>*Controllers are required for multiplayer play.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LurkBait Twitch Fishing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2767520/LurkBait_Twitch_Fishing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A Twitch-powered interactive cozy fishing game for your viewers. Every game needs a fishing minigame, now your stream can have one too!<br/><br/>Add as an overlay for your stream and let your viewers fish with commands, points, bits or subs. Boost viewer engagement and reel in the lurkers with a fun interactive game that runs itself — while you focus on your content.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767520/extras/Lurkbait_Catch.gif?t=1708562224"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Supports triggering a cast with chat commands, channel points, bits, subs and gifted subs or a combination of all 5 triggers<br/></li><li>Easy and convenient Twitch login, authentication is stored locally with no additional signups or fees<br/></li><li>All casts are automatically queued, so nobody misses out on their chance to fish<br/></li><li>Four weather options to change the vibe<br/></li><li>Create custom catches with your own images, choose their value and their rarity will automatically be calculated<br/></li><li>Automatic performance scaling when you're running intense games to keep things running as smooth as possible<br/></li><li>Pause queue button, useful when you're trying to wrap up stream<br/></li><li>Allow viewers to display the leaderboard and the fish dex with commands<br/></li><li>Allow streamers and mods to manually cast on behalf of a viewer with a command<br/></li><li>A help command is automatically created that lists your specific cast triggers for viewers<br/></li><li>Optional stats command so viewers can check their gold, leaderboard position and total catches<br/></li><li>Convenient mute button for when you need to focus on your game</li></ul><br/>Check out the demo to test LurkBait to see how it integrates with your stream, and how it impacts performance. However in the demo version, only the streamer can cast and catch fish.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2767520/extras/Lurkbait_Catches.gif?t=1708562224"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customization options</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Customize all commands and the global command prefix, including the cast, leaderboard, dex and help command<br/></li><li>Choose your own channel point redeem name<br/></li><li>Choose to hide the game when not in use, or to remain visible with the auto-hide toggle<br/></li><li>Customize commands and command prefixes<br/></li><li>Choose minimum bits and allow multiple casts<br/></li><li>Create timeouts for cast, leaderboard and dex commands<br/></li><li>Cast delay option to not interfere with your alerts<br/></li><li>Optionally boost the chances of catching ultra-rare fish so they appear more frequently<br/></li><li>Graphics quality settings and resolution<br/></li><li>Transparent window or chroma-key option<br/></li><li>Game volume</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">IMPORTANT</h2>This is a game purely intended for Twitch streamers, if you aren't a Twitch streamer, this probably isn't for you!<br/>This game features catchable objects that reference drug and alcohol consumption, this might not be suitable for all family friendly streams.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anamnesia - part 1: am i my body?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2799320/Anamnesia__part_1_am_i_my_body/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2799320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Can you find the truth?</strong><br/>Nine people wake up trapped in an abandoned research facility. Split into three teams, separated into different halls, the members of the two Answer Teams need to compete in a game of life and death. The goal: to figure out the "truth" behind the secret member of the Question Team: Emilia.<br/><br/><strong>Do you really want to?</strong><br/>Each part of Anamnesia will cover the same timeframe from the perspective of a different protagonist. Part 1 centers around Adrian, a member of Answer Team A. Will he manage to uncover the secrets hidden deep within himself in order to learn the truth and get out alive? Or, much more importantly: does he even want to?<br/><br/><strong>Find your own truth.</strong><br/>Throughout the story you can scroll up at any time to check Adrian's log: a recording of all conversations he has previously witnessed, stored on a chip in his brain. Maybe doing so can reveal hidden details he missed...<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Roughly 70,000 words (4-6 hours) of mostly linear storytelling<br/></li><li> A complete character arc as part of a larger narrative<br/></li><li> Unique in-universe interpretation of the genre-typical backlog feature<br/></li><li> An original soundtrack and beautiful artwork</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>迷宮校舎 | School Labyrinth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2423300/__School_Labyrinth/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2423300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">【Overview】</h2><br/><strong>School Labyrinth</strong> is a 1-4 player co-op horror game.<br/><br/>Children sneak into a school at night to try out their courage, and are trapped in the school building.<br/>The labyrinthine structure, eerie footsteps, and disturbing presence.<br/>The school building, which should be familiar to them, has taken on a completely different appearance than usual.<h2 class="bb_tag">【Game System】</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Randomly generated stages</strong></li></ul> <strong>School Labyrinth</strong> is a complex labyrinth that changes its shape every time you play.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Online Multiplayer</strong></li></ul>Up to 4 people can cooperate to escape from the <strong>School Labyrinth</strong>.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Escape</strong></li></ul>The only way to escape from  <strong>School Labyrinth</strong> is to find an emergency exit.<br/>Split up with your friends and try to find the emergency exit somehow.<br/>But don't get lost by yourself...<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Anomaly</strong></li></ul>There is a disturbing presence in the school building, and it seems that there is something else there besides you and your friends.<br/>Is the person beside you really your friend?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kneedle Knight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2491720/Kneedle_Knight/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Kneedle Knight</i> is a third-person, puzzle platformer game developed by students at SMU Guildhall Cohort 32. In <i>Kneedle Knight</i>, the player controls a mouse knight that uses his magical needle to sew fabric which he can merge into, moving back and forth between 3D and 2D. <br/><br/>Sir Lukoss the Small was a noble knight sent on a quest to defeat the evil Witch of Fabric. The Witch, using her enchanted fabric, imprisoned and transformed many citizens and knights into malicious fabrications. Sir Lukoss climbed up through her fortress to put an end to her tyranny, only to be hexed by her magic and transformed into a mouse. In the dark dungeon of the Witch’s lair, the mouse finds a magic needle, granting him special powers to sew fabric of his own and merge in and out of the enchanted threadwork. <br/><br/>Now Sir Lukoss must use his newfound weapon to sew his path forward and up through the evil stronghold. The mouse knight can use his needle to solve puzzles, overcome challenging obstacles, and defeat the animated candle minions of the Witch. All with the hopes of returning to face the Witch of Fabric yet again to finish his noble quest.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Single-player, puzzle platformer game<br/></li><li>Playtime (main story): 1-2 hours<br/></li><li>Playtime (100% achievements): 2 hours<br/></li><li>Steam leaderboard support for level speed running<br/></li><li>Made in Unreal Engine 5<br/></li><li>Original soundtrack</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spider-Guy: Trapped in the Cheese Place</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2641000/SpiderGuy_Trapped_in_the_Cheese_Place/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Spider-guy has been imprisoned by the dastardly Cheddar-Head within the cheese place. You take control of our protagonist spider-guy as he fights through hordes of the viscous cheese amalgamations that lie between you and the exit. This action packed platformer side scroller is vibrant with depictions of cheesy horror. Spider-Guy: Trapped in the Cheese place is a single player game that uses left, right, and jump to control the character.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DangoVerse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2308370/DangoVerse/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2308370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Game featuring VTubers and their surrounding community</strong><br/>Inspired by Vampire Survivors and HoloCure, you must survive waves of "chats" and defeat bosses along the way.<br/><br/><strong>Characters</strong><br/>You can choose from 3 characters, each with unique skills and a special ability.<br/><br/><strong>Upgrades</strong><br/>With every level-up, you can enhance defensive, attack, or passive items to aid you in defeating various bosses.<br/><br/><strong>Enemies</strong><br/>A wide variety of enemies will try to impede your journey to the top.<br/><br/><strong>Bosses</strong><br/>Engage in battles with different bosses that appear from time to time.<br/>As you level up, the bosses will become more challenging.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoSlider</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2742640/GeoSlider/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2742640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							GeoSlider is an educational, geography-themed puzzle game. The goal is to find misplaced continent pieces or islands and slide them back to their proper locations as quickly as possible. As you progress, you will improve your navigational skills and gain a better understanding of the locations and sizes of different regions of the Earth.<br/><br/>The game includes a puzzle pack with puzzles that range from simple to more demanding. It can be played in two modes:<br/><br/><strong>Challenge mode</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Puzzles have a time limit that increases as they become more difficult<br/></li><li>For each correctly placed piece, the remaining time is extended</li></ul><br/><strong>Relaxed mode</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The time limit is disabled, take as much time as you need</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YUMPR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2797100/YUMPR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2797100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Get involved in this 2-D pixel platform game that will make you experience fun, stress, success, anger, and FUN. Adapt or Die, improve your in game mechanics to be able to succeed this adventure, which be sure is going to become harder as you keep advancing.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Soundtrack</h2><i>More than 15 minutes of music that you can enjoy while playing, don't worry about repetitive music, there are more than 30 songs with around 30 seconds of duration.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Control</h2><i>Move YUMPR at your will with your keyboard or Xbox Controller.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Variety of enemies and obstacles</h2><i>Have fun avoiding unique enemies and obstacles, learn the jumping mechanics, improve your skills to advance the journey.</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Difficulty</h2><i>Start with easy levels, see how they get tougher until you reach a point where you need to master the game, giving it replayability when trying to complete all the achievements.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/22222自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/444444史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/666666传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1708542869"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1708542869"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Into the depths below</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2336390/Into_the_depths_below/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The mines beneath Trianis tempt adventurerers with the promise of danger, exitement and wealth. Though many already lost their lives you yet heed the call.<br>
Create a party of up to five characters and explore the depths below!<br>
<br>
Features:<br>
 - Create your party<br>
   Choose from 11 different classes, each wih dozens of unique skill trees and different mechanics. You can later add skill trees from other classes, allowing for <br>
   sheer endless viable party compositions. <br/>
<br/>
- 12 long levels in four different biomes<br/>
   The mines are of course only the beginning. Each new level brings new dangers and treasure, new random events and monsters to defeat.<br/>
<br/>
- Gameplay focus<br/>
   Less emphasis on story allows you to focus on dungeon delving. Experiment, find your favourite class combinations and press on.<br/>
   However prepare to die a lot. The depths below are unforgiving and cruel.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenger Sharks</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398980/Avenger_Sharks/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Avenger Sharks</strong> is a retro twin-stick shooter.  Featuring sharks.  <strong>OUT FOR VENGEANCE!</strong><br/><br/>Your fishy friends have been kidnapped (fish-napped?) by evil forces.  Battle wave after wave of enemies as you fight to rescue them.  Increase your chances by collecting power-ups, health potions and UPGRADES as you progress.  Invoke <strong>FISH FRENZY</strong> as needed to even the odds, as well as any trusty friends you find along the way.  These friends include a dinosaur.  Why?  Because we wanted to have a dinosaur in the game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prime</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802080/Prime/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"<strong>Prime</strong>" is a board game inspired by chess and checkers. In the game, two opponents face off: the whites and the blacks. The game is played on a 64-square board, similar to that of chess.<br/><br/>The pieces are marked with a number, which is added each time to the captured piece's number or increased by 1 or 2 units when the piece is promoted (reaching the opposite side of the board).<br/><br/>Pieces with the number 1 are pawns and can move forward by only one square. Pieces with even numbers can move forward and sideways by only one square, while pieces with odd numbers can move forward and diagonally forward by only one square. Pieces with prime numbers starting from 5 can move in any direction (vertical, horizontal, and diagonal), provided the path is clear.<br/><br/>Pawns, even-numbered pieces, and odd-numbered pieces are eligible for promotion when they reach the opposite side of the board: pawns and even-numbered pieces increase their value by one unit, while odd-numbered pieces increase by 2. After promotion, the direction of the piece is reversed.<br/><br/>"Prime" pieces do not have a fixed direction as they can move in any direction (like the queen in chess). However, after capturing, if they become "even" or "odd," they also inherit the direction of the captured piece. In the event that a "Prime" captures another "Prime," the direction will be favorable to the side of the board closest to it.<br/><br/>At the beginning of the game, each player has 8 pawns, 4 even-numbered pieces, 2 odd-numbered pieces, and 2 prime-numbered pieces. The player who captures all opponent pieces wins. The game can also end when both players possess only "Prime" pieces: in this case, the winner is determined by who has more pieces, and in case of a tie, the game is a draw or a tiebreaker.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pogo-Gogo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2820680/PogoGogo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2820680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A game about pogoing up skyscrapers. An important message is waiting for you at the top of the tallest building, but there may be even more climbing to do after that. Make hilarious fails, unbelievable saves, or just explore the tiny open world and its inhabitants. There are 100 purple crystals scattered around the town and some are hiding in the most unsuspecting places.<br>
<br>
Available to play on both controller or keyboard/mouse.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1708534852"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1708534852"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1708534852"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
