<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Transmute</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1191660/Rebel_Transmute/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/Rebel_Transmute_Logo_Decorated_Steam.png?t=1710176486"><br/><br/>In this modern metroidvania you play as Moon Mikono, a space scrapper turned adventurer on a mission to uncover the true fate of her missing mother.<br/><br/>To accomplish this mission in your own, unique way you'll be swapping out game changing augments to suit your playstyle.  Aggressive and greedy?  Inquisitive and cautious?  Maybe you just want an army of friendly creatures!  With over 50 unique upgrades, Rebel Transmute allows you to play through a classic sci-fi adventure in YOUR style.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHALLENGING AND CUSTOMIZABLE COMBAT</h2>Use a variety of spells known as Bloodcasts, your trusty Foray-issued Blaster, and a variety of game changing Augments to take on a world of dangerous creatures and space travelers.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/16.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE AND MAP A VIBRANT SCI-FI WORLD</h2>The sprawling world of Rebel Transmute is full of stunning vistas: From vibrant greenery in the Overgrowth, to the fluorescent reefs of the Coral Fissure, to the sparkblood crystal-strewn Surface.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/09.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">Additional Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Encounter over <strong>80 unique enemies</strong> and over <strong>10 formidable bosses</strong>! From mutated worms and electrified beasts, to rogue AI's and gigantic bugs. All offering different and exciting challenges and interactions.<br/></li><li>Discover <strong>game-changing abilities</strong> hidden throughout the outpost.  Spin Bash, Wall Jump, and Void Dash your way across an interconnected network of tunnels, caverns, and research laboratories!<br/></li><li>Augment your playstyle with <strong>48 optional upgrades</strong> that can drastically change how you play the game.  Fight alongside a reprogrammed drone, twist your attacks into spiraling laser blasts, or even summon tentacles to block projectiles!<br/></li><li>Make use of a versatile mapping system to help track your progress.  Use custom markers, track your completion percentage, and find hidden terminals to uncover unexplored areas.<br/></li><li>Experience a <strong>personal and heartfelt story</strong>. As Moon searches for her mother she’ll also encounter various robot life, all with their own stories, personalities, and quests.<br/></li><li>A <strong>hand-painted pixel art</strong> aesthetic lends each and every character, enemy, and sector a personal touch.<br/></li><li>An immersive and atmospheric score, crafted to perfectly match every moment, from bombastic fights to solemn exploration.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635350/United_Penguin_Kingdom/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/Storage.gif?t=1709984701"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635350/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1709984701"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERHOUSE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2533960/SUMMERHOUSE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/extras/summerhouse_new_store_page.gif?t=1709984408"><br/><br/>SUMMERHOUSE is a small-scale building game and a love letter to the feeling of long lost summer afternoons.<br/><br/>Craft a neighbourhood of tiny, beautiful lived-in homes in a variety of settings: the sea, the city, or the mountains. While there are some little secrets to uncover, there are no rules, and you can’t win or lose. Just chill out, build to your heart’s content and soak up the atmosphere.<br/><br/>If relaxation and creation are your thing, this is a game for you :)<br/><br/><i>Please keep in mind that this is a small game with no goals or challenges, created by a single person🙂</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORE BLASTERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/BORE_BLASTERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/BLAST.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_blast_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Blast your way through rocks and dirt with your machinegun drill. Carve through the ground to uncover precious ores and defeat menacing foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/LOOT.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_loot_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Uncover ancient relics and artefacts hidden in the deep. Amass a fortune in rare gems &amp; ores.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/UPGRADE.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_mortar_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Invest in powerful upgrades and unlock new abilities, turning your humble gyrocopter into a fearsome force to be reckoned with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/DISCOVER.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_discover_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Explore a diverse range of biomes, from treacherous volcanic caverns to lush overgrown underground forests, each with its own unique challenges and rewards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/FEATURES.png?t=1709907021"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intense mining action with fast-paced blasting<br/></li><li> Constant progress - even failed runs aren't punishing<br/></li><li> Diverse biomes to explore<br/></li><li> Purchase upgrades to overpower your gyrocopter<br/></li><li> Navigate the overworld to unlock new mine shafts<br/></li><li> Collect and loot rare gems, ores, and artefacts to upgrade your gear and abilities<br/></li><li> Endless replayability with procedurally generated levels</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_drones_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/>Drawing inspiration from mining games like Motherload and Galactic Mining Corp, Bore Blasters takes the genre to the next level with high octane action and fast paced gameplay. Fans of digging and collecting will find plenty to love, while the addition of deadly enemies and mysterious artefacts will keep even the most seasoned miners on their toes.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/WL_arrow.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_missiles_frame.gif?t=1709907021"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Realm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1330000/Stolen_Realm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/GreenDragon.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TURN-BASED STRATEGY MEETS ACTION RPG IN THIS DUNGEON CRAWLING LOOTER</strong></h2><br/><br/>Stolen Realm is a <strong>simultaneous turn-based tactical dungeon crawling looter with action RPG elements</strong> where you control up to <strong>6 heroes, solo or through online co-op</strong>, venturing forth in adventures set in a high-fantasy, low-poly world. <br/><br/>Stolen Realm features an <strong>innovative turn-based combat system</strong> where <strong>simultaneous turns</strong> allow every team to take their actions at once, creating quick combat encounters that blend the tactical depth of titles like Divinity: Original Sin with the thrill of a fast-paced action RPG. Every battle scales based on the number of players involved, so you can easily jump in and out of the game even in the same playthrough!<br/> <br/>With a <strong>highly customisable class system</strong>, Stolen Realm allows you to create traditional RPG classes or break the mold to forge a unique champion of your own as you draw from a pool of hundreds of possible skills. Make a spell-slinging assassin, a priest born of frost, or a shadow-infused knight. Further customize your build by earning and reforging <strong>loot that truly changes the way you play</strong>: wield Abbadon the Soul Crusher, a mythic mace that raises slain enemies as skeletal warriors to fight for you, or unsheath the Bloodletter, a cursed sword that grants additional power at the cost of your lifeblood. D&amp;D-like events where attribute-based rolls will have permanent effects on your character add yet another layer to building a character that is truly your own. Anything is possible in this title that keeps compelling choices at the forefront of your experience.  <br/><br/>Keeping the core appeal of RPGs at its forefront, Stolen Realm ensures you spend all your time, fighting, building your characters and making compelling choices that determine your immediate path or effect your character, rather than getting bogged down in side quests and other RPG-bloat.   After each battle, pick your path between story events, resource gathering, shops and treasure rooms, until you get to the final boss of each <strong>procedurally generated adventure.</strong> If you’re up to a challenge, crank the difficulty up with <strong>6 different difficulty levels</strong> – or pick <strong>Hardcore Mode with permadeath</strong>, where every battle can be the last!<br/><br/>Also features <strong>Roguelike Mode</strong>, a fast paced version of the game where you can mix and match builds that are simply not possible in the traditional campaign!<br/><br/>Carve a place in history with your sword and magic. Rise to honor and glory in the battlefield. <strong>Recover the Stolen Realm.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/CycloneKick.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag">PRAISE FOR STOLEN REALM</h2><br/>“The tactical depth of Divinity: Original Sin” - GamesRadar+<br/><br/>“we’re losing our evenings to… Stolen Realm” - TheXboxHub<br/><br/>“A gorgeous looking game” - PC Gamer<br/><br/>“You can be a fire warrior. You can be a healing necromancer. You can do all sorts of weird s**t.” - <strong>Sacriel</strong><br/><br/>“What I like about this game is it’s straight to the point. You just go in, you’re building your character, you’re getting items…and you just fight. There’s no bulls**t.” - <strong>Shroud</strong><br/><br/>“It’s rad” - <strong>Sequisha</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/Dwarven_Warmachine.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play solo or with friends in up to 6 player online co-op, allowing you and your friends to wreak havoc amongst your foes<br/></li><li>Experience thrilling and fast-paced turn-based battles thanks to a simultaneous team turn system<br/></li><li>Full story campaign, roguelike mode and streamer mode<br/></li><li>Use over 300 skills in 10 distinct skill trees allowing for complete and flexible character customization<br/></li><li>Navigate hex-based battlefields where positioning is key due to battle shrines with special effects, exploding barrels and movable crates<br/></li><li>Find and loot over 700 unique items, fully customizable with modifiers, as you explore a wonderful world full of magic, secrets and unexpected dangers<br/></li><li>Co-op focused design keeps gameplay fast paced and strategic for up to 6 players <br/></li><li>Easy drop-in, drop-out design and automatic scaling that allows you to join or drop out mid-quest <br/></li><li>D&amp;D-like attribute-based rolls in special events that have permanent character effects<br/></li><li>Fight against over 200 types of enemies in battles that will be different every time: thanks to the Enemy Modifications feature, every creature you face on the battlefield will be unique<br/></li><li>A world that changes on each expedition, from frosty peaks guarded by the elusive Blue Dragon to overgrown jungles where the rock giants roam. <br/></li><li>Pick your path between battles, choosing where to go between story events, resource gathering, shops, fights, and treasure rooms until you get to the final boss of each adventure<br/></li><li>6 different difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Choose between Normal Mode and Hardcore Mode with permadeath if you want a real challenge!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWE 2K24</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2315690/WWE_2K24/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2315690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							FORTY YEARS OF WRESTLEMANIA<br>
<br>
WrestleMania is the biggest event in sports entertainment, where Superstars become WWE Legends. Experience a gripping retelling of WrestleMania’s greatest moments in 2K Showcase of the Immortals, where you can relive a collection of some of the most unforgettable, career-defining matches.<br>
<br>
AN ICONIC ROSTER<br>
<br>
WWE 2K24 boasts a star-studded roster featuring WWE Legends like “Stone Cold” Steve Austin, Undertaker, and Andre the Giant, alongside current WWE Superstars like “The American Nightmare” Cody Rhodes, John Cena, Rhea Ripley, and Roman Reigns, whose larger-than-life entrances and signature moves are heightened by ultra-realistic graphics.<br>
<br>
NEW MATCH TYPES<br>
<br>
From Guest Referee to Casket, Gauntlet, and Ambulance matches, there are a bevy of new match types to experience in WWE 2K24, including support for multiple Superstars in Backstage Brawl.<br>
<br>
PROVE YOURSELF IN MyRISE<br>
<br>
Unleash your raw talent and become the undisputed champ in MyRISE, featuring two thrilling career arcs and original storylines chronicling your ascent to WWE stardom from the men's and women’s divisions.<br>
<br>
BUILD YOUR FACTION<br>
<br>
Assemble your favorite WWE Superstars and Legends in MyFACTION. Acquire cards, build a dominant faction, compete in online multiplayer and the all-new ranked quickplay. Plus, earn exciting promotional and final rank rewards as you climb the new seasonal leaderboard!<br>
<br>
CONTROL THE WWE UNIVERSE<br>
<br>
Develop feuds, weekly shows, and more in Universe mode, WWE 2K24’s ultimate sandbox, with expanded rivalry actions, all-new cutscenes, and support for double-title matches!<br>
<br>
CALL THE SHOTS IN MyGM<br>
<br>
Oversee the biggest brands and Superstars in sports entertainment as you challenge rival general managers for the top spot in MyGM. Explore more match types, more brands, and new general managers. Trade Superstars between brands, make executive decisions on contracts, and amp up the drama.<br/>
<br/>
**Online play including MyFACTION requires an internet connection and 2K Account. Terms apply.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duelists of Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1664200/Duelists_of_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/DoE_EVO_Trailer_-_steam_gif_short_30fps.gif?t=1710102934"><br/>Duelists of Eden is a card-grid-fighting game set after the events of One Step From Eden. Build your custom deck and battle online in real-time action! There are over 14 unique characters with strengths and weaknesses to encourage creative spell combinations and synergies. Will you combo slashes, fire, or even use bombs to eliminate your competition?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/SaffronWitch_steam_header-features.gif?t=1710102934"><h2 class="bb_tag">Deckbuilding</h2>Fight in a mix of strategy and real-time action! Create your own unique combination of spells to take down the competition. <br/>Save and edit an unlimited amount of decks in the editor!<h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic cardtridge and combo system</h2>Create combos on the fly, adapting the scenario and what spells you and your opponent have.<h2 class="bb_tag">Tutorial and training mode</h2>Learn the ropes in the tutorial mode and deep dive into the mechanics via training mode. <br/>Training mode includes hitboxes, character states, quick deck edits, speed modifiers, and more!<h2 class="bb_tag">Custom rollback netcode</h2>The game was completely rebuilt to support custom rollback netcode, for the smoothest experience possible.<h2 class="bb_tag">Replay mode</h2>Review your matches in replay mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/Selicy_OSFE_gif_steam.gif?t=1710102934"><br/><br/>Local multiplayer may require a controller.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Keeper Gold™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996630/Dungeon_Keeper_Gold/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Being the Dungeon Keeper and all, this is your home, too. And it’s your business to take these loathsome creatures of darkness and hone them into screaming, frothing, clawing forces of destruction. Lure them in with food and the promise of dank and fetid places to sleep. Keep them in line with the back of your hand and the threat of dire consequences. Pit their scaly hides against the best that the Forces of Good can muster, and they’ll die for you as they rip steaming entrails out of the hapless heroes.<br/><br/>It’s a degenerate and nasty job…and you love it. Yes, home is where your heart is. In a box. Packed in salt. That's right — Dungeon Keeper, Bullfrog's classic dungeon management strategy, gives you no extra credit for having any morals. After all, the underworld isn't black and white!<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Revolutionary game packed with tons of dark humor, an impressive variety of hellish creatures, and highly addictive gameplay<br/></li><li>Build your dungeon &amp; protect it with a labyrinth of dark corridors, a web of deadly traps, an arsenal of powerful spells, and an army of bloodthirsty demons<br/></li><li>A refreshing title for someone tired of rescuing princesses, saving worlds, and all that love, happiness, and political correctness junk. Just this once, be the bad guy!</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Keeper™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2616460/Dungeon_Keeper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2616460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Discover your dark side as you build an evil underground kingdom and defend it against the forces of good. Carve out a living, breathing world and attract a host of devilish creatures to swell the ranks of your dark hordes. Form an alliance with the Horned Reaper to expand your empire and invade the realms above. In this dungeon-building, treasure-defending, hero-destroying adventure, it feels good to be bad — and the badder, the better! <br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Get your hands on even more evil tools.</strong> Use everything at your disposal — torture devices included — to create the deadliest dungeon imaginable. Set traps, send dastardly demons to do your bidding, and unleash the powers of the underworld with a brand-new magic system. <br/></li><li><strong>Rule your way.</strong> Keep your minions well-supplied with bustling infrastructure and good pay, or scare them into miserable servitude. There’s no extra credit for good behavior. <br/></li><li><strong>Bring your friends to their knees.</strong> Play with up to 4 frenemies, and prove who’s the most ruthless dungeon keeper in all land.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sim City 3000™ Unlimited</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2741560/Sim_City_3000_Unlimited/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Create and control your urban empire with more power than ever before. With SimCity 3000 Unlimited, you get all the great features of the original SimCity 3000 plus much more. Expand your SimCities with 2 new building sets from Asia and Europe. Take on 13 challenging scenarios, or create your own. Unleash 4 new disasters, including an unforgiving whirlpool and plummeting space junk. This is truly SimCity without limits!<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Re-create cities from around the globe with hundreds of new buildings.<br/></li><li>Reunify East and West Berlin in one of 13 scenarios.<br/></li><li>Spruce up your city with over 95 world landmarks.<br/></li><li>Protect your citizens from 4 new disasters.<br/></li><li>Select hundreds of buildings from SimCity 3000 and all-new Asian and European buildings.<br/></li><li>Create unique masterpieces for your metropolis with the Building Architect Plus tool.<br/></li><li>Inflict 9 disasters, including toxic clouds, plague of locusts, space junk, and a whirlpool.<br/></li><li>Play 13 challenging scenarios, or make your own with the SimCity Scenario Creator.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoria: Age of Shattering</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159090/Zoria_Age_of_Shattering/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fk3fPxX8" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/join_disco_2.jpg?t=1710009094"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/YOU_ARE_THE_COMMADER.gif?t=1710009094"><br/><br/>You will lead a diverse team through the various lands of an Uram continent and against challenges <strong>countless groups of monsters and bosses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/WORLD.gif?t=1710009094"><br/><br/>Zoria has now fallen prey to the sheer brutality of the hellspawn that roams its land. Its<strong> lush forests, mysterious caves, and majestic buildings</strong> have transformed into haunting and dreadful locations. Take your time and explore unknown areas, as each holds a mystery. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/Combat.gif?t=1710009094"><br/><br/>Combat is bread and butter, and <strong>you will engage in it easily.</strong> Use the <strong>unique skills </strong>of all of your party members: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attack from close range or distance with different attack patterns and directions,<br/></li><li>Heal or shield allies with various spells and commands,<br/></li><li>Inflict status aliments like damage over time, stun, immobilize, and other elemental effects,<br/></li><li>Leverage your environment to gain the upper hand or create new scenarios to distance yourself from the enemy.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/CRAFT.gif?t=1710009094"><br/><br/>Keep a keen eye on your <strong>equipment and vitality</strong> as they both deteriorate over time. A <strong>bonfire in Zoria's provides a safe spot</strong> to restock your resources and prepare for the next battle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/success.gif?t=1710009094"><br/><br/>Take care of each of your warriors' <strong>skill development</strong>, and it will repay you on the battlefield. Remember that having an individual with the right skills can <strong>get you into previously inaccessible places and quests</strong>. It may turn out that interacting with a specific character with various objects in the world of Zoria may lead you to discover hidden treasures or make your travel easier.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/base.gif?t=1710009094"><br/><br/>You have to be wise in and out of the battle. You cannot win the game without making progress - this also counts toward your outpost. You may regularly <strong>update the base by unlocking new wings to the buildings</strong>, and by doing so, you will be rewarded with either resources, quests, or items. <strong>Different buildings will have different numbers of available upgrades.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159090/extras/followers.gif?t=1710009094"><br/><br/>In your outpost, you can<strong> plan and assign tasks to your companions</strong>. Send selected party members on an autonomic mission, in which you won't participate but will receive what they find along the way. You will also get some of the experience they gain. <strong>Never forget that their lives are in your hands!</strong><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159090/Zoria_Age_of_Shattering/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159090/Zoria_Age_of_Shattering/</a></img></img></img></img></img></img></strong> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potions: A Curious Tale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/378690/Potions_A_Curious_Tale/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Add Potions: A Curious Tale to your wishlist!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/Wishlist_616.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/LunaCombatGif.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Use your wits to strategize conflict resolution that goes beyond pure combat-- you’ll have to think on your feet and act quickly to sidestep danger and trick, charm, and scare your opponents into dropping valuable resources. <br/><br/>As powerful as your potions are, you’ll find yourself up against monsters that can shrug off your most powerful attacks. Manage your resources carefully and use the environment and even other monsters to defeat your enemies, or you may find yourself with an empty satchel when you need your elixirs the most.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamCraftingVideoFullPotTitleNX.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>On her path to potions mastery, Luna must gather rare ingredients even before she brews her first potion. While her grandmother and friends teach her basic skills and recipes, Luna must fill her vials through experimentation and discovery. <br/><br/>Explore the deep crafting system as you discover new ingredients across 7 biomes to craft over 100 unique potions with different element combinations. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PuzzleGifTitle.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Solve devious puzzles and mysteries with your wits and your arsenal of mystical potions. With a little help from your grandmother (a powerful witch in her own right) and Helios, your cat familiar, you’ll overcome the challenges of these enchanted lands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/StoryTitle.png?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Growing up is hard, and it’s even harder when you’re a witch! Encounter fairy tale and folklore characters as you guide Luna on her quest to become a potions master. With her sharp-tongued familiar at her side, Luna learns important coming-of-age lessons: Respect is earned, advice can be deceiving, and adults aren't always right.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FQS2SN55CC4" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamHeaderDiscord616.png?t=1709876407"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PetCatHeart.gif?t=1709876407"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Saboteur™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/24880/The_Saboteur/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/24880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Not all wars are fought on the open battlefield. Download The Saboteur to visit 1940s Nazi-occupied Paris, as you play tough Irish racecar mechanic Sean Devlin. Working with the French Resistance, Sean is out for revenge against ruthless Nazi Colonel Kurt Dierker, who executed Sean’s best friend.<br/><br/>This open-world action thriller takes you through the seedy streets of Paris as you seek to undermine the German authority and lead a rebellion. Fight across rooftops and through dangerous alleys, and operate a wide variety of vehicles as you navigate your terrain. You can even climb the Eiffel Tower or Notre Dame Cathedral for a sniping mission.<br/><br/>Use stealth and disguise to strike at the heart of the Nazi war machine by disabling trains, destroying bridges, and blowing up enemy facilities. As you work to remove the oppressive forces from parts of the city, the drab black-and-white palette gives way to bright colors, signifying that you’ve inspired the townspeople. The more you incite the people, the more they’ll aid you by intervening in fights or providing a quick getaway from pursuing Germans. The Saboteur presents a fresh take on World War II and features dramatic cinematic elements. The action and intrigue is yours to experience via download on the PC now.<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>First Ever Open-World Paris</strong> — Climb the Eiffel Tour, snipe from Notre Dame Cathedral, and brawl on the Champs d’Elysee as you sabotage your enemies. Fight, climb, and prowl through the dark alleys, rooftops, burlesque houses, and seedy streets of the City of Lights — the ultimate playground for the Saboteur.<br/></li><li><strong>The Art of Sabotage</strong> — Being the Saboteur is all about attacking while staying unnoticed. Get your mission intel at underground clubs and cabarets. Eliminate your adversaries with stealth attacks, disguise, distractions, and explosives. Master a variety of weapons, automobiles, and skills to sabotage enemy operations. <br/></li><li><strong>The Will to Fight</strong> — An action-packed experience and thrilling storyline are made even more engaging by an innovative visual style, characters, and the new “Will to Fight” technology. Experience how the city reacts and changes around you as you free it from Nazi oppression. Only you can restore hope and grandeur to Paris.<br/></li><li><strong>French Resistance Strikes</strong> — Call for support from The Underground in the form of getaway cars, weapon deliveries, distractions, and much more.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1808680/Snufkin_Melody_of_Moominvalley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_1_opt_c.gif?t=1709917468"><br/><br/>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley is a story-rich musical adventure game about Snufkin restoring the valley and helping the quirky and memorable characters and critters who call it home. A series of hideous parks have cropped up in Moominvalley, disrupting the landscape and its harmonious nature. As Snufkin you will distract police officers, pull out signs, and knock over misplaced statues as you vigorously try to restore nature and the inhabitants’ home while putting an end to the industrious Park Keeper’s plans…<br/><br/>Experience a beautifully crafted and quintessentially Nordic game, brought to life with stories, emotions, and a melancholic atmosphere set in Tove Jansson’s vivid and beloved world of Moomin. You are invited to a wholesome experience for every age that combines open-world mechanics with puzzles, stealth, and melodic elements!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_2_opt_c.gif?t=1709917468"><h2 class="bb_tag">GORGEOUS STORYBOOK STYLE BRINGING A WORLD TO LIFE</h2><br/>Immerse yourself in a beautiful and imaginative world that captures the very essence of the Moomin stories; an extensive tapestry of graphical books and cartoons brought to life in a never-before-seen way. <br/><br/>Experience the harmonious symphony with every footfall, elevated by music and melodies from the Icelandic post-rock band Sigur Rós. Befriend Moominvalley inhabitants as Snufkin with a few tunes from his harmonica. Wander Moominvalley with your heart open and your steps light. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_3_opt_c.png?t=1709917468"><h2 class="bb_tag">A CAST OF WONDERFULLY WHIMSICAL CHARACTERS</h2><br/>Get to know a diverse cast of characters with strong yet whimsical personalities, depth, and complexity. Embark on a journey to not only find the cause of the hideous parks but to also discover and interact with the charming Moominvalley inhabitants.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_4_opt_c.gif?t=1709917468"><h2 class="bb_tag">A MUSICAL ADVENTURE</h2><br/>Explore a host of locations where the sun dips below the horizon, casting a warm amber glow across the meadows; where the scent of wildflowers mingles with the crisp breeze, carrying promises of untold stories and hidden wonders; and where you as Snufkin - with your hat pulled low and harmonica in hand - head out. Gain inspiration by exploring Moominvalley and by solving puzzles.<br/><br/>Main features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Set out on a cozy, story-rich adventure game in a gorgeous storybook art style <br/></li><li> Get the strict Park Keeper and his horrible parks out of Moominvalley with the help of your trusty harmonica, a bit of stealth, and the friends you’ll meet along the way<br/></li><li> Meet over 50 charming characters and creatures calling Moominvalley their home<br/></li><li> Experience narrative gameplay and a myriad of charming stories and quests involving the beloved characters inspired by Tove Jansson’s work<br/></li><li> Explore Moominvalley’s open world and solve musical and environmental puzzles along the way to uncover the happenings in the valley<br/></li><li> Immerse yourself in the beautiful soundscape of music and melodies composed in collaboration with Sigur Rós</li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.snufkin.game%2Fdiscord" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_Discord_c.png?t=1709917468"/></a><br/><br/>© Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley. Developed by Hyper Games. Published by Raw Fury AB. © Moomin Characters ™						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Storm Shadow:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802380/Heavy_Storm_ShadowPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FwmfaDVPKSa" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/dss.png?t=1710177558"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Differences between the prologue and the full version<br/>The prologue opens up a character<br/>The prologue opens up a map</strong><br/><br/><strong>Unlock the true potential of your mech and witness its constant growth and upgrades! In deserts, ice and even satellites, kill thousands of swarms to strengthen your mech!<br/>At the end of each battle you will gain valuable resources to upgrade your mech's weapons and armor, unlocking new skills and powerful equipment.<br/>Through battles, you'll gain the bonds of your mech's pilots, forming modules in different directions to shape your unique fighting style.<br/>Grow and upgrade your mech in real time to make it more and more invincible and become the ultimate weapon against the swarm!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong>Monsters are coming at you like wave after wave, and as your mech's guns move, the monsters explode into a fog of blood and fall in pieces, painting the earth in scarlet. Operate your mech to dodge attacks, kill through the siege, and find a way to survive among hundreds of enemies!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong>Explore your own powerful combat combo by unlocking more and more powerful weapons and skills! Become stronger by killing and choosing, picking up resources, choosing the most suitable enhancements, and finally killing the terrifying bosses head-on!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3Z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong> offers a rich arsenal of multiple primary and secondary weapons, as well as numerous skills with unique features. These weapons and skills will provide endless possibilities for your battles. In the future, there will be even more powerful mechs waiting to be harnessed by you! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong>The game already offers 3 challenging maps, each with unique enemy combinations and powerful bosses waiting to be challenged for a completely different leveling experience. As the game continues to update, you will meet more new maps and new modes of play to make your Meat Pigeon adventure even more colorful. </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thaumaturge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684350/The_Thaumaturge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Thaumaturge_accolade_616x320_steam.png?t=1709742147"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/TT_claim_EN_small.png?t=1709742147"><br/><strong>The Thaumaturge is an isometric, story-rich RPG with a unique take on turn-based combat, character development features, and investigation mechanics</strong>, facing you with morally ambiguous choices – set in a world teeming with mysterious powers and strange ethereal beings called <strong>salutors</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/City_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>The year is 1905. Warsaw lives under the yoke of imperial Russian tsardom. Its inhabitants constitute a diverse group of different ancestries, views, and beliefs with often conflicting interests: Russian soldiers, Jewish merchants, Polish townspeople, and more. Despite the circumstances, the city is a buzzing metropolis, where one can attend a breathtaking party with the high society, and later get robbed in one of the dark alleys of the Praga district. A city of great hopes and dreams on one hand and dark desires on the other.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Buka_2.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>A <strong>thaumaturge</strong> bears both a gift and a burden at the same time. This parallel holds true for <strong>Wiktor Szulski</strong>, the game’s titular protagonist, who is drawn back to the tumultuous streets of 20th-century Warsaw by family matters. The gift of thaumaturgy is intertwined with family legacy, passed down through one's ancestors. This mystical inheritance significantly shapes Wiktor’s life journey tied around a pursuit of unearthly entities and their hosts. As only a thaumaturge can tame these ethereal entities - known to a select few as <strong>salutors</strong> - utilizing their mystical abilities to discover secrets hidden within the human soul and speak to the Darkness, no one understands quite like Wiktor how everyone suffers their own demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Wiktor_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Shape your story</strong> – as a full-fledged RPG, it allows you to alternate your choices and make you deal with the aftermath. <br/></li><li><strong>Develop your character</strong> – creating your own version of the thaumaturge will allow you to approach situations in different ways. <br/></li><li><strong>Experience unique turn-based combat</strong> and defeat your foes using human attacks and skills as well as psychic strikes delivered by salutors.<br/></li><li><strong>Influence and manipulate</strong> the temperaments of other characters to bend their will to your liking. <br/></li><li><strong>Tame the power of salutors</strong> – use the unique set of their skills to gain an advantage while exploring the world and when bringing your adversaries to their knees. <br/></li><li><strong>See the world that’s inevitably gone</strong> – explore the uncommon, heavily researched historic period of the early XX century Warsaw, where crime and luxury are often two sides of the same coin. Meet historical figures and learn about their involvement in the story. <br/></li><li><strong>Created in Unreal Engine 5</strong> to deliver a detailed &amp; beautifully crafted world.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1709230702"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1709723687"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1709723687"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709723687"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709723687"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1709278523"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Dino Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_12" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🦖🐾 WELCOME TO 100 DINO CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🦕🐈</h2>🦎 Join the cutest adventure in the Dino park with Cats and Dinos! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of dinosaurs location and dino-cats as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x200.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Dino Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Extra.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816050/100_Dino_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815630/100_Dino_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x1.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solium Infernum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1893810/Solium_Infernum/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for Solium Infernum, the grand strategy game of politics, intrigue and betrayal, set in the ultimate arena of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingDarkSide2.gif?t=1709962908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_IndulgeYourDarkSide_eng.png?t=1709962908"><br/>Satan's mysteriously vanished and Hell is in an uproar. Play as one of eight all-powerful and menacing Archfiends and indulge your Machiavellian dark side. Command legions, enlist champions, cast sinister rituals, and trick, rob, and insult your rivals to be crowned Hell’s new Dark Majesty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingStrategy2.gif?t=1709962908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_StrategyFromHell_eng.png?t=1709962908"><br/>Experience Solium Infernum's legendary devilish political machinations. Requiring nerves of steel and a true heart of darkness, every order you give will have lasting consequences. Get into the minds of your rivals, second-guessing their every move both on the map and on the floor of Hell’s parliament as you sling insults and demands in the only truly political strategy game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Eight playable Archfiends<br/></li><li>Eight single-player Chronicles<br/></li><li>Single-player Skirmish mode<br/></li><li>Revelations Tutorial Scenario<br/></li><li>Sessional and Asynchronous 2-6 player Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Dozens of Infernal Legions, including unique enormous Titans. <br/></li><li>Champion Praetors and dark Artifacts fit for any Archfiend!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingMulitplayer.gif?t=1709962908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_InfernalMultiplayer_eng.png?t=1709962908"><br/>Play 2-6 player multiplayer games with your soon-to-be ex-friends in a single session of deceit and politics, or put your friendships to the test in quick daily bursts with Solium Infernum’s infamous asynchronous multiplayer for a truly harrowing scheme-in-your-sleep experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/Heading_DarkArt2.gif?t=1709962908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_DivineMadness_eng.png?t=1709962908"><br/>If you love dark art, you’re in the right place. Brimming with striking visions of Hell unlike anything you’ve seen before, Solium Infernum is an infernal feast for the eyes with multitudes of individual dark paintings to enjoy. Every item of the game is accompanied by mind-blasting artwork, a feat declaring Solium Infernum a winner of the 2022 Game Makers Sketchbook.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingRessurect.gif?t=1709962908"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_CultClassic_eng.png?t=1709962908"><br/>Originally inspired by Milton’s epic poem, Paradise Lost, League of Geeks’ (known for seminal digital board game Armello) sophomore title is a re-imagining and modernisation of Vic Davis’ critically acclaimed cult-classic of the same name, hailed as a masterpiece of strategy game design. <br/><br/>Once again, prepare to lose yourself within ‘the cold glory of a difficult decision’ as we resurrect Solium Infernum from the depths of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/label_praise.png?t=1709962908"><br/>Note: The following quotes refer to the original Solium Infernum (2009) by Vic Davis.<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum is a political wargame set in hell… The game is now finished, and none of the friends survived. By which I mean, we all hate each other now.”</i> <br/>- Rock Paper Shotgun<br/><br/><i>“It’s a game about playing other people, in both senses of the word…. This is game design based on psychology as much as rules.” </i><br/>- Quarter to Three<br/><br/><i>“More than any game I've played in years, Solium Infernum nails the sensation of staring at a screen and losing yourself in the cold glory of a difficult decision.”</i><br/>- Game Developer (formerly Gamasutra)<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum kicked my knees out from under me ... this game took my past experience with strategy games and threw it, like a pro basketball player, into a bin eighty feet away.”</i><br/>- Eurogamer<br/><br/><i>“One of the best games of the year.”</i><br/>— Three Moves Ahead<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_toReign.png?t=1709962908"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Civilizations</h2>We are developing tech trees for multiple civilizations, which will include armor, weapons, buildings, crafting stations, and more. Greece, Persia, Rome, and Egypt will be added, with Greece and Persia scheduled to make their debut in 2024.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/多文明时代，即将来临！.gif?t=1709782498"><h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1709782498"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/2【替换Gif】自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1709782498"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1709782498"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/4【替换Gif】史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1709782498"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1709782498"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/6【替换Gif】传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1709782498"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1709782498"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exanimum: The Silent Call</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2601030/Exanimum_The_Silent_Call/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2601030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Exanimum: The Silent Call - It is a first-person indie psychological horror game.<br/><br/>The terrifying and bizzare events that happened to Jason and his daughter Jessica on the road to Greenfield town are dragging them into this eerie adventure, leading them into an unknown world. As Jason and Jessica venture deeper into the depths of the forest, an unsettling silence envelops their surroundings, the birds cease their songs, the fog thickens, and the rain intensifies. However, fear is silently approaching with every step they take, relentlessly pursuing them.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2601030/extras/ETSC.gif?t=1710179723"><br/><br/>Creepy Atmosphere: The game immerses players in a creepy atmosphere by drawing them into dark areas with realistic sound effects and graphics.<br/><br/>Psychological Tension: Players experience tension-filled moments in a journey filled with terrifying secrets and threats.<br/><br/>Fear could be approaching at any moment, providing players with constant suspense.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Transmute</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1191660/Rebel_Transmute/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/Rebel_Transmute_Logo_Decorated_Steam.png?t=1710176486"><br/><br/>In this modern metroidvania you play as Moon Mikono, a space scrapper turned adventurer on a mission to uncover the true fate of her missing mother.<br/><br/>To accomplish this mission in your own, unique way you'll be swapping out game changing augments to suit your playstyle.  Aggressive and greedy?  Inquisitive and cautious?  Maybe you just want an army of friendly creatures!  With over 50 unique upgrades, Rebel Transmute allows you to play through a classic sci-fi adventure in YOUR style.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHALLENGING AND CUSTOMIZABLE COMBAT</h2>Use a variety of spells known as Bloodcasts, your trusty Foray-issued Blaster, and a variety of game changing Augments to take on a world of dangerous creatures and space travelers.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/16.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE AND MAP A VIBRANT SCI-FI WORLD</h2>The sprawling world of Rebel Transmute is full of stunning vistas: From vibrant greenery in the Overgrowth, to the fluorescent reefs of the Coral Fissure, to the sparkblood crystal-strewn Surface.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/09.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">Additional Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Encounter over <strong>80 unique enemies</strong> and over <strong>10 formidable bosses</strong>! From mutated worms and electrified beasts, to rogue AI's and gigantic bugs. All offering different and exciting challenges and interactions.<br/></li><li>Discover <strong>game-changing abilities</strong> hidden throughout the outpost.  Spin Bash, Wall Jump, and Void Dash your way across an interconnected network of tunnels, caverns, and research laboratories!<br/></li><li>Augment your playstyle with <strong>48 optional upgrades</strong> that can drastically change how you play the game.  Fight alongside a reprogrammed drone, twist your attacks into spiraling laser blasts, or even summon tentacles to block projectiles!<br/></li><li>Make use of a versatile mapping system to help track your progress.  Use custom markers, track your completion percentage, and find hidden terminals to uncover unexplored areas.<br/></li><li>Experience a <strong>personal and heartfelt story</strong>. As Moon searches for her mother she’ll also encounter various robot life, all with their own stories, personalities, and quests.<br/></li><li>A <strong>hand-painted pixel art</strong> aesthetic lends each and every character, enemy, and sector a personal touch.<br/></li><li>An immersive and atmospheric score, crafted to perfectly match every moment, from bombastic fights to solemn exploration.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 13: Taxidermy Trails</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2492740/Project_13_Taxidermy_Trails/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2492740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Project 13: Taxidermy Trails, a Walking Simulator set in a mesmerizing Taxidermy Museum. In this immersive experience, you assume the role of an kidnapped Probant forced to find a way to escape. Complete all 13 Walks to get out of this Nightmare.<br>
<br>
Your mission is clear: report any anomalies you encounter during your walks. But beware, a single misstep means starting over. Only by consistently reporting accurately will lead to the real Exit.<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
Repeating Museum Corridor: Explore a hauntingly repetitive environment, where each step could lead to discovery or deception amidst the eerie displays of taxidermy.<br>
<br/>
Over 35 Anomalies: Uncover the secrets hidden within the museum as you encounter over 35 unique anomalies. Stay very vigilant, as every detail holds significance.<br/>
<br/>
Confirmation After Each Walk: After each walk, confirm whether you experienced any anomalies. Your precision determines your progress.<br/>
<br/>
Escape on the 13th Walk: Success lies in your ability to navigate the corridors and accurately report anomalies. Reach the 13th walk unscathed, and you may find the exit.<br/>
<br/>
Variable Duration: The duration of your expedition is unpredictable, ranging from 40 minutes to "a lot longer." Sharpen your senses and hone your observation skills to expedite your journey.<br/>
<br/>
Embark on this surreal adventure where reality blurs, and your choices shape your destiny. Are you prepared to unravel the mysteries of Project 13: Taxidermy Trails and overcome the challenges that lie ahead? The museum corridors await – enter if you dare						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnGaCho Dreamy Butterfly</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810380/EnGaCho_Dreamy_Butterfly/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"EnGaCho" is an arcade-style  side-scrolling action game where you advance while defeating enemies and earning money.<br/>The main character "EnGaCho'' goes on a journey to defeat the evil nouveau riche and help the people who are suffering from poverty...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/extras/Dotto.png?t=1710173857"><h2 class="bb_tag">When you are in trouble, money will solve the problem!</h2>EnGaCho's journey will be tough. You should use the money you earn to power up EnGaCho.<br/>It is up to the player to decide whether to be aggressive or focus on durability.<h2 class="bb_tag">100 stages in total!</h2>However, that doesn't mean you have to clear everything. There are many warp zones within the stages.<br/>You can attack the final boss using the shortest route, or you can work hard to earn a score. Again, it's up to the player.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/extras/Dotto2.png?t=1710173857"><h2 class="bb_tag">tips</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Don't miss the power-up items scattered throughout the stage.<br/></li><li>Once you cleared a stage, you can play it as much as you like in Practice mode.<br/></li><li>If you save money instead of spending it, you can get more money and score.<br/></li><li>Also check out the SHOP on the title scene.<br/></li><li>Boss battles should be fought with proper countermeasures.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/extras/Dotto3.png?t=1710173857"><br/><br/>Make full use of all options and grab glory!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH ALL - MOUSES</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2853610/SEARCH_ALL__MOUSES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2853610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SEARCH ALL - MOUSES</h2> is a hidden object game in which you need to find all the mice in a large location. The mice will be located in a variety of places, from the most prominent to barely noticeable places. The entire game location looks lively because of the animation elements. Find all the mice! Don't let them go unnoticed :)<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/>- Animation elements on location;<br/>- 100 mice to find;<br/>- Pleasant soundtrack;<br/>- The gameplay can be interrupted at any time, and the game will automatically save the result;<br/>- Implemented hints! If you find it difficult to find an item, use the hint!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Backrooms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1085680/True_Backrooms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1085680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The most accurate depiction of the backrooms.</strong><br/><br/>Wander an ever growing maze in this horror themed walking simulator. Try to escape before you succumb to madness or before any monsters notice you. You might not be alone. Game length varies wildly dependent on the player, but most can expect a 20-40 minute horror experience.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/>Cool retro graphics.<br/>4:3 aspect ratio.<br/>General controller support.<br/>Unique Scares.<br/>A huge labyrinthine plane of existence.<br/><br/>Too many games miss the mark when it comes to recreating the backrooms. It should be about getting lost, losing hope, and going insane from the monotony. So I have created it. Can you reach the end of the backrooms?<br/><br/><strong>Warning: This game is designed to make you experience insanity, player discretion is advised, and the game contains some flashing lights.</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Empire</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1449550/Chinese_Empire/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1813230/Wild_West_Builder/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1813230/Wild_West_Builder/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/addtowishlist_gif.gif?t=1710168458"><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FC5KpZ9AEex" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/discord.png?t=1710168458"/></a><br/><br/>Become the Chinese emperor and build your own, great empire! Put more developed buildings up using accessible raw materials. Plan carefully each path and buildings arrangement. Build your own great empire and make new history!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/1.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>BUILDING</strong><br/>The key to creating an economically strong empire is the skillful placement of individual buildings. Plan the location of each of them well and you will certainly use their potential effectively. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/2.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>CROPS</strong><br/>For centuries, cultivation in China has been an extremely important part of the economy. Make the best of what the local areas have to offer!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/3.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>DEVELOPMENT</strong><br/>Starting from a small village, expand your empire to colossal dimensions! Over time, build new buildings available, all the time taking care of not only economic development, but also cultural development.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/5.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>DYNAMIC LIGHTING</strong><br/>The entire production has been dressed in a realistic graphic design to reflect the charms of the lands in which we will be building our empire as much as possible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/4.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>ROAD SYSTEM</strong><br/>Thanks to a well-planned network of roads, residents will move faster, which will increase the efficiency of your economy and help keep your empire in order.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats of the Ming Dynasty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2854690/Cats_of_the_Ming_Dynasty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to "The Cats of the Ming Dynasty," a delightful game of finding cats. Set against the backdrop of "Along the River During the Qingming Festival," a vibrant genre painting by Qiu Ying, a Ming Dynasty Chinese painter, the game incorporates 600 hand-drawn cats, creating interesting interactions between the cats and historical scenes and characters.<br/><br/>-----Game Features-----<br/><br/>- Relax and enjoy ancient artworks.<br/>- 6 different scenic scenarios.<br/>- 600 adorable hand-drawn cats.<br/>- Comforting and relaxing music.<br/>- Cute cat sound effects.<br/>- Clicking on the game name on the cover allows you to view the complete "Along the River During the Qingming Festival."<br/>- 100 carefully crafted achievement icons.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854690/extras/1.png?t=1710166609">.<br/><br/>------------------------						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece Link</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690960/Piece_Link/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Drag and Connect the Pieces!</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690960/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif.gif?t=1710165404"><br/><br/>Piece Link is a puzzle game that involves arranging blocks of various shapes to fill a playing field. The main objective of the game is to fit the blocks into a designated square so that all the blocks are used and there are no empty spaces. This requires strategic placement of the differently shaped pieces into a grid, aiming to form a complete square without any holes. The game is designed to be both entertaining and educational, challenging players' problem-solving skills and spatial reasoning.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUSFASLEX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2769380/JUSFASLEX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2769380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							13 years ago, a man named Joann decided he would bring God back into our world. He couldn't succeed, but his idea lives on through Theodore, an aloof dreamer who's trying to create a utopian society in a new world.<br/><br/>JUSFASLEX is a story about a boy's struggle to stay himself and get along with the new inhabitants of his dimension: Emma, a spirited redhead older than him, and Rebecca, a charming, reserved girl who likes being alone just like him.<br/><br/><strong>Game features:</strong><br/>- Short kinetic story<br/>- The atmosphere of a Victorian manor house<br/>- Ukrainian voice acting						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Road of Heroes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2724960/The_Road_of_Heroes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Hero's Path, a concise hero development system. Every battle offers a unique character development opportunity. With attribute points in hand, you can freely decide which attribute to enhance. With skill points available, you have the freedom to choose which skill to learn or improve.<br/><br/>Skill System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage1.png?t=1710160933"><br/>You are free to decide which skill to prioritize learning or which abilities to enhance when upgrading skills.<br/><br/>Attribute System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage2.png?t=1710160933"><br/>The attribute column on the right allows you to freely choose which attribute to enhance when you have attribute points.<br/><br/>Shop System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage3.png?t=1710160933"><br/>After obtaining gold during battles, you can purchase beneficial BUFFs at the Pig Merchant.<br/><br/>Equipment Crafting System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage4.png?t=1710160933"><br/>When you are in battle, you will obtain 'Molds,' 'Materials,' and 'BOSS Drop Materials.' Only when you have all three types of materials can you craft equipment. Each material has different attributes, and crafting equipment will combine the attributes of the three materials into one piece of equipment.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage5.png?t=1710160933"><br/><br/>Equipment System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage6.png?t=1710160933"><br/>When you craft and equip gear, the attributes of the equipment take effect in the combat scenes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FROM ASHES, BLOOM</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2335130/FROM_ASHES_BLOOM/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335130/extras/fab_gameplay.png?t=1710160338"><br/><br/>🌵 <strong>Protect</strong> the oldest tree on Earth from Humanity<br/>🍀 <strong>Tear</strong> through hordes of enemies<br/>🌷 <strong>Sow</strong> trees to help you<br/>🌴 <strong>Active</strong> Tower Defense rogue-like gameplay<br/>🌻 <strong>Personalize</strong> your creature with new attacks<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335130/extras/fab_features.png?t=1710160338"><br/><br/>🌿 <strong>Huge</strong> amount of upgrades<br/>🏭 <strong>Various</strong> of starting situation with unique skins<br/>👾 A never seen before character with <strong>10/10 procedural animation</strong><br/>😇 Play as an <strong>invincible</strong> mass destruction weapon						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTRL Phreak</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1679360/CTRL_Phreak/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1679360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore a vast network of stolen data, encrypted chatrooms, and backdoor connections as you traverse a shrouded corner of the web only the most elite hackers are able to access. At the end of it all lies The Mainframe, the highest security target known to hacker-kind. You will play as a scrappy hacker penetrating the Deep Web in search of The Mainframe.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1679360/extras/NodeNetNav.gif?t=1710159105"><br/><br/>Grow more powerful to become the LEET H4X0R you were always meant to be: download RAM, discover Keywords, and buy upgrades from the shadowy hacker known as "D34L3R". Fight elite hacker bosses to reach Access Points to deeper levels of the Web.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1679360/extras/Boss.gif?t=1710159105"><br/><br/>Engage in high-octane, keyboard-mashing, hacker-to-hacker combat. Make choices that matter via a retro cyber terminal interface. Can you reach the bottom of the Internet and achieve immortal hacker glory?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1679360/extras/TerminalChatter.gif?t=1710159105"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboSync</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2761130/RoboSync/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/withlist-follow.gif?t=1710161592"> <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FAdZF7EAUC6" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/Join_our_discord.png?t=1710161592"/></a><br/>RoboSync is an immersive puzzle game that puts your logical thinking skills and precision to the test.<br/><br/>In each level, you'll find robots moving in unsynchronized patterns. Your mission? Time the release and blockage of passages just right, coordinating your robots' movements to unlock all the locks simultaneously. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/clip_lvl2-shorter.gif?t=1710161592"><br/><br/>It's crucial to carefully consider every move, executing commands precisely to achieve flawless synchronization. With progressively challenging levels, the game introduces new mechanics to keep the experience engaging.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/Clip_lvl6.gif?t=1710161592"><br/><br/>Solve the challenges swiftly to earn the coveted 3 stars and attain impeccable synchronization for a special medal in each level. Get ready for an exhilarating journey where your mental agility will be constantly challenged."<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/clip_lvl14.gif?t=1710161592"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2689880/Cyber_Story/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							CyberStory is a cyberbullying intervention game designed to empower players with effective coping strategies. Set in a digital landscape, players navigate challenging scenarios and situations, gaining insights into the complexities of cyberbullying. Through interactive narratives, engaging challenges, and decision-making scenarios, CyberStory provides a safe and supportive environment for players to enhance their coping skills.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Shooter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2843970/Monster_Shooter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2843970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an epic intergalactic battle in "Monster Shooter." This thrilling third-person shooter immerses you in the role of humanity's last hope. Face off against the Roncosferas, voracious aliens originating from the distant planet Ronclumen, on a critical mission to protect the military base and precious resources of the planet Hoperium.<br>
<br>
Take control of a brave space soldier, armed to the teeth with advanced technology. Face endless waves of enemies in a fight for survival, using strategy, skill and an impressive arsenal. Every point adds up in your quest to defend every vital part of the facility, as humanity waits with hope in the balance.<br>
<br>
 The destiny of humanity is in your hands. Accept the challenge, become the last line of defense and defend the future of civilization against the relentless Roncospheres. The planet is counting on you!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screen Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827410/Screen_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
<strong>This screen effect program is a software that provides a visually unique and exciting experience.</strong><br/>These programs use graphic elements to provide a visually appealing experience for users.<br/><br/>Following features are supporting now:<br/>1. Twinkle Visual Effect<br/>2. Fire Visual Effect<br/>3. Impact Visual Effect (with Click)<br/>4. 3D sphere Test						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yumpgril</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2835610/Yumpgril/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2835610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Yumpgril is a challenging precision platformer also known as a rage game. Inspired by various rage games that came before Yumpgril is designed to be brutally difficult and punishing.<br>
<br>
*Brutally difficult<br>
*Simple mechanics<br>
*No hand-holding<br>
*No checkpoints<br>
*Very punishing						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suramon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2721300/Suramon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2721300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Explore an open world filled with wild slime monsters. Battle slimes to capture their DNA in cubes, use them for crafting along your adventure. Return home and expand your farm. Plant crops and earn precious gold. Meet the locals and befriend them, giving gifts to earn their love. This is Suramon.</strong><br/><br/>This genre-blending game puts a focus on capturing Slime Cubes, rather than the monsters themselves in typical monster capture games. After inheriting a farm from your uncle and moving to a mysterious valley, the player discovers a world that is filled with colorful slime creatures called Suramon. These creatures roam free and play a part in the day-to-day life in this world. Players will run their farm and try to make a living while exploring the region and fighting the 100 different breeds of slime monsters that wander the land. Each slain Suramon drops a Suramon Cube: a highly sought after element. Each Cube is made up of the organic slime material for each slime, and will differ in color and style to the creature it comes from.<br/><br/>Once the player becomes a Suramon Scout, they will be tasked with collecting the different Cubes for a research lab so they can be used for further scientific discoveries. They will also be tasked with filling their SuraDex: an encyclopedia of all the Suramon that call the region home. Players will quickly learn of a mysterious and shadowy organization called Fuchsia Corp. An organization that wants to capture all of the Suramon for themselves, and use them for devastating purposes. Can the player stop them before it's too late?<br/><br/>Explore a vibrant world filled with colorful slime creatures and colorful villagers who want to get to know you. Battle the Suramon slime monsters and collect Cubes. Grow your farm and renovate your farmhouse. Befriend and gift the local villagers to grow your friendship with them. Fall in love with different romance options and get married. And don't forget to eat and drink to survive! The world of Suramon awaits.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore a large open world.<br/></li><li>Capture slime cubes from monsters and use them to craft.<br/></li><li>Plant seeds, water crops, and pick them when they are ready.<br/></li><li>Time system with passing time and color change as the day passes.<br/></li><li>Mining system with a button mash mini-game. Mine for gold, jewels, and more.<br/></li><li>Play 3 different mini-games in the casino including slots and card games. <br/></li><li>Solve a conspiracy and stop an evil threat.<br/></li><li>Peaceful and soothing soundtrack with a medieval flare.<br/></li><li>Form relationships with NPCs and give them gifts.<br/></li><li>Romance NPCs and get married.<br/></li><li>Expand and renovate your farm, unlocking new equipment.<br/></li><li>Sandbox style gameplay with freedom to explore as you wish.<br/></li><li>Steam Deck support.<br/></li><li>Steam cloud save support.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antipaint</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1418390/Antipaint/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A Paint-tastic Adventure!</h2><strong>Embark on a quest to become the greatest artist in the world.</strong><br/>The battlefield is your canvas, the enemies are your paint. Literally. The art you make is yours to keep.<h2 class="bb_tag">Paint or Slay Your Way</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/extras/brush_previews.gif?t=1710144089"><br/>Choose from a variety of brushes and characters. From a slow and steady thick brush to a quick and nimble paint roller - we've got you covered.<h2 class="bb_tag">Even The Best Painter Needs A Helping Hand</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/extras/item_previews.gif?t=1710144089"><br/>Finishing a painting rewards you with versatile items. Enlist the help of a friendly painting bucket, install some paint turrets, give your enemies moustaches or become a robot. Find a way to express your true self!<h2 class="bb_tag">Face The Great Works Of Art</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/extras/boss_preview.png?t=1710144089"><br/>You can't be the greatest if there's other art out there. You'll have to defeat various (and dubious) works of art to secure your title.<h2 class="bb_tag">Art to Remember</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/extras/Gallery_Final.gif?t=1710144089"><br/>After the paint has settled and the brushes are cleaned, why not take a step back and admire your masterpieces in the gallery.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of a Wish</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2302080/Death_of_a_Wish/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/DeathWishHeader.gif?t=1710183750"><br/><strong>Death of a Wish</strong> is a vicious action-RPG where <strong>style is salvation</strong>. <br/><br/>Play as Christian as he unites with new comrades to challenge the cult that raised him. By taking down the four Sanctum Faiths: Father, Sister, Cardinal, and Priest, they will upend the order of the world.<br/><br/>Fight your way through a nightmare filled with horrifying monsters and terrifying people. Master brutal attacks and flashy combos as you struggle against the Corruption consuming you with style and grace. Shine your light in this surreal sea of darkness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/keydetails2.png?t=1710183750"><h2 class="bb_tag">ENGAGE IN VICIOUSLY GRACEFUL COMBAT</h2>Unleash Christian’s cursed powers in a demanding and rewarding combat system. Be careful not to succumb to the ever-encroaching Corruption; achieve high ranks in combat and perform graceful combos to hold the Corruption at bay.<h2 class="bb_tag">CUSTOMIZE YOUR MARKED POWERS</h2>Rend your foes asunder with magical combos called Arias. Enhance your abilities with powerful Virtues that alter your approach to battle and the rhythm of combat. With a limitless array of ways to fight stylishly, build your character with passion to destroy your foes.<h2 class="bb_tag">DESCEND INTO THE NIGHTMARE</h2>In the dreamworld of Paradiso, repressed memories and unspeakable feelings come to life as the nightmarish city of Neo-Sanctum. Delve into the secret underworld of the esoteric and abandoned to meet new comrades who will aid you on your journey.<h2 class="bb_tag">SURREAL AND SPECTACULAR</h2>Christian’s world is rendered with a surreal aesthetic like no other. Harsh, pulsating scratches upon a sea of darkness render a thick atmosphere brooding with emotion. Battles come to life in an animated spectacle of light and motion that remains easy to parse in play. <br/><br/>For audio, Nicolo Telesca’s chilling score mixes electronic sounds with live instrumentation and complements the visuals by eliciting feelings of tense anxiety and electrifying catharsis.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/discord2.png?t=1710183750"><br/>Join the official Discord at <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FvJ7JnsAMcK" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/vJ7JnsAMcK</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/ezgif-4-1c4b73cf2b.gif?t=1710183750"><br/><br/><i>Game contains imagery that may be harmful to players with photosensitive epilepsy or similar conditions. See content warnings below. </i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paragon Pioneers 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2454420/Paragon_Pioneers_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2454420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>» Embark on a Grand Adventure with Paragon Pioneers 2! «</strong></h2>Dive into the captivating world of <strong>Paragon Pioneers 2</strong>, an engaging <strong>city-building idle game</strong> filled with extensive content promising months of immersive gameplay. Discover and conquer customizable islands, carefully shaping your empire to satisfy the needs of your citizens. <strong>Even with limited playtime</strong>, you can delve deep into this simulation, experimenting with various strategies to enhance your realm. Build a magnificent palace and establish your legacy as the most renowned leader in Paragon's history!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>» What Can You Expect? «</strong></h2><strong>BUILD</strong> your empire with over 300 diverse buildings.<br/><strong>PRODUCE</strong> more than 130 goods with intricate production chains.<br/><strong>RESEARCH</strong> over 200 unique perks to tailor your playstyle.<br/><strong>EXPLORE</strong> three distinct regions, each offering unique challenges.<br/><strong>CONQUER</strong> islands using an intuitive and multifaceted combat system.<br/><strong>IMMERSE</strong> yourself in easy-to-learn gameplay, free from ads and online requirements.<br/><strong>RELAX</strong> knowing your empire grows, even when you're not actively playing.<br/><strong>OBSERVE</strong> your scurrying inhabitants in a charming medieval/fantasy world.<br/><strong>SHAPE</strong> every island with a unique map generator to suit your needs.<br/><strong>ADAPT</strong> the game’s difficulty to your preferred play style.<br/><strong>ENJOY</strong> extensive replayability with powerful custodians that grant unique abilities.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>» What’s New in the Sequel? «</strong></h2><strong>NEW MAJOR FEATURES</strong> – Introducing a diverse research system featuring over 200 unique perks that significantly influence gameplay. Explore three distinct regions, each with its own mechanics and exclusive production chains. Tailor your adventure with customizable difficulty levels.<br/><br/><strong>DOUBLE THE CONTENT</strong> – Your islands now have rivers and you can build water mills. Encounter more than double the number of buildings, goods, and units than before. Delve into even more complex production chains for optimization. Boost your crop and livestock production with support buildings as technology advances.<br/><br/><strong>GRAPHICAL OVERHAUL</strong> – Witness the scurrying activity of inhabitants transporting goods and ships docking at islands, all enhanced by dynamic water visuals and more vivid graphics.<br/><br/><strong>IMPROVED INTERFACE</strong> – The menu structure has been refined, and additional shortcuts introduced, ensuring seamless navigation. Trading routes have also been simplified, making their management more intuitive than ever.<br/><br/><strong>ENHANCED PRESTIGE MECHANIC</strong> – Construct your palaces more progressively with new challenges and a focus on long-term happiness of your inhabitants. A new reputation system offers greater freedom in custodian selections.<br/><br/><strong>AND MUCH MORE</strong> – Enjoy numerous quality of life improvements inspired by the awesome Discord community for a smoother gameplay experience. Expect enhanced stability, more device adjustment options and much more…<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>» Thank you for playing Paragon Pioneers 2! «</strong> ❤️</h2>My passion project <strong>Paragon Pioneers 2</strong> is very special for me as it continues my dream of being a game developer. It makes me really happy when my creations bring joy to others and I invite you to join this journey and share your experiences with me :)<br/><br/>Happy Building!<br/><br/>👋 Tobias						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reversi Temple</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2855830/Reversi_Temple/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the original Reversi game or play with the Othello starting positions in this highly-acclaimed strategy board game. The rules are simple, but the game is hard to master.<br/><br/>Reversi a strategy board game that involves two players, played on an 8×8 uncheckered board. Play against an AI player with 3 levels of difficulty (Easy, Medium, Hard).<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855830/extras/reversi-gameplay.gif?t=1710140431"><br/><br/>Enjoy the charms of LoFi music whilst you play in various temple-like locations.<br/><br/>Be able to create a giant board to play on, or maticuliously place pieces to roleplay matches or end games.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855830/extras/reversi-zoom-out.gif?t=1710140431"><br/><br/>Play 2 player local multiplayer with your friends or family. Rather than setting up a physical board, quickly play on your computer with Reversi Temple.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Shadow</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789280/My_Shadow/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Mind can sometimes be too imaginative. While you tuck yourself into your bed and turn the lights off, the creatures of the night begin to appear. As you hide under your bedsheet, they surround you. As you begin to drift away, they take you, down, deep into the depths, of your mind...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789280/extras/SurroundingHands-ezgif.com-crop.gif?t=1710163289"><br/><br/>Welcome to the hauntingly surreal realm of My Shadow, a mesmerizing 2.5D Horror Puzzle Platformer that thrusts players into the enigmatic depths where reality and imagination intertwine. As the night descends, a mysterious world materializes, inviting you to embark on an otherworldly journey through the intricate labyrinth of your own mind. <br/><br/>Traverse the intricacies of the distorted dollhouse, solving puzzles that gradually unveil the truth about your innermost demons.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trash Horror Collection 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2846790/Trash_Horror_Collection_4/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/logo_page_steam_trash4.png?t=1710109556"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/c2.png?t=1710109556"><br/><br/>We present a true trash horror experience from the 80s, the golden age of VHS tapes. There are 7 short horror games inspired by the American series "Tales from the crypt", with cult horror and a touch of comedy.<br/><br/><strong>STORY MODE:</strong><br/><br/>Unlike the other collections, in this one we bring a "story mode", which brings together all 7 games in a new bizarre and bloody story.<br/>If you have already played a game, you can skip it and continue with the story mode.<br/><br/><strong>GAMES INCLUDED:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> DEER </li></ul>Samuell lives isolated in his house on the edge of a lake, his great passion is hunting deer. But he will realize that everything he sowed... he will reap now!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/deer02.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Poop Killer 7 </li></ul>A bathroom supply store owner will have to challenge the poop killer to survive. Facing deadly challenges to retrieve the infinite shit jewels.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/peRYlF.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Poop Killer 8 </li></ul>A few years after the Poop Killer's attack on a VHS tape rental store, shitting is officially prohibited.<br/>Alex is on his first night shift at the VHS store, he agreed to work over Christmas because he needed some extra money.<br/>After an inevitable mix-up, the feared poop killer dons a Santa suit for his shit attack.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/poop8_1.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hello, I came to kill you </li></ul>Lincoln is a single boy and decides to venture online and look for a girlfriend.Yes, he finds a beautiful girlfriend... crazy and psychotic.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/hello02.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Community </li></ul>Marky is a young man who is running from the police, he decides to move to an isolated place with few neighbors.<br/>After moving to a small community, he discovers that his new neighbors are not very normal.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/communitygif_01.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The lights went out </li></ul>Your car breaks down on an empty and dark road, you look for help... perhaps your only option is to knock on the door of a sinister house isolated from everything.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/thl.png?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Meat </li></ul>After his father's death, Jerry and his brother Cris take care of the restaurant that was their father's great passion. To prevent the restaurant from going bankrupt, they decide to do terrible things.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/meat2.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/c1.png?t=1710109556"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IIslands of War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1162470/IIslands_of_War/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fc3NQd47" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/discord.png?t=1710075461"/></a><br/><br/>Build and battle floating islands in the skies! Fly around the realms of a shattered world and interact with an assortment of islands and factions! Battle procedurally generated enemies, sometimes even more than one at a time!<h2 class="bb_tag">Build</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/editing_small.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>Build your powerful island from loads of blocks and attachments with the island editor. Place your blocks to form your base island, then load up on weapons, shields, reactors, batteries and so much more to try and give yourself the best advantage in combat. Assign weapons and modules to any keybind you desire, all configurable from the super easy to use editor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Fight</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/missile.gif?t=1710075461"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/mortar.gif?t=1710075461"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/laser.gif?t=1710075461"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/ramming.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>As the saying goes, there's more than one way to blow up a floating island! Take out all their floatrons to make them fall out of the sky or destroy their warp core and watch their island explode in a fiery inferno!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/warp_gate.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>Explore a vast realm, with factions, cities, and pirates! Find abandoned regions and grab some free loot, or a merchant with powerful items to sell! Encounter different enemy classes, with a variety of strengths and weaknesses! Every island is procedurally generated, so each encounter will be unique!<h2 class="bb_tag">Loot</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/loot_collection.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>Collect items to maximize your island's potential! Forge items together to upgrade them from the bronze tier to the crystal tier!  Every single item has the potential to be unique, and almost every property can be upgraded by tech. Infuse tech into items to give them cool buffs like damage penetration, increased health, or reduced cooldowns!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/items.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>With over 150 items, and with over 50 item properties and behaviors, the possibilities are endless!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soulmaze</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713430/Soulmaze/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help two poor soul mates apart by destiny find each other over the ages!<br>
Take control of two characters simultaneously and independently! Pick up all items and reunite the characters anywhere in the mazes. Do it as fast as you can so the poor souls can enjoy the rest of their lives together. The destiny will separate them in case they find each other before collet all items. The goal is make the characters meet as fast as possible after collecting all items.<br>
Soulmaze is inspired in the belief in soul mates exploring love definitions while challenge the ambidexterity and multitask skills of the player.<br>
The blue soul is controlled by the left thumb stick or by the WASD keys and the red soul is controlled by the right thumb stick or by the arrow keys. There are 50 mazes divided into 5 ages that progressively challenge the player. The reference times to move forward through the mazes demands the simultaneous control of the character! Get confused and have fun!						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOCK CONNECTOR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2737730/BLOCK_CONNECTOR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2737730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							BLOCK CONNECTOR is a casual game with a very simple rule: connect blocks of the same colour, so even people who are not good at puzzle games can easily start playing.<br>
<br>
We didn't use a game engine, but used our own library.<br>
<br>
No need to think too much, just simply match the colours and keep defeating the boss, the polyhedron!<br>
<br>
This is a slightly new puzzle game that retains the fun of existing dropout puzzles while adding its own originality, so you can play it with a fresh sensation.<br/>
<br/>
We hope it will help you pass the time!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Count Pumpcula</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1995930/Count_Pumpcula/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/UploadCustomImage_600x100.jpg?t=1710047796"><br/><br/>Embark on an exciting 2D-Metroidvania journey through the Eastern Archipelago of Lanthir Range! Along the way you’ll need to save the Sagelings from a dark curse in the forest of Orn, fight prehistoric creatures that were thought to be extinct, escape the beasts that lie within the Isle of Orad, and slide through the icy catacombs of Krakens Pass. In your down time, relax with charming new companions on the enchanting Island of Travellers Cove.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/UploadCustomImageCave2_600x100.jpg?t=1710047796"><h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag">About the creator</h2></h2><br/>Count Pumpcula is the passion-project of artist and self-taught Indie developer, Luke Edwards. Combining his love of gaming with his creativity, he has spent the past 3 years single-handedly developing every aspect of this game. Join the journey and immerse yourself in this amazing product of his imagination.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/UploadCustomImageForest_600x100.jpg?t=1710047796"><h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag">features</h2></h2></h2><br/>   - 2D-Metroidvania adventure through the Eastern Archipelago of Lanthir Range!<br/>   - Traditional, hand-drawn animations and environments.<br/>   - Challenging game-play and platforming.<br/>   - A world of ancient mysteries and lore that players can investigate.<br/>   - Explore the cursed forests, icy catacombs and prehistoric caves in search of secret areas.<br/>   - Feel the depth and immersion of the game with beautiful parallax effects.<br/>   - Meet new quirky and charismatic companions along the way.<br/>   - Purchase powerful new abilities on your adventure to grow stronger and open new paths.<br/>   - Character movement is fluid with mechanics like coyote time and precise jumping height.<br/>   - Strong attack abilities will leave enemies stunned in your path.<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag">the World Of Lanthir</h2></h2><br/>The Story of Count Pumpcula takes place in Eastern Archipelago of Lanthir Range. It currently consists of 7 main areas where you will have to dash, jump and fight to return to your Castle. Here are a few of the environments that you will be faced with:<br/><br/>Travellers Cove: A quiet, peaceful and magical island where the player can rest and relax with your fellow island companions.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/Cove.gif?t=1710047796"><br/><br/>Krakens Pass: Home to the cold-blooded creatures that live within Poseidon's dominion.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/KingPoseidon.gif?t=1710047796"><br/><br/>Ulunn Cave: An ancient underground area that has become entangled with the roots of the towering Forest of Orn.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/Rock1.gif?t=1710047796"><br/><br/>The Dark Woods: A misty landscape which consists of tall pine trees that tower over a small but friendly Inn.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/DarkWoods.gif?t=1710047796"><br/><br/>Isle of Orod: Rock beasts and blind bugs dwell under these dark and dusty mountains. The creatures that live here are as unforgiving as their sharp stalactite surroundings.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/Cave3.gif?t=1710047796"><br/><br/>Forest of Orn: A tree village that is home to the Sagelings. Although protectors of these lands, they too need help as a curse lies upon their forest...<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/Tree1Shoot.gif?t=1710047796"><br/><br/>Minas Gilath: A tall tower that ascends to the clouds and stars where only the purest of beings reside. None shall pass unless the Sage Knights deem you worthy.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/Tower.gif?t=1710047796"><h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag">Shop At Noon's Pub</h2></h2>Trade with the local barter and get flashy and fun new abilities that will help you progress in the game.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1995930/extras/Pub.gif?t=1710047796"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyvern Studios Solitaire: 30th Aniversary Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2853790/Wyvern_Studios_Solitaire_30th_Aniversary_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2853790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Wyvern Studios Solitaire: 30th Anniversary Edition</strong> is a tribute to the original game released in the 1990's by Wyvern Studios. It features both <u>Klondike Solitaire</u> and <u>Pyramid Solitaire</u>. It includes <u>9 different deck styles</u> to choose from and features joystick support for the full experience. The base game is offered for free and can be played as is without any cost forever. We plan to offer rulesets DLC with additional solitaire versions and content DLC with more fun deck styles that you can choose to purchase, or not. We will also be offering a Solitaire Construction Set DLC that will allow you to create and share hundreds of unique solitaire creations.<br/><br/>The 9 deck styles in the base game include three(3) traditional playing card decks and six(6) photo decks guaranteed to be "Family Friendly!"<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2853790/extras/Wyvern_Face_Card_Previews.png?t=1710043397"><br/>TRADITIONAL DECKS<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Traditional Face Cards<br/></li><li>Easy Read Alphanumeric Cards<br/></li><li>Wyvern Memories Face Cards</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2853790/extras/Wyvern_Photo_Deck_Previews.png?t=1710043397"><br/>FAMILY FRIENDLY PHOTO DECKS<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fireworks<br/></li><li>Fungi<br/></li><li>Insects<br/></li><li>Minerals &amp; Gems<br/></li><li>Natural Textures<br/></li><li>Space Exploration</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Weird Dream</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2532300/The_Weird_Dream/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2532300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Weird Dream is a 2D Metroidvania game set in the ruins of Alpha City. Control a mysterious bunny while confronting Alpha City’s mutated inhabitants. Level up your skills, and unravel the truth behind the City’s untimely destruction. The city holds many legends about the origin of a being only known as the Astral Lord, yet they all share a common detail: the Astral Lord answers sincere prayers and fulfills every desire.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Impeccably Tight Controls</strong> - Use a combination of in-game abilities, rhythm, and your own reflexes to traverse a skill-demanding world with controls that are easy to learn and less easy to master!<br/></li><li><strong>Flexible Character Building</strong> - Unlock and experiment with new abilities to forge your unique combat style via an adaptable rune system<br/></li><li><strong>Fragmented narratives</strong> - Uncover the dark secrets of this world by collecting monster profiles and story fragments<br/></li><li><strong>Exciting Boss Fights</strong> - Challenge over 40 bosses. Utilize your powerful abilities to overcome formidable foes and earn more-than-generous rewards<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2532300/extras/boss.gif?t=1710123494"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Diverse Exploration Areas</strong> - Embark on open-world exploration across seven distinct biomes and over 300 intricately detailed areas<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2532300/extras/过图.gif?t=1710123494"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Mythical Setting</strong> - Explore the mysteries of The Weird Dream’s world with over 30 hand-drawn comics spanning 80 pages<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2532300/extras/图鉴.gif?t=1710123494"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Languages</strong> - English and Simplified Chinese will be available at launch; other languages incl. Japanese will be available in an upcoming update</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mythical Mayhem</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2388600/Mythical_Mayhem/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2388600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Mythical Mayhem is a fantasy deck building game.  It is currently released with a robust campaign mode, tutorials, many scenarios and the ability to create a custom game with all of your unlocked content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Version 1.0.0.0 Features (Last Update: March 9, 2024)</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fantasy strategy deck building game<br/></li><li>Recruit Heroes<br/></li><li>Defeat Foe's and Arch Villains in combat that has a random element<br/></li><li>Single Player <br/></li><li>Custom game allowing you to choose your decks<br/></li><li>Campaign Mode<br/></li><li>Realm Balance<br/></li><li>Many different ways to play</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Version 1.0.0.0 Decks</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>8 Generic Unnamed Hero Decks<br/></li><li>32 Named Hero Decks<br/></li><li>9 Side Quest Card<br/></li><li>22 Quest Cards<br/></li><li>10 Gear Cards<br/></li><li>11 Relic Cards<br/></li><li>14 Dark Sagas <br/></li><li>10 Dark Sagas Chapter Card Variations<br/></li><li>23 Arch Villain Decks <br/></li><li>8 Arch Villain Ambition Card Variations<br/></li><li>28 Foe Decks<br/></li><li>19 Minion Decks<br/></li><li>35 Scenarios<br/></li><li>5 Benefactor Cards<br/></li><li>9 Drinking Deck Cards<br/></li><li>Custom Game Creator</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avium</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2622850/Avium/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622850/extras/gif-1.gif?t=1710040081"><br/><br/>Discover the world of the future with Avium, a role-playing adventure game where you can enjoy an open world, deep story, and future technology. Test new generation weapons, investigate complex crimes, explore the city and its inhabitants. And defeat your enemies, who are trying to destroy peace and order.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622850/extras/title-0.png?t=1710040081"><br/><br/>Gary, Jake, Derek, and Sarah together make up the Vanguards Vigilante Group in Avium, a desert city that thrives on the edge of Cyberpunk style. They're doing their best to keep the peace and uphold the law, but growing animosity against all vigilantes has reached its peak. <br/><br/>While exposing corruption in Avium's various districts alongside hunting down your nemesis, the sentient robot menace known as Haz-Mat, you'll get to fly and fight as the vigilante Jake aka "Diezel". You will have to uncover many mysteries and secrets of this world, find yourself on the brink of death and challenge new vices and problems of the future world in an age where emotional instability, political nepotism, and social upheaval dominate logic. The race toward the next stage in human evolution begins. In the aftermath of democracy and rise of totalitarianism, we have colonized the Solar System, making our once estranged planets part of our new empire. Cutting edge cybernetics, super power drugs, the loss of thousands of years of history, and the power vacuum between rivaling corporations all plunge Avium, the cyber capital of Earth, into revolt.<br/><br/>However, a far greater force of darkness looms on the horizon, threatening to end humanity's reign across all dimensions, all times, and all stages of evolution...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622850/extras/gif-2.gif?t=1710040081"><br/><br/><strong>Campaign Length</strong>: 3hrs.<br/><strong>Free Mode</strong>: Choose one of three Open World Areas, independent from the story of Avium.<br/><strong>Arcade Mode</strong>: Tutorials, Boss battles, Elimination battles, Zombies, and a race to play.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622850/extras/title-1.png?t=1710040081"><br/><br/>1) <strong>"A single button can save the universe"</strong> - Avium sets you up to pay attention to the world and your pop-in messages to understand the world of Avium, what to do, and when to do it. Hints, collectibles, Easter eggs, tricks, clues, lore, abilities, and details are at your disposal. Reading between the lines in what you're given leads you to understand Avium and of what it's trying to warn you. Don't take anything at face value. Nothing is free. 'Interacting' at certain points during certain two important cutscenes give you the edge or save the universe altogether...<br/><br/>2) <strong>"Accessible Lore, if you want it. Deep world, if you don't"</strong> - You have access to as much lore as you'd find in a book through the use of pop-in tutorial messages, lore in-world, and NPC dialogues. But a majority of your arsenal/abilities, allies' motivations, and world order are not directly given to you, but instead are revealed only to the most curious. Explore &amp; investigate, and you will find the truth! Or don't...<br/><br/>3) <strong>"No single weapon is the best in the game"</strong> - Avium is also designed to give you immense choice in how you fight enemies. While Enemies and Bosses are not overly complex, every weapon affects common enemies and bosses differently. Choose your weapons wisely to defeat the enemies. Watch those pop-ins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622850/extras/gif-3.gif?t=1710040081"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622850/extras/title-2.png?t=1710040081"><br/><br/><i>"Avium is a snapshot of our society today, but 100 years from now. <br/>Our incredible ability to adapt, left unchecked, has the potential to be our downfall. We are creatures of evolution. On one hand, it gave us marvels of medicine and technology, life-extending wonders! On the other hand, it has changed our sense of definition. <br/><br/>As we progress, we're leaving behind history, tradition, and religion--a by-product of progress. We're naturally and unintentionally replacing all of the past with this die-hard pursuit of truth, spectacle, or convenience, or sometimes all three. This is the natural course of adaptation. Taking this to its extreme means that anything we "know" today can't possibly stand the test of time as a concrete definition. Everything we "know" is subject to redefinition because of some discovery in our near future. Rules and laws become adapted. Constitutions and democracies become adapted. <br/><br/>There will come a point in time when we can redefine anything to mean anything except what it was originally defined as. This coupled with everyone's avarice to be "right" welcomes widespread disconnect that pits everyone's definitions against everyone else's on Earth. So instead of there being one definition, there are 8 billion, 10 billion, fifteen billion definitions. And you have just as many perspectives, justifications, and personal rights that bolster those opinions and a growing irrational determination to shut down any opposing view because these views you've defended are now part of your identity, your livelihood--adapted to each individual. And because these anecdotal "truths" are so personal and irrefutable to you, you can make anything you say as authentic as you want it to be perceived. <br/><br/>Our adaptation taken to its ultimate conclusion spells the eventual breakdown in our psychology, our biology, our history. If nothing can matter more than one's own personal freedoms and personal rights and personal truths, all of which you've gone to such great lengths to redefine as "objective truths" in a world where proof can no longer be obtained by a majority without shattering our concept of our self-indulgent reality, then what is reality? <br/><br/>As you're sailing through the endless ocean of "truth", no one can tell you anything. You can do and be anything! And THAT is exactly where the Big Four (Guise, Falcon Industries, GAMMA, and the Right Hand) want us: Stuck in the sensational illusion that we have the freedom of choice when, in fact, we are drowning in the ocean of "freedom", guided only by our desires and pleasures and unified only by our hatred of opposition. It's no wonder 98.6% of the human population now unironically shares the same beliefs, goals, and hatred.<br/><br/>In such a world, Avium lets you get a taste of what could be, lets you witness both the benefits of such a "unified" society and the obvious pitfalls of isolationist self-pursuits.<br/><br/>Evolution isn't a gift, it's a negotiation. <br/><br/>What would you give for it?"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622850/extras/gif-4.gif?t=1710040081"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2622850/extras/title-3.png?t=1710040081"><br/><br/>If you're seeking:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><i>Looter-Shooter</i></strong> elements with <strong><i>Open-world Exploration</i></strong></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An arsenal of <strong><i>Missiles-Turrets-and-Flight</i></strong> via your jet-like War-Suit and breakneck speed <strong><i>Combat</i></strong></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><i>Boss Battles</i></strong></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><i>Slide, Triple Jump, Dashing, Wall-Dashing</i></strong>, and <strong><i>Superhero Landing</i></strong> Locomotion Features</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><i>Hacking</i></strong> doors with code</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Defensive &amp; Offensive <strong><i>Teleportation</i></strong></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A <strong><i>Magic System (Ice, Fire, Electricity, Telekinesis)</i></strong> for unlocking puzzles &amp; minor combat</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><i>Laser Vision</i></strong></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong><i>Stealthy Assassinations</i></strong> &amp; <strong><i>Invisibility</i></strong></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The ability to seamlessly <strong><i>swap from FPS to TPS</i></strong></li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dystopian capitalism, neon skylines, allegory, tragedy &amp; betrayal...but you also want to dip your toes in the Hard Sciences of the fermi paradox, quantum mechanics &amp; multiverses, general relativity, the Kardashev scale, Bekenstein bound, Planck time, extraterrestrial life, robotics, artificial intelligence, war, black holes, evolution, and did I mention LASERS??</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fun little <strong><i>Easter Eggs</i></strong> and references that pay homage to the games that inspired Avium.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>And <strong><i>Photo Mode</i></strong>! Take stunning pics up to 4K right here in-game, exactly how you want them, and export the photos to your personal drive automatically! </li></ul>Then welcome to Avium!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WarBots</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1892900/WarBots/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1892900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1892900/extras/fight-3.gif?t=1710015049"><br/><br/>This is a <strong>platformer</strong>, <strong>2D MOBA</strong> game with shooting robots. <br/>An <strong>5v5 PvP arena</strong> where the goal is to destroy the enemy team's core or capture the base on the center and keep it. <br/>You can customize your weapon and robot by choosing different <strong>equipment</strong>, which you can acquire by reaching higher levels.<br/>Capture the base in the middle to support the advance. While you're dead, you control a small but deadly drone.<br/>The matches are approximately 20 minutes long.<br/>The game supports solo, <strong>LAN</strong> and <strong>online</strong> matchmaking. (...and simulation games where you only observe bots in spectator mode)<br/><br/>On an icy planet, the robots of two bases fight each other to destroy the energy core of the enemy base.<br/>If the game successfully finds an audience, we plan to add a lot of new content and features to it.<br/>This game is the basis for our later developments with the real goal of creating development solutions to develop our future multiplayer games.<br/>We develop the following functions, maps, or equipment according to demand. You can vote for our next developments on our website.<br/><br/>The game is designed to work with selfhosted sessions, so it will work offline, without servers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Short Lore:</h2>WarBots are designed for WAR at a giant scale.<br/>Humans created a whole planet to produce, test and develop warbots and send them out across the galaxies to eliminate potential threats. The Main Constructor's AI designed to protect life, but since its launch it didn't contacted any and also didn't heard anything about its makers. The Main Constructor is now fully operational and running tests on WarBots.<h2 class="bb_tag">Drones</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1892900/extras/drones.gif?t=1710015049"><br/>When the player's WarBot is destroyed, a death sphere is spawned. Until the player respawns, they take control of this small but deadly drone, allowing them to continue wreaking havoc on their enemies from beyond the grave.<br/>Drones are vulnerable, but when dies, it explodes.<h2 class="bb_tag">Color Game</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1892900/extras/color-game.gif?t=1710015049"><br/>In the Color Game, if you press a square, the one you pressed, and the adjacted ones are changing color. <br/>If the full panel have the same color, and its not controlled by that team, the neutral base changes side to that team.<br/>If you got stuck, after a few seconds, it will show you what to change next.<br/>After the the neutral base is captured, the control panels will be unavailable for a short period of time.<h2 class="bb_tag">Equipment</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1892900/extras/equipments.gif?t=1710015049"><br/>Equipment is an essential part of the game, offering a wide variety of weapon modifications and gear that can drastically alter your stats and playstyle. With each equipment and weapon modification offering a unique combination of advantages and disadvantages, players must carefully choose the best setup to match their preferred tactics. Whether you're looking to improve your durability, increase your speed, or boost your damage output, there's an equipment or weapon modification that can help you achieve your goals and dominate your opponents.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taurus War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2755100/Taurus_War/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2755100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2755100/extras/PIC_TBS_E.png?t=1710077014"><br/>【2024 NEW SCI-FI GAME】<br/>Taurus War is a Sci-Fi turn-based strategy game.Simple and quick to learn, even if you have no experience in turn-based games.<br/>【VARIOUS TACTICS】<br/>Different units have different exclusive skills, such as summoning, invincibility, blocking,healing, etc., and various units will form a variety of tactical play methods.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2755100/extras/PIC_UE_E.png?t=1710077014"><br/>【UNREAL ENGINE】<br/>This game uses UE5 technology to create SCI-FI battlefield<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2755100/extras/PIC_TIME_E.png?t=1710077014"><br/>【ENDLESS PLAY TIME】<br/>Explore Taurus ,train units, and more.Simple one touch game play with lots of levels that will keep you entertained for hours.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge of the Antagonist - BL (Boys Love)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831570/Revenge_of_the_Antagonist__BL_Boys_Love/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831570/extras/P_Summary.png?t=1709999233"><br/><strong><i>Enemies on camera, enemies off camera!</i></strong><br/><br/>At a performing arts school, Gerald doesn't stand out, so he secretly envies the popular kid, Damian, who Gerald thinks is undeserving of his popularity due to his lack of talent. His insecurity worsens when Damian unintentionally mocks him in front of the entire class. Years after graduation, Gerald becomes a C-list actor who's usually typecast to act in antagonist roles. Meanwhile, Damian becomes a popular heartthrob who's usually the protagonist in romance dramas. Gerald feels bitter that he has to work hard all these years to land auditions, but Damian gets roles automatically handed to him because of his popularity despite his acting being lackluster. His rival's success constantly reminds Gerald of his insecurities and makes him feel like a loser.<br/>One day, Gerald gets the role of the antagonist in a romance drama. By chance, Damian happens to be the male lead in that same drama, and they'll both have to fight over the female lead. Because of his pent-up jealousy and insecurities, Gerald swears to use various underhand tactics on set to embarrass his rival. Damian, on the other hand, is not going to sit back and let himself be provoked. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831570/extras/P_Characters.png?t=1709999233"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831570/extras/P_Gerald.png?t=1709999233"><br/>Gerald is aromantic and asexual. Even though his smirk makes him seem like a flirty player, he doesn't like being flirted with. He's not interested in romance, so he's never cared about acting in the romance genre. But for once, he decides to act in one as an antagonist in hopes of getting his name out there. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831570/extras/P_Damian.png?t=1709999233"><br/>Despite looking like a typical cute, romantic protagonist, Damian is aloof. He doesn't talk to people off camera unless it's necessary. He only wants to open up to someone who's genuine with him. Since Damian has been the male lead in multiple romance dramas, he'd sometimes flirt and say cheesy lines without intent. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831570/extras/P_Features.png?t=1709999233"><br/>30K Words (2-3 Hours Playtime)<br/>2 Endings (Neutral Ending &amp; Good Ending)<br/>9 Main CGs + 2 Minor CGs<br/>Original Sound Tracks<br/>Acting Expression Selection Mini-Game						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
