<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Sixty Four</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659900/Sixty_Four/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Upgrade a factory in an extraordinary world. Progress to unlock new resources and machines, leading to new ways to expand and grow.<br/><br/><strong>❒ From Foundation to Complexity</strong><br/><br/>Begin your journey with a simple machine generating distinct cubes. Use combinations of cubes to unlock advanced machinery and new gameplay elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_3a_smaller.gif?t=1709591697"><br/><br/><strong>❒ An Evolving Factory Adventure</strong><br/><br/>Your factory is not just a collection of idle machines; it's a dynamic environment of challenges and strategy. Face new situations and discover opportunities with every innovative and abstract machine you encounter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_4a_smaller.gif?t=1709591697"><br/><strong>❒ A Fresh Mix of Gaming Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Sixty Four combines simple yet engaging elements from idle, incremental, and strategy games. Pursue constant improvement and unravel the secrets behind messages from an unknown entity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_5a_smaller.gif?t=1709591697"><br/><br/>Music by Jake Chudnow						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thaumaturge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684350/The_Thaumaturge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/TT_claim_EN_small.png?t=1709581107"><br/><strong>The Thaumaturge is an isometric, story-rich RPG with a unique take on turn-based combat, character development features, and investigation mechanics</strong>, facing you with morally ambiguous choices – set in a world teeming with mysterious powers and strange ethereal beings called <strong>salutors</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/City_3-01.gif?t=1709581107"><br/><br/>The year is 1905. Warsaw lives under the yoke of imperial Russian tsardom. Its inhabitants constitute a diverse group of different ancestries, views, and beliefs with often conflicting interests: Russian soldiers, Jewish merchants, Polish townspeople, and more. Despite the circumstances, the city is a buzzing metropolis, where one can attend a breathtaking party with the high society, and later get robbed in one of the dark alleys of the Praga district. A city of great hopes and dreams on one hand and dark desires on the other.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Buka_2.gif?t=1709581107"><br/><br/>A <strong>thaumaturge</strong> bears both a gift and a burden at the same time. This parallel holds true for <strong>Wiktor Szulski</strong>, the game’s titular protagonist, who is drawn back to the tumultuous streets of 20th-century Warsaw by family matters. The gift of thaumaturgy is intertwined with family legacy, passed down through one's ancestors. This mystical inheritance significantly shapes Wiktor’s life journey tied around a pursuit of unearthly entities and their hosts. As only a thaumaturge can tame these ethereal entities - known to a select few as <strong>salutors</strong> - utilizing their mystical abilities to discover secrets hidden within the human soul and speak to the Darkness, no one understands quite like Wiktor how everyone suffers their own demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Wiktor_3-01.gif?t=1709581107"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Shape your story</strong> – as a full-fledged RPG, it allows you to alternate your choices and make you deal with the aftermath. <br/></li><li><strong>Develop your character</strong> – creating your own version of the thaumaturge will allow you to approach situations in different ways. <br/></li><li><strong>Experience unique turn-based combat</strong> and defeat your foes using human attacks and skills as well as psychic strikes delivered by salutors.<br/></li><li><strong>Influence and manipulate</strong> the temperaments of other characters to bend their will to your liking. <br/></li><li><strong>Tame the power of salutors</strong> – use the unique set of their skills to gain an advantage while exploring the world and when bringing your adversaries to their knees. <br/></li><li><strong>See the world that’s inevitably gone</strong> – explore the uncommon, heavily researched historic period of the early XX century Warsaw, where crime and luxury are often two sides of the same coin. Meet historical figures and learn about their involvement in the story. <br/></li><li><strong>Created in Unreal Engine 5</strong> to deliver a detailed &amp; beautifully crafted world.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crusader Kings III: Legends of the Dead</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671060/Crusader_Kings_III_Legends_of_the_Dead/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							What good are grand accomplishments and heroic deeds if no one sings of them after you have gone? A royal legacy is only useful, after all, if it can provide cover and legitimacy for those who come after you. Live on in the memory of your subjects and rivals in <i>Legends of the Dead</i>, a Core Expansion for <i>Crusader Kings III</i>.<br/><br/><strong><i>Crusader Kings III: Legends of the Dead</i></strong> adds new heroic gameplay, as you stoke the flames of your fame into a towering bonfire.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671060/extras/legends-v4-opt.gif?t=1709571372"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Legends:</strong> Commission an epic retelling of your family history or build your own heroic reputation through great deeds. Promote this legend, far and wide, and see how the stories of the past reverberate through the centuries, and add more glory to legendary dynasties.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Legendary Playstyle:</strong> Leverage your living legend status through new Decisions and actions, keeping the stories of your family in the minds of a continent, strengthening the legitimacy of your rule and allowing further choices. <br/><br/></li><li><strong>Legendary Buildings:</strong> Your legendary reputation gives you access to new elite buildings, cementing your legacy for future generations.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Legendary Feasts: </strong>Poets and bards can ornament your celebrations with songs and odes to your greatness, inspiring your guests to spread the tale of your legendary generosity.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Court Chroniclers:</strong> Hire an official historian to spread the story of your dynasty’s great accomplishments, or use your poets and musicians to turn your actions into art.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Two New Legacies:</strong> A new Heroic dynastic Legacy for the heirs of legendary characters, even using the great deeds of ancestors to justify claims from the distant past, as well as a Legitimacy Legacy that promotes your dynasty as the true rulers of the realm.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671060/extras/blackplague-opt.gif?t=1709571372"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Illness and Mourning:</strong> New diseases like the Bloody Flux, Measles and Holy Fire may ravage your court, but you can honor your deceased loved ones with dignified Funeral rites, according to your faith.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>The Black Death:</strong> The greatest scourge of the Middle Ages strikes down noble and commoner alike, radically transforming the political and social environment. Prepare your realm and prepare your soul, because a rampaging plague may be the strongest enemy facing your rule.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>New Art:</strong> Both life and death are given new energy with the celebrated art style that Crusader Kings III fans have come to appreciate. A new exclusive Map Table, new varieties of clothing, unit models and holding designs for extra flavor.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mortal Glory 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2216660/Mortal_Glory_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif1.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en1.png?t=1709567748"><br/>Roll an explosive barrel at your enemy, throw them into a pit or take out two enemies by knocking them into each other. With a wide variety of tools available to you, your creativity will determine how you deal with the competition. Unique arenas, randomized environments and occasional special rules ensure that each fight offers new tactical opportunities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif2.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en2.png?t=1709567748"><br/>A wide variety of fantasy races are seeking glory, each with their own unique racial strengths. Whatever your tactics are, finding the best recruits is essential!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif3.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en3.png?t=1709567748"><br/>There is a vast collection of unique relics, character perks and more to discover. Finding clever combos and deadly synergies will unlock new strategies and occasionally turn your gladiators into unfairly strong demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif5.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en6.png?t=1709567748"><br/>Various difficulty settings will accommodate your preferred playstyle and there are increasingly harder challenges to master. But beware... The AI is brutally talented at the highest levels.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif6.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en4.png?t=1709567748"><br/>With every step comes a new challenge or perhaps... an opportunity? It is up to you to guide where your team should travel next... and suffer the consequences.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif4.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en5.png?t=1709567748"><br/>Each playthrough is different! With various tactics to try and additional increasingly harder challenges to master, the arena will keep welcoming you back again and again. Thanks to conveniently paced combat, Mortal Glory 2 is also great to play if you only have a moment to spare.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/EndHead.png?t=1709567748"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spell Disk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292060/Spell_Disk/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Spell Disk is a rogue-lite action game with a unique synergy building mechanic so that your runs can never be the same. Strategize and create your own spell combo synergies to blast through enemies on your way! Each run is unique, so you must plan out how to build your power.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/combo_paper.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Discover combos and synergies that no one’s seen before! Maximize your power to better your chance of escaping the dungeon of Spell Disk.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Items_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Craft spells, disks, and artifacts during your run that synergies with each other in their own ways.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292060/extras/Lobby_Updated.gif?t=1709316039"><br/>Unlock new weapons and powers to hack and slash through the enemies blocking your way.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivaland: Dream House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2606170/Vivaland_Dream_House/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/extras/ezgif-3-474fd0310c.gif?t=1709314012"><h2 class="bb_tag">Introducing the Vivaland Prologue: Dream House</h2><strong>Build Mode: Craft Your Dreams</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in one of the core game modes of Vivaland: the Build Mode. It's a sandbox where you have control over architectural and design elements, enabling you to construct and decorate a house from the ground up!<br/><br/><strong>Get to Know the First Town of Vivaland</strong><br/><br/>The town of Vivaland offers 8 residential lots, each awaiting your personal touch. Claim your slice of the town, visit your friends' properties, and collaborate on grand projects that will redefine the neighborhood.<br/><br/><strong>Seamless Single and Co-op Experience</strong><br/><br/>Begin your Vivaland adventure either as a lone explorer or with your friends by your side – the choice is yours. You can build together with up to 8 players<br/><strong>Content</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Walls Toolkit:</strong> Build with single wall, curved wall and the room tool!<br/></li><li><strong>Doors &amp; Windows:</strong> Choose entrances and views that reflect your taste.<br/></li><li><strong>Foundations, Multiple Floors, and Stairs: </strong>Build structures that rise to new heights.<br/></li><li><strong>Furniture:</strong> Design with a vast selection of interior items.<br/></li><li><strong>Roofing:</strong> Choose from 10 distinct styles and an array of roof patterns.<br/></li><li><strong>Different styles of items:</strong>  Bohemian, Retro, Victorian, Antique, Cottagecore, Gothic, Modern, Minimalist, Industrial.</li></ul><br/><strong>Functional Freedom</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Resizable Objects:</strong> Adjusting the size of decorative objects.<br/></li><li><strong>Recolorable Furniture and Decor: </strong> Fine-tune your interior design with your color palettes. Save favorite shades and match your items.<br/></li><li><strong>Room Dimension Flexibility: </strong>Tweak the height and width of your rooms.<br/></li><li><strong>Grid Function: </strong>Precise item placement is a breeze with toggleable grid support.<br/></li><li><strong>Intuitive Controls and Snapping: </strong>Seamlessly move and arrange objects.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUARDS!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2514460/GUARDS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/4playerchaos.png?t=1709330868"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/chaosgif.gif?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">1-4 PLAYER CO-OP</h2>Work together as a team and fight your way through the wretched streets of New Alestead. You will need to rely on your teammates if you are going to make out of the city alive.<h2 class="bb_tag">LIGHTNING FAST ACTION</h2>New Alestead has a disease... and you are the cure! Dispense justice quickly and thoroughly because these criminals wont wait to attack you one at a time.<h2 class="bb_tag">EVERYTHING IS A WEAPON</h2>Sometimes you need to improvise! Use crates, barrels, planks, bits of door, arms, a variety of City Watch approved civility moderation tools or even your foot to bring criminals in dead or alive.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/scoutplanexecute.png?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">MISSION DISPATCH</h2>It's not all City sanctioned murder and wanton property destruction, sometimes you actually need to arrest some people, secure contraband or escort important VIP's out of the city.<h2 class="bb_tag">ON STAKEOUT</h2>When you find the criminals hideout, you will be outnumbered and outgunned. Wait and watch from the shadows to observe enemy patrol patterns, gang composition and any environmental objects that you might be able to use to your advantage.<h2 class="bb_tag">NO PLAN SURVIVES FIRST CONTACT</h2>When it all kicks off you're going to have to think on your feet and coordinate with your partners. Just try to make sure you take out more bad guys than other officers in the process!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2514460/extras/takebackcity.png?t=1709330868"><h2 class="bb_tag">A CITY RULED BY GANGS</h2>Three rival factions control the city. The Fogtoof Boyz, an Orc gang with a reputation for violence and destruction. The Commision, a band of rogue merchants whose lust for power put them on the wrong side of the law, and The Corpse Cult - an religious organization infecting the city by turning its followers into mindless zombies.<h2 class="bb_tag">FIND THE KINGPINS</h2>Each gang has a kingpin. Take out the kingpin, you take out the gang. You will have to work your way up the food chain in order to find the kingpins location and assault their hideout.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brew Barons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1636710/The_Brew_Barons/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A tranquil world becomes ever more corrupt by the day, spoiled by a strong-armed pirate organization that forcefully impose their brewing monopoly over the lands. Armed with your own brewery and seaplane, it's up to you to explore, forage, craft, sell and deliver your handcrafted brews with aid from fellow pilots who've joined your cause to overthrow the corrupt pirate organization and restore peace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif1a.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Assemble your plane from a variety of parts, each with their own traits.<br/></li><li>Chose your pilot and copilot of whom have strengths and weaknesses.<br/></li><li>Explore the world in search of ingredients to bring back to your brewery. </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1636710/extras/steamgif2.gif?t=1709308740"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Pick and choose which foraged ingredients to blend. <br/></li><li>Distill and/or Ferment, each producing a different outcome. <br/></li><li>Design and name your bottle to your liking.<br/></li><li>Design your very own bar to sell your brews and bring fame to your establishment!<br/></li><li>With fame comes special delivery orders from other bars to stock your brew </li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mobius Machine</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2281940/The_Mobius_Machine/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2281940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Carve your path through a <strong>vast alien world</strong> filled with <i>brutal lifeforms</i> and <i>malfunctioning machines</i>.<br/>Explore beyond the <i>Crash Site</i>, through the desolate <i>Spaceship Graveyard</i>, into the depths of the <i>Mining Grounds</i>, and up to the <i>Floating Forests</i>.<br/><br/>The Mobius Machine is a <strong>classic 2D adventure</strong> game with <strong>detailed 3D visuals</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2281940/extras/machine.gif?t=1709287020"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore Seamlessly</h2>Explore a complex interconnected <strong>open world</strong>, discovering it your own way.<br/>Stumble upon the breathtaking environments of the Isolaria moon. On <strong>land</strong>, <strong>underwater</strong> and in the <strong>skies</strong>. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2281940/extras/exploration.gif?t=1709287020"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fight</h2>Combat an array of deadly adversaries: the local fauna, infected colonists, and abandoned machines that once worked in the facilities.<br/>Defeat more than 80 distinct enemies, including the <strong>epic bosses</strong> that guard the most precious gear.<h2 class="bb_tag">Shoot Anywhere</h2>Designed for both <strong>Gamepad</strong> or <strong>Mouse and Keyboard</strong> controls. Run and jump around while shooting in any direction using a tight control system.<br/>You can have 2 weapons equipped at any time, and use them as you need.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2281940/extras/combat.gif?t=1709287020"><h2 class="bb_tag">Evolve</h2>Acquire the gear that will make you more mobile and unlock new areas. <strong>Climb walls</strong>, <strong>dash</strong>, <strong>dive underwater</strong>, <strong>glide through the air</strong> and evolve the way you interact with the world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your arsenal</h2>Collect blueprints and craft new <strong>weapons</strong> and <strong>upgrades</strong> in order to fight more effectively. Each new item you acquire will give you more options and increase your chances of survival.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1709230702"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robin Hood - Sherwood Builders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159420/Robin_Hood__Sherwood_Builders/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fk2N3rpRuB3" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/fc521c8bf21bff775962df4f130bb74eb5577a46.png?t=1709562813"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif01.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Robin Hood - Sherwood Builders is an action-adventure RPG with base-building elements, where you take on the role of a classic hero who stands up to the tyranny and injustice that haunts Sherwood. As Robin, you’ll fight, hunt, craft, steal, and of course help the local people thrive to spite the Sheriff of Nottingham and his ruthless regime – all within an open-world environment that can be freely explored.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif02.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Robin Hood is a famous hero of medieval English folk tales, believed to have during that time roamed the forests of Sherwood with his band of loyal outlaw companions. In the game you’re going to meet those legendary characters as well, such as Lady Marian, Little John, Friar Tuck, Allan-a-Dale, and Will Scarlet. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif05.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Robin's main goal is to help a fledgling community of refugees and rebels advance and expand. Starting with what could be described as a small forest settlement, with a bit of care, hard work, and good luck, it can end up as a town full of people. Recruit local peasants, rebels on the run from the law, and even the citizens and guards of Nottingham themselves as your new outlaw settlers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif04.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>You start your adventure with building a forest camp, which can soon be expanded following the arrival of new residents. You will be responsible for properly managing the space you secured for yourself within Sherwood Forest to build up the village.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif03.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Another important part of taking care of the settlement will be to manage the community members’ professions and tasks, training them to become craftsmen, hunters, or guards, and to manage the settlement’s resources, either gathering them yourself or stealing them from convoys and noble estates.<br/><br/>As Robin's people grow large in number and strong in sword arm, an uprising in Nottingham may just become a reality, ending the Sheriff's tyranny once and for all.<br/>Can Robin Hood and his Merry Men survive and put an end to injustice? Their fate is up to you!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godrop:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802550/GodropPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Prologue and the official version of the difference between<br/>Levels: one in the prologue, four in the official version<br/>Follow-up Program:<br/>The game will continue to update content after release, which includes:<br/>More bosses: different fighting styles and types of boss fights.<br/>More tech: weird and wacky tech combinations.<br/>More weapons: more basic weapons and weapon variants.<br/>More game modes: In addition to the basic level mode there will also be a survivor mode and parkour mode. </strong><br/><br/><strong>A special roguelike game that focuses entirely on ramming, piercing, and spraying as the core gameplay. You will play as Gotrop, a powerful unknown alien invasion weapon, facing the layers of barriers set up by the arrogant and ignorant humans in the solar system, using good movement and killing to steal the energy of human warships, driving our strong interaction force outer armor for invincible transformation, and destroying all the enemies in our way with incredible maneuverability and invulnerable ramming ability! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y1.png?t=1709446521"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/1.gif?t=1709446521"><br/><strong>A combat system focused on energy. Just by being in motion you can generate a constant stream of energy, and mysterious alien technology also allows Gotrop to steal energy directly from his enemies. There is energy can be transformed into an invincible droplet state, invulnerable and unbreakable, our enemies can not cause any damage to us, but we can directly puncture the inside of their battleships havoc! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y2.png?t=1709446521"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/2.gif?t=1709446521"><br/><strong>A large number of tech components have been beamed into the solar system, and Gotrop can access tech for morphing upgrades simply by cleaning up the battlefield! Whether it's a drill that can drill into enemy ships faster, outer armor that can reflect all attacks, or a spout that spews bullets, they can be acquired after sweeping through the enemy! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/y3.png?t=1709446521"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802550/extras/3.gif?t=1709446521"><br/><strong>The solar system has been fortified by humans and is in crisis. Gotrop will break through layers of asteroids, energy stands and turret arrays until he completely destroys the human space fleet and takes over Earth! </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1709568697"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1709568697"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709568697"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1709568697"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709568697"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1709568697"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritfall</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1835240/Spiritfall/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/PlatformFighterRoguelike.png?t=1709235442"><br/><strong>Spiritfall</strong> combines tight Platform Fighter combat, smooth movement, and Roguelite mechanics into one! Trek across dangerous lands, string together deadly combos to fend off swarms of enemies, and harness an ever-changing set of powers through a randomly generated map. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/SynergiesAwait.png?t=1709235442"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/GIFDivineSynergiesQuality.gif?t=1709235442"><br/>The divine spirits offer powerful blessings that enhance your abilities in combat. Discover your favorite abilities, and experiment with different builds. With over 150+ blessings to choose from, these gifts allow for a range of tactical approaches that encourage you to find synergies that fit your playstyle.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/StrongerFromDefeat.png?t=1709235442"><br/>Death is but a temporary setback. Reawaken stronger than before at the Sanctum and continue your adventure. Use the resources you gathered to upgrade your skills, unlock unique powers, and awaken mighty weapons with unique movesets.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1835240/extras/Community.png?t=1709235442"><br/>A heartfelt thank you to our Early Access community! Your feedback has been invaluable during Spiritfall's development, helping make the game what it is today. We invite you to keep shaping our world together. Connect with fellow players on Discord and get the latest news by joining our newsletter.						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minami Lane</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Minami Lane is a small, wholesome management game set on a Japanese-inspired street. Create and manage your own street, make sure everyone is happy, and watch the villagers live their lives! Enjoy 2 to 4 hours of playtime, cute tanukis and lots of cats!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Gameplay.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Build your street</strong></i><br/>Build homes to add villagers to your street, then improve their happiness by beautifying every inch and building a variety of shops &amp; attractions! These include ramen shops, boba cafes, bookstores and more, each with unique inventories and effects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Building.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Manage your shops</strong></i><br/>Attract customers with everything from floral bouquets to karaoke! Shops you create will need your careful guidance to offer the right products at the right prices. Lead them to success and make your neighborhood thrive.<br/><br/><i><strong>Watch your villagers live their lives</strong></i><br/>Once you start the day, you'll get to see each villager react to your street and offer helpful feedback on how to improve! Memorize their preferences and refine your street the following day.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Review.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/><i><strong>Reach your objectives</strong></i><br/>Complete missions to unlock new levels with more buildings, villager types, and other surprises.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/Features.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane offers:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2-4 hours of play time<br/></li><li>Create and customize your own adorable street<br/></li><li>Manage shops by adjusting their inventory, recipes, and prices<br/></li><li>Play strategically to complete each level's mission objectives<br/></li><li>Keep the streets clean by picking up trash<br/></li><li>Tanukis and cats!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Ramen.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>What Minami Lane does not offer:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hardcore strategy<br/></li><li>Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Tons of missions<br/></li><li>New levels after release</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/GameModes.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>In Minami Lane's missions, you'll need to strategically plan each day and use random events to your advantage to complete multiple objectives. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/615p-Bike.gif?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>The sandbox mode focuses on creativity and relaxation, allowing you to immerse yourself in the peaceful, cozy world without the stress of objectives.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2678990/extras/DevTeam.png?t=1709132463"><br/><br/>Minami Lane is the collaborative effort of Dorian (Doot), Doriane (Blibloop) and Antoine (Zakku). Doot, a former data scientist turned game developer, brings light strategy and management gameplay, while Blibloop breathes life into the isometric world with her Studio Ghibli-inspired, hand-drawn designs. Zakku adds the finishing touches with joyful, wholesome music compositions and soundscape. We really hope you will enjoy this tiny game we made with love 💕<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2678990/Minami_Lane/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1709278523"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shashingo: Learn Japanese with Photography</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1632490/Shashingo_Learn_Japanese_with_Photography/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore bright, fictional Japanese streets filled with details and interesting objects to capture with your camera. Each photograph you take will translate the name of the content into Japanese and English so you can learn with your surroundings.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Take_Photo.gif?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A stylised, approachable 3D environment<br/></li><li>In-game photography system<br/></li><li>Japanese audio<br/></li><li>Photo album to store your flash cards<br/></li><li>A game mode that tests your memory<br/></li><li>Beginner phrases and grammar lessons<br/></li><li>Day/Night and weather cycle<br/></li><li>Display romaji, kana, furigana <i>(recommended)</i> or kanji</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Flash_Cards.png?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Create Stunning Photography Based Flashcards</h2>Every photo flash-card you take will be unique to you. The idea behind this is to strengthen the relationship between a word and how you see its physical appearance. In the real world, you can then see such objects and make connections to the Japanese words you've already learned while playing Shashingo.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1632490/extras/Shashingo_Photo_Album.png?t=1709246737"><h2 class="bb_tag">Track Your Progress in the Photo Album</h2>Your photo album is where you keep your collection of Photo Flash-Cards. If you remember them well in Find Mode, they'll be separated into the 'mastered' tab and shown with a gold star sticker. However, if you're struggling to remember a word in Find Mode, they'll be marked with a purple exclamation mark sticker, so you know which words you need to practice more.<br/>You can also mark your favourite words &amp; images with a cute little heart sticker to add them to your favourites page.<br/><br/>At the back of your in-game photo album, there are numerous pages of Japanese lessons designed for beginners that will teach you how to speak Japanese and use the vocabulary that you learn in Shashingo. Also included are some key words and important phrases that can help you in your future conversations.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dicefolk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996430/Dicefolk/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FtN3yxBv4tq" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Join_Our_Discord_600x224.png?t=1709379465"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Dicefolk is a tactical roguelite game based on customizable dice and monster-catching mechanics. On your adventure as a Chimera Summoner, you'll meet dozens of unique and powerful creatures that you can recruit to create the perfect team.<br/><br/>Play as Alea, a young Dicefolk hero who discovers her ability to befriend Chimera and fight back against evil forces threatening humanity’s extinction.</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle_Start.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H2.png?t=1709379465"><br/>Embark on a thrilling quest to save humanity from the grasp of an evil sorcerer. Build a team from over 100 unique, hand-drawn Chimera to suit your playstyle. Unlock all the talismans to uncover the mystical secrets behind the Chimeras’ existence.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Map.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H3.png?t=1709379465"><br/>With a large variety of Chimeras to befriend and command, you'll need to strategize and adapt your playstyle to suit each battle. From tough tanks to speedy attackers, each Chimera brings a unique set of abilities to the table. Your tactical choices will determine your success in battle!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Recruiting.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H4.png?t=1709379465"><br/>It’s all up to you! Customize your dice for maximum influence over your Chimeras’ attacks and abilities. Control the order in which battles play out and choose when parties take action. Dicefolk defies RNG and gives you unprecedented influence on the roll of the dice! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H5.png?t=1709379465"><br/>Each playthrough offers its own rewards, and the Chimeras you encounter in one run can be entirely different than those you find in another. With different Chimeras comes different strategies to assemble your team for the perfect run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Anim_H5.gif?t=1709379465"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Dino Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_12" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803000/100_Dino_Cats/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🦖🐾 WELCOME TO 100 DINO CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🦕🐈</h2>🦎 Join the cutest adventure in the Dino park with Cats and Dinos! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of dinosaurs location and dino-cats as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x200.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Dino Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Extra.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816050/100_Dino_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709146681"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815630/100_Dino_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=DinoCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/600x1.png?t=1709146681"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803000/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709146681"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803010/100_Robo_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815640/100_Dino_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709485776"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709485776"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solium Infernum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1893810/Solium_Infernum/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for Solium Infernum, the grand strategy game of politics, intrigue and betrayal, set in the ultimate arena of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingDarkSide2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_IndulgeYourDarkSide_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Satan's mysteriously vanished and Hell is in an uproar. Play as one of eight all-powerful and menacing Archfiends and indulge your Machiavellian dark side. Command legions, enlist champions, cast sinister rituals, and trick, rob, and insult your rivals to be crowned Hell’s new Dark Majesty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingStrategy2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_StrategyFromHell_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Experience Solium Infernum's legendary devilish political machinations. Requiring nerves of steel and a true heart of darkness, every order you give will have lasting consequences. Get into the minds of your rivals, second-guessing their every move both on the map and on the floor of Hell’s parliament as you sling insults and demands in the only truly political strategy game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Eight playable Archfiends<br/></li><li>Eight single-player Chronicles<br/></li><li>Single-player Skirmish mode<br/></li><li>Revelations Tutorial Scenario<br/></li><li>Sessional and Asynchronous 2-6 player Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Dozens of Infernal Legions, including unique enormous Titans. <br/></li><li>Champion Praetors and dark Artifacts fit for any Archfiend!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingMulitplayer.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_InfernalMultiplayer_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Play 2-6 player multiplayer games with your soon-to-be ex-friends in a single session of deceit and politics, or put your friendships to the test in quick daily bursts with Solium Infernum’s infamous asynchronous multiplayer for a truly harrowing scheme-in-your-sleep experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/Heading_DarkArt2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_DivineMadness_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>If you love dark art, you’re in the right place. Brimming with striking visions of Hell unlike anything you’ve seen before, Solium Infernum is an infernal feast for the eyes with multitudes of individual dark paintings to enjoy. Every item of the game is accompanied by mind-blasting artwork, a feat declaring Solium Infernum a winner of the 2022 Game Makers Sketchbook.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingRessurect.gif?t=1708670283"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_CultClassic_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Originally inspired by Milton’s epic poem, Paradise Lost, League of Geeks’ (known for seminal digital board game Armello) sophomore title is a re-imagining and modernisation of Vic Davis’ critically acclaimed cult-classic of the same name, hailed as a masterpiece of strategy game design. <br/><br/>Once again, prepare to lose yourself within ‘the cold glory of a difficult decision’ as we resurrect Solium Infernum from the depths of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/label_praise.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Note: The following quotes refer to the original Solium Infernum (2009) by Vic Davis.<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum is a political wargame set in hell… The game is now finished, and none of the friends survived. By which I mean, we all hate each other now.”</i> <br/>- Rock Paper Shotgun<br/><br/><i>“It’s a game about playing other people, in both senses of the word…. This is game design based on psychology as much as rules.” </i><br/>- Quarter to Three<br/><br/><i>“More than any game I've played in years, Solium Infernum nails the sensation of staring at a screen and losing yourself in the cold glory of a difficult decision.”</i><br/>- Game Developer (formerly Gamasutra)<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum kicked my knees out from under me ... this game took my past experience with strategy games and threw it, like a pro basketball player, into a bin eighty feet away.”</i><br/>- Eurogamer<br/><br/><i>“One of the best games of the year.”</i><br/>— Three Moves Ahead<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_toReign.png?t=1708670283"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kneedle Knight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2491720/Kneedle_Knight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2491720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Kneedle Knight</i> is a third-person, puzzle platformer game developed by students at SMU Guildhall Cohort 32. In <i>Kneedle Knight</i>, the player controls a mouse knight that uses his magical needle to sew fabric which he can merge into, moving back and forth between 3D and 2D. <br/><br/>Sir Lukoss the Small was a noble knight sent on a quest to defeat the evil Witch of Fabric. The Witch, using her enchanted fabric, imprisoned and transformed many citizens and knights into malicious fabrications. Sir Lukoss climbed up through her fortress to put an end to her tyranny, only to be hexed by her magic and transformed into a mouse. In the dark dungeon of the Witch’s lair, the mouse finds a magic needle, granting him special powers to sew fabric of his own and merge in and out of the enchanted threadwork. <br/><br/>Now Sir Lukoss must use his newfound weapon to sew his path forward and up through the evil stronghold. The mouse knight can use his needle to solve puzzles, overcome challenging obstacles, and defeat the animated candle minions of the Witch. All with the hopes of returning to face the Witch of Fabric yet again to finish his noble quest.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Single-player, puzzle platformer game<br/></li><li>Playtime (main story): 1-2 hours<br/></li><li>Playtime (100% achievements): 2 hours<br/></li><li>Steam leaderboard support for level speed running<br/></li><li>Made in Unreal Engine 5<br/></li><li>Original soundtrack</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Civilizations</h2>We are developing tech trees for multiple civilizations, which will include armor, weapons, buildings, crafting stations, and more. Greece, Persia, Rome, and Egypt will be added, with Greece and Persia scheduled to make their debut in 2024.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/多文明时代，即将来临！.gif?t=1709560771"><h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1709560771"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/2【替换Gif】自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1709560771"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1709560771"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/4【替换Gif】史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1709560771"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1709560771"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/6【替换Gif】传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1709560771"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1709560771"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator: Dark Fate - Defiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1839950/Terminator_Dark_Fate__Defiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif1.gif?t=1709216510"><br/><strong>Terminator: Dark Fate – Defiance</strong> is a <strong>real-time strategy game</strong> based on the Terminator: Dark Fate universe that follows the war between humanity and Legion's synthetic intelligent machine network.<br/><br/>In the<strong> single-player campaign</strong>, you take the role of a commander in the Founders, a force made up of the remnants of the US military and guide your army in an attempt to foil Legion's plan to exterminate the last remnants of humanity. In skirmish and multiplayer modes, play as three very diverse factions: Founders, Movement and Legion.<br/><br/>Take control of an army carried over from mission to mission on a series of large strategic maps. Make decisions about unit placement, battle tactics and abilities so that you don’t just survive but can become the leader of the resistance against the machines. Hone your skills and military expertise by replaying and achieving the best possible outcomes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic battlefields: realistic tactics and consequences</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif2.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Engage in complex, realistic battles where your <strong>tactical decisions</strong> are vital to your survival and ultimate victory. Use a variety of military equipment, vehicles and ammunition types in your battles against the enemy. Recruit and train new units, assign new skills and acquire new weapons and equipment to continue the resistance.<br/><br/>Encounter tense battles. Your battlefield tactics and choices have deep consequences that will impact through the campaign, with other factions and characters either joining you or fighting against you, and with certain missions being available or not depending on your actions. <br/><br/><strong>Your resources are limited</strong> and you must protect your army. Weapons of war receive damage through a modular component damage system where armour characteristics, component malfunctions and hull structure all affect if your troops survive.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the survival of mankind</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif3.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Recruit others to your cause and <strong>grow your army</strong>. Mix and match the composition of your troops to fit your preferred battle tactics. Use infantry units, heavy armoured military vehicles, plasma cannon technology, drones and other flying units and even human skirmishers to achieve victory.<br/><br/>Use the battlefield to your advantage! <strong>Physics-based building demolition</strong> lets you generate a realistic set of tactical consequences, especially in urban areas.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem: Skirmish and Online Battles</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif4.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>The excitement amplifies in <strong>skirmish and multiplayer modes</strong>, where <strong>you can play as three distinct factions</strong>: Founders, Movement, and Legion. <br/><br/>Engage in epic battles across vast strategic landscapes, testing your skills and military expertise. Every decision matters, impacting alliances, missions, and the overall survival of mankind.<br/><br/>Challenge your skills in skirmish and online multiplayer matches, facing off against AI or real-life human opponents in intense 1v1 and 2v2 battles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1709312324"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1709312324"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708975190"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonder</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692570/Sonder/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Local Co-op requires a gamepad controller for both players. Online Co-op supports mouse and keyboard. </i><h2 class="bb_tag">Psychological narrative </h2>- After a mass-scale destruction of all artificial intelligence, a scrapped robot and soul form an unexpected friendship. After a mysterious train knocks them out, they wake up in a world shaped by their own thoughts. Will they be able to cooperate and escape this dark reality?<h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive atmosphere </h2>- Immerse yourself in an atmospheric world crafted with a stylish, minimalistic approach that captivates your attention and enhances the shared adventure. Unleash the power of collaboration, confront existential mysteries, and embark on a gaming journey like no other.<h2 class="bb_tag">Collaboration </h2>- Work together - succeed together. Each character has unique abilities that allow them to manipulate the world in their own way, meaning they can only proceed if they cooperate. In combat, maximum efficiency can be achieved by combining the player’s powers, allowing them to neutralize the most dangerous of foes.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708702172"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Bananas</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2613730/Go_Bananas/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2613730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Go Bananas is a fast paced arcade platformer where you play as Blue the monkey and race to collect as many bananas as you can before the timer runs out!<br/><br/>Explore hand crafted levels, racing through each level to collect bananas. When you collect all the bananas you move on to the next level, chosen at random from over 100 designed and balanced challenges.<br/><br/>Try to beat your best Banana Total with each go! Keep an eye on the clock and watch out for juicy Super Fruits to extend the time limit and maximise the banana collecting action.<br/><br/>Play in short bursts or sink in for an extended banana chasing session and enjoy the happy vibes all day!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>100+ Banana filled Levels<br/></li><li>Addictive arcade gameplay<br/></li><li>Challenging obstacles to avoid<br/></li><li>Play in quick bursts<br/></li><li>Hilarious post game Monkey Puns<br/></li><li>Simple, straight forward fun! </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vertical Velocity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2505630/Vertical_Velocity/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this game the sun has fallen to the earth and the moon has taken over. You the player have to get the sun back into the sky by finishing courses and getting through their obstacles. You will however be forces to master the controls in order to succeed. The moon hasn't made it easy for you and plans to cause an ice age. By staying determined and focused you will take your place back in the sky. This game features a simple look with fun arcade music. It is a 2d platformer that features simple obstacles but be warned this game is not for the faint of heart. Inspired by many of the rage platformers on the market. There are plans for more content in the future, and thank you for reading have a good rest of your day/night.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alian</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2683560/Alian/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2683560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is an ordinary shooting game.<br>
In these days of overflowing original games, it is hard to know which one to choose even if there is a game you want to play, or you want to enjoy a normal game system but the extra features get in the way, don't you think so?<br>
This game consists of four stages with different difficulty levels.<br>
The objective of the game is to clear each stage.<br>
This game operates with only the minimum system necessary to make the game work, and you can fulfill your desire to conquer the game with simple rules that aim to clear the stages by moving left and right and shooting only.<br>
There should be no loss if you have it for now.						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking the Stone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2818560/Cracking_the_Stone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2818560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cracking the Stone is an interactive comic about following the life of a boy who is learning what it's like to struggle with grief.<br>
<br>
As tragedy overwhelms the boy, take control of his early life and help him learn what it's like to follow his own path, all the while blocking out the negative emotions that fly toward him as a consequence of his journey through life.<br>
<br>
What is it like to juggle the complexities of childhood &amp; adolescence with the struggle to keep one's emotions at bay and stave off existential dread and depression? Cracking the Stone aims to answer that question via an emotional journey through an interactive medium!<br>
<br>
Note: This free demo is an incomplete version of the story ends on a cliffhanger! It contains only portions of the first 2 of 5 planned chapters in the story.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DrawBall</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822910/DrawBall/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2822910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Draw ink to guide each ball into its appropriately coloured hole! Can you beat all 30+ levels? DrawBall is a fun puzzle game where the aim of the game is to complete levels by drawing ink to guide coloured balls into a correctly coloured hole. DrawBall includes over 30 in built levels and a level editor so you can create and export your own levels and even import levels made by others! You can also share your levels and download other users' levels on our DrawBall Level Portal!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Hunt - Number Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2777670/Color_Hunt__Number_Jigsaw_Puzzle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2777670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Color Hunt is a fun and relaxing puzzle game. It’s more than just coloring- it's a randomly generated number block jigsaw game that'll take your brain to another level! <br>
<br>
Gorgeous Art, challenging number grid block matching, jigsaw puzzle strategies with shape fit mechanics. Experience one of the most original board games, earn rewards and unlock new levels, solve puzzles which get larger each level, freely choose from all available puzzle pieces in a smooth scrolling ribbon, build up art galleries, complete daily levels &amp; hundreds of missions….<br>
<br>
In this unique and soothing game, you exercise your number, color and shape-based pattern recognition while resting your analytical mind in a tactile and meditative experience.  <br>
<br>
WITH COLOR HUNT YOU CAN<br/>
▶ PLAY the full Coloring Jigsaw Board game experience offline and on the go.<br/>
▶ CLICK to play and navigate between 100+ levels, categories, daily levels, and missions<br/>
▶ GET more levels, category packs, and art exhibit customers.<br/>
▶ BUILD UP art galleries and daily level streaks<br/>
▶ EARN extra money by completing daily level streaks and mission.<br/>
▶ SOLVE over a hundred randomly generated grid based levels that get harder as you go.<br/>
<br/>
WHY PLAY COLOR HUNT?<br/>
▶ RELIEVE your stress with smooth and tactile jigsaw coloring controls<br/>
▶ LEVELS which get harder every time and require skills and pattern recognition to be beaten.<br/>
▶ CUSTOMIZE galleries by building and improving art exhibits for each completed picture.<br/>
▶ CONSTRUCT GALLERIES and attract an audience.<br/>
▶ LEARN to recognize number, color and shape based patterns on a randomly generated grid <br/>
▶ ACHIEVE infinite daily streaks and completion on hundreds of missions!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox Trot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743060/Fox_Trot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get ready to run, jump, duck, and dodge your way through the forest with our newest game, <strong>Fox Trot!</strong> Play as a speedy little fox on a mission to collect as many coins as possible while avoiding dangerous animals and obstacles in your path.<br/><br/>With each passing moment, the forest changes and the obstacles get trickier, so you'll need to be quick on your feet (or paws) to survive. Use your sharp reflexes and lightning-fast instincts to dodge everything from trees and rocks to sneaky critters and raging bears.<br/>But don't worry, you're not alone on this journey. Along the way, you'll get power ups, to help add to your score while unlocking <i>cool new skins</i> with the coins you collect.<br/><br/>On top of all that you will also have the opportunity to collect <i>daily login rewards</i> as well as <i>complete daily challenges</i>!<br/><br/>So what are you waiting for? It's time to channel your inner fox and show the world what you're made of. With endless gameplay and infinite fun, Fox Trot is the perfect game for anyone who loves a good challenge and a lot of laughs. <br/><br/><strong>Download it now and let the running begin!</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acid Planet: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2837110/Acid_Planet_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ACID PLANET: PROLOGUE features the thrilling first mission of Acid Planet. Under the careful watch of Cpt. Briggs, you'll learn the basics of planetary survival and kaiju hunting techniques. <br/><br/><i>Acid Planet is a Strategic Wave-Defense game with elements of Action Roguelike, RTS and Horde-Survival. It's a game for people who like building, strategy, quick runs, risk-reward trade-offs and battles on an epic scale. </i><h2 class="bb_tag">BUILD YOUR BASE</h2>Construct towers and drone factories to defend your ship from the horde. Build support towers to buff your offensive capabilities - placement matters. Develop your economy for future waves.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837110/extras/GG1.gif?t=1709585429"><h2 class="bb_tag">FIGHT THE HORDE</h2>Deploy exotic weaponry and armies of drones to repel waves of mutated monsters. Guide swarms, flank siege monsters and battle challenging elites. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837110/extras/GG2.gif?t=1709585429"><h2 class="bb_tag">EVOLVE TO PERFECTION</h2>Choose a powerful new ability or upgrade after every wave. Get strong enough to bag an Emperor-class Kaiju. If you're a real hot-shot you can challenge the hellish and experimental HYPER-EVO protocol.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837110/extras/GG3.gif?t=1709585429"><br/><br/><br/><i>On the Acid Planet (formerly known as Earth), human beings have sadly become extinct. Under the toxic clouds, hordes of rampaging bio-monsters run wild and have grown to gigantic size. <br/><br/>As a SCAV Corporation clone, you will conduct salvage operations from our orbital station. Be aware of monster activity on the surface. Your top priority is the capture of the Kaiju cores. Human crew are expendable as required. Good luck!</i><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play the challenging first mission of Acid Planet<br/></li><li>Action Tower-Defense gameplay with RTS and Roguelite elements<br/></li><li>Defend against massive swarms of monsters and gigantic Kaiju<br/></li><li>Control your hero and command armies of drones in real-time<br/></li><li>Huge variety of synergetic towers, drones, perks, crew-members and upgrades<br/></li><li>Original soundtrack by Cletus Lupus<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837110/extras/SP1.gif?t=1709585429"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2837110/extras/flames-600.gif?t=1709585429"/></img></li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discarnate: Locust</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2555750/Discarnate_Locust/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2555750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is not going to be the easy path. Trust me..."They say the path to hell is paved with good intentions... then I am saved... this must be the path to heaven"... In this groundbreaking Horror/Puzzle game, we will test your abilities to their full extent, you will be tasked with retrieving an item that has been locked away in the depths of a seemingly abandoned house, and that is all the information you will get. Fight your way through vengeful spirits while at the same time dealing with the most intricate, brain twisting puzzles in the world. Do not be fooled into thinking this is "just a game". Only the enlightened few shall claim the fruits of their labor. <br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2555750/extras/SelfReliance.png?t=1709576162"><br/>We will not hold your hand through puzzles or make the test linear and easy to follow. We aim to conduct a test of skills, a test able to challenge every player equally and fairly. Every puzzle can be completed with the clues inside the house, Every puzzle is solvable, Every puzzle is challenging in its own way. There is no clue or hint system in our test, once you enter you are fully on your own until completion or failure. Only the enlightened few shall claim the fruits of their labor.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2555750/extras/Handcrafted.png?t=1709576162"><br/>Every single puzzle in our game has been hand-crafted by our team in order to push your mental capacity to its limits. Be assured that the answer to our test cannot be found online. Only the enlightened few shall claim the fruits of their labor.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Umbra Fields</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2652040/Umbra_Fields/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652040/extras/Wishlist_now.gif?t=1709575995"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652040/extras/Choose.gif?t=1709575995"><br/><br/>No matter what you choose, and what you do, you will have an impact upon the world. Do you wish to be a criminal, or a savior? That is up to you.<br/><br/>Choose between 15 distinct classes:<br/><br/>Warrior: A well balanced with a focus on strength. Made to do any quests.<br/><br/>Doctor: Healers that can heal the sickness across each nation, yet are weak on their own.<br/><br/>Thief: Shopkeepers never sell to them, with their moves constantly under watch. Going to The Prison, is the least of the thief's worries.<br/><br/>Hunter: They live for the hunt and the slaughter. They can be found to get good pay from hunting rare beasts.<br/><br/>Rune Master: The old and intelligent beings that can read cosmic words.<br/><br/>Summoner: They can summon creatures to protect themselves. Hated by most, they are targeted for creating abominations upon the world.<br/><br/>Ice Spearmen: Fishermen who fish whenever they can find any remaining, clean water.<br/><br/>Investigator: A detective that can use guns, talk to enemies when able, and can take on cases for others. If you are cunning enough, some will join you by speech alone.<br/><br/>Priest: The Gods need priests to spread their holy words, teaching them holy magic. <br/><br/>Brute: A Warrior that has no honor, fierce in the wild, yet cannot live among civilization.<br/><br/>Storm Evoker: The Forbidden one was one of these, a being that can control the storms. The outcasts worship Evokers, others fear them.<br/><br/>Fowler: Flying beasts that can travel to any place they please, but are hunted.<br/><br/>Fire Elemental: Due to the Great War, The Flame has made all Fire Elemental to be worshiped and adored. Yet not all feel the same way.<br/><br/>The Slime: A mistake not meant to live. An experiment to remove all bones so you can no longer be injured and stronger in battle, it comes with a downside. Your body is made out of a liquid mush that is weak to everything. Only those who wish for pain choose the slime<br/><br/>The Blameless: One who is random with their speech, and their spells. They cannot be blamed for their actions, as every time they open their mouths, it is unknown what will come out. Beasts of the Umbra Fields attack them last, knowing their randomness can be beneficial. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652040/extras/survive.gif?t=1709575995"><br/><br/>Whatever you become, you shall be the prey of others from man to beast. Master who you are and what you will become to manage your stamina, hit weaknesses, stun enemies, and kill to survive. Do quests to get stronger, to learn more to use more magics and skills.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652040/extras/choose2.gif?t=1709575995"><br/><br/>The Flame: A land of The Flame, an active volcano where Fire Elementals are born.<br/><br/>The Land of the Sea: A land once known for it's Ice, it has become melted to be a grand Sea.<br/><br/>The Gaea Forrest: The last of nature, all connected to the goddess Gaea.<br/><br/>Angelic Constabulary: A land for the last of the an holy order that wants to maintain law.<br/><br/>The Prison: Those who break the law are sent to the Prison to rot, while it's controlled by a Mafia.<br/><br/>Lich Fields: Sky islands full of the rot and sickness where Wizards and Summoners roam free.<br/><br/>Pig Nation: A nation isolated from the rest after The Great War, run by the pigs who have no God.<br/><br/>No Man's Land: The only thing that connects the nations together, only the outcasts live here and the beasts roam free.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion Fling</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2756030/Fusion_Fling/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2652040/Umbra_Fields/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2652040/Umbra_Fields/</a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822390/Whiteout_Frontier/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2822390/Whiteout_Frontier/</a><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2858360/Critterball_Derby/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2858360/Critterball_Derby/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2756030/extras/FusionFling.gif?t=1709575784"><br/>You are contracted by Blue Billy Bear to create fusions of different items, and to manage the sizes of them in this puzzle adventure to prevent overflow! Strategically match, fling, and fuse many creative and new fusions to gain more score.  Challenge using new fusions to conquer the leaderboard. How many new fusion combinations can you create? Those who experiment will be rewarded with higher scores.<br/><strong>General Overview</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fling items into the arena with simple moving of the mouse and clicking to flick items.<br/></li><li> Fling items together to create a fusion which creates a new item.<br/></li><li> Create fusions to discover more combinations of items combining to make new items and gain more points.<br/></li><li> Manage the size of your Items through fusions and interactions.<br/></li><li> The biggest thing to interact with is Nuclear Balls. They can contaminate items that touch them, or improve them. Every time they contaminate, they shrink. Blowing one up increases the size of Nuclear Balls overall. <br/></li><li> If Nuclear balls get too big, or items gets too small, then it's game over.<br/></li><li> Calculate the score and see where you fair on the leaderboard.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sixty Four</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2659900/Sixty_Four/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Upgrade a factory in an extraordinary world. Progress to unlock new resources and machines, leading to new ways to expand and grow.<br/><br/><strong>❒ From Foundation to Complexity</strong><br/><br/>Begin your journey with a simple machine generating distinct cubes. Use combinations of cubes to unlock advanced machinery and new gameplay elements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_3a_smaller.gif?t=1709591697"><br/><br/><strong>❒ An Evolving Factory Adventure</strong><br/><br/>Your factory is not just a collection of idle machines; it's a dynamic environment of challenges and strategy. Face new situations and discover opportunities with every innovative and abstract machine you encounter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_4a_smaller.gif?t=1709591697"><br/><strong>❒ A Fresh Mix of Gaming Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Sixty Four combines simple yet engaging elements from idle, incremental, and strategy games. Pursue constant improvement and unravel the secrets behind messages from an unknown entity.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2659900/extras/tst_5a_smaller.gif?t=1709591697"><br/><br/>Music by Jake Chudnow						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReThink 3.5</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2838460/ReThink_35/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2838460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ReThink 3.5 is one of the first person puzzle games I made during the pandemic time, but could not release for a variety of reasons. <br>
I rebuilt the game in Unreal Engine 5, so that all the content that was in the game will not be wasted and is accessible to those who want to play through it. <br>
This also allows the game to utilize and benefit from all the other improvements that were made for the newer games, resulting in a better experience.<br>
<br>
As the Name implies, the game fits between ReThink 3 and 4 in terms of how the puzzles are designed, but it also comes with its own unique feature that is not in the newer games (yet).<br>
<br>
Content wise, there are more than 40 puzzles in the game, all built around the utilization of lasers and logic.<br/>
<br/>
On the technical side of things, the game comes with improved performance over the previously released ReThink games. <br/>
Especially slower CPUs and Graphics cards should benefit from this*, while players with faster hardware also should see improved performance.<br/>
<br/>
Graphically, the games peaceful setting looks great on highest settings, while still looking like the older games (ReThink 1-3) on lower settings - retaining its compatibility with older hardware. (In fact, the rebuilt game runs a lot better than the original one would have.)<br/>
<br/>
*System requirements and the engines driver requirements still apply.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thaumaturge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684350/The_Thaumaturge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/TT_claim_EN_small.png?t=1709581107"><br/><strong>The Thaumaturge is an isometric, story-rich RPG with a unique take on turn-based combat, character development features, and investigation mechanics</strong>, facing you with morally ambiguous choices – set in a world teeming with mysterious powers and strange ethereal beings called <strong>salutors</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/City_3-01.gif?t=1709581107"><br/><br/>The year is 1905. Warsaw lives under the yoke of imperial Russian tsardom. Its inhabitants constitute a diverse group of different ancestries, views, and beliefs with often conflicting interests: Russian soldiers, Jewish merchants, Polish townspeople, and more. Despite the circumstances, the city is a buzzing metropolis, where one can attend a breathtaking party with the high society, and later get robbed in one of the dark alleys of the Praga district. A city of great hopes and dreams on one hand and dark desires on the other.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Buka_2.gif?t=1709581107"><br/><br/>A <strong>thaumaturge</strong> bears both a gift and a burden at the same time. This parallel holds true for <strong>Wiktor Szulski</strong>, the game’s titular protagonist, who is drawn back to the tumultuous streets of 20th-century Warsaw by family matters. The gift of thaumaturgy is intertwined with family legacy, passed down through one's ancestors. This mystical inheritance significantly shapes Wiktor’s life journey tied around a pursuit of unearthly entities and their hosts. As only a thaumaturge can tame these ethereal entities - known to a select few as <strong>salutors</strong> - utilizing their mystical abilities to discover secrets hidden within the human soul and speak to the Darkness, no one understands quite like Wiktor how everyone suffers their own demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Wiktor_3-01.gif?t=1709581107"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Shape your story</strong> – as a full-fledged RPG, it allows you to alternate your choices and make you deal with the aftermath. <br/></li><li><strong>Develop your character</strong> – creating your own version of the thaumaturge will allow you to approach situations in different ways. <br/></li><li><strong>Experience unique turn-based combat</strong> and defeat your foes using human attacks and skills as well as psychic strikes delivered by salutors.<br/></li><li><strong>Influence and manipulate</strong> the temperaments of other characters to bend their will to your liking. <br/></li><li><strong>Tame the power of salutors</strong> – use the unique set of their skills to gain an advantage while exploring the world and when bringing your adversaries to their knees. <br/></li><li><strong>See the world that’s inevitably gone</strong> – explore the uncommon, heavily researched historic period of the early XX century Warsaw, where crime and luxury are often two sides of the same coin. Meet historical figures and learn about their involvement in the story. <br/></li><li><strong>Created in Unreal Engine 5</strong> to deliver a detailed &amp; beautifully crafted world.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across Kiloparsecs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2505080/Across_Kiloparsecs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2505080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The accidental death of a good friend has left you stunned.<br/><br/>As you begin to come to terms with this new reality, you find hints that maybe it wasn't an accident after all.<br/><br/>Discover what <strong>really</strong> happened on your home station in this short science-fiction visual novel. Someone is hiding something, and it's up to you to find out what. Was it just an accident, or a murder? Powerful forces could be at work and you might be endangering not only your life, but the lives of your closest friends.<br/><br/>Experience branching storytelling where your choices have consequences in this visually-rich tale featuring a full cast of characters.<br/><br/>This game has a soundtrack of space-themed ambient music composed by Bloodless Mushroom.<br/><br/>This is a prologue to the upcoming tactical space strategy game "Kiloparsec Uprising".<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2644180/Kiloparsec_Uprising/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2644180/Kiloparsec_Uprising/</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild West Saloon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2571670/Wild_West_Saloon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2571670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2571670/extras/header_1_en.png?t=1709585507"><br/>Buy tables and shelves. Fill shelves with beverages like beer or whisky. Hire waitresses and other workers to help you make your customers happy.<br/>Remember - happy customers are paying customers!<br/>But also keep an eye on your workers happiness, otherwise they might leave you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2571670/extras/header_2_en.png?t=1709585507"><br/>Besides all of your customers being thirsty some customers enter also your saloon hungry. Build a kitchen and cook them some food.<br/>Serving food pays better but requires more work. You can also hire chefs to help you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2571670/extras/header_3_en.png?t=1709585507"><br/>You can place objects and decorations freely in your saloon. Choose between multiple objects to place, like tables, shelves, bars, furnaces and more!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connor</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2762220/Connor/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into the heart-pounding world of '<strong>Connor</strong>,' an immersive VR adventure that seamlessly blends intense action, strategic shooting, exhilarating driving, and challenging platforming. As Connor, an elite agent, you find yourself thrust into a high-stakes mission when your wife is kidnapped by the Hive—an enigmatic rival organization with a grand vision for global transformation.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762220/extras/Guns.png?t=1709576327"><br/>Embark on a relentless quest through a series of time-sensitive levels, each set in diverse environments ranging from bustling malls to labyrinthine warehouses, bustling docks, a perilous tanker, a speeding train, a soaring plane, and a high-speed car chase. The clock is ticking, adding an extra layer of urgency to your mission. Every second counts as you navigate through dynamic scenarios, utilizing a combination of sharpshooting skills, precise driving manoeuvres, and agile platforming to overcome challenges and adversaries.<br/><br/>'Connor' offers a riveting single-player experience that pushes the boundaries of VR gaming, delivering a seamless fusion of various gameplay elements. Immerse yourself in a cinematic narrative, fuelled by the pursuit of rescuing your loved one and thwarting the Hive's world-altering plans. With stylized visuals, responsive controls, and a pulse-pounding soundtrack, 'Connor' is poised to be an unforgettable VR journey that demands skill, speed, and strategy. Are you ready to take on the Hive and rewrite the fate of the world?<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F7s9xuk2Vc7" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/7s9xuk2Vc7</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2762220/extras/joindisord.png?t=1709576327"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andarin Weppes: Pre-Dementia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2361510/Andarin_Weppes_PreDementia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FE7RXsHcppA" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361510/extras/dc300x60__1_.png?t=1709571607"/></a> <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/NextInGame/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361510/extras/Steam_FollowUs.jpg?t=1709571607"/></a><br/><br/>Step into the tangled mind of a dementia patient as he visits the house of his late grandpa, who also suffered from the ethereal embrace of dementia. Witness your perception warp, gravity surrender its grasp and the very essence of space and time tumble into a puzzling dance as your advancing dementia twists your reality into the unfamiliar.<h2 class="bb_tag">Pre-Dementia</h2><br/>Play through <strong>6 levels</strong> and acquaint yourself with the early stages of dementia where your illness only mildly affects your mind. You'll notice and have to overcome subtle anomalies in your environment. Explore as much of the house as you can and get familiar with the environment before your illness starts affecting you more severely.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Key Features</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>A Surreal Dwelling:</strong> Explore a once-familiar house now shrouded in the mystique of dementia. Traverse its non-Euclidean environments, where up and down lose meaning, and rooms meld in perplexing arrangements.<br/></li><li><strong>Unravel Puzzles:</strong> Engage your mind in solving intricate puzzles scattered throughout the enigmatic abode. Each riddle holds a piece of the profound story that connects memories, dreams, and reality.<br/></li><li><strong>Journey Through Memory:</strong> Witness the convergence of memories and delusions as you venture deeper into the shifting chambers of the mind. Experience the blurred boundaries between lucidity and illusion.<br/></li><li><strong>Ambiguous Reality:</strong> Embrace the uncertainty. Prepare to question what is real and what is not, as the lines between reality blur.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361510/extras/DropGif.gif?t=1709571607"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Rewind:</strong> Fear no more from mistakes of the past.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361510/extras/RewindGif.gif?t=1709571607"><br/><br/>Prepare your mind for a symphony of illusions and truths, and immerse yourself in a journey where the journey and the destination are an enigma. Dare to tread the paths that defy reason and embrace the boundless realm of a dementia inflicted mind. Step forth into the mysteries of Andarin Weppes:Pre-Dementia and uncover the surreal truth that awaits within.</img></li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VaporAeon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798390/VaporAeon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into the vibrant world of retro-futuristic sports with the latest game from Brindle Development, a 2D Vaporwave Volleyball extravaganza! Embrace the casual yet competitive spirit of arcade gaming as you experience the thrill of precision platforming in this colorful journey.<br/><br/>Immersed in stylized visuals reminiscent of the 1980s, our game offers a unique atmosphere that blends seamlessly with the world of sports and artificial intelligence. Engage in intense matches with friends or challenge AI opponents as you navigate through a dynamic 2D platformer environment.<br/><br/>Key Features:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Character Customization: Personalize your avatar and stand out on the neon-lit volleyball court.<br/></li><li>Artificial Intelligence: Test your skills against advanced AI opponents for a challenging single-player experience.</li></ul><br/>Whether you prefer multiplayer mayhem or solo play, our game caters to all types of players. Play locally with friends in co-op or local multiplayer mode, or connect online for thrilling matches against players from around the world.<br/><br/>Get ready to serve, spike, and score in this atmospheric sports adventure that pays homage to the golden era of the '80s. Are you up for the challenge? Take the court and let the retro gaming excitement begin!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOVA CORE CHAOS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2738480/NOVA_CORE_CHAOS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738480/extras/NCC_NAME.gif?t=1709568013"><br/><br/>NOVA CORE CHAOS is a chaotic co-op cooking game for one to five players. You and your fellow robot friends need to work as a team to prep and fill energy cores with their designated elements to help customers evolve into the Novas they want to be! But be fast, these customers don't like waiting too long!<br/><br/><strong>CUSTOMERS NEED CORES, YOU NEED TO CRAFT!</strong><br/>Robots will come flooding in, asking for a energy core, so they too can have awesome powers just like you. It's your job to grab the empty energy cores, refine their shape and fill them with the correct energy sources. If you give a customer the wrong Nova-core, they'll end up angry! Make too many customers angry and you'll lose the game! So stay focused while making your energy cores. There's a total of 20 different combinations for you to make!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738480/extras/STORE_RUN.gif?t=1709568013"><br/><br/><strong>5 UNIQUE NOVAS, 5 UNIQUE PLAYSTYLES</strong><br/>Every playable Nova has their own unique ability to help make the energy cores. Use these to speed up the workflow! Each Nova can only be picked once, but every Nova can help out with every task!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738480/extras/STORE_GIF_ABILITY.gif?t=1709568013"><br/><br/><strong>UP TO 5 PLAYERS</strong><br/>Work alone or together with up to 5 friends to help the customers evolve into a Nova! Just invite a friend from you friends list and start making energy cores!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2738480/extras/STORE_CLAPPING.gif?t=1709568013"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behold Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2338910/Behold_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2338910/extras/gifbb3.gif?t=1709567781"><br/>Guess which army will win, and watch them fight for your amusement. Behold Battle is a simple auto battler, where you see heroes and monsters fight to the death in randomly generated battles.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/>- A normal game mode that has 20 rounds with increasing army complexity. Guess correctly to continue, or game over if you are wrong too many times.<br/><br/>- A simulator where you create both armies and watch them battle.<br/><br/>- 72 different units, some with unique attacks such as spawning undead minions.<br/><br/>- From small to gigantic battles, and many difficulties to test your prediction powers.<br/><br/>- Gold betting mode, and a spell mode where each side gets a random spell.<br/><br/>- Complete challenges to earn more spectators.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mortal Glory 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2216660/Mortal_Glory_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif1.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en1.png?t=1709567748"><br/>Roll an explosive barrel at your enemy, throw them into a pit or take out two enemies by knocking them into each other. With a wide variety of tools available to you, your creativity will determine how you deal with the competition. Unique arenas, randomized environments and occasional special rules ensure that each fight offers new tactical opportunities.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif2.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en2.png?t=1709567748"><br/>A wide variety of fantasy races are seeking glory, each with their own unique racial strengths. Whatever your tactics are, finding the best recruits is essential!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif3.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en3.png?t=1709567748"><br/>There is a vast collection of unique relics, character perks and more to discover. Finding clever combos and deadly synergies will unlock new strategies and occasionally turn your gladiators into unfairly strong demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif5.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en6.png?t=1709567748"><br/>Various difficulty settings will accommodate your preferred playstyle and there are increasingly harder challenges to master. But beware... The AI is brutally talented at the highest levels.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif6.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en4.png?t=1709567748"><br/>With every step comes a new challenge or perhaps... an opportunity? It is up to you to guide where your team should travel next... and suffer the consequences.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/gif4.gif?t=1709567748"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/en5.png?t=1709567748"><br/>Each playthrough is different! With various tactics to try and additional increasingly harder challenges to master, the arena will keep welcoming you back again and again. Thanks to conveniently paced combat, Mortal Glory 2 is also great to play if you only have a moment to spare.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2216660/extras/EndHead.png?t=1709567748"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Red Button</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2828820/The_Red_Button/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2828820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">- Man vs The Red Button</h2>You are in front of a red button you must no press.<br/>Will you dare to defy the unknown, or will you walk away, forever wondering what could have been?<br/>Only the strongest will be rewarded and enter the Empty Place.<br/><br/>This game includes:<br/>- A button<br/>- A choice<br/>- 10 ranks to climb. <br/>- 80.6mb of data<br/>- You don't need a mouse, a keyboard or even a screen to play it.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2828820/extras/9b734b1ec653705b191ad649de2fb806.gif?t=1709566985"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unknown</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658180/The_Unknown/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the mind of Mike and explore the depths of a twisted reality in this heart-pounding psychological horror first-person platformer. Dodge deadly obstacles at every turn and unravel the truth hidden deep within Mike's psych as you navigate his tormented memories.<br/><br/><strong>But beware; she is watching your every move.</strong> <br/><br/>Can you solve the puzzles and escape this nightmarish world before its too late?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658180/extras/scary.gif?t=1709562749">.<br/><br/><strong>Solve Puzzles</strong><br/><br/>Master the nightmarish world within Mike's mind and, solve puzzles as you work your way back to reality. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658180/extras/puzzle.gif?t=1709562749">.<br/><br/><br/><br/><strong>Dodge deadly obstacles</strong><br/><br/>Plan each move carefully; and avoid deadly obstacles.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658180/extras/Saws.gif?t=1709562749">.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><strong>Psychological Puzzle Solving:</strong> Delve into the depths of Mike's mind as you solve intricate puzzles and unravel the mysteries of his suppressed memories.<br/><br/><strong>Immersive Atmospheric Experience:</strong> Immerse yourself in a hauntingly atmospheric world, where every shadow and sound contribute to the suspenseful and emotional journey.<br/><strong><br/>Precision Dodging:</strong> Master the art of precision dodging as you narrowly escape the razor-sharp edges of deadly saws. Each movement counts, making every evasion a pulse-pounding moment of skill and strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Sinister Narration:</strong> Experience an unsettling narrative as the tormenting voice narrates Mike's journey, injecting a sinister tone into every revelation and decision, creating an immersive and eerie storytelling experience.<br/><br/><strong>Do you have what it takes to escape the unknown?</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WE ARE FOOTBALL 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1951410/WE_ARE_FOOTBALL_2024/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1951410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to <strong>WE ARE FOOTBALL 2024</strong> – the NEW football management experience from the creators of the legendary On the Ball and EA SPORTS FIFA Manager Series! Dive into the world of football like never before. Choose an existing club or start your own. Manage either men or women, lead your club to new heights, and become the next manager legend!<br/><br/>Be there with your team on the pitch. In our immersive 3D game engine, you can directly influence the action on the pitch through instructional shouts. Simulate the same game a thousand times over, witness matches 50 years into the future or switch between games in conference mode on match day. Relive highlights, analyze goals, and enjoy a comprehensive season summary.<br/><br/><strong>WE ARE FOOTBALL 2024</strong> offers an extensive feature set to adapt the game to your needs, including a powerful external editor to set up league systems, clubs, players, managers, employees, referees, sponsors, fan chants, derbies, and more. Configure the game to your skill level and preferences with over 100 options and difficulty settings to make this YOUR road to glory.<br/><br/>Now immerse yourself in the thrill of football management with <strong>WE ARE FOOTBALL 2024</strong>!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1951410/extras/WAF2024_Teaser-Social_England_616x200_25fps.gif?t=1709564071"><h2 class="bb_tag">KEY FEATURES</h2><br/><strong>User Interface and Technical Enhancements:</strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Clear menu with tabs and customizable wing menus for easy navigation <br/></li><li>In-game editor for changing club and player data at any time<br/></li><li>Over 12,000 generic AI-generated pictures and aging youth players for realism<br/></li><li>21:9 monitor support <br/></li><li>Hotseat multiplayer for up to 4 players</li></ul> <br/><strong>Game Content:</strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>3 game modes for club play: Free club selection, club creation, and career mode<br/></li><li>Develop your own managerial skills and use individual skill development trees for each player<br/></li><li>Diverse manager functions (finance, sponsors, HR, organization, fan support, and more)<br/></li><li>Organize your own tournaments and preseason tours<br/></li><li>Extensive options for play styles, formations, and other tactical instructions<br/></li><li>Modern training and realistic training schedules, including training groups<br/></li><li>Team chemistry with player relationships, hierarchies, and effects of player hobbies<br/></li><li>Simply click on players to watch their previous goals<br/></li><li>Comprehensive youth area with screening days, headhunting campaigns, youth boarding schools, and expandable international youth centers for early talent discovery<br/></li><li>Improved transfer market where your personal reputation as a negotiator counts<br/></li><li>Stadium editor that lets you expand, upgrade, and customize your home ground<br/></li><li>Expandable 3D club grounds with new buildings and many new details and improvements <br/></li><li>Optional simulation of the manager's private life, including family and children who can start a professional football career or become a department head at your club</li></ul> <br/><strong>National Team Integration:</strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Separate European Championship and World Cup modes for both men and women<br/></li><li>Option to choose a national team to manage directly at the start of the game or long-term takeover offers for national teams during gameplay</li></ul><br/><strong>Match: </strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>3D match display with 9 cameras, slow motion, replay, live rating changes, and optional action boxes with additional information within scenes <br/></li><li>See your tactical instructions implemented on the pitch <br/></li><li>New "Tactical Analysis" option provides information on how the result came about <br/></li><li>Short or long 3D scenes and an alternative quick calculation <br/></li><li>Intervene during the match in decision-making situations by giving commands to the players </li></ul><br/><strong>Editor: </strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Edit any country in the world with both women’s and men's leagues <br/></li><li>Fully editable league systems with promotion/relegation regulations, cups, and playoffs <br/></li><li>Automatic creation of leagues, teams, and players <br/></li><li>Extensive editors for logos and jerseys with integration options for your own graphics <br/></li><li>Automatic conversion of existing WAF databases </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1951410/extras/WAF2024_Logo_Steam.png?t=1709564071"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bullet Bunny</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2317880/Bullet_Bunny/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2317880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FXnftUHWK8e" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2317880/extras/discrod.png?t=1709560653"/></a><br/><br/>Fight and fend off waves of enemies in this twin stick shooter game with rogue-like elements!<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2317880/extras/key_feautures2.png?t=1709560653"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Twin-stick shooter <br/></li><li> Rogue-like: As you play, you will unlock new characters, guns, and backgear!<br/></li><li> Level up and choose from over 75 powerups!     <br/></li><li> Characters are unique with there own supers and passives!<br/></li><li> Different modes like Endless Mode &amp; Dark Mode!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Variety of Guns</h2> Tons of guns to choose from, ranging from your basic pistol to intense toxic blasters. Unlock and master them all!<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2317880/extras/2024-01-23_15-07-15.gif?t=1709560653"><h2 class="bb_tag">Hero's with unique Supers</h2> Characters are unique with their own supers and passives. From magnet throwing bunnies to blood bursting spells, each character offers a different experience. More characters planned post-launch. <br/><br/>  <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2317880/extras/2024-01-23_14-03-10_-_Trim.gif?t=1709560653"><h2 class="bb_tag">Powerups &amp; Masteries</h2> Every time you level up choose from over 75 powerups. Find what powerups suit you best and build the most overpowered set up!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2317880/extras/pain_snowy_-_Trim.gif?t=1709560653"><h2 class="bb_tag">Intense Bosses</h2> Defeat intense bosses every run!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2317880/extras/Nikki_forest_rain_-_Trim.gif?t=1709560653"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazy Mind</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2380340/Hazy_Mind/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2380340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FnzV7AUMzJz" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2380340/extras/teststeamdescription0.png?t=1709560566"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2380340/extras/teststeamdescription.png?t=1709560566"><br/>You wake up in your room, feeling disoriented, with no recollection of anything.<br/><br/>In the midst of your confusion, you come across a person you don't recognize. Who is she, and why is she in your home?<br/>But the central question lingers: why can't you remember anything?<br/><br/>To find answers, you realize you must converse with that stranger. <strong>The decision of whether to trust her or remain cautious now lies in your hands</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2380340/extras/teststeamdescription3.png?t=1709560566"><br/><strong>- Voice acting<br/>- Multiple endings for varied gameplay experiences<br/>- A captivating and intriguing story<br/>- Interactive storytelling that keeps players engaged<br/>- Truly horrifying soundtracks that intensify the atmosphere</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2380340/extras/teststeamdescription2.png?t=1709560566"><br/>Over time, more screenshots and a gameplay trailer will be added. I will continually update and provide all necessary information, ensuring you don't miss anything.<br/>Thank you for your attention!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gauntlet</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701020/The_Gauntlet/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701020/extras/SteamDescriptionGIF_1.gif?t=1709557306"><br/>The Gauntlet is a new Game Show hosted by a notorious evil master-mind known as Bad Bat. You, one of his new contestants, must race through a multitude of lethal obstacle courses all of which have been designed with your demise in mind. If you can make it through Bad Bat’s chambers the fastest, you can leave with the Grand Prize! Your Life.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701020/extras/SteamDescriptionGIF_2.gif?t=1709557306"><br/><strong>Campaign</strong><br/>Sprint, slide, jump and ride your way through a variety of obstacles as you experience Bad Bat’s brutal Game Show in campaign mode. Do what you need to get to the end, but just make sure that when you enter that elevator, that you are not the slowest contestant.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701020/extras/SteamDescriptionGIF_3.gif?t=1709557306"><br/><strong>Speedrun Mode</strong><br/>Think you could have gone even faster in a particular gauntlet? Once you complete the campaign you will unlock “Speedrun Mode” in which you can tackle each Gauntlet whenever you want. Work on new routes, tackle different obstacles and work towards a new high-score!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hey! Here are some letters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2745650/Hey_Here_are_some_letters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Okay, so you have these letters, right? You can combine them into words, like this. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745650/extras/word_small_longer.gif?t=1709557125"><br/><br/>You click on the word to get a score for the number/type of letters you have in the word. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745650/extras/word_clear.gif?t=1709557125"><br/>(You get 8 points for the word, "WORD", as 4 + 1 + 1 + 2 = 8)<br/><br/>If two or more words share any letters, they join into a group, When you clear the group, you get a multiplier score for each word in the group.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745650/extras/ClearWord.gif?t=1709557125"><br/><br/>There are two modes, an Endless Mode, and a Matrix Mode.<br/><br/>In the Endless Mode, new letters spawn and are added to the grid every time the timer bar runs out. The new letters spawn faster and faster as time goes on.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745650/extras/Endless.png?t=1709557125"><br/><br/>In the Matrix Mode, every tile in the grid is filled in, and the goal is to clear all of the letters to get the highest score you can.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2745650/extras/Matrix.png?t=1709557125"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Up !</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2842590/Only_Up/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842590/extras/003.gif?t=1709581344"><br/><br/>⭐⭐⭐ Embark on an exciting journey in Only UP ! Play as Jacky, a teenager from the ghetto who wants to get out of poverty and join the wealth of the Space ! As you explore a huge world full of secrets and mysteries, you will have to climb as high as possible ! ⭐⭐⭐ <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842590/extras/002.gif?t=1709581344"><br/><br/>Cross abandoned favelas, haunted factories, arid deserts, Japanese cities culminating at several thousand miles of altitude, a cemetery of planes and dinosaurs! Reach the highest peak of this mysterious island to deserve your trip to Space !<br/><br/>Only Up begins in a junkyard, where the player character, Jacky, must run, climb, jump, and vault through assorted objects and platforms. Around the map, there are beds the player can use as trampolines to skip portions of the obstacle course. The player must reach the top of the map to win the game and may slow down time to control Jacky's movements. There are no checkpoints and the player cannot save their progress...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842590/extras/004.gif?t=1709581344"><br/><br/>🏃Try to become the best speedrunner and compare your time with other runners ! 🏃<br/><br/>Features: <br/><br/>-Biggest map yet<br/>-Speedrunning features<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842590/extras/001.gif?t=1709581344"><br/><br/>Best World Record: (updated daily)<br/> <br/>1* LeGrekko:   42,42 Min<br/>2* Kaiser003:  48,49 Min<br/>3* Yuan09xo:  49,32 Min<br/><br/>Join the leaderboard by sharing a video of your performance and your Steam' nickname will appear in the TOP 3 !						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Did It?</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2430280/Who_Did_It/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2430280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to the Federal State Police!</h2>Who Did It? Is a detective puzzle-game. Your job is to read the given case files, clues &amp; suspect info to find out who the murderer is!<br/><br/>The game has 30 detailed, completely unique cases to complete in 4 difficulty's!<br/>Are you a real detective and can you master them all? Can you finally close the case?<br/><br/>You play as a intern-detective at the Federal State Police. Your job is to place all suspects in the correct rooms using the given clues. You have a few try's or just one depending on the difficulty.<br/><br/>Featuring a storyline connecting the levels together.<br/>Do you have what it takes to master all 30 cases and close them all for good?<br/><br/>We only have one question left for you to answer:<br/><i>Who Did It?</i><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 30 Detailed, Completely Unique Cases.<br/></li><li> 4 Difficulty Modes From Easy to Really Hard.<br/></li><li> Clues, Hints and Suspect-info Per Case.<br/></li><li> storyline Connecting the Levels together<br/></li><li> Soundtrack and Atmospheric Audio<br/></li><li> Game Stats (see What Progress You've Made!)</li></ul><br/>Don't miss any future updates! Subscribe to our newsletter now! <br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fbeldrproductions.nl%2Fnewsletter" rel="noopener" target="_blank">http://beldrproductions.nl/newsletter</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win or Crash!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840050/Win_or_Crash/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Win or Crash! is a heart-pumping racing game that will push your driving skills to the limit. <br>
<br>
You'll find yourself racing on an incredibly dangerous track that winds its way high above the ground, testing your reflexes and nerves like never before. As you navigate the treacherous course, you'll need to avoid obstacles and stay on the track as you push your car to its limits. But the track is so dangerous that it's almost inevitable that you'll skid off at some point. <br>
<br>
That's where the real fun begins! When you crash, your car will automatically deploy its wings, helping you to glide back onto the track and get back into the race. But don't let that fool you into thinking that you can just careen off the track without consequence. You'll still lose precious time and risk falling too far behind to catch up with your opponents.<br>
<br>
With stunning graphics and heart-pounding action, Win or Crash! is a racing game like no other. Can you navigate the treacherous track and come out on top? Play the game and find out!<br/>
<br/>
Game features :<br/>
-	High-stakes racing<br/>
-	Stunning graphics<br/>
-	6 participants						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Roller Coaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840030/Sky_Roller_Coaster/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for a heart-pounding adventure like no other in the exhilarating Sky Roller Coaster game! This adrenaline-fueled thrill ride is not for the faint of heart, so we strongly advise against eating before embarking on this wild journey. <br>
<br>
Inspired by the iconic American roller coasters, Sky Roller Coaster promises pulse-pounding excitement at every turn. However, amidst the excitement lies unforeseen danger. When a group of thrill-seeking friends push the limits and the train breaks down, chaos ensues. Mysterious traps materialize, adding a layer of suspense and intrigue to the experience. Something sinister lurks beneath the surface, and it's up to you to guide the intrepid adventurers safely back to ground zero.<br>
<br>
Strap in tightly and prepare for the ride of your life as you navigate treacherous trails filled with cunning traps. Your mission is clear: reunite the fractured train and guide your friends to safety without encountering any unexpected obstacles. With mouse controls offering precise navigation, every twist and turn will test your reflexes and strategic thinking.<br>
<br>
Do you have what it takes to conquer the Sky Roller Coaster and emerge victorious? Fasten your seat belts, hold on tight, and brace yourself for the ultimate roller coaster ride of life!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombies vs You</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840040/Zombies_vs_You/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into a world overrun by the undead in this thrilling survival game. <br>
<br>
No longer can you stroll the streets without fear; now, every corner holds the potential for a deadly encounter with zombies. As the protagonist, you find yourself thrust into this nightmare scenario, armed only with a handful of bullets and your wits. Your mission: to navigate the treacherous landscape, using your weapons strategically to fend off hordes of ravenous zombies while staying one step ahead of their relentless pursuit.<br>
<br>
Main Features:<br>
1. Survival Horror Setting: The game is set in a world overrun by zombies, where every corner is fraught with danger, creating a tense and thrilling atmosphere.<br>
2. Protagonist's Challenge: Players take on the role of a protagonist thrust into this nightmare scenario, armed with limited resources and tasked with navigating the dangerous landscape filled with ravenous zombies.<br/>
3. Strategic Gameplay: Players must strategically manage their ammunition, choosing when and where to engage the zombies to maximize their chances of <br/>
survival. This includes deciding which weapons to use for different situations.<br/>
4.Weapon Variety: The game offers a selection of firearms with different attributes, such as the rapid firepower of an AK-47, the precision of a revolver, or the versatility of a Glock 19. Each choice has its own advantages and drawbacks.<br/>
5.Diverse Zombie Types: The undead come in various forms, each presenting its own unique challenges. This diversity requires players to adapt their tactics on the fly to effectively deal with different types of zombies.<br/>
6.Escalating Difficulty: The number of zombies escalates with each passing moment, increasing the intensity of the gameplay and putting pressure on players to constantly replenish their resources and stay one step ahead of the undead horde.<br/>
<br/>
Are you ready to confront the horrors of the apocalypse head-on? Arm yourself, steel your nerves, and prepare to face the undead menace in this pulse-pounding adventure.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambulance Chauffeur Simulator 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840020/Ambulance_Chauffeur_Simulator_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the adrenaline rush of emergency response in Ambulance Chauffeur Simulator 2. Take the driver's seat of an ambulance and race against the clock to deliver doctors to critical accident scenes. Your decisions and skills will determine whether patients receive timely medical attention or face dire consequences.<br>
<br>
Navigate bustling city streets and rugged mountain terrain, overcoming traffic and unpredictable obstacles. With every second crucial, precision driving is paramount. Each mission presents unique challenges, from weaving through urban traffic to tackling steep mountain passes.<br>
<br>
Ambulance Chauffeur Simulator 2 offers a pulse-pounding experience, demanding quick thinking and daring maneuvers to save lives. Can you handle the pressure and make split-second decisions in the face of danger? Download now and test your mettle as an ambulance chauffeur!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
<br/>
- Drive 3 distinct ambulance models<br/>
- Conquer 10 challenging levels<br/>
- Race against the clock to save lives						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunts above Clouds 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2840010/Stunts_above_Clouds_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2840010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Whoever said only airplanes can soar through the skies clearly hadn't experienced the adrenaline rush of Stunts above Clouds 2. Brace yourself for an exhilarating adventure as you take on our latest version, featuring 20 heart-pounding stages designed to push your limits like never before.<br>
<br>
Your mission remains unchanged, but the stakes are higher and the challenges more intense. Take the driver's seat of a high-powered car and navigate through treacherous roads where every twist and turn demands unwavering control. One wrong move could spell disaster, but for the fearless daredevils among us, the thrill is irresistible.<br>
<br>
Are you ready to defy gravity and conquer the impossible? With 20 electrifying levels, mind-bending stunts, and the added excitement of collecting money along the way, this is not a journey for the faint of heart. Are you crazy enough to make it to the end and claim your victory?<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- 20 adrenaline-pumping levels<br/>
- Insane stunts that will leave you breathless<br/>
- Collect money to unlock even more daring challenges						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
