<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1747760/Momodora_Moonlit_Farewell/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1747760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Momodora: Moonlit Farewell" is the latest installment in the Momodora series. Join Momo, High Priestess of the village of Koho, as she embarks on a divine mission to save her people from imminent destruction at the hands of the demon hordes summoned by a malevolent bellringer.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story:</h2>Momodora: Moonlit Farewell presents the account of the greatest calamity to befall the village of Koho, five years after the events of Momodora III.<br/> Once the toll of an ominous bell is heard, the village is soon threatened by a demon invasion.<br/>The village's matriarch sends Momo Reinol, their most capable priestess, to investigate the bell and find the bellringer responsible for summoning demons. It is their hope that by finding the culprit, they will also  be able to secure the village's safety, and most importantly, the sacred Lun Tree's, a source of life and healing for Koho...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Gorgeous pixel art and animation<br/></li><li> Action-packed gameplay focusing on melee combos, dodging enemy attacks, and firing arrows at enemies<br/></li><li> The "Sigil" system, which allows for greatly customizable play styles<br/></li><li> Intense and core-shaking boss battles<br/></li><li> Deep exploration into a world rich in lore and atmosphere<br/></li><li> Freely adjustable difficulty levels, allowing you to relax and explore the alluring world at your own pace or take on mighty foes for a real challenge</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Developer's Voice:</h2>Hello!<br/><br/>This is rdein, creator of the Momodora series. Recently my team and I have announced the latest installment in the series, “Moonlit Farewell”. This is a concluding story, following through from the events of Momodora 3. With this new tale, I also intend to close the book on many of the past games’ mysteries and questions.<br/><br/>I’m aware that many players are more familiar with the story of Kaho, which is set in a distant past. As such, I’m designing “Moonlit Farewell” to be as enjoyable as possible without prior knowledge of Momodora 1 to 3’s stories. Moreover, the series has always been focused on action and minimal stories. So please, don’t worry too much about “catching up”!<br/>Lastly, we hope to bring you our best game with this new title, using all the knowledge we’ve learned in the past 10 years. Please look forward to it!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696480/Nothing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2696480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play. Or is it?<br>
<br>
Just do Nothing as the timer goes up. If you do Something, you lose.<br>
<br>
If you don't like doing Nothing, go play Something instead.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Town Idle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2207490/Factory_Town_Idle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2207490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Factory Town Idle is a unique town builder where you manage an entire economy from a simple but powerful set of menus. At the start, simple clicks will harvest resources, create housing &amp; production buildings, and assign workers to craft items. You'll choose which items to sell at the markets, and which to refine into better items. As you gain experience, you'll acquire tools that help automatically manage your growing town - which you will need in order to manage its increasing demands.<br/><br/>Eventually you will gain the ability to expand into exotic biomes, unlocking valuable resources &amp; recipes exclusive to those regions. All along, you'll need to invest your earnings back into research and upgrades so that your town can earn you increasingly large piles of coins.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Make gourmet food, machinery, fine clothing, books of knowledge, potions, enchanted jewelry, and many other types of items<br/></li><li>Discover new recipes as your production skills increase<br/></li><li>Cultivate crops and prospect for ores to boost natural resources<br/></li><li>Huge list of quests which unlock powerful perks when completed<br/></li><li>Use aqueducts, water wheels, steam power, electricity, farm equipment, trains and research labs to give your production a boost<br/></li><li>Several different Biomes with unique resources, as well as advantages &amp; weaknesses to work around<br/></li><li>Exchange goods between multiple towns to maximize the benefit of local specialties<br/></li><li>Detailed production stats let you know where your bottlenecks are so you can keep your supply chain flowing<br/></li><li>Set production limits and priorities to precisely allocate your resources<br/></li><li>While away from the game, you earn Time Tokens you can use to fast-forward the simulation when you're ready to play again</li></ul><br/>(Trailer music from the original Factory Town soundtrack, by Clark Aboud)						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Flame: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517810/The_Last_Flame_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_1.png?t=1704928980"><br/>The Last Flame is a roguelike auto-battler which focuses on build creation, strategy and decision making. Recruit special heroes, fight deadly encounters, loot and craft powerful gear, discover and create unique synergetic builds! Every run, you will need to create powerful builds that will take down your foes!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_A3.gif?t=1704928980"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_2.png?t=1704928980"><br/>The Last Flame offers an incredible amount of build diversity. Combine heroes, items, relics and origins together to create amazing builds! Hero and team building have been designed with flexibility and freedom at their core which allows you to discover and create unique synergetic builds every single run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Builds.gif?t=1704928980"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/SP_TITLE_3.png?t=1704928980"><br/>In between the automated combats, you will have to cleverly guide your heroes through the adventure by making the smart decisions! Manage your resources, choose the optimal path in the map, make powerful builds, and strategically position and plan the combat phase!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_Tactical.gif?t=1704928980"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/comingToFullVersion.png?t=1704928980"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get access to a lot more stuff! Make amazing builds with over 250 items, 55 heroes, 120 relics and 55 origins.<br/></li><li>Continue the adventure in the third act, and meet the final boss in a special act!<br/></li><li>Face 30 challenging enemies and 10 bosses!<br/></li><li>Progress through 5 difficulties which will challenge your knowledge and strategy!<br/></li><li>Push your builds to their limit in the endless mode, a mode where you try to reach the highest floor!<br/></li><li>Experience the game in diverse and fun new ways with the challenge modes!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517810/extras/GIF_FIGHT_ENDLESS.gif?t=1704928980"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portal: Revolution</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/601360/Portal_Revolution/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Portal: Revolution is a fan-made mod for Portal 2 which plays before the events of Portal 2 in the dead and decaying Aperture facility.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/ezgif-7-f507c3c464_1_.gif?t=1704560425"><br/><strong>Over 40 new puzzles</strong><br/>The campaign contains 40 brand new puzzles making use of new test elements and presents existing mechanics in a new way not seen in Portal 2.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Resurrected "Pneumatic Diversity Vent" element<br/></li><li> New laser cube variant<br/></li><li> Over 15 puzzles using only the blue Portal-Gun<br/></li><li> Gel Cleansing Field</li></ul><br/><strong>Difficulty</strong><br/>Portal: Revolutions puzzle difficulty starts where Portal 2 stops, but fear not. All new mechanics and advanced portal tricks are taught to you. We have ensured through rigorous playtesting that every player can solve the puzzles. Although very few chambers require portals to be fired mid-air, no puzzles require advanced tricky movement.<br/><br/>Depending on your experience with Portal 2 mechanics, you can expect about 5 to 7 hours of playtime.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/601360/extras/banner_story_2.gif?t=1704560425"><br/>Set inbetween Portal and Portal 2, Portal: Revolution tells a brand new story using new characters. You play as a test subject who is awoken by a personality sphere called Stirling and join his mission to find a powerful device capable of restoring Aperture to its former glory.<h2 class="bb_tag">ENGINE</h2>Portal: Revolution uses a modified version of Portal 2: Community Edition's engine, which is a custom version of the Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Source Engine branch using licensed source code provided by Valve Software.<br/><br/>This allowed us to introduce many mechanics and improvements to the engine to create an experience which would be impossible in Portal 2.<br/><br/>-----------------------------------<br/><br/>Something you want to say? <br/>Email us: <a href="mailto:hello@secondfacesoftware.com">hello@secondfacesoftware.com</a><br/>Support: <a href="mailto:support@secondfacesoftware.com">support@secondfacesoftware.com</a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Memories</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2495450/Winter_Memories/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fkaguragames" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Steam_Page_Discord-EN.png?t=1705043544"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Header_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter-Memories-Cards_GIF.gif?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Trading_Others_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_1-EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/>After the unforgettable summer memories you’ve made half a year ago, Yui, Rio, and Miyuki are back. With the change of seasons and the cold falling snow, a new page to your story is about to begin. <br/><br/>Revisit the peaceful, seaside town, and spend time catching up with your family and friends.<br/><br/>What new memories will you make this winter?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_3-EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Miyuki_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Rio_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_Yui_EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2495450/extras/Winter_Memories_Description_4-EN.png?t=1705043544"><br/><strong>A Relaxing, Adventure RPG<strong><br/><br/><strong>Explore the Beautiful, Seaside Town<strong><br/><br/><strong>Manage How You Spend Your TIme<strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong></strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2480450/Pesticide_Not_Required_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The free prologue for Pesticide Not Required, a game that combines auto-attacking bullet heaven roguelites with farming game mechanics to create an expansive set of strategies and build combinations. Destroy huge hordes of evil insects, grow tons of crops, create your own build path, and unlock unique characters to play with!<br/><br/>This prologue version contains similar mechanics to the main game, but has less achievements, progression unlocks, unlockable characters, weapons, maps, and enemy varieties.<h2 class="bb_tag">Create Overpowered Builds</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/CombatChaosFisher.gif?t=1705021513"><br/>You are the bullet hell! Grow an arsenal of ridiculous weapons and craft your own unique build with a combination of 40+ stats. Additionally, each character has their own unique traits that keep runs fresh.<h2 class="bb_tag">Farm, Fish, and Mine</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/FarmFishMineWinterGif.gif?t=1705021513"><br/>Earn vital gold and experience from growing crops, catching fish, and mining. Expand your plot to harvest huge quantities of crops and build carefully to enhance your farming, fishing, and mining capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Automate Your Farm With Pets</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2480450/extras/PetsGifAutumn.gif?t=1705021513"><br/>Recruit friendly pets that will enhance your farm, collect loot, and kill enemies.<br/><br/>Other Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Season-themed map variations with multiple difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Many unlockable characters with special traits<br/></li><li>Persistent skill tree upgrades<br/></li><li>Quick ~20-minute play sessions<br/></li><li>Tons of achievements to unlock<br/></li><li>Full gamepad and keyboard support<br/></li><li>Go WUMBO!</li></ul><br/>Pesticide Not Required: Prologue is inspired by awesome games like Brotato, Vampire Survivors, and Atomicrops.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esports Godfather Origin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2739460/Esports_Godfather_Origin/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/游戏简介英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>"Esport Godfather" is a management simulation card game that revolves around the theme of MOBA esports. In this game, you will assume the role of a coach in an esports club and personally build your own team! Starting from scratch, what kind of playstyle will you devise for your team? In a constantly evolving meta, can you derive a unique understanding of what it takes to win? How will you unlock the potential of your handpicked athletes and mold them into superstars?<br/><br/>Ultimately, will you be able to become a legendary figure in the esports industry, crafting your own esports story and lifting the championship trophy?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/选手培养英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>Each athlete is unique! They all have their own strengths and weaknesses.<br/>If an athlete's efficiency in earning money increases over time, they are undoubtedly a skilled late-game specialist.<br/>Successful ambushes can unlock hidden potential, propelling some athletes onto the path of godlike.<br/>As a coach, it's your responsibility to analyze each athlete's characteristics, devise training plans tailored to their needs, and guide them on their journey to becoming superstars!<br/><br/>· Every athlete possesses distinct abilities that will impact their performance on the battlefield!<br/>· An athlete's hero pool is crucial for Ban &amp; Pick strategies!<br/>· The tactic cards utilized by athletes in matches serve as the foundation of all strategies!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/版本变更英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>The meta environment is ever-changing!<br/>Changes in the equipment pool, the structure of economic income, and the source of decisive advantages, even slight alterations to the rules can drastically shift the priorities of Ban &amp; Pick and alter the strategic approach!<br/><br/>· Equipment will be added or removed as the versions change!<br/>· The timing of crucial team fights will shift with each version update, making team composition crucial!<br/>· Does harassment grant more gold? Do kills damage towers? Each gameplay rule brings a fresh experience!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/指挥战斗英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>You have the power to command the battlefield, with athletes attentively listening to your orders.<br/>Should you play it safe and focus on farming under the towers, or launch aggressive assaults and initiate attacks?<br/>Perfect team composition requires perfect leadership! The game is ever-changing, and you must face your opponents head-on!<br/><br/>· Each hero and athlete possesses their own tactic cards. It is through creative combinations and strategic application that they become unstoppable!<br/>· Offense or defense? Aggression or caution? The outcome rests in your hands. Formulate strategies and implement tactics!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/其他内容英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/>· Over 50 unique heroes in the starting lineup, each with their own special abilities!<br/>· 200+ tactic cards, granting you control over the battlefield!<br/>· Diverse athlete training options! As a mentor, it's important to tailor your teachings to each individual!<br/>· Unearth young talents and cultivate new forces in the youth training camp!<br/>· Choose sponsors, a top-tier club deserves the support of top-tier sponsors!<br/>· Trash-talking sessions, asserting dominance is a must before crucial matches!<br/>· Abundance of events, includes unexpected occurrences, athlete communication, team pep talks!<br/>· Training match plans, knowing your opponents inside out ensures victory after victory!<br/>· Regular season, playoffs, transfer periods—different decisions await you at different times!<br/>· When athletes reach their limits, you must help them break through and reach new heights!<br/>· Create a custom team logo for your club!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2739460/extras/工作室LOGO英文.png?t=1704780687"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/curator/37765503</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowbreak: Containment Zone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668080/Snowbreak_Containment_Zone/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snowbreak: Containment Zone is a 3D sci-fi RPG-shooter powered by the Unreal Engine 4 that offers a next-gen, cross-platform gaming experience, sharing your progress across all of your devices. <br/><br/>The Descent of the Titans turned a once-vibrant city into the devastated wasteland of Containment Zone Aleph. As the Adjutant of Heimdall Force, bravely undertake missions alongside Manifestations with the powers of gods and unique personalities, seeking to bring this bitter winter to an end...<br/><br/>[Enjoy Hybrid Combat]<br/>Snowbreak's weaponry injects realism into a sci-fi setting, with designs closely simulating future firearms technology. This combines with the otherworldly, RPG-like skill mechanic to create a refreshing combat experience.<br/><br/>[Take on Titans]<br/>The Descent of the Titans completely changed the world, and the battlefield. Feel the thrill of battling giants in this dystopian future!<br/><br/>[Befriend Operatives]<br/>Spend time with your Heimdall Force companions in the Base system. Decorate, chat, and give gifts to grow closer!<br/><br/>[Play Co-Op in Gigalink] <br/>Tired of exploring alone? Join up with friends and fight enemies together!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Nights More: Genesis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713070/Few_Nights_More_Genesis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Please note: This is a free prologue and it includes act 1, and only 1 playable character and blood school is playable, The maximum heritage gained is limited to 50, and the maximum difficulty can be set to 2. As well only one castle will be available. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Blood3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Conquer castles and claim your birthright!</strong><br/> <br/>The fight to reclaim your place in this world begins. Rebuild lost ruins, make them stronger and defend them against your enemies. After you regain your strength, move on to conquer more territories and eventually claim your birthright.<br/><br/>Few Nights More offers the unique fusing of castle management and turn based rogue-like combat. Fight against humanity, the undisputed masters of this world in your absence. Choose between eight different Vampire Lords, each with their own ambition and history. Find your trinkets, skills and perks along your way. Design your very own castle by placing the right rooms, adding decors that directly contribute to your army and your Vampire Lord. Conquer more castles so your influence and power grow, until you claim your birthright.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713070/extras/Ferocity3.gif?t=1703285110"><br/><br/><strong>Core Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Design your castle by adding new Rooms, Traps and Minions. Stack up on some buffs with shiny decors to get ready for the invasion screen to defend it to the end of every night!<br/> <br/></li><li> Choose among 7 different Vampire Lords with unique History, Gameplay and Abilities.<br/> <br/></li><li> Master 1 out of 3 Disciplines each time you play, each with 60 unique skills.<br/> <br/></li><li> Acquire new random skills, perks and trinkets to survive the nights.<br/> <br/></li><li> Excel in either being a Prestigious Vampire, a Seductive one, or master a Terrifying presence against your enemies.<br/><br/></li><li> Test the builds you made against a variety of Hunters, Veterans and Unique Bosses in an action packed turn based combat system.<br/> <br/></li><li> Endure three acts across 12 difficulty levels, striving to survive and progress. Accumulate Heritage Points to enhance your lord's starting stats, skills, and unlock new castles and talents unique to each lord.<br/><br/></li><li> Engage in the boundless challenge of Infinity Mode, where you can continuously test your limits without relying on a castle. Each night, you will be presented with three options to advance, growing stronger as you push yourself to see how far you can go.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Penguin Kingdom: Huddle up</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635360/United_Penguin_Kingdom_Huddle_up/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Build your settlement and satisfy the needs of your penguins with better food, elegant decorations, entertainment venues, high-tech coolers, and luxury houses while dealing with killer whales and thief seals.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/GeneralView5.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Design your penguin settlement</h2>Shape a settlement worthy of your penguins. Set up new energy generators to activate more houses, workplaces, and coolers. Build workplaces to produce materials, food, and medicine.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/SnowBlock2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Protect your settlement</h2>Build defense towers against killer whales and thief seals. Killer whales attack your buildings and try to destroy them. Seals come to the food storages to steal food.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/KillerWhale01.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Happy and educated penguins</h2>Build some entertainment venues and let your penguins enjoy skating in the ice rinks, watching films at cinemas, playing video games in the game centers, racing in the karting tracks, exercising at gyms and in the fight clubs, visiting the museums, doing yoga, etc. Don't forget to focus on the spirituality of your penguins and increase their happiness with shrines and wishing wells. Focus on education and provide enough seats for your penguins at schools, high schools, and libraries. Make a huddle-up call to gather all your penguins and celebrate together.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/FightClub2.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Focus on economy</h2>Please be careful with spending your gold and focus on finding ways to earn more. Purchase or make barter to reach rare resources, sell your products to increase wealth, and grow your settlement. If you become the king, you can use continuous trades with the help of your bazaars.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Storage.gif?t=1703868247"><h2 class="bb_tag">Become the King</h2>Reputation score is the overall evaluation of your settlement in the kingdom. Meet the requirements, improve your reputation, and cheer up your penguins to level up from a village to a king. Become the king to explore new lands, find new settlements, and decide their joining approval to the kingdom.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635360/extras/Huddle3.gif?t=1703868247"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Asian Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2667970/100_Asian_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🗼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 ASIAN CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🗺️🌸</h2>🏮 Join the cutest adventure in the Asian temples locations! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Cats.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level <br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Asian Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733930/100_Asian_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Extra.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733590/100_Asian_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733940/100_Asian_Cats_Artbook/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Artbook.png?t=1703182951"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2733950/100_Asian_Cats__Donation_S/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Donation.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/600x1.png?t=1703182951"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2667970/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1703182951"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=100AsianCats_Bot</a></img></th></tr></table> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed robber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2551020/Onearmed_robber/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Experience the challenge of robbing banks, but now with only one arm! Grab a friend and you'll have two arms in total.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Loadout_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Unlock and buy new guns, which can be customized to fit your playstyle. If you are trying to go stealth, the optimal choice might be a suppressor, but if you're going loud, damage and bullets is all that matters, so put on an extended mag and get going!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_git_LoudOrStealth_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Each heist is suited for any playstyle, whether you want to sneak in and take out guards quietly, or you go in guns blazing shooting everthing in your sight until you reach the vault, the choice is yours. <br/><br/>As you become a more experienced robber new tools will be unlocked, which will make it easier for you to complete the heists. Each tool has a special purpose, and unique tools make it possible to complete heists in new ways you couldn't do before. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2551020/extras/Steamsite_gif_Looting_Final.gif?t=1702819908"><br/><br/>Whether you go loud or stealth, once you are in the vault, the objective is the same: Gather as much loot as possible, and get out alive!<br/>If you can't fit all the loot in the vault in your duffel bag, you can either run back to the truck and get a new one, or get your friends to help you carry out everything!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(the) Gnorp Apologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1473350/the_Gnorp_Apologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							(the) Gnorp Apologue is a game where you help small beings called gnorps get rich. It is a unique incremental game with interesting upgrades, and visuals to match the numbers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/everything.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Hit the rock</strong><br/>What is the rock? Irrelevant question — when struck, it outputs shards, and shards are amazing. They allow you to purchase and upgrade gnorps, and build new structures. The gnorps must have them. Hitting the rock is only half the battle, however, as the gnorps must retrieve the shards before they can use them. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/rs2.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>Acquire and upgrade gnorps</strong><br/>Gnorps represent the heart of the game. They are responsible for both shard generation and collection. Gnorps adapt varying methodologies to reach their goal. Some slam the rock with their heads, others shoot it with arrows and guns. You have gnorps that grow flowers, and gnorps that use psychic powers. They even build rockets and drones. All for a single purpose — the accumulation of shards.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/mountaineer.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/><strong>A strategic incremental </strong><br/>(the) Gnorp Apologue is about making numbers goes up, but how you do that is up to you. At your disposal: <br/>- All the gnorps, with their varying strengths and weaknesses<br/>- Upgrades that enhance and modify both gnorps structures and gnorps<br/>- The Talent Stone, offering unlocks that allow for extreme, synergetic effects<br/>- Status effects to enhance and modify shard generation<br/>- A special resource, Zybellium, that can greatly enhance your gnorps<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/gd6.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>If you enjoy theorizing about and executing builds in games, this game is for you. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/talents_reduced.gif?t=1702589491"><br/><br/>Will you help the gnorps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1473350/extras/comp.png?t=1702589491"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Nights at Freddy's: Help Wanted 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2287520/Five_Nights_at_Freddys_Help_Wanted_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2287520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Find out if you have what it takes to be a Fazbear Entertainment Superstar!<br>
<br>
Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is the sequel to the terrifying VR experience that brought new life to the iconic horror franchise. As a brand new Fazbear employee you’ll have to prove you have what it takes to excel in all aspects of Pizzeria management and maintenance. <br>
<br>
Go Backstage as a VIP to help Roxanne Wolf &amp; the S.T.A.F.F Bots get ready for their performances in the Pizzaplex Salon!<br>
<br>
Head into the Fazcade and enjoy classic games like Bonk-a-Bon and Fazerblast! See if you can top all the high scores!<br>
<br/>
Take care of things behind the scenes in the Staff Only section of the Pizzeria. Deliver First Aid to patients who aren’t quite feeling themselves, and help animatronics perform routine diagnostics &amp; maintenance.<br/>
<br/>
Our Food Prep courses will help you get the federally mandated amount of value preparing food in the Pizzaplex. Experience all the joys of high-speed food service &amp; get ready to feed some hungry bots!<br/>
<br/>
Head over to the Ticket Booth to test out our E-ticket attractions, such as Captain Foxy’s Cowboy Adventure! On this lighthearted log ride, you’ll float through the old West as a gunslinger in search of booty! <br/>
<br/>
And finally, if you’re short on dread, dive into the world of our Sister Location! These special minigames are VR versions of classic experiences from Five Nights at Freddy’s: Sister Location. These fan-favorites brought to life promise to be as fun as they are terrifying!<br/>
<br/>
So what are you waiting for?!? Five Nights at Freddy’s: Help Wanted 2 is now accepting applicants for all positions, effective immediately.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1190970/House_Flipper_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FQncyKz9V3H" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/join_our_discord.png?t=1704804364"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/1_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>It doesn't matter if you're a makeover veteran or if you're only starting out - you'll feel at home in no time!<br/>House Flipper 2 introduces new mechanics and revamps the ones from the original game.<br/>The good old hammer, the trusty paint roller, and the sturdy mop, all await your return! The new visuals make our fixer-uppers look crisp as never before!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/2_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Why renovate a house when you can just build one? Unleash your creativity in the Sandbox Mode! Use it to recreate real-life buildings or design projects that exist in your imagination.<br/>Remember: building from scratch is no easy task! But let's face it, it's definitely worth putting in extra effort to design the house of your dreams.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/3_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>Between the mountain tops and the endless sea, there lies the town of Pinnacove.<br/>A place where time slows down, and the friendly residents are ready to entrust you with their homes.<br/>Can you discover some of the stories within these walls?<br/>Your old pal Tom, who seems to know everybody in the neighborhood, will gladly share some local knowledge with you.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1190970/extras/4_en.gif?t=1704804364"><br/><br/>In House Flipper 2, you are the foreman!<br/>You get to decide what 'relaxing gameplay' means!<br/>Do you enjoy building? Choose the Sandbox Mode which allows you to construct houses from scratch. Or maybe you prefer cleaning and decorating? In the Story Mode, you will delve into long and engaging renovation projects, as well as deal with some quick jobs.<br/>Sit back and relax, here comes the new age of House Flipper!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy Versus: Rising</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2157560/Granblue_Fantasy_Versus_Rising/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2157560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The latest installment in the GBVS series is taking the genre to new heights! Rise to glory in the definitive fighting game experience for beginners and veterans alike.<br>
<br>
It's a Party! Claim Your Crown in Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
Need a break from matches? Take a breather and experience a one-of-a-kind island lobby filled with fun attractions. You can even go head-to-head with other players online in a variety of obstacle courses and survival games in an all-new party mode, Grand Bruise Legends!<br>
(Avatar, character, and mode availability is limited in the Free Edition.)<br>
<br>
Stay Focused on the Battle, Not the Controls<br>
Newcomers can fully enjoy the intensity and thrills of one-on-one combat without needing to memorize complicated controls—simple inputs can be used to perform skills with the press of a single button!<br>
<br>
A Captivating Story Campaign Awaits<br>
Embark on a journey through the vast skies of Granblue Fantasy and immerse yourself in an epic adventure while mastering the fundamentals of gameplay. As you take on more quests in this action RPG-inspired experience, you'll continue to grow stronger.<br>
<br>
Personalize the Experience On Every Level<br>
Express yourself and show some love for your favorite Granblue characters through a variety of character colors, weapon skins, lobby avatars, and even a selectable partner character to cheer you on and give you advice!<br>
<br>
Get Creative with the Digital Figure Studio<br>
The only limit is your imagination—construct original dioramas from a massive collection of high-quality 3D models from the Granblue Fantasy Versus series!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1704281211"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1704281211"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1704380508"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1704380508"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1704928839"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1704928839"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1704928839"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1704928839"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1704928839"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1703186631"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1703186631"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with seven other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702596786"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702596786"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1704392583"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1704392583"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1703009148"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1704666031"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1705031379"> </img></a><br/><br/>Vegas Infinite is for players aged 18+ only.<br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spellslinger</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2556670/Spellslinger/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2556670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Harness the power of the <strong>Elements</strong> and gather <strong>Spells</strong> to defend yourself against <strong>Hordes of Enemies</strong>!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2556670/extras/Store.png?t=1705044327"><br/><br/>In this game, you are a Wizard, trapped in a castle, as magical creatures are attacking you from every side.<br/>The only way to survive is to fight back with a vast array of different Spells. Spells are cast automatically, however, it's up to you to find the best Combination!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2556670/extras/StoreSpells.png?t=1705044327"><br/><br/><strong>Spell Traits:</strong><br/>It's not only about getting the strongest Spells, it's about finding a Combination, that will grant you even more Power.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2556670/extras/StoreTraits.png?t=1705044327"><br/><br/>Every Spell belongs to one <strong>Element</strong> and one <strong>School</strong>. <br/><br/><strong>Elements</strong> grant <strong>Unique</strong> bonuses to their respective Spells.<br/>Want to <strong>Freeze</strong> your Enemies? <strong>Burn</strong> them to <strong>Ashes</strong>? Or make them <strong>Explode</strong> into <strong>more Projectiles</strong>?<br/>Gather Spells with the same Element to activate these Traits and make them stronger by getting more of the same Element.<br/><br/>Knowing Spells of the same <strong>School</strong> will give you the power of their creators.<br/>Harnessing the power of<strong> Fairies</strong> will give you <strong>regenerative</strong> abilites, or you can become as <strong>strong</strong> as a <strong>Dragon</strong>.<br/>Activating the <strong>Phoenix</strong> School will grow your power <strong>over time</strong> and give  you the ability to <strong>revive</strong>.<br/><br/>Gameplay:<br/>The controls of this game are very simple. You can walk and you can jump. Spells and abilities get activated automatically. <br/>You need to survive 20 waves of an onslaught of enemies, that get stronger every wave. Later waves introduce new enemies and there's a big threat in the final wave.<br/><br/>So you walk around casting spells on enemies that will drop loot upon defeat. Gather gems to buy new spells and items to become stronger.<br/>Enemies might occasionally drop an item which you can take or sell at the end of a wave.<br/>Sometimes enemies also drop Heal Orbs, which heal you upon collecting them.<br/><br/>Occasionally Chests will spawn, that you can open by simply touching them. They contain loot, but pay close attention, because not every chest is dormant.<br/><br/>In the shop you can view your current Spells in the top left, where you can also decide to buy new empty Spellbooks. In order to learn a new unique Spell you need at least one empty Spellbook. Buying a Spell that you already have, will add 1 experience point to it. 3 Spells of the same kind will make a level 2 Spell and 9 of a kind make a level 3 Spell, increasing not only the Power, but also giving unique bonuses to certain Spells.<br/><br/>Every Spell has Base Power, Scalings (indicated by the respective Symbol in the Description) and the "Damage" stat acts as a final percentual Modifier for all Player Damage sources. (1 Damage = 101% of original Damage). <br/><br/>In the Shop items can be bought, rerolled or locked (so they reappear next wave). Prices will increase with higher wave numbers.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmic Collapse</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707300/Cosmic_Collapse/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Physics based planet matching!</h2><br/>It is time to tidy up the solar system. Can't have all these planets laying around. <br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Shove planets into each other to make bigger planets<br/></li><li>No stress, take your time<br/></li><li>Like Suika Game but more forgiving and extra features<br/></li><li>Play strategically to trigger insane combos<br/></li><li>Earn missiles to get out of tricky situations<br/></li><li>Totally accurate simulation of celestial bodies</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Tips and tricks</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Use smaller planets to nudge bigger ones<br/></li><li>You get more points for chaining collapses. Try to line up planets in the correct order before collapsing them all<br/></li><li>Keep it tidy, lots of small planets will make the end game difficult<br/></li><li>Use your missiles wisely, they can be a total game changer</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Revenge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2730590/Medieval_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A gripping mini-game set in medieval England, where the life of a farmer's son takes an unexpected turn with the Viking raids on England. As the family faces tragedy, the son swears revenge, embarking on a challenging adventure where your strength, persuasiveness, and ruthlessness depend on the cards you choose.<br>
<br>
-Over 100 card choices<br>
<br>
-Interactive drawings based on your decisions<br>
<br>
-Titles based on your choices<br/>
<br/>
Start your adventure as a farmer striving to survive in the harsh medieval times, seeking revenge!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ring of the devil</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748540/ring_of_the_devil/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a fighting game.<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
The map design is fantastic.<br>
<br>
<br/>
<br/>
Adjusting gameplay and operations based on the map greatly enhances the gaming experience.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
The aesthetics of physical stimulation and violence in boxing, simple yet not simple game controls, and rich and innovative game mechanics have overwhelmed other fighting games, allowing players to quickly get started while leaving ample room for freedom.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Players can make rich combinations according to their own needs to obtain a better gaming experience.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
It inherits classic combat elements well, allowing players to enjoy intense battles and feel the tense atmosphere of life and death in the game. With its superb production level, it meets the player's requirements for a refreshing sense of attack and skill release.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrestricted Pest Control</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2543410/Unrestricted_Pest_Control/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Unrestricted Pest Control is a top-down shooter with rogue-lite elements and a unique room/floor system. As an exterminator, you step into a nuclear research facility to fix its bug problems with your extensive solution methods.</strong><br/><br/>Insects are famous for their adaptation and survival skills. A small push of radioactivity makes things a little bit complicated. They have outgrown themselves, gained new skills, and mutated distinctively. You must use your weapons wisely if you want to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543410/extras/Movie_002.gif?t=1705039864"><br/><br/>You will have different skills that can be gained by defeating after bosses, but remember, you can use only one of them. Get a shield, slaying hoops, or a grenade to destroy everything. Choose the skill that serves you best.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543410/extras/Movie_001_1.gif?t=1705039864"><br/><br/>With the unique room and floor system, this game demands strategizing your path. You are starting on the ground floor and your main goal is to reach the top floor. You must survive every room and reach the floor boss to be able to reach the upper floor. <strong>Be careful if you die, you will go back to square one.</strong> But don’t worry, once you unlock a floor, it stays unlocked. This allows you to reach the upper floor from the very first room. <strong>You can go final boss directly in theory :)</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2543410/extras/Movie_003.gif?t=1705039864"><br/><br/><strong>Clear every room to reach the bosses. Defeat the bosses to reach the upper floors. Clean the whole facility to reach ultimate satisfaction.</strong> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanks Etc.</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709400/Tanks_Etc/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tanks Etc. is an arcade that offers both cooperative and competitive gameplay - perfect for couch gaming with friends. Set in a futuristic world, the game lets you control sophisticated tanks and mechs in adrenaline-fueled battles. It offers familiar modes like deathmatch, capture the flag, and king of the hill, each demanding different strategies, from individual combat prowess to team coordination.<br>
Tanks Etc. also creatively reinvents classic games; for example, it transforms hot potato into a tense, tank-based challenge and turns hide and seek into a strategic game of stealth and pursuit. These innovative twists add depth and excitement to the traditional arcade experience.<br>
With its range of game modes catering to various playstyles, from fast-paced action to strategic team play, Tanks Etc. is a versatile and engaging game for players who love cooperative camaraderie and competitive thrills.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Story in the Dream World 3 -Sinister Island's Mysterious Mist-</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1954680/Story_in_the_Dream_World_3_Sinister_Islands_Mysterious_Mist/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1954680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The prelude to the third story...<br>
<br>
Yeonseul and Hyeyoon met various water gods and spirit creatures...<br>
Yeonseul fainted for a moment, then woke up. Since Enter Sangbian Island a rather heavy mission and identification of the cause, the duel was somewhat unreasonable.<br>
“Except for the god of the sea, everything was fine in its own way.”<br>
"Shinjike gave me a sense of being elegant and lonely somewhere, and Hae-gwi seemed like a gentle man with strong strength in a rough battlefield."<br>
“Of course, both of you are trustworthy.”<br>
“But how to help... I can't help but feel anxious because I don't know what will happen if I go to Sangbian Island...”<br/>
Then, in a daze, I looked towards the shore from inside the shrine. Under the deep blue sky, the moon was shining brightly, and the seawater reflected the moonlight softly.<br/>
“There is a moon as big as that in this place... I like it because it is moderately bright and not dazzling.”<br/>
The tremendous tension and anxiety before the big event calmed down little by little while watching the moon and listening to the sound of the sea.<br/>
Hyeyoon also fainted and got up. The shrine where Hyeyoon is located is deeper inland than Yeonseul's shrine, so the seawater is not visible. There is only a thin stream.<br/>
“Imoogi..? pal?"<br/>
I was still in the temple, dazed and dazed, as if it was still sudden.<br/>
After a daze, I came out of the shrine and looked at the moon.<br/>
The soft moonlight and the sounds of insects and streams seemed to calm Hyeyoon's heart.<br/>
"Shinjike-nim... Hae-gwi-nim..."<br/>
“Am I the right person for the job… I don’t know…”<br/>
Hye-yoon lacks confidence. But someday someone has to do it. Besides, there are colleagues who will come together.<br/>
"okay. There was also Yeon-seul... Would you think that the grace I received was repaid with help? I'm glad I don't get sick...”<br/>
It was as if the various environments around her were comforting and encouraging Hyeyoon, who thought of herself as weak. I can't help but feel anxious...<br/>
<br/>
How to play the game<br/>
1. Common Mode<br/>
Avoid and shoot down the attacks of various henchmen that appear for a certain amount of time whenever you enter each chapter!<br/>
After a certain amount of time, the boss comes out, talks to the player, and starts a duel with the player.<br/>
Beat the boss to enter the next chapter or view the endings!<br/>
<br/>
2. Boss Rush Mode<br/>
It is a mode that can be unlocked by breaking it once, regardless of the number of times (within a limited number of times) connecting the normal mode to the difficulty level.<br/>
There are no henchmen spawning in this mode, and no dialogue with the boss.<br/>
And, it comes out a little stronger than the boss in normal mode!<br/>
Only, if you duel with the boss and beat the boss, you go to the next chapter or the game ends right away!<br/>
(There is no separate ending in this mode.)<br/>
<br/>
3. Achievements<br/>
The fun of clearing the 23 achievements in the game has also been added!<br/>
<br/>
Game control keys<br/>
(If there is no separate guide key, the key will be used.)<br/>
Back: X, Esc<br/>
Menu/Weapon Selection: Z, Enter<br/>
Menu/character movement: arrow keys (if you press Shift for a character, it moves slowly)<br/>
Fire weapon, talk to boss: Z<br/>
Use Bomb, skip boss dialogue: X<br/>
Fire special bullets (when the gauge is maxed out): C<br/>
Pause menu: Esc						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Only !</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731880/Ghost_Only/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731880/extras/title03__1_.png?t=1705032230"><h2 class="bb_tag">For the Resurrection of the Ancient demon!</h2>It's a real-time strategy game where you become a ghost, defeat heroes with skulls, and resurrect the ancient demon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Save the Altar!</h2>The altar is a place for the resurrection of the ancient demon.<br/>The heroes will break into the ghost's estate to deter it.<br/>Control the skulls and bring the ancient demon resurrect safely.<h2 class="bb_tag">Control the Skulls!</h2>Wake up the already dead skulls.<br/>Join forces with the skulls.<br/>Learn black magic and regain skull's memory to strengthen your skulls.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2607320/Illegal_Mahjong/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607320/extras/11.png?t=1705043804"><br/>Yuri, the former heiress of a company, finds her father's business bankrupt.<br/>To repay the debts, Yuri must compete in mahjong and continue to win.<br/>Can Yuri truly defeat her formidable opponents?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607320/extras/22.png?t=1705043804"><br/>In this game, you control Yuri and compete in mahjong against various opponents.<br/>If you manage to score the highest points by the end, you can repay the debts all at once. If any of the opponents surpass Yuri's score, it's game over for her.<br/>Moreover, unlike regular mahjong, you can acquire skill points during the mahjong matches which Yuri can use to learn cheating skills.<br/>Unlock these cheating skills and climb your way to victory against high-ranked tables with an advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2607320/extras/33.png?t=1705043804"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full voiceover for the heroine<br/></li><li>Mahjong skills can be utilized</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Fries Pusher Friends</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2714330/French_Fries_Pusher_Friends/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>For video creators and streamers</strong><br/>STP WORKS permits the use of our games for video distribution to YouTube and other sites, and monetization through video distribution platform partner programs.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Game Overview</strong><br/>Do you love French fries? Then this game is for you! A game where you push out fries with French fries to create a set of a burger, fries, and a drink. The goal is to fulfill as many orders as you can before you run out of HP. It's a challenge you wouldn't want to miss!<br/><br/><br/><strong>Stick to sound effects</strong><br/>We have recorded the actual sounds of fries from a famous fast food joint to use as sound effects in the game. You can enjoy a realistic and immersive potato sound experience.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Online Multiplayer</strong><br/>Enjoy both random and friend matching. You can experience a once in a lifetime meet in a random match, get excited with inside jokes in friend matching, and of course, it's also possible to play solo. Play as you prefer, and you can play with up to 4 people at the same time.<br/><br/><br/><strong>Leaderboard</strong><br/>Compete for scores with French fries lovers all over the world.<br/><br/><strong>Upgrade</strong><br/>You can enhance various abilities using the money earned from playing the game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2421370/Cryptis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2421370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><i>Reawakened In Desolation...</i></h2><br/>Awaken amidst a desolate realm, your last memory being a life far removed from this nightmare. Embark on a journey of relentless violence, navigating through hordes of bloodthirsty undead. What sinister force has brought you to this place? Plunge into a tale shrouded in shadows and unveil the chilling truth.<h2 class="bb_tag">Next-Gen Visuals Meet a Retro Aesthetic</h2>Built in the mesmerizing Unreal Engine 5 and harnessing the cutting-edge capabilities of Nanite and Lumen, <strong><i>Cryptis</i></strong> immerses you in a haunting world where retro-inspired designs meet breathtakingly realistic lighting.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic and Diverse Gameplay</h2>No two encounters are the same. Your journey will see you wielding an array of weapons, tools, and abilities that allow for varied approaches to confrontations, ensuring a fresh and thrilling experience with every battle.<br/><br/><strong><i>Embrace the chaos, slaughter your bloodthirsty adversaries, and overcome the darkness. The very fabric of this realm quivers at your presence. Leave nothing left standing.</i></strong><br/><br/>Welcome to <strong><i>Cryptis</i></strong>. Your nightmare has just begun...<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2421370/extras/library_logo_6_48.png?t=1705024319"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleigh Strikers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2327340/Sleigh_Strikers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2327340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2327340/extras/about.png?t=1705023432"><br/>In Sleigh Strikers Santa's elves have engineered the ultimate gift-giving gadget: the <strong>Present Launcher 1225</strong>. With the reindeer missing, it's up to you to deliver the goods in a blitz of festive fury. Race through 10 increasingly challenging levels, each faster and more frantic than the last, and bring back the missing reindeer to save Christmas. Ready, aim, unwrap!<br/>Challenge the rest of the world at your present delivering skills and deliver your way to the top of the Global Leaderboards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2327340/extras/challenge.png?t=1705023432"><br/><strong><i>Ready to Sleigh?</i></strong> the frosty fun ramps up with each level. Your mission: zip presents or coal down chimneys, scoring points for precision. But beware, a merry mix-up between the naughty and nice lists will cost you! Aim like an elf on expresso to snag those high scores and stars. While it's all jingle bells and joy to start, mastering the leaderboard is a craft only the most dedicated Santa's helpers will perfect.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2278480/BUZZ/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2278480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>BUZZ is a challenging 2D platformer with fast, fluid gameplay.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2278480/extras/BUZZ_Pink__1_.gif?t=1705022227"><br/><br/><strong>Slice through the void to gain momentum</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2278480/extras/BUZZ_Red.gif?t=1705022227"><br/><br/><strong>Rebound off anomalies to reverse momentum</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2278480/extras/BUZZ-Rebound.gif?t=1705022227"><br/><br/><strong>Surf the goo to maintain momentum</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2278480/extras/BUZZ-Goo.gif?t=1705022227"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Accessible two button controls makes it easy to pickup<br/></li><li> 50 Levels<br/></li><li> Optional extra tricky collectible on every level<br/></li><li> Replay ghosts, leader boards and personal bests<br/></li><li> Full controller support<br/></li><li> Dynamic Soundtrack</li></ul><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2278480/extras/Purple_buzz.gif?t=1705022227"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orienteering Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707860/Orienteering_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>🧭 Orienteering Simulator 🧭</strong><br/><br/>Version: <i>v.1.1 Martinsflue</i> (Release)<br/><br/><br/>🔰 - Learn how to orientate yourself in this friendly environment. In "Find-Posts"-Mode, you will have to find your target using a compass and a map, while in "Orienteering"-Mode, you have to pinpoint your location on the map.<br/><br/>🔓 Choose between multiple maps, gamemodes, weather conditions &amp; more to create your personalized experience. Fulfill achievements to unlock new compasses that you can use during your explorations.<br/><br/>⬆️Update! Check out the new map "Martinsflue"! Orientate in a harsh environment containing lots of height difference, stones and winding paths. Want even more fun? Try out the Martinsflue-Extra-Map's "Stones-Only", "Contour-Lines-Only" or "Paths-Only"!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Glitch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2705800/Time_Glitch/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Time Glitch</strong> invites you to immerse yourself in a short, unique blend of dungeon crawling and time manipulation. You find yourself at the end of a grand tabletop campaign, facing an undead king who wields the power of time itself. However, every defeat sends you back to the gates of the final dungeon, where your experience began.<br/><br/>But here's the twist – you retain your memories, particularly knowing which die yields what number. Armed with this information, guide your characters strategically through the final battle. Role dice to cast spells and launch attacks, but be cautious – the world's fate hangs in the balance, and so does the friendship among your party.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Strategic Dice Rolls:</strong> Remember the outcomes of your dice rolls to make crucial decisions. Your success hinges on choosing the correct paths and actions to overcome challenges. The game is designed to be completed in roughly 20 minutes, offering an engaging experience that fits into a short gaming session or 1 hour if you want to get all the endings.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705800/extras/TG_-_Dice.gif?t=1705001699"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Bite-sized tabletop RPG Journey:</strong> Immerse yourself in the final moments of a tabletop RPG, complete with an undead king who controls the very fabric of time.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705800/extras/TG_-_Evil.gif?t=1705001699"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>4th Wall Breaking Fun:</strong> Delight in the unique experience of playing a bite-sized tabletop RPG journey within a game. Enjoy the subtle humor and surprises as you navigate the game world and the meta-narrative.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705800/extras/TG_-_4th_wall.gif?t=1705001699"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Friendship and Fate:</strong> Every decision matters not only for the fate of the in-game world but also for the bonds between your characters.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2705800/extras/TG_-_Friends.gif?t=1705001699"><br/><br/><br/>Can you break the cycle, defeat the undead king, and ensure a triumphant end to your campaign? Explore the intricate blend of time travel and tabletop RPG in Time Glitch – where the past is your greatest weapon.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2675290/LASERS/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675290/extras/gif.gif?t=1704999613"><br/><strong>LASERS</strong> is a free multiplayer game about surviving deadly laser mazes. Only one player can win. Will it be you?<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dodge lasers or die trying. One wrong step will cost you your limbs<br/></li><li>Online multiplayer for 1-10 players<br/></li><li>Race against the clock to be the last player standing<br/></li><li>Over 20 handmade levels to beat<br/></li><li>Full of thick gym bros and girls to play as<br/></li><li>Unlock emotes and outfits by increasing your Halo Rank<br/></li><li>Dark, pounding synth music</li></ul><br/><strong>This game was created for fun by a tiny indie studio. If you enjoy it, please show us your support and we'll continue to work on it!</strong> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syllogism</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2740350/Syllogism/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2740350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join an exciting journey through a variety of biomes, each with its own unique theme and environment. From lush tropical forests to mysterious ruins, amazing adventures and mysteries await you that will not leave you indifferent.<br>
<br>
Explore an open world full of beautiful views and locations, and enjoy a relaxing atmosphere while immersing yourself in unique challenges that will challenge your imagination and logical thinking.<br>
<br>
What awaits you in the game:<br>
-36 main and 20 additional puzzles in 6 different zones, united by the main mechanics, but at the same time unique and interesting.<br>
-An open world where you can go anywhere and also unravel the mysteries and secrets hidden in it<br>
-Puzzles with unusual mechanics, involving the environment, the world, around you, and another puzzles <br/>
-Atmospheric soundtrack that will immerse you into the world of the game<br/>
-Themed locations, from the desert and ancient buildings to Asian gardens<br/>
-Explore every corner of this world, because every little thing matters<br/>
-Enjoy beautiful stylized graphics that will surround you with a relaxing and pleasant environment.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reigns: Three Kingdoms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2437040/Reigns_Three_Kingdoms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2437040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Inspired by the beloved Chinese epic "Romance of the Three Kingdoms," this game thrusts players into the turbulent final years of the Han dynasty. Players will encounter the many factions, wars, and heroes of the saga as they swipe through to make high-stakes decisions, team up with the right army at the right time, gain power, and more.<br/><br/>Discover new ways to enjoy this franchise's unique card-based swiping mechanic as you uncover the many secrets of a vast storyline, deploy strategy in turn-based battles and encounter a host of unexpected mini-games.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience a distinctive narrative told through encountering a vast variety of characters and scenarios.<br/></li><li>Play dozens of quests with specific arcs, heroes to recruit, people to wed, and children to raise.<br/></li><li>Recruit new heroes to fight with you in new turn-based card battles.<br/></li><li>Build your own dynasty and see your political progress.<br/></li><li>For the first time, take your recruits into battle against other players in online-ranked card battles.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Handlers</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2448830/Time_Handlers/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/ezgif-3-5c44fea8ab.gif?t=1704992138"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/arrow.png?t=1704992138"> In Time Handlers, dive into an exhilarating cooperative adventure with a friend. Become employees of the mysterious Time Company tasked with repairing the spatio-temporal rifts that threaten the balance of time and space that manifest across different eras. Face bewildering and exciting challenges.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/ezgif-3-9b1461a64a.gif?t=1704992138"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/arrow.png?t=1704992138"> In this 3D puzzle game, you explore a mysterious tower filled with challenging obstacles. Each floor presents new complex puzzles that require close communication and flawless cooperation between the two players. Be creative, solve twisted riddles, and use your wits to progress.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/narrator.gif?t=1704992138"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/arrow.png?t=1704992138"> The narrator will follow your progress in the tower, so be prepared for sharp comments and witty remarks that spice up your interactions with the game.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/ezgif-3-be0981b756.gif?t=1704992138"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/arrow.png?t=1704992138"> Your ultimate goal is to climb the tower's floors, solve all the complex puzzles, and reach the heart of the spatio-temporal rift. Only skillful puzzle-solving will allow you to restore order in the universe and mend the tears of time.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/ezgif-3-20a84d761b.gif?t=1704992138"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/arrow.png?t=1704992138"> Will you succeed in solving puzzles to repair the rift that threatens time?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/arrow.png?t=1704992138"> What are these rifts really?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2448830/extras/arrow.png?t=1704992138"> What is the narrator's purpose and who is he?<h2 class="bb_tag">Answer these questions through the different trials you will encounter!</h2> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>吸血鬼与下午茶 Vampires and Afternoon Tea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2741060/_Vampires_and_Afternoon_Tea/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Love oriented visual novel, female lead name cannot be changed, no achievement system.<br/>The text volume is about 60000 words, and there are two characters that can be explored, with over ten endings<br/><strong> Synopsis: </strong><br/>The girl Cecily, who got lost in the forest, was taken in by the mysterious man Kyle. Please try to discover the secrets of this house within 12 days, or you may meet a tragic end.<br/><strong>Characters：</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741060/extras/IMG_4476.PNG?t=1704989858"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741060/extras/IMG_4477.PNG?t=1704989858"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741060/extras/IMG_4475.PNG?t=1704989858"><br/>This work was previously released for free online<br/>Compared to the free version, the Steam version has added future discussions. You can search and download the free version before considering whether to purchase this game<br/>Please do not record extra<br/>Player communication group: 851809496<br/>Production team: 不眠鸟制作组<br/>Production tool: THE NVL Maker<br/>Thank you to everyone who provided assistance during the production process, as well as to you who are currently reading this page						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unknown Fear</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2619300/The_Unknown_Fear/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2619300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A horror game focused on a mystery story. In addition to an experimental system where game events are controlled by an AI, making these events dynamic, making each game unique.<br>
<br>
The game is part of a series of original games called THE UNKNOWN FEAR which will be 5 horror and mystery games. Each game will tell a part of this story and only with the 5 will everything make sense.<br>
<br>
In this first game you will play the role of a person who doesn't even remember his own name, but who will be forced to complete a task given by a mysterious scientist who is indifferent to his safety and promises in exchange his freedom and a new life.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bondman Of Traps</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2703290/Bondman_Of_Traps/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explorer Daniel finally obtains the map of the hidden treasure after a long quest. He parachutes onto the location of the treasure, a place not visible on the world map. Our hero must navigate through a challenging and perilous journey, overcoming deadly traps, to ultimately reach the great treasure.<br/><br/>Will you be able to reach the treasure despite all the obstacles and traps, or will you become a Bondman of Traps?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703290/extras/ilkgif.gif?t=1704986581"><h2 class="bb_tag">Conquer the Challenging Platforms One by One</h2><br/>Passing through platform elements is truly challenging. In some platform sections, you must make quick decisions and take action. So, plan, prepare, and take action. There's no need to rush. Or is there?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703290/extras/ikincigif.gif?t=1704986581"><br/><br/>The game features different mechanics filled with surprises in some platform elements. You can't rely only on traps; platforms may also deceive you and contain traps for you to make mistakes.<h2 class="bb_tag">Identify and Solve the Traps</h2><br/>Most traps will take your life and try to kill you. Recognize the obstacles, analyze the movements, and improve your reflexes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703290/extras/ucuncugif.gif?t=1704986581"><h2 class="bb_tag">Trust Yourself and Your Reflexes</h2><br/>In Bondman Of Traps, dozens of traps and numerous platform elements will do their best to make you fail in this journey. So, what will you do? Accept this challenge. Solve the secrets of the traps. Improve your reflexes and show them who you are.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2703290/extras/dorduncu.gif?t=1704986581"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROSS DUNGEON</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2547960/CROSS_DUNGEON/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2547960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Connect the tiles and conquer the dungeon.<br>
Monsters and treasure await!<br>
Defeat monsters and move on.<br>
Power up when you get the treasure.<br>
Let's proceed while collecting treasures.<br>
<br>
―――――<br/>
<br/>
■Keyboard control<br/>
<br/>
・Menu, title<br/>
<br/>
Movement: wasd, arrow keys, mouse drag<br/>
Submit: j, Enter, left mouse click<br/>
Cancel: Escape, Backspace, k<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
・In Game<br/>
<br/>
Movement: wasd, arrow keys, mouse drag<br/>
Put tile: j, Enter, left mouse click<br/>
Rotation: k, Space<br/>
Skip: l, rightShift<br/>
Menu: i, rightCtrl<br/>
Skill: o, leftCtrl<br/>
Camera movement: right mouse drag<br/>
Camera movement mode switching: u, rightAlt<br/>
Zoom: pageUp pageDown, mouse wheel						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Veggies</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2365250/The_Last_Veggies/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365250/extras/GameIcon_SteamDescription.png?t=1704987057"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>The Story</strong></h2>A giant meteor full of weird looking creatures has crashed on our planet. Those monsters overran our cities and ate all our food before we were even ready to defend ourselves. The survivors have set up giant safezones that are monster free but they are running out of food. Carl and his friends, a special team of veggie loving monster killers have been sent to the farmlands, the last green spot on earth to look for a new food source. Grow veggies, deliver them to the safezones and fight of those evil creatures as long as you can!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>The Game</strong></h2>In the Last Veggies it is all about Veggies and Monsters. Plant veggies, deliver them to make some money or defend them at all costs. Use your income to buy random items and upgrades for yourself, your weapons or your farm! Fight waves of monsters and defeat even more powerful bosses! Collect golden carrots by defeating enemies to unlock new playable characters, maps or even gamemodes!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365250/extras/TheLastVeggies_Steam_GIF_2.gif?t=1704987057"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Veggie Delivery</strong></h2>An Endless gamemode with Veggies, Monsters, Raiders, evil Bosses and even Lootatos for the right amount of fun! Here you have to plant, defend and deliver your veggies to make a living and to secure the survival of humanity. Delivering veggies will provide you with some cash to buy upgrades for yourself or your farm! watch out for Raiders that attack your farm and prepare yourself for insanely powerful bosses! Survive as long as you can! <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365250/extras/TheLastVeggies_Steam_GIF.gif?t=1704987057"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>The Last Veggies</strong></h2>You are slowly running out of seeds to plant veggies and there are not that many left... Defend the Last Veggies until help arrives! In this gamemode you will have to defend veggies to the last Wave. You will gain some money for each surviving veggies that you can use for upgrades and items to make surviving a little easier. There are no Bosses or Raiders here but that doesn't mean that this gamemode is easier! <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2365250/extras/TheLastVeggies_Steam_GIF_3.gif?t=1704987057"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Seed Savers</strong></h2>Oh no! Now we are running out of Seeds! Travel to secret location where humanity has stored the last of the seeds to make sure that there are always enough veggies. get those seeds to your vehicle and leave before you are overrun! This mode includes evil bosses, new creatures and tons of seeds!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A wide Selection of Characters</strong></h2>Carl has a lot of friends out in the Farmlands and you can play each one of them. Every Character comes with a unique set of skills and each character carries a different weapon that will change your playstyle completely!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Choose your difficulty</strong></h2>Each Map and GameMode can be played in 3 different difficulty levels. If those 3 difficulties are still not enough for you there are events that can be switched on or off to make the game even harder! But the higher the difficulty the higher the chance to fond rare golden carrots!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laser 77 - Virtual Lab</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2722630/Laser_77__Virtual_Lab/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2722630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							'Laser 77 - Virtual Lab' is a single-player, 2D, sci-fi action game inspired by the classic games of the early 80's. It uses virtual reality as a theme, posing as a futuristic sofware from 1977.<br/><br/>In the game, you take the role of 'Laser', a mysterious blue being from outer space. <br/>Armed with his trusty liquid sword and a powerfull light beam gun, he trains in the virtual labyrinth course of his ship to hone important abilities for future adventures.  <br/>When the simulation goes haywire, will Laser have the strength to overcome improbable odds while still beating the high score?<br/><br/>&gt; Confront the robots and holograms of the simulation in this retro inspired 2D action game.<br/>&gt; Hone your reflexes and train your awareness while battling different enemies and bosses using a variety of skills.<br/>&gt; Explore different areas packed with new critters and rescue friendly hostage robots that can watch your back.<br/>&gt; Access lore stations containing information about the beings and mechanisms inhabiting this original sci-fi universe.<br/>&gt; Find secret life stashes and itens to help you survive the hologram onslaught.<br/><br/>This game program includes:<br/>- 20+ stages<br/>- New abilities <br/>- Boss battles<br/>- High intensity action<br/><br/><strong>Do you have what it takes to clear the labyrinth?</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWISTEX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2518940/TWISTEX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2518940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							PLAY ON SCREEN OR IN VR<br>
<br>
Let's get twisting!!!<br>
<br>
TWISTEX is a falling block puzzle game with a 'twist'. It combines classic gameplay with original new mechanics.<br>
<br>
CLEAR RINGS, COLORS AND LEVELS<br/>
Clear 48 levels across 2 distinct game types, or see how long you can last in endless mode with 3 difficulties.<br/>
<br/>
FEEL THE PRESSURE<br/>
As the blocks get higher, so does the pressure. Try to keep your cool as the music and environment react to how you're doing.<br/>
<br/>
UNLOCK AND CUSTOMIZE<br/>
Clearing levels will unlock new towers, blocks, music and environments, for you to customize your experience.<br/>
<br/>
LEADERBOARDS<br/>
Compete for the top spot, or beat your friends, in the online leaderboards.<br/>
<br/>
VR OR NO<br/>
Play the non-VR version with a controller, keyboard or mouse, with plenty of options to suit your playstyle.<br/>
The VR version is a whole different experience, with motion controls made especially for VR.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Join the Discord server to get involved or follow the socials for the latest updates.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Machines Builder - First Siege</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2669550/Medieval_Machines_Builder__First_Siege/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669550/extras/BorderPostShooting.gif?t=1704981604"><br/><br/>Prepare to take your first steps into a world of medieval intrigue, craftsmanship, and warfare. Will you withstand the First Siege and lay the groundwork for a legacy that echoes through the ages? The journey begins with <strong>Medieval Machines Builder - First Siege</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Key Features</strong><br/><br/>🛠️ <strong>Tools:</strong><br/>Master the art of siege construction with a diverse array of tools at your disposal. Precision is key as you forge the instruments of war that will shape the battlefield.<br/><br/>🌾 <strong>Gathering:</strong><br/>Venture into the medieval wilderness to gather essential resources for your siege endeavors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669550/extras/BorderPostCrafting.gif?t=1704981604"><br/><br/>🎯 <strong>Testing:</strong><br/>Put your creations to the test on the proving grounds.<br/><br/>💥 <strong>Demolishing:</strong><br/>In war, destruction is as crucial as construction. Learn the delicate balance of tearing down enemy fortifications with powerful siege engines, unleashing chaos upon your foes.<br/><br/>🏰 <strong>Building Siege Machines:</strong><br/>Be the architect of devastation. Construct an arsenal of siege machines, from trebuchets to battering rams, each meticulously designed to breach enemy defenses and secure your dominance.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2669550/extras/BorderPostBuilding.gif?t=1704981604"><br/><br/>🔗 <strong>Connect with the Community:</strong><br/>Join a community of fellow lords and ladies, share your experiences, and provide feedback as we collectively shape the evolution of the Medieval Machines Builder. Join other medieval fans on our discord: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FYBVMXVCEAN" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.com/invite/YBVMXVCEAN</a><br/><br/>This is a prologue of the Medieval Machines Builder game that is coming out soon. If you've liked the prologue you will love full version of the game. Add it to the wishlist to be the first to know all news, a release date, and discounts.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1584680/Medieval_Machines_Builder/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1584680/Medieval_Machines_Builder/</a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metal Ascension</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2280490/Metal_Ascension/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2280490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2280490/extras/Gamplay1b.gif?t=1704978966"><br/><br/>Metal Ascension is a reverse bullet hell, survival game with rogue-lite elements! Defeat the wave of enemies on each floor to level up, install and upgrade your mech and establish fire superiority. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2280490/extras/ShopB.gif?t=1704978966"><br/><br/>In this fast-paced, top-down-shooter, use different combinations of weapons and pieces to destroy your enemies. Unlock up to 150 unique pieces to improve your mech. Can you reach the top floor and ascend as a legend?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2280490/extras/Combinations2b.gif?t=1704978966"><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Chose between: auto-firing weapons or manual aiming option<br/></li><li>Fast runs (under 30 minutes)<br/></li><li>Unlock over 150+ pieces to customize and improve your mech<br/></li><li>Survive waves lasting 20 to 60 seconds each and kill off as many enemy mechs as you can during that time<br/></li><li>Collect materials and get items from the shop between waves of enemies<br/></li><li>Gain experience destroying mechs to upgrade your stats</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unnatural: Benighted</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2210000/Unnatural_Benighted/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2210000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2210000/extras/Follow.gif?t=1705047697"><br/><br/><i>This game is an independent work inspired by American urban legends and is not affiliated with any TV series, movies, or copyrighted fictional universes.<br/><br/>All characters, events and coincidences that may occur during the game are purely coincidental and have no relation to real people, places or events. Any coincidences with real situations, personalities or historical facts are purely coincidental. The content and plot of the game are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only. The developers are not responsible for possible misinterpretations or unintended consequences of game events. <br/>Play at your own discretion and exercise good judgment in all things.</i><br/><br/>A gripping story of two hunters of unclean forces investigating the disappearance of people.<br/><br/>The main character, Sim, has a wife who goes missing. During the investigation, he learns that she is in the hands of a powerful demon who is blackmailing our protagonist in every way possible.<br/>He enlists the help of his best friend Dan, who also has a personal grudge against the demon.<br/><br/>They will have to put a lot of effort to get out of this difficult situation.<br/><br/>When they start actively searching for the main suspect, the danger on their way grows to unbelievable proportions. The police and the hunters of unclean powers think that the same man is behind all these crimes...<h2 class="bb_tag">Monsters</h2>.Along the way, we will encounter all kinds and horrible monsters that we will have to fight.<h2 class="bb_tag">Fear and Terror</h2>.Evil awaits them in every home, every village, and every forest.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slayin DX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2451720/Slayin_DX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2451720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The mobile hit Slayin returns with an all new look!  Gather your twitch skills and control one of 6 heroes as they hold back wave after of wave of monstrous foes.  Collect coins along the way and spend them wisely at passing merchants to give you the leg up in your never ending battle.  Can you defeat the dragon and his minions?<br/><br/>Slayin DX includes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The original Slayin.<br/></li><li>Slayin DX mode. This is the same gameplay as the original game but with updated pixel art.<br/></li><li>Remappable keyboard and gamepad support.<br/></li><li>Leaderboard graveyard where you can customize your own tombstone and display it amongst your friends.<br/></li><li>Unlockable characters, gameskins and more. </li></ul><br/>Slayin is a single screen action rpg.  The rules are simple: hit enemies with your weapon, but don't let them hit your body.  it sounds simple, but requires a bit of finesse and practice.  The more enemies you slay, the better the treasure they drop.  Treasure is valuable for upgrading your hero, but it also heals you in battle, so keeping a high combo in the later stages is the only way to survive.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRosty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2284860/VRosty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2284860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A Snowman's Journey Into The Anthropocene</h2><br/>One day VRosty, the little snowman, wakes up from a long dream, because it is too hot. He needs your help to find the reason for the warming. Guide him on his long journey through &gt;30 stages and keep him cool!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2284860/extras/Clip_Controls_230525_10.gif?t=1704972156"><h2 class="bb_tag">A VR-puppet-puzzle-platformer</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Puppet-on-a-string controls<br/></li><li>VRosty hangs like a puppet under your hand<br/></li><li>Move yourself with the joystick and hold A so that VRosty follows you <br/></li><li>Jump by quickly moving the controller upwards<br/></li><li>Throw snowballs with the Trigger button and aim by tilting your hand<br/></li><li>Solve puzzles based on physics and the unique controls<br/></li><li>Pull-along VRosty through &gt;30 stages<br/></li><li>Collect &gt;100 snowflakes<br/></li><li>Keep cool</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2284860/extras/Clip_Shooter_01_Landscape.gif?t=1704972156"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gratuitous Space Shooty Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2763030/Gratuitous_Space_Shooty_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2763030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Gratuitous Shooty Game is a hobby space shooter made by the developer of Gratuitous Space Battles, reusing the art from that game :D.<br>
<br>
This game is just a simple space shooty game where you use the left and right arrow keys to control your ship, and the spacebar to fire. Ever-more deadly waves of alien ships attack you in a suspiciously slow and predictable pattern, enabling your single spaceship to somehow overcome incredible odds and defeat all of them, given enough skill.<br>
<br>
Watch out for bonuses that drop from alien ships, especially those cheeky ones that fly across the top of the screen.<br>
<br>
At the end of each battle, your level score becomes a cash bonus, but you are penalized for every alien ship that flies off screen intact. Think of this as you paying reparations to the relatives of those whose houses are blown up by those pesky aliens who got away.<br/>
<br/>
After each level you get to upgrade your ship using your bonus cash. Invest in better shields, better lasers, faster thrusters to move your ship, or a better rate of fire.<br/>
<br/>
For budgetary reasons, your planet only has a budget for a limited number of ships, and for reasons that are unclear, only one can be launched at a time. If you run out of ships, you fail. Sadface.<br/>
<br/>
Technical stuff: Windows only, because meh. Fixed resolution of 1920x1080						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OnlySociety: Secret</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2747590/OnlySociety_Secret/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2747590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The games are primarily action role-playing games. The player takes on the role of the protagonist, "Yue," defending the last stand of the town as part of quests given to them by locals during the death epoch involving recruiting members, growing, and gathering various resources to craft equipment.<br/><br/>History timeline:<br/>Termination<br/>The flu disease happened in 2019 is just only the tip of the iceberg due to overpopulated human. There come by the avalanche of human extinction where screams from the death realm can be heard in the midgard was known as "Virus X".<br/><br/>Extinction<br/>The universe will always have in order. During the even of extinction, while God still had job for his children's, God responded by giving word of gospel which blessed the homosapiens with his energy to stay secure on our feet. "Keep your feet on the ground and keep reaching for the stars". Casey Kasem. <br/><br/>Death<br/>God in having its battle in divine realm and death is walking upon the living reason over population in the Niflheim. During the era of extinction, God left homosapiens wisdom. There are more jobs to be done and it depends on how homosapiens manifest the remaining wisdom.<br/><br/>You <strong>don't</strong> only live once. You live every day and die only once.<br/>However, you are given the chance to make a change.<br/>So, use it wisely.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War Hospital</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1553000/War_Hospital/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1553000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1553000/extras/Gif_Key_Art.gif?t=1705047184"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1553000/extras/WarHospital_Description_EN_1.jpg?t=1705047184"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1553000/extras/Gif_1_EN.gif?t=1705047184"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1553000/extras/WarHospital_Description_EN_2.jpg?t=1705047184"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1553000/extras/Gif_2_EN.gif?t=1705047184"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1553000/extras/WarHospital_Description_EN_3.jpg?t=1705047184"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1553000/extras/Gif_3_EN.gif?t=1705047184"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1553000/extras/WarHospital_Description_EN_4.jpg?t=1705047184"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unstoppable</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2289780/Unstoppable/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2289780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Unstoppable</i> is an adrenaline-pumping horror adventure where you’re tasked with escaping Schindler Tower.<br/><br/>A mysterious gas has turned office workers insane … Now everyone is out for blood. Face dimly-lit corridors filled with death, search for clues to find a cure, and keep the psychotic horde at bay any way you can. Will you get to the bottom of the infection or die in the dark?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2289780/extras/UN-steam-realisticcombat-v01.gif?t=1704963614"><br/><br/><strong>Realistic Combat</strong><br/>Challenging, physics-based combat. Feel the weight of each blow and dodge infected enemies. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2289780/extras/UN-steam-fightingenemies-v02.gif?t=1704963614"><br/><br/><strong>Unpredictable Enemies</strong><br/>The infected do not all think alike – watch out for new weapons and attack patterns. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2289780/extras/UN-steam-weaponbreaking-v02.gif?t=1704963614"><br/><br/><strong>Finite Resources</strong><br/>Your weapons are limited – use them well. Balance item durability against increasingly difficult enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2289780/extras/UN-steam-shadowedworld-v01.gif?t=1704963614"><br/><br/><strong>Shadowed World </strong><br/>Play a game of cat and mouse in the shadows. Stay cautious – the infected can hear your footsteps! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2289780/extras/UN-steam-episodicstory-v01.gif?t=1704963614"><br/><br/><strong>Episodic Story</strong><br/>What is this mysterious gas, and who unleashed it? Unravel the global conspiracy with each new chapter. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2289780/extras/UN-steam-survivalmode-v01.gif?t=1704963614"><br/><br/><strong>Berserk Mode</strong><br/>Strive to keep your humanity as the infection builds in your system. Stay sharp or join the infected.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Package Runner</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2484370/Package_Runner/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In "Package Runner", you are the 22th package handler of ZENITH COMPANY. Your task is to fix packages and put them in order. When the "Central Control" demands, you must remember the location of each package and find it quickly. As time goes on, you'll detect the truth of the company.<br/><br/><strong>\\ Work Hard \\\...</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484370/extras/work.gif?t=1704961724"><br/><br/><strong>\\ Rest Time \\\...</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2484370/extras/house.gif?t=1704961724"><br/><br/><strong>\\ Features \\\...</strong><br/><strong>-</strong> Stylized 2.5D graphics, relaxing gaming experience. <br/><strong>-</strong> Over 3000 items (up to 247 types to collect) in a huge workspace.<br/><strong>-</strong> In rest area, you can collect decorations, get stronger by feast.<br/><strong>-</strong> Easter eggs in the game will reveal the whole story behind gameplay.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
