<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Zoo: Eurasia Animal Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2675740/Planet_Zoo_Eurasia_Animal_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2675740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Wrap up warm and explore the heart of Eurasia with Planet Zoo: Eurasia Animal Pack! Immerse yourself in vast landscapes and untamed beauty as you welcome captivating species to your zoos, including seven habitat species and one exhibit reptile.<br/>Come face-to-face with this stunning array of animals that call this breathtaking region their home. Among them are the majestic wisent, embodying the strength and resilience of the Eurasian wilderness, the wild boar with its broad head and short tusks, and the remarkably fearless wolverine. Alongside these unique additions, the Eurasia Animal Pack also features a brand-new campaign scenario in which players must design and build a zoo in secret to surprise Nancy with a retirement present to cherish forever.<h2 class="bb_tag">EIGHT AMAZING NEW ANIMALS </h2>Marvel at the magnitude of Eurasia, from its winding rivers and dense forests to the heights of its mountains, and discover eight incredible new animals. Introducing the wisent, wild boar, wolverine, takin, saiga, sloth bear, mute swan, and the Hermann’s tortoise. Observe your guests marvelling at these extraordinary additions as you create open and diverse habitats for them.  <h2 class="bb_tag">BRAND-NEW ANIMATIONS </h2>Visitors will look on with delight as each animal settles into its habitat whilst they each display their fascinating and unique behaviours. It's hard to miss the magnificent wisent. This colossal bison navigates through dense forests and deep snow with ease, as its powerful steps echo their power and resilience. Wolverines are renowned for their fearlessness; watch on as these little adventurers climb on and rest from their habitat’s branches. Observe the graceful mute swan - named for its quiet nature, they opt for their body language to do all the talking; from their impressive wing stretch and the dunking of their head, this is a sight your guests won’t want to miss. The wild boars interacting with each other are also not to be overlooked. Known for their social nature, spot the adorable piglets as they trot through their mothers' legs and cosy up with playful and loving nuzzles. Look on with amazement as saigas explore their habitats with their fascinating snout. This eye-catching feature moves around as they interact with their surroundings. These species are native to the largest continental area on Earth so make sure they have plenty of room to roam in lovingly designed and crafted habitats. <h2 class="bb_tag">A COMPELLING NEW CAMPAIGN SCENARIO </h2>Can you keep a secret? Meet with Bernie Goodwin again in this campaign scenario. Aid him with his secret mission to design and build a zoo as a surprise retirement gift for Nancy Jones to watch over in her twilight years. Having worked together for over 30 years, Bernie is bursting with excitement while working on this project for his oldest friend. Can Bernie keep his plans under wraps, or will Nancy catch on?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - Moto Freak Pro Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2625050/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__Moto_Freak_Pro_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2625050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Pack includes:<br>
<br/>
- 2400 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- Operator Skin for Clyde Hogan<br/>
- 2x Weapon Blueprints<br/>
- Animated Calling Card<br/>
- Weapon Sticker<br/>
- Weapon Charm<br/>
- Animated Emblem<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons of Sundaria</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/587520/Dungeons_of_Sundaria/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/587520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The Dungeons:</h2> <br/>* 8 Huge Dungeons filled with hundreds of fiendish monsters and dozens of diabolical bosses.<br/>* Three Levels of Difficulty: Normal, Hard, and Nightmare.  <br/>* Online single player or co-op up to 4-players.<br/>* Local Split-screen multiplayer co-op up to 4-players (only requires a single game copy).<h2 class="bb_tag">Make your Hero:</h2> <br/>* 7 Races: Human, Dwarf, Elf, Halfling, Orc, Goblin and Drog'al (lizard).<br/>* 5 Classes: Champion, Ranger, Cleric, Wizard, and Rogue. <br/>* Customize the appearance of your Hero.<h2 class="bb_tag">Become a Legend:</h2> <br/>* Collect a huge variety of Weapons, Armor, and Accessories to customize your Hero and grow in power.<br/>* Craft powerful equipment and become a force of reckoning.  Multiple tiers of armor and weapons.<br/>* Embrace the Heroism system, allowing you to continually increase the power of your Hero.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taora : Beginning</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2594640/Taora__Beginning/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/steampageTop.png?t=1702337332"><br/>Taora is an island that is infested with zombies and hold many places to explore and loot.<br/> <br/>   You can build your base, craft and upgrade your gear, explore many unique places, loot materials or gears. You can upgrade your vehicle to suit your needs.<br/> <br/>   Upgrade you characters` skills to fit different conditions like hacking electronics, reapiring broken things, healing the wounded or fighting with zombies.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FqXsk9F68D2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/discord.png?t=1702337332"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/gamefeatures.png?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Looting: </h2>Loot materials needed for crafting, base building etc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/Kiyafet_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Vehicles: </h2>There are many vehicles for you to use on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/AraclarGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Crafting: </h2>You can craft and upgrade your gears, vehicles, weapons, armors that make you a real survivor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Open World: </h2>You can hop on your vehicle and explore unique places on Taora.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/DriveGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive: </h2>Shoot and kill as many zombies as you can to survive.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/ShootingGif_1.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Base Building: </h2>It is important to build your base to survive  on Taora. You can store your loot and weapons on your base, build various tools or tables that help you to improve your weapons, vehicles and survivors.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2594640/extras/BaseCraftGIF.gif?t=1702337332"><h2 class="bb_tag">Skills: </h2>Skill up your character on different aspects, they can be a soldier to kill hordes of zombies, or a mechanic that can craft tools, disarm traps, unlock safes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Against the Storm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1336490/Against_the_Storm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are the Viceroy – a leader charged by the Scorched Queen to reclaim the wilderness and discover lost riches for the Smoldering City, civilization's last bastion against the Blightstorm that destroyed the old world. Unlike most survival city builders where your focus is on a single city, in Against the Storm you must build a vast, prosperous network of settlements populated by diverse fantasy races, each with their own specializations and needs.<br/><br/>The wilderness holds many hidden dangers, and never-ending storms will batter your population into submission. If your settlements should fall, then the expedition may end – but not the game. Against the Storm is a roguelite city builder, meaning you will carry forward the resources, upgrades, and experience of your past expeditions each time you set off for a new journey into the wild.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Biomes_6s_v2.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_4.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Foxes, Beavers, and lizards stand alongside humans and harpies in the struggle to survive. Utilize each group's strengths as you balance their varying needs, from housing and culinary preferences to taste in luxuries and recreation. Will you manufacture raincoats, brew ale, and bake pies to boost morale in the face of the oppressive hostility of the forest, or will you prioritize the needs of one species over another to operate more swiftly for the Scorched Queen?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Villagers_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_2.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Experience core city builder gameplay enhanced by roguelite replayability. Build and manage multiple settlements spread out across a large world map, all while collecting valuable meta-progression resources to upgrade the Smoldering City. Feel the pressure of an expectant monarch as the Scorched Queen demands constant progress while recurring Blightstorms pose an inevitable threat to your settlements. Manage your reputation to secure your success at any one settlement before moving on to establish another, constantly seeking new opportunities for growth, taking on unique challenges across multiple biomes, and bracing for the inevitable destruction of everything but the Smoldering City itself. How will you maximize each cycle to not just ensure the best fate for the Smoldering City, but for your career as Viceroy as well?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Roguelite_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_5.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>With hundreds of gameplay modifiers and 6 distinct biomes, every city location presents unique challenges for even the most resourceful Viceroy. Adjust your strategy to changing weather conditions and experiment with rosters of building blueprints and perks that can help your society thrive or bring it to ruin. Will you take on and complete additional objectives and delve deeper into the dangerous forest for potential boons, or will you approach with caution to ensure you operate within your capabilities? All the while, you never know what wares the Trader will bring next year, and the forest holds treasures and resources, but also ancient threats.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/Monsters_6s.gif?t=1702218649"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1336490/extras/en_AtS_Headline_6.png?t=1702218649"><br/><br/>Laying the foundations for a new city is one of the most exciting moments in a city-building game. In Against the Storm, you'll have the opportunity to repeatedly experience this by creating new settlements, while still interacting with your network of previously established cities in a growing world.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Sunshine® 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1540210/Arizona_Sunshine_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_HeaderImage_Crop.png?t=1701985511"><h2 class="bb_tag">Sharpen your machete and load your shotgun: It's time to say hello to your old pal, Fred.</h2> Arizona Sunshine® 2, the next-gen sequel to the fan-favorite VR apocalypse, packs even more gore-geous zombie action! <br/> <br/>Welcome back to sun-kissed, zombified Arizona. Narrated by the unmistakable quips of our dark-humored protagonist, Arizona Sunshine 2 sets you on an all-new limb-strewn adventure in search of answers. In a post-apocalyptic world where every bullet counts, experience the thrill of realistic combat as you wield all-new and fan-favorite weapons--from shotguns to machetes and flamethrowers. <br/><br/>And what's better than braving the end of the f*cking world? Surviving it with your new best friend--Buddy. Not only is Buddy your four-legged companion through thick and thin, he’s also the goodest boy and will help take down those pesky Freds for you. And that's not all, because fan-favorite co-op mode makes its return as well.<br/><br/>In a desolate world, suddenly you’re not so alone anymore. It’s funny how things go.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Form an unexpected friendship as you set out on a cinematic VR journey of intense survival<br/></li><li>Experience the thrill of combat as you physically wield weapons, from shotguns to machetes--and flamethrowers<br/></li><li>Explore gore-geous, next-gen VR environments, all the way to the end of the f*cking world<br/></li><li>Discover all the ways to slay a Fred through a brand-new, next-gen mutilation and gore system<br/></li><li>Enjoy the full campaign from a new perspective with a friend in 2-player co-op<br/></li><li>Join up to three other players in 4-player co-op Horde mode, with additional free maps dropping across Year 1!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1540210/extras/AS2_FooterImage.jpg?t=1701985511"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2186680/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2696650/Warhammer_40000_Rogue_Trader__Limited_Outfit" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/limited_free_dlc.png?t=1702000678"/></a><br/><br/>A free DLC available to everyone who owns the game. This is a limited time offer which must be claimed before January 31st, 2024. Hurry before it vanishes!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the Koronus Expanse.</h2>Begin your adventure aboard your personal, giant voidship, traveling between the multitude of systems within the Koronus Expanse, a barely charted and incredibly perilous region of space. Despite being considered a backwater of the Imperium, this region encompasses an enormous stretch of the void, filled with dangerous creatures and prodigious opportunities for profit and exploration.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Your decisions matter, Lord-Captain.</h2>During quests show your subjects mercy or disdain, stay faithful to the God-Emperor, or consort with enemies of Mankind - your every decision and every act, even in character creation, is changing the in-game open world and those who inhabit it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-2_1.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gather your crew.</h2>Rogue Traders never travel alone. Gather your retinue of righteous heroes, twisted psykers, and perfidious xenos. All of them are ready to follow you into the darkness between the stars. They will offer you counsel, aid you in battle, and allow you to amass ever more power. In return, you can guide them through their own personal journeys, changing their destinies forever.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-3.gif?t=1702000678"><h2 class="bb_tag">Plan your actions carefully.</h2>Slaughter the enemies of Mankind in a fully-fledged isometric turn-based tactical combat. Take advantage of cover, the environment, and careful positioning to overpower your enemies. When that is not enough - use your companion`s powerful abilities to turn the tide of battle and achieve victory even in the direst of situations. Our video game adaption of the classic Rogue Trader ruleset allows an enormous number of possibilities for you to explore.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2186680/extras/new_steam-4.gif?t=1702000678"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Date with Death</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2415010/A_Date_with_Death/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/quote_ADWD.png?t=1701962059"><br/><br/>You're just an ordinary person... or so you thought. For your entire life, you've been narrowly avoiding death by pure luck... or is it something more? When a strange program suddenly appears on your computer, and someone claiming to be the Grim Reaper says he's come for your soul, your life as you know it is thrown upside down.<br/><br/>As you delve deeper into the mysterious man that calls himself the Grim Reaper, you begin to wonder if fate brought you two together for a reason. Can you resist his charm, or will you fall for the one destined to take your soul?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>A Date with Death is a supernatural romance chat simulator visual novel about the week long bet you enter against the Grim Reaper to attempt to keep your soul. Create your own character, from appearance to pronouns, decorate your apartment, and spend the (possible) last week of your life getting to know the one hunting for your soul.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2415010/extras/about1__1_.gif?t=1701962059"><br/>💀<strong> Custom Character Creation:</strong> Build your own protagonist, from their physical appearance to their pronouns and name. Update them throughout the game!<br/>💀 <strong>Room Design:</strong> Decorate your apartment to your liking and create a cozy space that you'll love coming back to.<br/>💀 <strong>Pet Your Furry (or scaley?) Companion:</strong> Yes, you can pet the dog. Snuggle up with your furry friend and let their cute antics help you unwind.<br/>💀 <strong>Choices That Matter:</strong> Make decisions that will affect your character's fate and lead you to one of multiple possible endings. What kind of relationship will you have with the Grim Reaper?<br/>💀 <strong>Gorgeous Original Art:</strong> Lose yourself in stunning visuals that bring the story to life, and feel like you're truly part of the world of A Date with Death.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1702449188"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1702394215"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1702394215"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1702203824"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1702203824"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1702026390"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1702026390"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1702026390"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1702026390"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1702026390"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-8 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">8-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with three other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1702474594"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1702474594"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1702474594"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1702474594"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1702474594"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1702474594"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.<br/>If you are easily intoxicated, changing the following settings may help.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera shake】</strong><br/>The camera shakes when you walk or run, but if you set the value to 0.0, the camera will not shake.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Acceleration】</strong><br/>If you set the maximum value to 30.0, the camera will move without delay.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Sensitivity】</strong><br/>If the sensitivity is high, the camera will move significantly when the mouse is moved. <br/>Adjust the value if you find it difficult to operate the camera with the default value of 1.<br/><br/><strong>【Motion Blur】</strong><br/>Afterimages will appear when the camera is moved. Recommended to disable at 30FPS<br/><br/><strong>【Preset】</strong><br/>Set the overall graphic settings.<br/>If you do not have sufficient specs, it is better to set it to "Low" to avoid sickness.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1702363362"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats and Seek</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672090/Cats_and_Seek/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Hey, do you have 5 minutes to spare? Let's play hide and seek with 100 cats in Osaka! 😻 Can you find them all?<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2>🎮 1 level<br/>😻 100 Hidden cats<br/>🏆 100 Achievements<br/>🔆 Brightness setting<br/>🎨 Choose your favorite color<br/>🔔 Free hints<br/>💾 Save system<br/>🔍 Zoom<br/>🔉 Cute cat sounds<br/>🎁 Extra level DLC (105 cats)<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/game_play.gif?t=1702478921"><br/><br/>And if bored with black and white doddles you can choose <strong>your own favorite color</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/change_color.PNG?t=1702478921"><h2 class="bb_tag">Follow our Dev Page for updates.</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/developer/noobzilla" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/follow.png?t=1702478921"/></a> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1702044720"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astral Ascent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1280930/Astral_Ascent/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astral Ascent is a 2D platformer rogue-lite game set in a modern fantasy world. As one of 4 Heroes with very different personalities, you must escape from <i>the Garden</i>, an astral prison guarded by 12 powerful and vicious bosses, the Zodiacs.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYSTYLE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Gif_playstyle.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Unlock dozens of unique spells for your 4 distinct characters. Optimize your own build or try out new ones to take down 12 powerful bosses. Get stronger with time to match up with your foes. Each run will test your skills and your reactivity.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TWELVE ALMIGHTY BOSSES TO FACE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Zodiacs.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The Zodiacs are 12 experienced guardians dispatched over 4 gorgeous worlds. They’ll bring to the battlefield unique attacks, abilities, and patterns, backstories to uncover, and reasons to be fighting you. Get yourself warned!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4 PLAYABLE CHARACTERS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/4_Character_banniere_steam7.png?t=1700851162"><br/><i>Unique characters. Unique weapons. Unique ways to play.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Ayla:</strong> The sole survivor of her guild of assassins, she uses her twin daggers to eliminate her enemies before they can react. Her speed and proficiency are unmatched.<br/></li><li><strong>Kiran:</strong> This orphan learned life the hard way. He uses his strength to deliver attacks powerful enough to create shockwaves. Brutal.<br/></li><li><strong>Calie:</strong> This talented sculptor wants her freedom back. She will use her magical gemstones to pierce enemy defenses and shred them to bits. She is unforgiving.<br/></li><li><strong>Octave:</strong> Trained by a powerful witch, this young fighter summons ethereal guns to attack his foes. When needed, he can conjure bigger weapons as well. Lethal in all cases.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A STORY THAT OPENS UP, ONE PIECE AT A TIME</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/ZimZim2.png?t=1700851162"><br/>Astral Ascent is a rogue-lite infused with narration. Replayability is part of our story which will be unraveled piece by piece. As you get stronger, you will discover more about the characters, their motivations, and the secrets of the world they’re trapped in.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL CO-OP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Coop.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The weight of destiny is too heavy to carry by yourself? Don’t worry and bring a friend to play in our <strong>two-player co-op</strong> mode. Fight and crush your enemies together in local co-op or online using the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/remoteplay?snr=1_614_615__1601" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Steam's Remote Play Together</strong></a> feature.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A VAST, COLORFUL FANTASY WORLD WAITING TO BE EXPLORED</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Panning.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Dash across gigantic landscapes. Explore original and hand-crafted areas. Discover the world created by our artists, with a gorgeous art and frame-by-frame animation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1701808865"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1701863253"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1701863253"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1701863253"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1701948634"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1701948634"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1701948634"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roboquest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/692890/Roboquest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Oasis.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>Roboquest is a fast-paced FPS with Roguelite mechanics playable in singleplayer or 2 players co-op.<br/><br/>Shoot and run your way through randomly generated environments, pick-up upgrades along the way and blast the powerful big bad bosses you encounter.<br/><br/>Upgrade your basecamp and unlock persistent upgrades to customize your playstyle and dive further on each subsequent run.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Title_Features.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act2.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><strong>Fast Movement</strong> – <i>Master the frantic movement mechanics in order to run and jump through the levels with evasive maneuvers against the enemy bullet-hell.</i><br/><br/><strong>Guardian Classes</strong> – <i>Choose from several classes: lead your army of drones, blast tons of enemies at once with a powerful rocket or stealth-in for a sudden burst attack.</i><br/><br/><strong>Build Customization</strong> - <i>Create your build along the way with unique sets of upgrades for each class, find powerful synergies and further personalize your playstyle.</i><br/><br/><strong>Weapon Diversity</strong> – <i>From regular shotguns, rifles and snipers to the almighty mortar and flare gun, Roboquest offers a large diversity of weapons to choose from.</i><br/><br/><strong>Random Levels</strong> – <i>Each with a different theme and atmosphere, generated with a careful mix of pre-placed and randomized chunks, the levels offer a fresh challenge each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Run, fall, run again</strong> – <i>Tough challenges await you, and mastery is required. Learn the way of the enemy and master movement and shooting to prevail. Prepare to return to your basecamp if you are destroyed by the evil bots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Persistent Upgrades</strong> – <i>Collect wrenches during your runs and use them to upgrade your basecamp and unlock new gameplay elements and choices to help you dive further into the game each run.</i><br/><br/><strong>Singleplayer or 2p-Coop</strong> – <i>Dive into the fray alone or in 2-player co-op with your brobot (and find even more brobots with the cross-platform and the public matchmaking).</i><br/><br/><strong>Polished experience</strong> – <i>Responsive input system with many quality-of-life ‘under-the-radar’ features to make it as fluid as possible and make sure nothing comes in your way when unleashing havoc on the badbots.</i><br/><br/><strong>Original Soundtrack</strong> – <i>High octane, custom-tailored soundtrack supports the fast gameplay and robot-smashing action.</i><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_Robot_StorePage.png?t=1700122097"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/Breakline_TheWorld.png?t=1700122097"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/692890/extras/GIF_Act1.gif?t=1700122097"><br/><br/>The year is 2700. Humans live scattered through the desert, struggling to survive. It’s looking pretty bleak.<br/>Until a young scavenger girl named Max stumbles across an old Guardian robot, laying abandoned in the sand. She reactivates him, knowing that with a Guardian by her side, she may be able to give mankind a fighting chance…<br/>Together, the two begin to explore the mysterious canyons that surround them, searching for answers and a way to survive.<br/>There’s just one problem. The canyons are crawling with evil bots, determined to stop them from advancing. But who are they? And what are they guarding?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watermelon Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658820/Watermelon_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							10 possible fruits and one goal, reach the Watermelon.<br/>Your job is to combine matching fruits to evolve them to the next one and eventually reach the coveted Watermelon.<br/>To help you, you have 3 different abilities at your disposal. But watch out, using these will cost you some of your points. Be smart about when you use them to get the highest score!<h2 class="bb_tag">MULTIPLAYER</h2>Measure your fruit skills against another player.<h2 class="bb_tag">GET THE WATERMELON</h2>How many Watermelons can you combine before your basket overflows?<h2 class="bb_tag">USE YOUR ABILITIES</h2>Power, level up and destroy — These abilities will help you reach the Watermelon, using any of those will also allow you to angle your aim.<h2 class="bb_tag">GOLDEN FRUIT</h2>If luck is on your side, you might even see the mysterious Golden Fruit. Find it and witness its effect firsthand.<h2 class="bb_tag">STATISTICS</h2>Track your progress with in-depth statistics. Visit the menu to see the number of fruits you've combined, your ability usage, and much more.<h2 class="bb_tag"></h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.codecks.io%2Fwatermelon-game" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658820/extras/Roadmap_Banner.png?t=1702238677"/></a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager 2024</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2252570/Football_Manager_2024/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2252570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a real boss and write your own football story in Football Manager 2024, the most complete edition in the series yet. <br/><br/>Whether you’re a manager who likes to build from the bottom or prefers to chase immediate glory, the perfect challenge awaits. The arrival of the new Meiji Yasuda Insurance Ltd J. League licence unlocks J1 League, J2 League, J3 League for the first time ever, giving you the opportunity to explore new horizons in Japan.<br/><br/>Wherever you manage, it's up to you to build a team capable of competing with the world's elite.<br/><br/><strong>Game Description </strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Continue your relentless journey to the top of the footballing world by using the new ability to import your existing career from Football Manager 2023.<br/></li><li>Craft a winning tactical approach, incorporating modern football’s most popular systems and cutting-edge positional innovations to deliver victories on the pitch. <br/></li><li>Master the transfer market, using new ways to shape your side to cultivate a squad capable of achieving your goals. <br/></li><li>Level up your players on the training field, developing the mentality and teamwork needed to transform contenders into champions. <br/></li><li>See your tactical vision come to life on Matchdays, with every game elevated by improvements to ball and player movements.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">NEW FOR THIS SEASON</h2><br/><br/><strong>TRUER FOOTBALL MOTION</strong><br/><br/>Enhancements to player animations, ball physics and lighting deliver the most immersive Match Engine in Football Manager history. Move to the cutting edge of football by using the new Inverted Full-Back player role, while more intelligent player rotational movements add more fluidity to every highlight. <br/><br/><strong>DOMINATE FROM SET PIECES</strong><br/><br/>Make an impact at both ends of the pitch with an overhauled Set Piece Creator. Lean on the expertise of brand-new Set Piece Coaches to develop winning routines in every scenario that will help you to outsmart your rivals. <br/><br/><strong>BRACE FOR TRANSFER BATTLES</strong><br/><br/>Showcase your squad-building skills in our most refined transfer market yet. You’ll face a trickier battle for talent as your rival opposition managers are now more strategic than ever in their recruitment decision-making. <br/><br/><strong>NEW AGENTS TO BUILD A DREAM SQUAD</strong><br/><br/>Better shape your perfect squad with the introduction of new Intermediaries that will help you offload surplus players for a cut of the final transfer fee. Additional functionality for existing Agents and the debut of TransferRoom, a football marketplace for transfers in real life, gives you more real-world powered tools than ever to build an elite team and dominate the competition.<br/><br/><strong>ELEVATE PERFORMANCES WITH TARGETS</strong><br/><br/>Motivate your team to achieve more on and off the field by setting them individual Targets. Whether you’re focusing on goals scored in a season or average training performances, challenge your star players and top prospects to maximise their ability. <br/><br/><strong>A HOST MORE ADDITIONS</strong><br/><br/>Enjoy greater variety in every career with the arrival of two new game modes. Real World mirrors when players actually joined your club. Your World sets club squads and budgets at the day your career starts, meaning that only players who joined before that date will be in your squad, giving you the opportunity to rewrite your team’s transfer window.<br/><br/>Elsewhere, you can look to dominate international management and plan for your country's future with a revamped National Pool that gives you a better overview of the talent at your disposal. Match preparation and briefing meetings deliver you winning insights before each fixture. <br/><br/>That’s not all though, with many more changes waiting for you to discover in every career.<br/><br/><i>This version contains information that is still under approval process by rights holders and may contain data that does not, at this time, accurately reflect real world data. For context, some club and player assets may be absent during this version.</i> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Invincible</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/731040/The_Invincible/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/The_Invincible_small_claim_EN.png?t=1702479275"><br/><br/>You are a highly qualified, sharp-witted astrobiologist named Yasna. Being entangled in a space race, you and your crew end up on the unexplored planet Regis III. The scientific journey quickly turns into a search mission for lost crewmates. Follow its trail, but be fully aware that every decision you make can bring you closer to danger.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/The_Invincible_gif_nr_1.gif?t=1702479275"><br/><br/>Uncover mind-boggling scientific phenomena in a cosmic, philosophical adventure set within eerie landscapes. Discover fragments of what’s lost and report to your Astrogator, let his voice aid you in hard times.<br/><br/>You couldn’t have foreseen humanity’s biggest threat. It will force you to rethink mankind’s ambitions and biases. Go on - make decisions, follow the mystery… but remember not to underestimate the brutal simplicity and brilliance of evolution.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/The_Invincible_gif_nr_2.gif?t=1702479275"><br/><br/>Robots, people… Choose whether to interact with different creatures on Regis III or how to do it. Friend, companion? Enemy? You never suspected what these words might really mean before you got here.<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in the atompunk atmosphere by using various tools, such as a telemeter or a tracker, and drive a vehicle through a stunning landscape. Experience realistic interactions with analogue technologies in a retro futuristic timeline.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/The_Invincible_nr_3.gif?t=1702479275"><br/><br/>The Invincible is a first-person game based on the motifs of The Invincible - an iconic novel of the world-known, hard science-fiction author and Polish futurologist Stanisław Lem.<br/><br/>There are places like Regis III, not prepared for us and for which we are not prepared. Still, our spacecraft inevitably comes closer to the destination - for our stories and fates to cross in a dead spot.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/731040/extras/Invincible_Steam_Deck_Verified_616x226.jpg?t=1702479275"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cards and Castles 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1719390/Cards_and_Castles_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1719390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Both incredibly deep and easy for new players to pick up, this fun and wacky CCG features a tactical board for a touch of strategy. Cards played spring to life on the battlefield as animated characters who can move and block enemies, adding depth to the traditional CCG formula. Build unique decks from 7 different iconic factions: Vikings, Crusaders, Warlocks, Pirates, Ninjas, Druids, and the NEWLY ADDED undead!<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Worldwide Online Cross-Platform Multiplayer<br/></li><li> Cross-Platform Accounts<br/></li><li> Multiplayer Lobbies, Friends Lists, and Chat<br/></li><li> Draft Mode<br/></li><li> Single Player Modes<br/></li><li> Collectible Cosmetics<br/></li><li> Lots of Free Cards<br/></li><li> Penguins</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raccoo Venture</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/849210/Raccoo_Venture/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Raccoo Venture is a fun 3D platformer that brings the nostalgia from 1990s in a playful and puzzle-filled world.<br/>Defeat multiple enemies and challenges, find new outfits to customize the hero, discover new friends who will help you on this journey to recover the holy relics.<br/><br/>Discover your true destiny through a journey full of magic and secrets. Save Verta's Harmony and prevent chaos from returning to the land. But be careful! Many puzzles and enemies will cross your path. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/raccoo_venture_raccoo_run.png?t=1702523682"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/Enemies.gif?t=1702523682"><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/raccoo_venture_desc_icon2.png?t=1702523682"> Everything is balance</img></h2><br/>In the beginning, the world was made of chaos. Creatures born from nature's disturb dominated the whole land of Verta and fed of disorder.<br/>Then came the Guardians, who united their powers and created a sacred relic, so powerful that it was able to contain the unpredictable forces of chaos, bringing balance to the world. The creatures were contained, Verta became fertile and all animals could live in harmony.<br/><br/>This relic was made by equal fractions of goodness and wickedness, and to not fall into the evil hands, the Guardians divided it into small pieces and hid it in the middle of the forest. From this day on we have never heard about the Guardians again and they have become a legend.<br/><br/>Years later, creatures known as Tattooed Tatus have found the relic and the balance of the world now is in great danger.<br/><br/>Only the sole heir from the power of the Guardians is able to prevent that from happening.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/raccoo_venture_custom3.png?t=1702523682"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/Outfits.gif?t=1702523682"><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/raccoo_venture_desc_icon2.png?t=1702523682"> One outfit for every occasion</img></h2><br/>Make things your way. Collect memorable Special Outfits that will give new looks and customize our esteemed hero.<br/>Find answers to the mysteries on your path, expanding new horizons in this magical land.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/raccoo_venture_magic2.png?t=1702523682"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/InvisibleFloor.gif?t=1702523682"><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/raccoo_venture_desc_icon2.png?t=1702523682"> Magical items</img></h2><br/>An ancestral tribe, named Visgo Vesgo, spread many of its magical items throughout Verta. They say that some of them are so hidden that it would take centuries to be found. Little is known about the reasons for being there and their true powers.<h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/raccoo_venture_desc_icon2.png?t=1702523682"> Smoother gameplay experience with gamepad</img></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/849210/extras/raccoo_venture_gamepad-en.png?t=1702523682"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>精灵幻境  Elven dreams</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2642640/__Elven_dreams/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2642640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In this game, you will enter a world full of magic and fantasy. As an elf manipulator, your goal is to explore mysterious locations, collect and capture more powerful elf companions, and hone your favorite elves in battle!<br>
<br>
Each sprite has a unique appearance, skills, and attributes, and you'll need to choose and train your sprite wisely to level up and evolve to take on different combat challenges.<br>
<br>
In battle, you'll have to use your elves' skills and strategies to dodge the projectiles and collisions of many hostile elves, challenging different bosses in each setting to find the combo that suits you best<br>
<br>
Beautiful graphics and sound effects will take you into a gorgeous and mysterious fantasy that immerses you in a world of elves and magic, where every elf you encounter can be captured. Get ready to start your elf collecting adventure!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>宿主ガードマン - Host Security Guard -</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686720/__Host_Security_Guard/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							『- Host Security Guard - 宿主ガードマン 』is a novel game in which the protagonist Masato, working at a security company, is recruited as the subject of a suspicious experiment for a raise, and he becomes involved in various incidents.<br>
A Bishojo Game released in 2017 under the "IncaRose" brand has been reworked for the "PandaShojo" platform for players around the world to enjoy.<br>
<br>
<br>
◆Introduction<br>
In the darkness that seems even darker than night.<br>
I squint my eyes and see something wriggling.<br/>
Something that awaits me.<br/>
I opened the case and swallowed its contents in a gulp.<br/>
And then...... I fainted.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
◆Synopsis<br/>
Sometime in the near future, there exists a new district of Kayamichi in eastern Tokyo.<br/>
In this new city, by taking a security-related job, one can receive support from the ward.<br/>
<br/>
The protagonist, Masato Fujita is one of them who receives support for living.<br/>
As time went by, the male-only shared house underwent changes,<br/>
and now left with him are Sanae Kouno, and her sister Hazuki.<br/>
They were all satisfied with their ordinary life supporting each other.<br/>
<br/>
One day, Masato was approached by Misaki, a senior colleague, and asked if he wanted to become the test subject for a certain experiment.<br/>
"It's shady. But I want the money..."<br/>
Faced with a sense of unease and the dilemma of a raise, after much deliberation, he decided to sign the documents.<br/>
<br/>
Not knowing that this choice would completely changed the lives of Masato and the others...<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
◆Characters<br/>
・Sanae Kouno<br/>
"I'll forgive you! IF you give me two Cat Cafe vouchers!!"<br/>
The eldest of the Kouno sisters, always with a smile, was gentle, graceful, and possessed both beauty and talent.<br/>
Younger than Masato, but still takes care of her two cohabitants and is a meddling schoolgirl.<br/>
She is skilled in cooking and is preparing for a chef's exam. A big fan of American comic books.<br/>
<br/>
・Kazuki Kouno<br/>
"In my opinion, I'd make you responsible for four weeks' worth of toilet and bathroom cleaning as punishment."<br/>
The younger sister of the Kouno sisters. She's a fundamentally good child but struggles to be straightforward and tends to have a sharp tongue.<br/>
To Masato, she is very informal, but to others, like her superior, she knows how to properly show her dependence.<br/>
Deep inside, she admires and cherishes Sanae, who takes care of her more than anyone else<br/>
<br/>
・Misaki<br/>
"Hey Fujita-san, thanks for your hard work, here's your coffee."<br/>
An easygoing and elusive woman at Masato's company who often picks on Masato.<br/>
She's constantly on the move between departments, switching between being a senior or junior depending on the situation.<br/>
She proposes the experiment to Masato to volunteer, but is she an ally or an enemy...?<br/>
<br/>
・Masato Fujita<br/>
A security guard working in a company. Loves Sanes's cook and delicious booze.<br/>
He ends up working as security at a suspicious research facility, feeling like walking on a tightrope every shift.<br/>
He cherishes the daily life in the shared house and finds happiness in it.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerWash Adventure VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2589440/PowerWash_Adventure_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Immerse yourself in the thrilling experience of power washing</h2>In PowerWash Adventure, you can conduct cleaning in a variety of scenarios, such as gardens, garages, parks, schools, etc. Flush away all the dirt and debris to restore them to their original states. Use the golden coins you earn to buy and upgrade different types and functions of high-pressure water guns to make your water gun more powerful and flexible, and enjoy the thrill of flushing and sense of accomplishment.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589440/extras/身临其境.gif?t=1702515661"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explores infinite possibilities in Multiverse</h2>Travel through diverse universes and embark on the rinsing adventures with different themes and styles. You can clean up traces of alien life in a space station, engage in intimate interactions with beautiful characters in a dream realm. Each scene has its own unique storyline and mission, giving you unlimited surprises and excitement.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589440/extras/梦境.gif?t=1702515661"><h2 class="bb_tag">Graffiti, and create your own stages</h2>That's not all, you can also use the supplies to become a graffiti master, unleash your imagination and creativity to spray-paint or clean up others' graffiti, furthermore, you can use your imagination to create your own stages and share them with other players to communicate with, or you can experience other players' stages to taste their creative ideas.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2589440/extras/涂鸦.gif?t=1702515661"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destiny Star Girlfriend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2361700/Destiny_Star_Girlfriend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY &amp; FEATURES </h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Localized for Steam based on the 2018 Android release <br/></li><li>Multi-choice, single-ending VN with 10+ hours till credits <br/></li><li>Award-winning graphics and theme song (“Magical Girl☆Conflict”) <br/></li><li>Spacey visual effects, CG artwork, and anime-style sprites <br/></li><li>Star-studded cast of professional Japanese voice talent </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">STORY </h2><br/>When campus nobody Seiji is attacked by unhinged space demons, it’s his classroom crush Yuuri who shows up to save the day! Her magical-girl powers easily vanquish the enemy, but a surprise ambush forces her to dive in harm’s way to shield him—leaving both fatally wounded. Luckily, Miss Fujiko arrives on the scene with an enchanted thread to bind both their life forces, sparing them from certain death.<br/><br/>Over the next three months as Seiji and Yuuri slowly recover, the pair are on doctor’s orders to stay within one meter of each other or risk snapping their “red string of fate.” With his dream girl only centimeters away at every waking moment, will Seiji finally summon the courage to shoot his shot?<h2 class="bb_tag">CHARACTERS </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361700/extras/enchara01.png?t=1702515599"><br/><strong>Yuuri Kamiizumi </strong><br/><i>Voice: Ichigo Momoi </i><br/><br/>A First-Class Stars bearing the name “Rigel.” As an expert manipulator of all things light magic, she pulverizes demons to dust with overwhelming baseball-themed finesse. <br/><br/>Popular on campus for her cute looks and nice-girl undercover persona. Beneath the mask, while still upbeat and generous, she can be conceited and a sore loser who often gets stuck on one-upping others. For all her bluster, it doesn’t take much to crack her defenses. <br/><br/><i>“Nuh-uh, this First-Class Stars has ZERO chinks in her armor. Not one!” </i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361700/extras/enchara02.png?t=1702515599"><br/><strong>Maja Krienke </strong><br/><i>Voice: Ion Momoyama </i><br/><br/>A young woman recruited and contracted by a Majin under mysterious circumstances. As a Stars Killer, she enrolls at Seiji’s academy to defeat Yuuri, Kanoko, and the other Stars. In contrast to Yuuri’s light-wielding magic, Maja commands the darkness—and wields a mean sword to boot. <br/><br/>Seriously single-minded, she is above all else a warrior of her word, which only makes her Majin alliance more puzzling. <br/><br/><i>“I am Maja Krienke. Once I defeat you, I will subjugate the entire Far East!” </i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361700/extras/enchara03.png?t=1702515599"><br/><strong>Kanoko Satake </strong><br/><i>Voice: Yuki Nekomura </i><br/><br/>A Stars bearing the name “Sadalmelik.” Though still a freshman, her Stars skills already surpass some of the organization’s best.<br/><br/>Chill and seemingly unfazed even in a pinch, she prefers to avoid social small talk, with few exceptions. Obsessed with her campus senior Yuuri as her magical-girl master and mentor, she devotes her time off to serving her every whim. Amazing in the kitchen and a wizard at domestic chores. <br/><br/><i>“I’d like nothing more than for you to rely on me for everything...” </i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2361700/extras/enchara04.png?t=1702515599"><br/><strong>Fujiko Yonamine </strong><br/><i>Voice: Yuuha Nitta </i><br/><br/>A retired Stars who bore the name “Ancha.” An active member of the Starry Sky Council’s East Kanagawa Branch. Revered for her powerful healing magic since her demon-vanquishing days, she continues to provide support spells while devoting her time to guiding the next generation of Stars. <br/><br/>Has her fair share of airhead moments, but is overall a mild-mannered pacifist. <br/><br/><i>“Yaaay! I got told I did a good job!” </i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerWash Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2699660/PowerWash_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Immerse yourself in the thrilling experience of power washing</strong></h2>In PowerWash Adventure, you can literally get your hands on the exhilarating feeling of rinsing and relieving pressure. The operation of the game is super simple: use the high-pressure water gun to flush items to clean. As a casual and stress relieving rinsing simulation game, you can start and end it at any time without gameplay pressure. We also offer a variety of immersive themes: weightless space, cleaning workshop, and a variety of animals on the prairie!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699660/extras/产品概述.gif?t=1702521884"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Offers a variety of scenarios and characters</strong></h2>You're a city cleaner protecting the the environment, you're an astronaut in space rinsing a space station, or you can be the archaeologist rinsing a statue of Anubis in the Sahara Desert. Richly themed levels and expansion DLCs allow you to experience the multiverse!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699660/extras/提供多种场景.gif?t=1702521884"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>No pressure, just flush!</strong></h2>The game's interactive mechanism is as simple as picking up a high-pressure water gun and rinsing the items in the scene to make them clean. Players can configure different nozzles for the water gun to feel the different spraying feeling and enjoy the immersive rinsing process. You can start and finish the game at any time, so you won't feel the game stress. We also provide a handy little helper to help you easily find hidden stains and unlock 100% of the rinsing progress, so say goodbye to compulsive disorder!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699660/extras/随心冲洗.gif?t=1702521884"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peeking at the peak</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2702580/Peeking_at_the_peak/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Peeking at the Peak" is a game where a melon climbs a mountain. Primarily, it involves jumping and rotating, using control buttons to maneuver the character effectively while jumping. Utilizing the terrain allows for larger jumps. It's recommended for those who enjoy high-difficulty climbing games. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2702580/extras/ContentExample008.png?t=1702513180"><br/>This game was influenced by 'Getting Over It with Bennett Foddy'.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emplacement</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2271500/Emplacement/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2271500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2271500/extras/final_smaller_build_base.png?t=1702512021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2271500/extras/final_building_base.gif?t=1702512021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2271500/extras/final_small_gain_resources.png?t=1702512021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2271500/extras/final_gain_resources.gif?t=1702512021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2271500/extras/final_small_build_army.png?t=1702512021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2271500/extras/final_building_army.gif?t=1702512021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2271500/extras/final_small_kill_king.png?t=1702512021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2271500/extras/final_kill_king.gif?t=1702512021"><h2 class="bb_tag">Description</h2>Emplacement is an innovative and strategic turn-based game that combines elements of tile-laying and combat. The game is played on an isometric board, with each player taking turns to place tiles in an attempt to gain the upper hand over their opponent. The game is similar to chess in that players must think ahead and anticipate their opponent's moves in order to succeed.<br/><br/><br/>As the game progresses, players can use their units to engage in combat with the other player's units. The main objective of the game is to defeat the other player by killing their king. The king is a special unit that is placed on the board at the start of the game, and should be protected by other units. The game is won by the player who successfully kills the other player's king.<br/><br/>Emplacement is a challenging and entertaining game that requires players to think creatively and strategically. The game's isometric perspective and turn-based gameplay add depth and excitement to the experience, making it a must-play for fans of strategy games. The game's simple yet engaging mechanics make it accessible to players of all ages and skill levels, making it an excellent choice for both casual and hardcore gamers alike						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Fusion Fever</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2682680/Color_Fusion_Fever/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2682680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Story</strong><br/>This is a game in which you combine stuffed cats of the same type to earn points.<br/><br/><strong>Description </strong><br/>Launch a stuffed cat by pressing the T button. Left-click to lift and move it, then hit it against a stuffed cat of the same type to evolve it. By doing so, you will receive points. However, if the cat is left unattended for a certain period of time, it will transform into a cat that will damage the player.<br/>The game is over when the player's health reaches 0.<br/><br/><strong>Feature</strong><br/>・puzzle element<br/>・Happy production						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADievals - The rise of Rusty Steelknee</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/916240/MADievals__The_rise_of_Rusty_Steelknee/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/916240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in the comedy and grotesque atmospheres of MADievals! <br/>A 3D point&amp;click adventure like you haven’t seen for a long time, perfect for the whole family!<br/>Set in a completely inaccurate Middle Ages, if you love the craziness of 90s adventures (like Monkey Island), you can't absolutely miss it!<br/> <br/>A fearless knight named Rusty Steelknee, hunter of precious relics, arrives in the Realm of Manzasun. Nothing is known about him, apart from the fact that he’s never separated from his helm, his horse Spoffy and his cast iron drawers, and that his purpose is to take possession of a golden relic.<br/> <br/>The realm, though, has been afflicted by a curse, the CuPeNEver, and surrounded by a terrible eternal darkness. Very soon, Rusty – due to both his proud temper and a series of not exactly accidental coincidences – will become involved in something much bigger than him. <br/> <br/>But the brave knight will know how to tackle the adventure head-on, and with his self-deprecating sarcasm he will be able to disentangle himself from extraordinary situations!<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fascinating and mysterious story, full of absurd and zany scenarios.<br/></li><li> Funny dialogues with lots of bizarre characters.<br/></li><li> Unusual puzzles but with their own logic.<br/></li><li> Ability to switch to 2D pixel art as many like nowadays, provocative women to conquer and a final prize of a million golden doubloons to win! (Okay, that’s not true, but the game is really funny, promise!)</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brinemegeddon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2709660/Brinemegeddon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2709660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							YET ANOTHER culmination of a YEAR  of hard work behind the scenes has ALMOST been COMPLETED! I just want to thank ALL of you who have supported my previous game GATETAIL in ANY way shape or form, each and every one of you have been a massive support and I thank you all for that!<br/><br/>NOTE: If you want to play the DEMO, here's the link to the gamejolt!<br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fgamejolt.com%2Fgames%2Fbrinemegeddon%2F861107" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://gamejolt.com/games/brinemegeddon/861107</a><br/><br/><br/><br/><strong><i>Uh oh, it's Brinemegeddon!</i></strong><br/><br/><br/>     Brinemegeddon is a colorful action-adventure strategy RPG with a comedic story-rich basis and immersive combat/puzzle based world sprinkled nicely with narrative, fast-paced combat, and fun minigames! Join Ashley and her friends, (People with ACTUAL names!?) as she procrastinates to the point where an ACTUAL demon takes over her mind and CHAOS AND CHARACTER ARCS ENSUE!!!<br/><br/>     In the world of Brinemegeddon, however, powerful interdimensional threats like demons traveling through the mind to other worlds are NOT taken lightly by those just outside reality's borders! Who KNOWS who (or what) might show up to "regulate" these dimensional delinquents!<br/><br/>     Do YOU have what it takes to make it through Brinemegeddon's combat, challenges, puzzles, and more in order to SAVE the rapidly shifting lands you ONCE called home!?<br/><br/>     Well, there's only one way to find out, now is there?<br/><br/><br/>Features:<br/><br/><strong>- 10+ unique challenging bosses (+Well ending)</strong><br/><br/><strong>- Action-packed team-based combat (Just don't use blizzard.)</strong><br/><br/><strong>- Vastly unique and varied locations (Have you ever been sent cross -country from an exploding bubble before?)</strong><br/><br/><strong>- Fun and interesting enemies (Randy's here too.)</strong><br/><br/><strong>- Tons of different minigames &amp; mechanics (FISHINGGGG RETURNSSS!!!!!!!!!!!!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>- Diverse &amp; interesting characters (&amp; The Swazzler.)</strong><br/><br/><strong>- Varied and challenging minigames + puzzles (Without relying on RNG!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>- Horror elements (No jumpscares.)</strong><br/><br/><strong>- Comedy (Ah yes.)</strong><br/><br/><strong>- Gambling (AGAIN) (WE CANT HAVE THIS IN OUR 13+ (simulated gambling) GAME.)</strong><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>As you can see, Brinemegeddon's a CHAOTIC and EVER-CHANGING world ready for YOU! (and you specifically.)<br/><br/><br/><br/>And, as always,<br/>Ribbit, ribbit.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Glitch Fairy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1811910/The_Glitch_Fairy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1811910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Glitch Fairy is a fast action platformer starring Monie, a spunky fairy with the unusual power to ''glitch'' her enemies.<br>
<br>
Story<br>
<br>
Our story begins when Monie gets her flying ability stolen by her arch nemesis, the minigun-wielding Princess ''Badassia'' Spalanie.<br>
<br>
Fortunately for our little fairy, she discovers a shrine that grants her a new magical power; The Glitch Beam, a powerful reality-bending tool that turns her enemies into all sorts of fun and useful things.<br/>
<br/>
Now flightless, but stronger than ever, Monie embarks on a quest to confront her old rival and get her flying ability back!<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
<br/>
The core gameplay of The Glitch Fairy focuses on jumping, shooting, dashing, and glitching. The Glitch Beam can be used as a speedrunning tool, or as a way to explore every nook and cranny each level has to offer.<br/>
<br/>
Glitching different enemies will lead to different results! Spawning black holes, turning your magic blasts into flying swords, making you run like a 50s cartoon, creating a ghost platform, spawning healing items, giving you a harpoon gun, you name it!<br/>
<br/>
Features<br/>
<br/>
-Glitch your way through 15 varied levels and over 12 secret bonus levels, including a magical forest, a busy tavern, a mesmerizing crystal cavern, a medieval battlefield, a haunted temple, deep space, and even a giant beehive!<br/>
<br/>
-Over 30 different glitches to experiment with.<br/>
<br/>
-Face off against 18 bosses, including a 7-foot princess wielding a minigun!<br/>
<br/>
-A killer soundtrack meticulously composed to fit the varied tones and locations of The Glitch Fairy’s story and scenery.<br/>
<br/>
-Hand-drawn cutscenes between every level!<br/>
<br/>
-Fast, speedrun-friendly gameplay! The Glitch Beam is the perfect accessory if you want to breeze through a level multiple times to get that Best Time.<br/>
<br/>
-A compendium to fill with over 100 entries, each with its own illustration and lore!<br/>
<br/>
-Collectables galore! Mysterious amethysts, Power Ups, rare currency, equippable artifacts, and, most importantly, dolls who can follow you on your quest!<br/>
<br/>
-Charming characters and a rich lore. If you dig deep enough, you might find something unexpected.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meeple Jump</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2344580/Meeple_Jump/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Chill in some lava in the casual <i>Meeple Jump!</i> platformer! Make your way from level to level, collecting stuff, and having a good time. Just... don't mind the Meeple's blank stare<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2344580/extras/Meeple.png?t=1702518781"><h2 class="bb_tag">PART ONE CONTAINS</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>The I-MEEPLE, a guidance module designed to give you useful (and sometimes really useless) information, exactly when you need it!</strong> (please note, I-MEEPLE is prone to occasionally giving you information when you do not need it)</li><li><strong>Cool and interesting game mechanics in each world, all of them really fun! </strong>(please note, "cool", "interesting", and "fun" are subjective terms and levels of such cannot be stated objectively)</li><li><strong>A number of worlds that is greater than 1.</strong> (please note, "numbers" are objective and levels of such can be stated objectively)</li><li><strong>Lava! Lava is super cool and you definitely won't fall in it a lot and also there are other things that kill you too but don't worry you won't die a singular time in my game!!!!! </strong>(please note, that statement is objectively false)</li><li><strong>The Main Meeple, You! We at BettaBowlGames went through a ton of playtesting of Meeple Jump, and results were always more positive when the playtester could play the game!</strong> (please note, "positive" is a subjective statement, yet somehow we know that this is objectively true)</li><li><strong>A storyline... somehow. Yes, somehow we got a storyline that made at least 1 sense into the meeple game! The quality of which, we are unsure.</strong> (please note, here at "BettaBowlGames" we for some reason put effort into the plot of Meeple Jump, why? Don't ask us, we probably don't know... I think.)</li></ul><br/>Oh huh, you're still here. This either means that you actually care what I have to say, or you for some reason stuck around, even though you had no intention of Wishlisting. Well I'll go ahead and blindly assume the former!<br/><br/>Anyhoodle, wishlist Meeple Jump or Else!<br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2344580/Meeple_Jump/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2344580/Meeple_Jump/</a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay Still 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2537770/Stay_Still_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/steam_wishlist_616x114_2__1_.gif?t=1702496190"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/SS2_LOGO.gif?t=1702496190"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/ShortDesc.png?t=1702496190"><br/>Hung, an adventurous risk-taker with an insatiable hunger for extraordinary experiences, seeks out a cheap and creepy house for a thrilling one-day rental. Little does he know that the house has a dark history, with a young girl's murder nearby. Ignoring the warnings, Hung decides to stay, and soon finds himself in the midst of a terrifying nightmare. He encounters the ghost of the murdered girl, setting off a series of haunting trials and challenges. Trapped and hunted in the haunted house, Hung must solve puzzles and face unimaginable horrors in a desperate attempt to escape. The chilling ghost story unravels as Hung's life hangs in the balance, leaving him forever scarred by the terrifying ordeal.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/Cheap1.gif?t=1702496190"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/Cheap2.gif?t=1702496190"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/Cheap3.gif?t=1702496190"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/Gamepl.png?t=1702496190"><br/>Prepare yourself for a bone-chilling adventure in "Stay Still 2," the thrilling ghost story that will keep you on the edge of your seat! Hung, a risk-taking adventurer, seeks out the most extraordinary experiences. When he stumbles upon a cheap, creepy house with a dark history, he can't resist the temptation to stay for a night filled with spine-tingling thrills.<br/><br/>Explore the eerie house and uncover its haunting past as you encounter mysterious figures and disturbing noises. Piece together clues and solve terrifying puzzles in a desperate attempt to escape the clutches of the vengeful ghost. But beware, the horrors within are beyond imagination!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/Gameplay1.gif?t=1702496190"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/Gameplay2.gif?t=1702496190"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/Gameplay3.gif?t=1702496190"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/Features.png?t=1702496190"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Immerse yourself in a chilling ghost story filled with suspense and mystery.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Navigate through the dark and eerie house to confront the ghost's tragic past.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Solve diabolical puzzles and riddles to find the key to your survival.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience heart-pounding moments and a sense of dread that will stay with you long after the game ends.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537770/extras/Features.gif?t=1702496190"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready or Not</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1144200/Ready_or_Not/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1144200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Los Sueños – The LSPD reports a massive upsurge in violent crime across the greater Los Sueños area. Special Weapons and Tactics (SWAT) teams have been dispatched to respond to various scenes involving high-risk hostage situations, active bomb threats, barricaded suspects, and other criminal activities. Citizens are being advised to practice caution when traveling the city or to stay at home. <br>
<br>
It has been noted that while Los Sueños is still seen as a city where riches can be found, for many more the finer things in life are becoming less and less obtainable. “The city is sprawling with cramped high-rise apartments and decaying affordable housing, which has been exploited by the criminal underground like a malevolent parasite,” states Chief Galo Álvarez. “In a city where people are just trying to survive, lawful action from the LSPD and the LSPD SWAT team remains an integral force preventing the stretched thin social fabric in this city from snapping under this chaotic strain.” <br>
<br>
In response to the burgeoning violent crime wave inundating Los Sueños, Chief Álvarez of the LSPD has enlisted the stalwart support of David ‘Judge’ Beaumont as the Commander of the LSPD SWAT team. Shortly following this announcement, the LSPD has also confirmed active recruitment for additional talent to join this specialized tactical police unit with the mission of bringing peace back to the city. <br>
<br>
“This assignment is not for the faint of heart,” comments Commander Beaumont, “Extremists, crooked politicians, countless weapons, human trafficking, and illicit drugs and pornography… the world of policing in Los Sueños is fraught with real and harsh realities, realities that the everyday person isn’t necessarily confronted with. These are realities that you will need to navigate with your team within the proper bounds of the law or face the consequences and make matters worse.” <br>
<br>
The Los Sueños Policed Department has officially posted new details on Commander “Judge” Beaumont’s updated assignment with the LSPD SWAT team: <br>
<br/>
New Expectations: Whether this is your first time in Los Sueños or not, the city has changed and so too have the tools and methods with which we conduct our work. The haunts you might have seen or heard about are re-imagined, and so have the angles with which we approach each call. Furthermore, we’ve received reports that identify at least 4 new high-risk police districts which we suspect may require future tactical intervention, plus at least 4 existing high-risk districts that underwent massive upheavals. <br/>
<br/>
Take Command: The role of the Commander of the LSPD SWAT is to compose their team from a large roster with unique talents, give tactical orders, meticulously plan, and carry out missions. Commanders are obligated to conduct each mission with integrity and look after their team’s mental and physical health. Officers with unaddressed deteriorating mental status may be unable to properly perform their duties or even feel compelled to quit the force. Incapacitated officers may be temporarily unavailable for missions, with the tragic prospect of death leading to a permanent loss. For SWAT Commanders in unusual circumstances based on individual choices they opt for, deadly mistakes may lead to their own permanent fatality. <br/>
<br/>
SWAT Team Quality Enhancement: Much anticipated improved SWAT training procedures, tactics, and experience in the LSPD has led to an overall increase in the quality and quantity of officers in our roster. Expanded tactical versatility allows our officers to take on any challenge with renewed confidence, blending coordination and independence seamlessly. There is also additional basic training now available to SWAT members to keep foundational knowledge and muscle memory in top shape. <br/>
<br/>
Equipment and customization: We have access to the best weapons and equipment that the LSPD can offer to fulfill our exceptionally dangerous role, including many new acquisitions. However, customization isn’t limited to the equipment we use. Through close-knit comradery while performing remarkable actions alongside the team, you’ll earn the clothes you wear, the patches on your sleeves, the artwork that may adorn your skin, and potentially even the timepiece on your wrist. Lastly, we have overhauled our headquarters' training facilities to better test our loadouts before heading out on call.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danger Drone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684290/Danger_Drone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Return the world to humanity by destroying the evil aliens. Show all your piloting skills, because your ship can be destroyed quickly, and the number of opponents will always increase with each level.<br>
<br>
Danger Drone is a horizontal scrolling shooter with a side view. The action of the flying games takes place in the distant future. The drone pilot will need to skillfully fly in space, overcoming gravity and resist the crowds of UFOs suddenly attacking Neon cities. Go through each of the proposed levels carefully fighting off crowds of enemies and only when you reach the end you will have the opportunity to destroy the bosses.<br>
<br>
Features: <br>
-Scroll-shooter with side view<br>
-Pixel graphics <br>
-Harmonious soundtrack <br/>
- Bosses						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Brave Little Cloud</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2635070/The_Brave_Little_Cloud/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2635070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the game <strong>"The Brave Little Cloud"</strong>, you will become the main character - a little cloud that fights against evil to protect its world. You will have to go through many levels, fighting various enemies and overcoming obstacles. Your task is to use your abilities to destroy all enemies and reach the final boss. But be careful, enemies will become stronger and smarter at each new level. The game "The Brave Little Cloud" is an exciting adventure that will give you unforgettable emotions and help develop logical thinking and reaction. Can you defeat evil and save your world? Try to play and find out!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692640/Room/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Room is a psychological horror game. </strong><br/><br/><strong>THE SUBJECT OF THE GAME</strong><br/><br/>In Room players find themselves trapped in an unnerving and ever-shifting nightmare where escaping one room only leads to the discovery of another, each more sinister than the last. Confronted by an ever-evolving environment, players must navigate through a series of intricately designed rooms, each harboring its own unique set of challenges and horrors.<br/><br/><strong>What to do in Room</strong><br/><br/>There are a lot of rooms and you try to escape. If you escape one room, another one comes. Find keys and other objects and escape.<br/><br/><strong>WARNING: This Game Contains Intense Horror Elements</strong><br/><br/>Enter at your own risk! This game is not for the faint of heart. Prepare to be immersed in a world of spine-chilling terror, where every step could be your last.<br/><br/>Be warned, the darkness holds unspeakable horrors that will test your courage and resilience. Brace yourself for a nerve-wracking experience that will keep you on the edge of your seat. Sudden jolts, eerie sounds, and unsettling visuals will push your senses to the limit.<br/><br/>Dare to explore, but beware! The atmosphere grows increasingly tense, enveloping you in a suffocating dread. Your every decision carries weight, and the consequences of your actions may haunt you.<br/><br/>Only the bravest souls will triumph in this twisted realm. Do you have what it takes to survive? Proceed with caution, for this game will plunge you into a realm of fear that lingers long after you've put down the keyboard and mouse.<br/><br/>Remember, this game is designed to invoke discomfort and fear. If you have a history of anxiety, heart conditions, or are sensitive to disturbing content, we strongly advise against playing.<br/><br/>You have been warned.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garden of Seif: Curse of Gravehollow Peaks</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2079430/Garden_of_Seif_Curse_of_Gravehollow_Peaks/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2079430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The Story</strong><br/>You're lost in the mysterious mountain range known as Gravehollow Peaks, notorious known as the place that no traveler has ever returned from and is cursed with eternal snow. <br/><br/>To make matters worse, you're trapped with none other than your untrustworthy rival assassin, Seth, also known as The Deathstalker. <br/><br/>Deep within the mountain's caves, a beast lurks, and will do everything to make sure you and Seth die just as the other adventurers did. Can you change this disastrous fate and convince this creature not to kill you?<br/><br/>❆Multiple endings<br/>❆10,000+ words<br/>❆Female protagonist<br/>❆1 dashing love interest<br/>❆1 mischievous but lovable fairy-godmother<br/>❆SFX and cinematic cut scenes<br/><br/><br/>Play through this adventure and help them get out of Gravehollow Peaks! The choice is entirely yours.<br/><br/><i>Garden of Seif: Curse of Gravehollow Peaks</i> is an alternate side story based on the upcoming game <i>Garden of Seif: Chronicles of an Assassin. </i><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1926650/Garden_of_Seif_Chronicles_of_an_Assassin/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1926650/Garden_of_Seif_Chronicles_of_an_Assassin/</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Train Models - JR East Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686770/Japan_Train_Models__JR_East_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Japan Train Models, the game where you can enjoy trains in its entirety, is now available with trains of JR West!<br>
<br>
There are three modes to play: Pazzle mode, Layout mode, and Encyclopedia mode!<br>
You can enjoy the fascination of trains as much as you want.<br>
<br>
Puzzle Mode<br>
This is a game mode in which players create pazzle by attaching train parts at puzzle intervals.<br>
All vehicles appearing in the game are officially licensed!<br/>
You can assemble these finely detailed vehicles as many times as you like.<br/>
<br/>
And the vehicles are not the only pazzle you can build.<br/>
At the end of each stage, you can create a diorama of the scenery where the cars run.<br/>
<br/>
Layout Mode<br/>
The layout base featured in this work is the new layout from the second edition of "Japan Train Models", the new layout base included in this work is the new layout from the second version!<br/>
Let's create a new cityscape different from the first version.<br/>
<br/>
You can place buildings and other structures on the layout to create your one and only original layout!<br/>
You can also take cool pictures by running the cars you built in the Pazzle mode!<br/>
By selecting morning, evening, or night time, you can enjoy the changes in scenery depending on the time of day.<br/>
There are also a variety of shooting modes, such as scenery from a train window or from the viewpoint of a cameraman placed on the layout!<br/>
In addition, you can move the placed cameraman. Take the best shot from your favorite place and angle!<br/>
<br/>
Encyclopedia Mode<br/>
You can check detailed data and 3D models of the vehicles!<br/>
Enjoy your favorite cars by enlarging and rotating them.<br/>
You can switch the internal camera and move to the carriages to feel as if you are on the train.<br/>
You can also see the detailed descriptions of the cars supervised by JR East.<br/>
<br/>
Equipped with a train car.<br/>
Japan Train Models - JR West Edition features the following 3 cars.<br/>
225-100 Series<br/>
117 Series<br/>
103 Series<br/>
<br/>
Here is your own railway space to create!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booze Masters: Freezing Moonshine</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1057600/Booze_Masters_Freezing_Moonshine/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1057600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play as Quella, a budding influencer who aims to break free from a vile boss. Booze Masters: Freezing Moonshine is an exploratory adventure mixed with an economic game, a hefty dose of abstract humor, and a copious amount of high-proof spirits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1057600/extras/paski_quella.png?t=1702478724"><br/><br/>Under the guidance of a brilliant moonshiner, you'll learn to craft alcoholic beverages that would dazzle even the wildest connoisseurs - including the world's coldest vodka. Throughout the adventure on the hill, you'll plant dozens of fantastical crops, gather tons of plants, and produce liters of substances that will help you conquer the cold.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1057600/extras/paski_JERRY.png?t=1702478724"><br/><br/>Head to the motel surrounded by crackling frost, where you'll encounter eccentric residents. To achieve your goals, you'll need to join forces and endure the twists of fate. Dozens of challenges await you, paving the way for a spectacular report.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1057600/extras/paski_ZERO_KAROTEN.png?t=1702478724"><br/><br/>Capture your stay at the resort and gather materials for social media. Unearth the bizarre inventions of a quirky scientist and confront the malicious nature. Blend alchemy with technology and distill spirits as if there's no tomorrow. Only this way can you outwit the game of an unfairly rigged fate.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1057600/extras/paski_DOCTOR_PROFESSOR.png?t=1702478724"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hell Well</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2628010/Hell_Well/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2628010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Survive as a dark sorcerer and collect fallen spirits to turn them into your own unholy defense against corrupt angels!</h2><br/><br/>Take the role of a dark sorcerer as you defend yourself against waves of angels seeking to destroy you! Presented in retro 4-tone style, Hell Well is a top-down tower defense survival game where your downfall is inevitable, but the challenge is to survive and take down as many foes as possible before your ultimate demise.<br/><br/>Collect fallen spirits and use them to set up demonic totem-like defenses to fend off holy attackers, then upgrade abilities and increase the level of your minions to continue growing your forces across procedurally generated ruins and graveyards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2628010/extras/HellWell_gif_05.gif?t=1702475429"><br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Survive waves of enemies in a mix of top-down action and tower defense!<br/></li><li>Collect fallen spirits and revive them as demonic defensive weaponry.<br/></li><li>Evade enemies and use spells to fend them off or lure them into traps!<br/></li><li>Collect new items in the dungeon hub and earn new color palettes.<br/></li><li>Upgrade your magic spells or level up your turrets with quick-thinking strategy!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2628010/extras/HellWell_gif_03.gif?t=1702475429"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Scroll</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713880/Magic_Scroll/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Magic Scroll is an addictive game based on physics and destruction. You have to destroy various structures with a pickaxe! In the game you will find many exciting and exciting levels of varying difficulty.<br>
Control your pickaxe and destroy everyone on your way! There are many unique buildings waiting for you in the game, so destroy them all!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Multi-level<br>
- Complete destruction of objects<br>
- Physics<br/>
- Colorful graphics						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realms of Flow</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2397600/Realms_of_Flow/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2397600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>'Realms of Flow'</strong> is all about calming down and drifting away into deep and soothing states of mind. It utilizes a combination of <strong><i>high-framerate stereoscopic 180°-video</i></strong> and interactive elements for breathing, mindful listening, playfulness, humming, and frequency entrainment.<br/><br/>You can choose from a growing number of experiences, each offering a different scenery, general atmosphere and meditative narration. <br/>In the <strong>Session Timing</strong> options you can set the start time and duration for the different guide features: <strong>Voice-over, Breathing Guide, Spatial Sounds, Humming Guide, Frequency Entrainment, and Element of Play</strong>.<br/>Each feature has various settings that you can adjust according to your preferences. For example, the breathing tempo, which affects a customizable visual focus object, can be a fixed user-defined tempo or controlled using your hand or belly movement. <br/><br/>The focus of this application is less on giving a step-by-step voice guidance, but on creating small cinematic journeys with a poetic and meditative touch. <br/><br/>Realms of Flow strives to offer unique immersive audio-visual atmospheres to provide thoughtful inspiration, evoke emotions, and create interesting, soothing, and meaningful states of mind that will hopefully enrich your palette of being. - <strong>Immerse yourself in the infinite Realms of Flow!</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Swords Firelink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2602350/Dark_Swords_Firelink/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2602350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an epic journey to save your village and the world of Iggrand.<br>
<br>
In the land of Iggrand, humans have ruled since their arrival on Cretea. But after encountering the primordial fire, wars ravaged the continent and brought mankind to the brink of extinction.<br>
<br>
From this time, we speak of the dark swords, the most powerful weapons of the Lordhem kingdom. With these swords, Lordhem nearly conquered the entire continent. But the united kingdoms rebelled, and Lordhem lost its power.<br>
<br>
Firelink is the heiress of a dark sword left by her grandfather Fianor. She had never wielded the sword until her village, Osthem, was attacked by a host of creatures commanded by a huge demon.<br>
<br/>
Seeking revenge and to protect Osthem from any future threats, Firelink wields the dark sword and embarks on an epic journey. Along the way, she begins to understand the sword's power and its influence on her, acquires new abilities, and faces huge monsters. She also plays an important role in the fate of Iggrand and the events that are about to unfold.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossing Frontier: Fate Foretold</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2580390/Crossing_Frontier_Fate_Foretold/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"> I. Game Introduction </h2>The game is a <u><strong>2.5D</strong></u> action game, focusing on the multiplayer online battle with exciting combat experience. This game is easy to control, featuring the talent upgrading system and free air combat combos, so that the gameplay relies on the player's own creativity, instead of the character limitations.<br/><br/>Players can choose various modes, including 1v1 or 3v3 battles against players or AI, <u><strong>story mode</strong></u> which players can enjoy the narration, and <u><strong>stage mode</strong></u> that players can <u><strong>play with friends</strong></u> and more.<h2 class="bb_tag"> II. Character Selection </h2>We offer a variety of characters for players to choose, including righteous swordswoman, cheerful and adorable witch, cold-blooded and harsh drillmaster, knight clad in armor and more. Also, new characters are added each season!<br/><br/><strong><i>「Any naughty spirit here?」——Isuna </i></strong><br/>Isuna is a journeying witch on a path of self-cultivation. Everywhere she goes, she brings her energy and optimism. Isnua extends a helping hand to those she meets along the way, taking care of troubling Y?kai and also lifting the people’s spirits with a smile.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/03-FINAL-2.png?t=1702466891"><br/>Disruptive mid-range support. Can heal and buff allies, while also detonating multiple talismans to deal massive damage.<br/>Can strengthen her team through multiple buffs, has simple, but varied methods of attack.<br/><br/><br/><strong><i> Soliders, fall in! Fight till your death by my side!」——Martin </i></strong><br/>A strict adherent to his orders and to military discipline, Martin “Blood Mail” Thard is a Colonel of the Aseriman Special Forces. An instructor in tactics and weaponry, he excels at training Aseriman warriors. Martin is a charismatic commander who leads by example and can always be found in the vanguard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/04-FINAL-2.png?t=1702466891"><br/>Melee fighter with powerful close-up and mid-ranged abilities.<br/>Highly effective in mid-to-close range combat, can launch relentless assaults with his regenerative abilities.<br/><br/><br/><i><strong>「Let’s make a scene!」——Eliseka</strong></i><br/>	Eliseka is Lieutenant General of the Aseriman Special Forces, known as “Cyan Flame” . Eliseka’s behavior is always like the big brother to everyone, straightforward and bold, treating her  subordinates like her friend, doesn’t have the authority a Lieutenant General supposed to have. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/11-FINAL-2.png?t=1702466891"><br/>A swordsman that relies on speed, can use differing charge times on abilities to deal with different scenarios. Her battlefield effect when awakened can accelerate the pace of battle.<br/>Possesses powerful single attacks and plenty of combo potential, abilities can be charged for varying lengths to execute different combos.<h2 class="bb_tag"> III. Game Modes </h2><strong>1. Story Mode</strong><br/>Story Mode contains the stories of every in-game character, revealing the background of different nations. Players will go through the main storyline, playing as one of the protagonists, Aros, to unlock the main story by clearing the stages. They will travel around the six regions of the world, fight various opponents, uncover the massive conspiracies hidden within Aserima, and earn exclusive items and titles after completing the story mode.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/PV自剪版.mp4_20230913_145216.870.png?t=1702466891"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/Map.png?t=1702466891"><br/><br/><strong>2. Stage Mode</strong><br/>If players want to try something different from the solo play of the Story Mode, they can choose Stage Mode. In this mode, players can form teams of 1 to 5 players and re-experience the various stages of the Story Mode from a multiplayer team's point of view. The system of this mode provides players with significant freedom to choose characters, challenging their limits to clear stages faster, and offer rewards for each completion.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/ROOM.jpg?t=1702466891"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/PV自剪版.mp4_20230904_152805.617.png?t=1702466891"><br/><br/><strong> 3. Brawling Mode</strong><br/>Players can engage in challenges with friends or online players in Brawling Mode. This mode supports 1v1 to 5v5 multiplayer brawls, featuring different mechanisms within different maps, such as airdrops with random effects, or environmental designs including storms, volcanic eruptions, holy light impacts and more.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/03.png?t=1702466891"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/PV自剪版.mp4_20230904152703.465.png?t=1702466891"><h2 class="bb_tag">4. Talents</h2>	Talents can enhance or change character’s skills Significantly. Players can level up their characters by progressing time and dealing damage to enemies, characters unlock one talent from three each level. Players can adjust the playstyle accordingly!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/天賦GIF__1_.gif?t=1702466891"><h2 class="bb_tag"> V. Avatar System</h2>This game features a wide variety of accessories that players can purchase from the store or obtain in limited events. Players can freely apply these accessories to their characters, creating unique and individualized characters. Please note that the use of accessories does not impact the fairness of the game.<br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2580390/extras/202309131454__1_.gif?t=1702466891"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sudoku XP</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2665590/Sudoku_XP/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2665590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a  sudoku game in different board sizes and difficulty.  It also has an Editor mode that allows the user to create their own custom puzzles, custom layouts, and custom initial patterns, all of whom can then be played in Game mode.  Furthermore, the customized items can also be shared, though it involves actually copying files from the user directory -- there is a button on the specific board mode so you can open that folder in explorer if you'd like to do this.<br>
<br>
The trailer shows off most of these features, including most of the Editor-related ones.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zooplop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2694140/Zooplop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694140/extras/Zooplop_Steam_Store_GIF_616.gif?t=1702461257"><br/><br/><strong>Zooplop</strong> is a physics-based puzzle game where you drop animals from a mechanical claw. When two animals of the same kind touch they merge into bigger ones! 🐭+🐭=🐥<br/><br/>Plan your moves carefully and avoid dropping too many animals at once, or you might run out of space. The game goes on forever or until all animals fill up the screen. Zooplop is easy to play but hard to master. How big can you go? Can you reach the whale? Can you merge the whale?! 🐋✨<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2694140/extras/Zooplop_Steam_Store_Line_616.png?t=1702461257"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Cute animals!<br/></li><li> Simple &amp; intuitive gameplay<br/></li><li> Colorful &amp; charming graphics<br/></li><li> Steam achievements &amp; leaderboards<br/></li><li> Music by HelloComics</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goblin Keep</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1079300/Goblin_Keep/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1079300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1079300/extras/EA-1-view.gif?t=1702461252"><br/>Explore a world enhanced by extreme view distance and lush visuals created with Unreal engine and new voxel technology.<h2 class="bb_tag">Destroy</h2>Play with full destruction physics using a custom system created with multiplayer in mind.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1079300/extras/EA-5-Destruction.gif?t=1702461252"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fight</h2>Loot weapons, cast spells, and fight animals and characters to survive.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1079300/extras/EA-2-Combat.gif?t=1702461252"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build</h2>Quickly plan with building tools, then recruit villagers to have them build.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1079300/extras/EA-3-Build.gif?t=1702461252"><h2 class="bb_tag">Attack and Defend</h2>Use siege weapons and magic to attack a friend's town or defend your own.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1079300/extras/EA-4-Siege.gif?t=1702461252"><h2 class="bb_tag">Craft and Trade</h2>Craft everything needed to start a town, then trade with your trader to buy crops to harvest. A Hunger system provides the need to eat as to not lose Max HP, but the option overeat to gain Max HP.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1079300/extras/EA-6-food.png?t=1702461252"><h2 class="bb_tag">Relax</h2>Get lost in a soundtrack of over two hours of sublime retro-inspired adventurous music, including 90 minutes by professional composer Claudia Correia.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1079300/extras/EA-7-music.png?t=1702461252"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Very Hard Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2708940/Very_Hard_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to VERY HARD GAME!!!<br/><br/>You play as this little blob called Blobby!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708940/extras/blobby.gif?t=1702459797"><br/>Blobby must make it through GameMastrs 100 rooms to win!!!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> You can change Blobby's Color! </li><li> Hard Mode! </li><li> Blind Mode! </li><li> You can Walk! </li><li> You can Die! </li><li> You might be able to Win!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708940/extras/ezgif-2-3df36334da.gif?t=1702459797"><h2 class="bb_tag">Don't Touch Walls!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708940/extras/ezgif-5-d30e0f73bb.gif?t=1702459797"><br/><br/>That's pretty much it! Oh and Watch out for these little guys!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2708940/extras/ff948ecc-451e-45f8-b91a-535e1c16ec61.png?t=1702459797"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mirage: Beyond The Screen</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706140/Mirage_Beyond_The_Screen/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706140/extras/pic1f.gif?t=1702455050"><br/>Embark on a spine-chilling journey into the heart of an animated nightmare with Mirage: Beyond the Screen powered by Unreal Engine 5. In this unique adventure horror-ish game set in a cartoon world, you'll unravel the mysteries of a haunted reality where the line between reality and computer game blurs.<br/><br/>Dive headfirst into an ethereal realm where dreadful illusions come to life, and otherworldly presences lurk around every corner. Navigate through cryptic shadows and face spectral enigmas as you strive to unveil the dark secrets hidden in this cartoon universe.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706140/extras/pic2f.gif?t=1702455050"><br/>Encounter nightmarish entities with ghastly apparitions and navigate a mystic puzzles fraught with unseen terrors. As you traverse cursed perceptions and explore obscure realms, brace yourself for a surreal nightfall where demonic mirages and sinister reflections challenge your sanity.<br/><br/>Beyond the veil of this animated world lies an enigma of eldritch aberrations and a vortex of fear that pulls you deeper into the adventure. Experience ghostly intrusions and shattered illusions as you embark on an astral descent into the unknown, where eerie echoes and lurking shadows heighten the suspense.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706140/extras/pic3f.gif?t=1702455050"><br/>Experience  a captivating blend of adventure and horror, immersing players in a captivating cartoon nightmare that defies the boundaries of traditional gaming. Are you ready to face the animated horrors that await, or will you become just another character lost in the twisted storyline? Enter the cartoon world of nightmares, and let the journey begin.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706140/extras/Picture_1.png?t=1702455050"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token Town</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688100/Token_Town/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Token Town is an idle like game where you use computers to mine crypto currency,<br>
<br>
Explore the map to find hidden shiny objects that increase your computer's speed<br>
<br>
Make 5 Million credits to repay your debt and beat the game						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>九霄风云录 Legends Of The Divine Land</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2358100/_Legends_Of_The_Divine_Land/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I don't know why, but in recent years, the aura of the Kyushu continent has undergone tremendous changes, making it impossible for the cultivators to condense the aura into golden pills.<br/>Everyone can only store spiritual energy in a certain part of the body, so a very strange phenomenon occurs, the higher the level, the more bulging a certain part of the body is. . .<br/>The female immortal cultivators felt that this was a conspiracy by the male immortal cultivators, so they formed an alliance to find out, and the story began like this. . .<br/><br/>This is a deck-building Roguelike game, the operation is relatively simple, just select a level to break through, and then choose the right teammates to join the team.<br/>The key to clearing the level is to reasonably match the skill fetters of your teammates to form a powerful attack or recovery style.<br/><br/>Another thing to note is that the more players in the team, the better. Sometimes 20 is enough, so don't be greedy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_双子门.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_叶绿谷.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_妖修.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_幺鸡派.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_小青小白.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_武魂.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_维生素.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_兽灵.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_食灵.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_神兽.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_杀马特联盟.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_气象门.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_七仙门.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_欧派联盟.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_萌兽.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_炼丹师.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_君子门.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_剑雨阁.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_合欢宗.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_二次元宗.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_魑魅魍魉魈魁.JPG?t=1702517535"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2358100/extras/游戏门派人物介绍_藏剑山庄.JPG?t=1702517535"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Two Bedroom Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2656640/Our_Two_Bedroom_Story/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2656640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a Steam version of a hit visual novel game released on the mobile reader app Love 365: Find Your Story by Voltage Inc. It is a collection of romantic, richly illustrated interactive stories with the following premise:<br/><br/>In the romantic comedy Our Two Bedroom Story, the heroine suddenly finds herself living with a handsome bachelor who she happens to work with! There, she discovers sides of him nobody else sees in the office, and the two grow closer over the course of their secret cohabitation.<br/> <br/>An opening movie and adventure feature have been added to the Steam release, so even players that have previously read the app version will discover more things to enjoy.<br/><br/><strong>The Story:</strong><br/>You work for a publishing house and decide to start living on your own.<br/>But a coworker’s in your new home?!<br/>“This is my house… but you could live with me.”<br/>When your new roommate hands you the key, your secret life together begins…<br/><br/><strong>Characters:</strong><br/>Minato Okouchi   "Bossy"<br/>Kaoru Kirishima   "Cool"<br/>Shusei Hayakawa "The Nice Guy"<br/>Chiaki Yuasa       "Crafty"<br/>Akiyoshi Zaizen   "The Growler"<br/><br/><strong>Contents</strong><br/>Includes "Main Stories" in the App "Love 365: Find Your Story".<br/>Collection of Main Stories spanning the series up until the Proposal Epilogue for Minato Okouchi, Kaoru Kirishima, Shusei Hayakawa, Chiaki Yuasa, and Akiyoshi Zaizen.<br/><br/><strong>Notices:</strong><br/>"the Proposal: His PoV" is only available in Japanese.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egyptian Ratslap - Card Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2553440/Egyptian_Ratslap__Card_Game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2553440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							As you enter the game, you will be welcomed with the smooth jazz music and the main menu screen. From there you can configure settings, look at a detailed instructions on the rules of the card game, or go right ahead and play the game! The aim of the game is to make the player use short term memorization skills to beat 3 bots who are all trying to have the most cards to win the game. And don't forget that anyone in the game can slap back in once they have lost all of their cards so make sure you keep track of what cards have been placed or you might be in trouble. Once a player has reached 52 cards, they have won Egyptian Ratslap!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knight's Path: The Tournament</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653240/Knights_Path_The_Tournament/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i>Knight's Path: The Tournament</i></strong> is a short (2-3 hour long) medieval RPG featuring challenging combat, an immersive progression system, and a nice little story. It serves both as an announcement and a teaser for the forthcoming open-world RPG <strong><i>Knight's Path</i></strong>, which is currently in active development.<br/><br/>You begin your journey with nothing. Once you acquire a weapon and learn how to fight, you can enter the tournament, where you test your might and earn rewards. These rewards can be used to purchase new armors and weapons, enhancing your capabilities for future battles. The tournament consists of four rounds and pits you against eleven unique NPCs, each with their own distinct fighting style, including the reigning, undefeated champion of the arena.<br/>Are you ready to face this challenge?<br/>Or, if you need a moment to relax, you can partake in various activities, like chilling by the fireplace or forming a heartwarming bond with a local cat.<br/><br/>Why are we releasing it for free on Steam? Here are our honest reasons:<br/><br/>We aim to make our game as immersive and enjoyable as possible, and for that, we need your help and feedback! Is there anything you'd change or add to enhance your gaming experience? What features do you love, and what would you like to see improved? Tell us, and help us shape the game!<br/><br/>We're also looking for a publisher, one that shares our vision and excitement for "Knight's Path" and can help the game reach its full potential.<br/><br/>We hope you find joy and excitement in this little adventure!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
