<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924780/Arzette_The_Jewel_of_Faramore/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/intro_gif.gif?t=1707886813"><br/><br/>After ten years of peace...the evil Daimur has returned! Princess Arzette is the Kingdom of Faramore’s only hope to restore harmony to the land!<br/><br/>In this brand new interactive action adventure game, you control the resourceful princess Arzette. Travel through multiple breathtaking locations filled with scum, villainy and secrets, speak with the locals to uncover mysteries and objectives, and take on the evil Daimur as <strong>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</strong> brings you the best interactive gaming experience since the invention of the CD-ROM!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/mortar_gif.gif?t=1707886813"><br/><br/><strong>Featuring:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hand painted backgrounds and incredible sprite art.<br/></li><li>Fully voice-acted cartoon cinematics with a colorful cast of characters.<br/></li><li>A sprawling world with diverse locations and many secrets.<br/></li><li>Acquire powerful items and abilities by exploring and helping those in need.<br/></li><li>Veteran dev team including artist Rob Dunlavey, Digital Foundry's John Linneman and Audi Sorlie, voice talent Jeffrey Rath and Bonnie Jean Wilbur, and award winning composer Jake "Button Masher" Silverman.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwatch® 2 - Ultimate Battle Pass Bundle: Season 9</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707800/Overwatch_2__Ultimate_Battle_Pass_Bundle_Season_9/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Explore the cosmic unknown!<br>
<br>
Includes:<br>
- Premium Battle Pass + 20 Tiers<br/>
- Beholder Sigma and Harbinger Lifeweaver Legendary Skins<br/>
- 2,000 Overwatch Coins<br/>
<br/>
With your Overwatch Coins, you can purchase in-game cosmetic items to customize your heroes. Owners of the Premium Battle Pass can also use Overwatch Coins to unlock Tiers and instantly access Legendary and Mythic content. Tier skips will not apply to any battle pass level beyond level 80 and will not unlock prestige tiers. Any excess tier skips you purchase past level 80 are banked and will be automatically redeemed at launch of the following season.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islands of Insight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2071500/Islands_of_Insight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Islands of Insight: a sublime shared-world puzzle game set in a fantasy realm of ancient wonders and natural beauty. Brimming with mysterious puzzles to solve, secrets to uncover, and vibrant landscapes to explore, this peaceful world of floating islands is the perfect place to unwind. Embark on a puzzle adventure of your choice, all at your own pace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_1-Title-Journey_EN.png?t=1707847143">‎‎‏‏‎<br/>Play as a Seeker on a peaceful journey rich in exploration and puzzle-solving. Embark on the Path of Discovery and let your curiosity guide you through a breathtaking open world where the answer is always in sight.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Journey_HD.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_2-Title-Puzzles_EN.png?t=1707847143"><br/>Seek out and solve an unparalleled collection of over 10,000 puzzles divided across 24 puzzle types. Every corner of the world holds a new eureka moment for you to discover. From enigmas of perspective to logic problems, environmental challenges and more, the puzzles you’ll encounter vary in difficulty and have been crafted by some of the best minds in puzzle design to create an engaging experience for both newcomers and seasoned puzzle fans.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Puzzles_HD.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_3-Title-Exploration_EN.png?t=1707847143"><br/>Freely explore the main island’s expansive open world where most of the puzzles and secrets are found. Wander the vibrant landscapes and architecture of its 5 distinct biomes or spread your wings to glide above them. Navigate the environment’s verticality and take your game to new heights. Unlock puzzle types and new areas in the campaign by completing 20+ Enclaves housing curated puzzle challenges. Go where you want. Solve what you want. The only path here is the one you make.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/3.IOI_Steam_Gif_Exploration___Discovery_2.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_5-Title-Experience_EN.png?t=1707847143"><br/>Customize your character. Increase your puzzle masteries to level them up while earning sparks to unlock new abilities. Complete daily quests. Seamlessly interact with other players in our shared world to gain or offer a bit of guidance, or choose to figure things out entirely on your own. With puzzles that refresh over time, a new discovery awaits with every visit to the islands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/4.IOI_Steam_Gif_An_Evergreen_Experience_2.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/>Age restrictions may apply to access this game.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2436570/DRAGON_QUEST_BUILDERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Build.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>The first title in the BUILDERS series, DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS, is bringing its handy crafting features to Steam!<br/>Gather, craft and build to defeat defeat the evil Dragonlord and restore Alefgard to it's former glory!<br/>In a world made out of blocks, everything that you see can be materials used to create! Farm ingredients, craft various items and build your base to unite the people roaming the ruins. From buildings to entire towns, you have the freedom to make your village your very own.<h2 class="bb_tag">■ Story</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Lightning.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>BUILDERS is set in the realm of Alefgard, the setting for the first ever DRAGON QUEST game.<br/>The world of Alefgard has been plunged into darkness, its light stolen by the evil Dragonlord, and this story begins with the appearance of a young hero with a mysterious ability to build things... And so the stage is set for an epic tale in which the dark world of Alefgard is returned to life with the power of creation!<h2 class="bb_tag">■ The first DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS title, helpful crafting features include:</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_3.png?t=1707862917"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Place blocks remotely, or destroy blocks with ease, with just a single click of the mouse!<br/></li><li> Now Includes a helpful Undo feature, which allows you to put things back to how they were before!<br/></li><li> Now Featuring Big Bash, a useful feature introduced in DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS 2 that allows you to break all objects in a particular area in one go!<br/></li><li> Terra Incognita, BUILDERS’ free build stage, the stackable block height is doubled!<br/></li><li> Includes fun side content, like collecting figurines of NPCs and monsters, or gathering pixels and exchanging them for a variety of handy items!<br/></li><li> Use Build Cards to share buildings with other players and bring their buildings to life on your island!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">■ Includes all DLC from previous versions of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_4.png?t=1707862917"><br/>The Steam version of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS includes all of the DLC from past versions including the free build mode, Terra Incognita: Magic Carpet, Boss Monster Model Set, Astronomy Set and Pixel Ring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Stack.gif?t=1707862917"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lysfanga: The Time Shift Warrior</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161620/Lysfanga_The_Time_Shift_Warrior/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/LYS_LOGO_STEAM.png?t=1707912273"><br/>After half a millennium of peace, a new danger hangs over Antala. Its fate depends on you, Imë, <strong>Lysfanga</strong> of the New Kingdom, protector of the realm. The ancient cities, previously locked in time, are now free again, and an old evil has escaped, threatening the peace. <br/><br/>But you won’t be alone. Gifted with <strong>temporal powers</strong> from the Goddess of Time herself, something no other Lysfanga has had before, you have the ability to <strong>rewind time in combat</strong> to summon <strong>clones of your past-selves</strong> to help you. Master your power to become legion, and crush hordes of the escaped demons, known as the <strong>Raxes</strong>.<br/><br/>With your <strong>army of past-selves</strong>, progress through the ancient cities to extend your arsenal of weapons and learn new spells, preparing for the much greater threat ahead... <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/MUSTER_AN_ARMY_OF_YOURSELF_V2_EN.png?t=1707912273"><br/>Use Imë’s godlike powers to rewind time a few seconds in the past and summon clones of yourself – remnants – to create an army and overpower your enemies. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/Lysfanga_gif_steam_v4.gif?t=1707912273"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/PUSH_YOUR_LIMITS_V2_EN.png?t=1707912273"><br/>Challenge your skills and your wits to outdo yourself. Master and replay each arena to beat your high scores, and challenge yourself by changing the difficulty settings and adding combat modifiers to unlock new rewards.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/TAILOR_EACH_FIGHT_V2_EN.png?t=1707912273"><br/>Each arena can be approached in countless ways. Adapt your strategy and use all the tools at your disposal to emerge victorious. Success will only depend on your combination of remnants, spells and weapons.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/Lysfanga_gif_steam_Fight.gif?t=1707912273"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/INVESTIGATE_GIGANTIC_ANCIENT_CITIES_V2_EN.png?t=1707912273"><br/>The old time-locks are gone. The Raxes are now free to create chaos again. Explore the abandoned cities of the old continent previously locked in time and uncover the truth behind the resurgence of the Raxes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blacksmith. Song of two Kings.</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2531370/Blacksmith_Song_of_two_Kings/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Text_Welcome.png?t=1707832591"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Stuff1.png?t=1707832591"><br/>Take your hammer and get the coals burning! It's time for fire, metal and magic! In this game you will: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Forge, bend, cut and sharpen metal. Work with wood and bone.<br/></li><li>Weave chainmail. Use potions and spells.<br/></li><li>Take blacksmithing orders, creating unique weapons, armor and other curious items.<br/></li><li>Upgrade your dwelling and forge.<br/></li><li>Find useful items and new friends who are willing to help. <br/></li><li>Explore high fantasy world while diving into the story of the game.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Text_Gameplay.png?t=1707832591"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Final1_small_1.gif?t=1707832591"><br/>You'll have to work in the forge literally by hand - grab the hammer and hit the workpiece with it, sending out sparks. Strike after strike to flatten or bend metal. Cut wooden boards, sticks and branches by grasping the saw handle and moving it back and forth. Tie ropes, attach chains. Push the levers of the tongs. Bring flasks to the blanks, spill potions. Use magic books to enchant blades, shields and armor! There are over 100 unique and repeatable schemes, as well as a free-to-play forge mode.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Gallery_Overview_Small.gif?t=1707832591"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Text_SmithyManagement_eng.png?t=1707832591"><br/>Much of what you find during your wanderings will prove useful in the forge. The properties of items and character skills are revealed in combinations with each other. It's no secret, for example, that dwarves are more willing to work in the forge if you put a couple of kegs of beer in the house!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Managment_Small.gif?t=1707832591"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Text_Adventure.png?t=1707832591"><br/>You have a journey ahead of you, blacksmith. You have seen it in your dreams. And now they lead you. So embrace it. Embark on your adventure and face your destiny!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Adventure_Small.gif?t=1707832591"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultros</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2386310/Ultros/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You wake up stranded, after seemingly crashing your ship on The Sarcophagus — a giant, space-drifting, cosmic uterus holding an ancient demonic being known as ULTROS. Trapped in the eternal loop of a black hole, you will have to explore The Sarcophagus and meet its inhabitants to understand the part you play. <br/><br/>Are you the gruesome breaker of this cycle, or can you become a link from destruction to rebirth? <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat1.png?t=1707822049"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat1.gif?t=1707822049"><br/>ULTROS is set in a multifaceted realm - a vast alien landscape teeming with life. Grounded in science fiction, ULTROS comes wrapped in an eccentric art style and a mystical soundtrack from the visionary El Huervo, renowned for his work on Hotline Miami. ULTROS explores meta-themes of mental health, life, death, and karmic cycles through deep lore and environmental storytelling.       <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat2.png?t=1707822049"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat2.gif?t=1707822049"><br/>Experience brutal, intimate, close-quarter combat with cosmic lifeforms, driven by a sense of urgency – where precision is paramount and every cut of your blade counts. Yet this intense combat is juxtaposed with cultivating the greenery and tending to plant life in The Sarcophagus, providing precious moments of contemplation and peace. In turn, this grants deeper access to obscured paths.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat3.png?t=1707822049"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat3.gif?t=1707822049"><br/>The rich world of ULTROS holds many secrets for those curious enough — and fearless enough — to seek them out. A unique loop-based mechanic will allow you to start over at key moments in the story, providing opportunities to unfold such secrets, unlock different areas of the world and new abilities on a branching skill tree. Experiment with and master your own specific fighting style as you explore the world of ULTROS. Each loop brings you closer to the truth...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1707823167"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1707823167"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1707823167"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1707823167"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1707823167"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1707823167"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1707823167"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1707823167"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KONOSUBA - God's Blessing on this Wonderful World! Love For These Clothes Of Desire!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2349140/KONOSUBA__Gods_Blessing_on_this_Wonderful_World_Love_For_These_Clothes_Of_Desire/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/KonoSuba_KeyArt_Landscape_WithLogo.png?t=1707479148"><br/>Follow Kazuma and company, as they discover a mysterious "Black Slab" which curses them with desires contrary to their personality. The gang must now find and feed ingredients to the slab to create outfits which match and fulfil their new desires, and thus break their curse. Are you ready to meet Darkness as a ruthless dominatrix? How about Aqua as a prim and proper goddess? Or Megumin as the proud leader of the Lolita League?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/new-narrative-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/01._Black_slab!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Witness a new story in visual novel form! Featuring a full cast of fan-favourite characters from the series, this wild adventure gives you the chance to build up affection with up to seven heroines!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/get-to-work-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/02._Schedule_overview!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Fill out a weekly planner for each character based on their strengths to earn funds and resources which can be used for making outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/make-decisions-orange-1.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/decision_making_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Each of them has her own story endings and special dress-up CGs, so pick your words wisely and avoid invoking their wrath! Your choices matter! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/Manage-resources-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/04._Resources_schedule_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Collect resources to create outfits by completing tasks and quests. Manage your finances carefully to afford the materials you are missing, and prioritise gathering the outfit-specific ingredients you will need.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/play-dress-up-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/05._Make_more_clothes!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Once the mystical outfits have been made it’s time to play dress-up! Be ready for twists and turns as your favourite characters’ personalities change with each curse and desire-fulfilling piece of clothing.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/DANCE-smaller-no-boaarder.gif?t=1707479148"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WitchHand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420880/WitchHand/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-01.gif?t=1707898632"><br/><br/>In <strong>WitchHand</strong>, you use cards to build your empire of witches. Maximize the production of your villages and use your resources strategically to upgrade and expand. Focus on trade, alchemy research, or war in order to secure your coven's place amongst the Council of Fates, influencing the destiny of all. Work with your neighbors to secure a better future or crush them and use their bones to fuel your spells. When the witching hour comes each night, your witch's powers are at their strongest, while unseen forces work against you. You must expand and manage your coven to new heights if you are to withstand the coming darkness. No rest for the wicked.<h2 class="bb_tag">A CIVILIZATION OF WITCHES</h2>WitchHand folds the 4X strategy formula into card-based gameplay. You'll perform strategic actions like exploring, expanding, and exterminating through real-time card placement. Manage worker placement, village production, and research in order to advance the strength and reach of your coven.<h2 class="bb_tag">WIELD THE POWERS OF THE WITCHES OF THE REALMS</h2>Each witch has a unique selection of spells, buildings, and units that defines them. Empower your villages and production with the Celestial Witch. Overpower your enemies with the might of the Chaos Witch. Cook delicious, stat-boosting meals with the Chef Witch. Choose the witch that best suits your playstyle and have full control over your research paths to further personalize your playthrough.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/spellbook_and_wonder_crop.gif?t=1707898632"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE THE MYSTERIES OF THE NINTH</h2>The Council of Fates does not have faith in your expedition to the Ninth. Make alliances with rival factions or declare war and take their resources for your own. Manage your relationships through trade and gifts or with a well-placed fireball spell. Grow your coven to new heights and prove the Council wrong.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES:</h2>🧭 <strong>Explore</strong> the Ninth Realm to discover new sites for your villages, necessary reagents to fuel your spells, and clues to the mystery of the Ninth's sudden appearance.<br/><br/>🏘️ <strong>Expand</strong> your coven by building new villages, perfecting production, and trading with the local factions.<br/><br/>🔥 <strong>Exterminate</strong> the beasts of the void, whose relentless assaults on your coven jeopardize your mission.<br/><br/>🧙‍♀️ <strong>Choose</strong> the witch to lead your coven, each with unique spells and playstyles.<br/><br/>⌛ <strong>Impress</strong> the Council of Fates and benefit from their powerful boons.<br/><br/>🕊️ <strong>Peaceful Mode</strong> - The option to play without the constant threat of extinction.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/combat-crop.gif?t=1707898632"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-04.gif?t=1707898632"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1707785084"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal from ECHOS</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1707785084"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLCARD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201540/HELLCARD/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hellcard</strong> is a <strong>cooperative roguelike deckbuilder</strong> that can be played in both <strong>Singleplayer </strong>and <strong>Multiplayer </strong>modes. The game takes place in the paper dungeons known from Book of Demons, and its main mechanics revolve around deckbuilding and fast-paced tactical card battles. <br/><br/>If you are excited about <strong>HELLCARD</strong>, be sure to <strong>wishlist </strong>the game on Steam. Otherwise, consider wishlisting anyway - who knows, we might surprise you yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif5_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/>What makes <strong>HELLCARD</strong> unique and different from other deck-building games is that <strong>monster placement actually matters</strong> and can be used to your advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif4_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> supports <strong>co-op battles</strong> with up to three heroes facing the Archdemon's hordes. In <strong>singleplayer mode</strong>, you can descend into the dungeons solo or recruit computer-controlled companions. In <strong>multiplayer mode</strong>, your friends or strangers can help you battle the hordes of hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif1-2-3-600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/r2g_logo_fixed.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>Return 2 Games</strong> is a series of unique mid-core games inspired by the golden days of PC gaming. Each R2G title is a tribute to a single hit game from the '90s: a reimagining of a single universal story for a brand-new audience, using modern means and innovative, often vastly simplified gameplay mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/pillars.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> was first envisioned as a new game mode inside the Book of Demons universe, but we soon realized that its design is huge and that it should be executed as a stand-alone spin-off game. If you want to learn more about Return 2 Games or support us in the development of the series, visit the <strong>Supporter Pack</strong> store page. On release, <strong>HELLCARD </strong>will be a part of it.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/</a><br/><strong>Book of Demons</strong>, the first part in the series is already here, be sure to check it out as it includes a free demo. <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/</a><br/>Also, be sure to check out <strong>Book of Aliens</strong>, the second book in the series and a tribute to MicroProse’ UFO: Enemy Unknown that’s also in the works:<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1707811616"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2187220/Apollo_Justice_Ace_Attorney_Trilogy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/extras/13_Apollo_CustomImages_600x338.png?t=1706177279"><br/><br/>Apollo Justice's Legal Journey Begins Anew!<br/><br/>Join rookie attorney Apollo Justice and his mentor, the legendary Phoenix Wright, in this collection of 3 games! This title features the 14 episodes of "Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney", "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Dual Destinies", and "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Spirit of Justice", and the 2 previously DLC-only Special Episodes for a total of 16 episodes!<br/><br/>Also included is a mountain of extra goodies that's sure to satisfy any Ace Attorney fan!<br/><br/>Orchestra Hall - Listen to the in-game background music and select orchestral arrangements!<br/><br/>Art Library - View illustrations, design specs, commissioned pieces, and even the special Spirit of Justice Prologue anime!<br/><br/>Animation Studio - Play around with character animations and recreate your favorite scenes!<br/><br/>This collection supports Japanese, English, French, German, Korean, and Traditional and Simplified Chinese. Mix and match to play in whichever languages you'd like!<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in this beautiful collection as you shout "Objection!" in these newly renovated halls of justice!<br/><br/>Some of the contents of the games in this collection are presented as initially released to preserve the games as originally created.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDER NIGHT IN-BIRTH II Sys:Celes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2076010/UNDER_NIGHT_INBIRTH_II_SysCeles/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sys:Celes sinks towards ruination.<br/>For the Immortalize, the collapse of all that is, looms on the horizon.<br/>The curtain rises on the final chapter of the Hollow Night. Catastrophe beckons...<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store1b.gif?t=1707122865"><br/><br/>Experience the Dramatic Stylish 2D Fighting Action in the latest entry of the UNDER NIGHT IN-BIRTH series!<br/><br/>The first numbered sequel in the series!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Choose from a roster of 24 total characters, with renewed visuals!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store2.jpg?t=1707122865"><br/>3 new characters join the battle: Moonlight Dancer "Twin Barrel Beauty" Kaguya, Indomitable Rampart "Steel Guardian" Tsurugi, and Endless Entity "Eternal Re-Birth" Kuon.<br/>You won’t be able to take your eyes off the intense battles between these 24 fighters with the highly detailed HD pixel art graphics!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Simple inputs make it easy to jump into the fray!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store3.gif?t=1707122865"><br/>New to fighting games? Not a problem – simple inputs mean even beginners can pull off moves with a single button!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Now supporting rollback netcode for an improved online experience!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store4.jpg?t=1707122865"><br/>With the addition of Casual Matches, it’s easier than ever before to dive in and enjoy online battles.<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Introducing new moves and game mechanics!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store5.gif?t=1707122865"><br/>All characters now boast new moves, such as Hyde’s Blaring Outrage and Linne’s Soaring Dragon.<br/>The new game mechanics Creeping Edge and Celestial Vorpal open up additional depth to gameplay.<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ The final chapter! A new tale of the Hollow Night…</h2>Sever the cycle. An end to the endless.<br/>May the tale of these countless Nights be concluded, on this eve, the moment of destiny.<br/>A long-awaited continuation to the tale of the Hollow Night unfolds!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summon Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2100140/Summon_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2100140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a card and board game with the following features:<br>
<br>
Deck Building: Players can build their own decks to battle with. Depending on different strategies and opponents, players can choose different cards to counter.<br>
<br>
Tactical Gameplay: The game uses a 3x10 chessboard, and players can freely place cards to fight. Players need to develop tactics and arrange card positions and usage order within limited space.<br>
<br>
Different Professions: Players can choose freely from four professions - swordsman, mage, monk, and archer. Each profession has different characteristics and skills, and players can choose according to their preferences and tactical needs.<br/>
<br/>
Competitive Battles: Players can battle with other players after building their decks, and it is fun to fight with other people. Through battles with other players, players can improve their strength and tactical skills.<br/>
<br/>
Team Dungeons: In addition to fighting against other players, players can also team up with others to challenge high-difficulty dungeons. Players need to defeat powerful bosses through cooperation and strategy to get more rewards and cards.<br/>
<br/>
Special Challenges: Players can participate in special rules challenges and use their intelligence to defeat other players. These special rules make the game more interesting and challenging, and players need to constantly think and try new strategies.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced: Each game is fast-paced (within 5 minutes), and can be played in short fragments of time. The fast pace of the game allows players to enjoy the game in a short time, while also being able to play at any time and anywhere.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2248950/TransSiberian_Railway_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take the helm of a classic Russian locomotive, discover the raw beauty and wildness of Siberia and try to survive on the longest railway line in the world. This is the Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator. A game for real adventurers!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/drinking1.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>Complete the tutorial and the first kilometers of the route for free.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/explosion_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><br/><br/>The Trans-Siberian Railway Simulator offers amazing rail and survival challenges on real Russian dangerous routes. Feel what it is like to put your hands at the helm of a powerful freight locomotive and explore the untouched natural landscape that is sure to delight you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2248950/extras/shooting_gif.gif?t=1707824452"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Prologue features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Detailed simulation of driving a VL10 locomotive - the locomotive control is slightly simplified.<br/></li><li> Locomotive repair system - Manage and replace locomotive parts that are constantly wearing out.<br/></li><li> Train traffic simulation - Follow rail signs and signals to avoid derailment or damage to a part of the locomotive.<br/></li><li> Work system - Earn by completing transport orders. <br/></li><li> Game modes (Survival) and (Simulator). It is recommended to play in the (Survival) mode. This is the leading game mode that is constantly being developed. <br/>For players who are not interested in survival mechanics, a simple Simulator mode is available. <br/></li><li> Mafia system - Complete missions for the mafia to earn extra money.<br/></li><li> Survival system with statistics of hunger, thirst, alcohol, hangover, disease and hypothermia - Eat and drink to avoid death. <br/>Keep the right temperature so you don't freeze.<br/></li><li> Shooting system - Use your weapons for hunting and self-defense.<br/></li><li> Purchase and sales system - Buy various items, food, tools, weapons and ammunition.<br/></li><li> Locomotive inspection mode - Inspect the condition of locomotive parts and replace them in time to avoid damage.<br/></li><li> Dynamic weather system with day and night cycle - Survive extreme weather conditions.<br/></li><li> Route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Novosibirsk-Main) - scale 1:1. Buy the full version with the route from (Novosibirsk-West) to (Krasnoyarsk).<br/></li><li> Police system - A corrupt militia watches over your movements.<br/></li><li> Much more to discover.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Capitalist Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_6" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱💼🐾 WELCOME TO 100 CAPITALIST CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆💰💵</h2>🤑 Join the cutest adventure in the Wall Street, New York, heart of capitalism! 🏙️ Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of architecture as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game 😊<br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x200.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 🎮 1 Level of Wall Street location<br/></li><li> 🐈 100 Hidden Cats <br/></li><li> 🎵 Awesome Soundtrack <br/></li><li> 🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks <br/></li><li> 🥇 Achievements <br/></li><li> 🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li> ⌛️ SpeedRun Mode (Timer) <br/></li><li> 💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li> 🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li> 😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li> 💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li> 👫 Community<br/></li><li> 🌐 No Text</li></ul><br/><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Capitalist Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779640/100_Capitalist_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Extra.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779660/100_Capitalist_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1706062420"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2779650/100_Capitalist_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=100CapitalistCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Artbook.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/600x1.png?t=1706062420"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743080/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1706062420"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_7" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot" id="dynamiclink_8" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743080/100_Capitalist_Cats/?utm_source=CapitalistBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traveler Eternal Night</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810120/Traveler_Eternal_Night/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the game "Traveler: Eternal Night" you will embody a brave fighter who goes on a dangerous journey to destroy the evil that threatens the world. You have to explore different locations, fight monsters and complete quests to become stronger. Your hero will have to endure many trials, but his courage and determination will help him overcome any obstacles. An exciting adventure awaits you, full of dangers and battles that will show what a true hero is capable of.<br>
<br>
Various enemies await you along the way, each of which has its own unique abilities and weaknesses. You will have to use a variety of tactics and strategies to defeat your enemies and overcome all the challenges.<br>
<br>
The game offers an interesting plot, colorful pixel graphics and exciting battles that will immerse you in a world of fantasy and adventure.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unknown Signal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2808760/Unknown_Signal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2808760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Unknown Signal is a 3D adventure game. You have received a mysterious signal and you have to find out what or who sent it. Arm yourself with the best weapons and explore the mysterious planet! Fight with unknown mechanical creatures, go through dangerous situations that await you on this mysterious planet! Find out what is hidden behind the mysterious signal and become a real hero!<br>
<br>
Features<br>
- Nice soundtrack<br>
- Colorful graphics.<br>
- Dangerous opponents						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrowstorm Ascendant</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2785750/Arrowstorm_Ascendant/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About This Game</h2><br/>Arrowstorm Ascendant is a rogue-like shoot 'em up based on "Seraph's Last Stand" and "Vampire Survivors". Defeat hordes of dragons and wyverns with your outstanding archery skills. With each new wave you fight more enemies with more power, while also selecting one new upgrade. Create the most interesting, powerful or game breaking build and try to reach the top of the leaderboards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785750/extras/gameplaynew-ezgif.com-resize.gif?t=1707912076"><br/><br/>Everytime you restart you lose your previous powerups, but you can acquire gold coins while playing to buy new upgrades:<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785750/extras/upgrades-ezgif.com-resize.gif?t=1707912076"><br/><br/>You can choose 4 green cards and 4 blue cards after each wave. Find the best build possible and reach the highest level you can!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785750/extras/cards-ezgif.com-speed.gif?t=1707912076"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 50 different cards with green, red or blue upgrades. Create your build using a combination of 4 blue and 4 green cards (red card are infinite).<br/><br/></li><li> 11 different skins to choose from, with each skin having its own advantage.<br/><br/></li><li> A leaderboard system divided by score, enemies defeated and coins obtained.<br/><br/></li><li> A boss fight once you reach a certain number of waves.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tale of (Your Name)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2746270/The_Tale_of_Your_Name/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an exploration through a procedurally generated dungeon, brimming with ferocious monsters, perilous traps, and challenging puzzles. Dive into a distinctive 2D roguelike shooter experience, where each game unfolds as a unique journey.<br>
<br>
In "The Tale of (Your Name)," take control of a character's role in a tabletop RPG setting, shaping their attributes and narrative. Collaborate with a group of friends to craft an epic medieval fantasy tale, featuring a protagonist armed with weapons ahead of their time.<br>
<br>
Select your hero from three remarkable adventurers, each endowed with unique abilities, and set out on a journey filled with perils and discoveries. Venturing through a dungeon fraught with monsters, traps, and puzzles, your objective in each room is to locate a key to progress to the next challenge. As you advance, encounter narrative events that unfold your story—make critical choices in these events to proceed, decisions that might lead to wealth or pit you against a formidable monster.<br>
<br>
Progressing through the dungeon, utilize your accumulated wealth to purchase and enhance your weaponry (yes, firearms in this setting—thanks to the campaign master's whimsy), as well as other resources.<br/>
<br/>
Prepare for an exhilarating journey where, with each move, a new chapter emerges, and the fate of the protagonist rests in your hands. In "The Tale of (Your Name)," your unwritten story awaits. Confront challenges, make strategic choices, and become the unforgettable hero or villain of this captivating tale.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFENDUN : Hero Defense</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2323810/DEFENDUN__Hero_Defense/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2323810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2323810/extras/defendun_620x180_.gif?t=1707908907"><br/><br/><strong>Defenden is a strategy merge defense game!</strong><br/><br/>There were two very powerful beings in the world, Bael and Deus, who were very close brothers, but for some reason their relationship deteriorated and they began to fight. Their fight had unacceptable negative consequences, and the dark energy that spread during the fight awakened long forgotten dungeon guardians and monsters, demons in volcanoes, and yetis in snowy regions. The angels and demons who came as reinforcements to stop the monsters from invading the villages and kingdoms of the uninhabited, gave the heroes the ability to merge with the monsters and use this ability to help them stop the onslaught of monsters. Help the heroes, Guardians!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2323810/extras/defendun_-1.gif?t=1707908907"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Combine units according to a recipe. </strong><br/>Mix and match your favorite units to a set recipe. Build your own team by combining over 100 different units, each with unique traits and skills. Sometimes units are stronger uncombined, but higher tiers are usually better.<br/><br/><strong>15 classes to differentiate units. </strong><br/>Build efficient teams with units that are categorized into 15 different classes. If you have a lot of units of the same class, you can use class enhancement cards effectively. (Individual characters do not have classes.)<br/><br/><strong>Defeat over 200 themed monsters. </strong><br/>To clear the stages, you need to know the characteristics of each monster. Whether it's physical or magical damage reduction, multiple births, or the ability to summon monsters, know the characteristics of each monster to clear the wave.<br/><br/><strong>Understand and utilize your unit's skills. </strong><br/>Understanding the skills of your units will help you organize your team. Try to balance physical and magical attack units, think about the ratio of damage over time, instant damage, and area of effect attacks, and combine units that stun, bind, and slow monsters.<br/><br/><strong>Earn different passives each game to create different combinations.</strong><br/>Fill up the monster kill gauge or defeat boss monsters to earn the chests in the bottom right corner and spend them to upgrade individual units and earn class upgrade gold.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2323810/extras/defendun_-2__about_this_game_.gif?t=1707908907"><br/><br/><strong>Clear the stage by understanding the boss's abilities. </strong><br/>Defeat bosses by recognizing their abilities to freeze or stun units, reposition units, or restore health.<br/><br/><strong>Understand the structures that embody the concept of the stage. </strong><br/>Understand the features of maps that match the stage's concept, such as lava on the ground to give debuffs and water at the bottom to match the sea concept, and place your units correctly.<br/><br/><strong>Use the diamonds you're rewarded for playing to become stronger. </strong><br/>Diamonds are rewarded for play and can be used to take units to the next game or to permanently strengthen a player's Passive. They're awarded after you play, so play a lot to customize your look by purchasing custom skins from the Shopkeeper and in-game event skins.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monument village</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2553250/Monument_village/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2553250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Monument village is a peaceful turn-based medieval city-builder.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>Start on a pristine island, and grow your village, building by building. You can build exactly one building per turn. At the end of each turn, all your buildings produce some resources.<br/><strong>The focus of the game is on building placement</strong>. Each building has bonuses and penalties depending on its neighbors, so take your time to choose where to place them and plan ahead.<br/><br/>As your village produces resources, you will gain knowledge and discover new innovations. Each one gives you a choice of bonuses and/or new buildings to unlock. You cannot get everything, so each playthrough will be different.<br/><br/>Every now and then, you will receive a request for some resources to be delivered. You have to do it, but you will have some time to adapt and prepare.<br/><br/>Finally, when your village and your economy has grown enough, you will be able to build your dream monument. Four monuments are available to choose from, each with its unique requirements and resources.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Simple yet deep building placement system</strong>: find the right place for each building to optimize its production and that of its neighbors, present and future<br/></li><li> <strong>Innovation system with many choices</strong>: choose unlocked buildings and bonuses from a large pool, making each playthrough unique<br/></li><li> <strong>Many game options</strong>: choose from different map types and monuments</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>You are a talented architect, eager to prove your skills and build the grand monument which sketch has been sitting on your desk for far too long. But you need a place to build it, and land isn't cheap.<br/><br/><br/>After many days of searching, you finally make a deal with a wealthy merchant named Tessa. She owns an island on which there is enough space for your project. You accept her conditions without much thought.<br/><br/>Maybe you should have read the fine prints:<br/>First surprise, the island is remote and pristine. You will have to find a way to attract workers and to gather resources from the island. Guess it's time to learn how to manage a village!<br/>Moreover, until the monument is finished, Tessa can request any resource from you, and you will have to comply. Fail to do so and she will kick you out of the island. The longer you take to complete your project, the more you will have to deliver.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Yellow Moon's School: The Ghosts Day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2813970/The_Yellow_Moons_School_The_Ghosts_Day/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2813970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Yellow Moon's School: The Ghosts Day is a top-down shooter game in which you <br>
must shoot ghosts and destroy them to save the school.<br>
<br>
You control a student with a gun and have to shoot and eliminate hordes of Ghosts <br>
while avoiding contact with them. Some ghosts have guns and will shoot you.<br>
<br>
When you destroy hordes, a new stronger horde will appear, so you may have to<br>
upgrade to win.<br/>
<br/>
When you kill a ghost, you earn money. Use the money to upgrade and get stronger.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Patagonians</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1665170/The_Patagonians/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The events of this terrible night began ten years ago.<br/>However, today they will overtake you and make you remember the promise made once.<br/>Rushing to find your missing daughter, you will become participants in terrible events.<br/>But this time it won't be possible to retreat.<br/><br/>The Patagonians is a 2D horror adventure inspired by horror movies from the 80s and 90s.<br/>You have to explore creepy and unpleasant locations filled with disgusting monsters.<br/>At the beginning of the journey, you will only have a torch in service.<br/>So sometimes the best solution to save your own life is to run away.<br/>To top it off, huge guardian bosses will stand in your way.<br/>Their main task is not to let you into the lair of the Patagonians.<br/>To win you will have to show ingenuity and patience.<br/>Get ready! It will be very difficult.<br/>What awaits you at the end of this story?<br/>I'll leave it up to you to find out for yourself.<br/><br/>Waiting for you:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Original 2D graphics.<br/></li><li> Atmospheric environment.<br/></li><li> 3 zones and more than 20 locations.<br/></li><li> 11 types of deadly enemies. <br/></li><li> Simple controls.</li></ul><br/>Explore locations, look for clues, solve puzzles, fight dangerous enemies or flee, destroy obstacles.<br/>Do whatever is necessary to reach your goal.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Multitool</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723690/Robot_Multitool/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Robot Multitool</strong> is a puzzle adventure about a multifunctional robot.<br/><br/>In your arsenal, you have the opportunity to cling and swing on a cable, release an electric charge of a certain power, shoot, remotely control a flying hand capable of pressing levers and buttons.<br/>All the mechanics open up gradually as you progress through the game.<br/>Thanks to all the robot's capabilities, you can interact with the environment to solve puzzles and skill tasks.<br/><br/><strong>Story</strong><br/><br/>At the beginning of the game, the drone connects the missing part to the robot and revives it. Due to the fact that the robot is broken, it is leaking energy. You must pick up a part for the flying arm and use it to get to the part that stops the leak as soon as possible.<br/>During the game, you will find electronic notes from an unknown robot that will give you information about the place where you are and give you hints. He wants to help you get to the place where he is being kept locked up so that you can free him. You will have to complete all the puzzles, skill tasks and battles that you will encounter on your way.<br/>It will not be easy to go all the way, as many robots will try to destroy you. Some of them you can just dodge, and some will have to fight. Also, puzzles require good ingenuity to solve them.<br/><br/><strong>Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Controlled flying arm:<br/><br/>You can aim and shoot your right hand at the right place. Then you can switch between hand control and robot control. The hand has an energy scale. The arm is able to fly until the energy runs out. As soon as the hand falls and touches the surface, its energy is fully restored.<br/>With the help of a controlled hand, you can reach levers and buttons that cannot be reached just like that. For example, the lever that opens the door you need is located behind a wall in which there is a small hole that only a hand can fit through.<br/>The ability to be in one place in the form of a robot and in another place in the form of a hand is extremely useful in passing. As soon as you need two hands to open a large door or activate a large lever, you can return the hand to the robot.<br/><br/>Cable:<br/><br/>Your other hand is capable of releasing a cable that can cling to certain flying objects. Hanging on the rope, you can swing, go up and down, shortening or lengthening the rope.<br/>You don't need a flying arm to hook, so you can control the flying arm by hanging on a rope. For example, you can hook a rope to a special object, and with your controlled hand press the lever that controls the movement of this object.<br/><br/>Weapon:<br/><br/>In the game you have to fight with some robots. To do this, you have a weapon that has a delay after each shot.<br/>By pressing a certain key, you can switch the arm/weapon aiming mode. In the first mode, you aim to release the flying arm. In the second, to fire a weapon.<br/><br/>Electro-shot:<br/><br/>When you pick up a certain part, the right hand will have a new mode. Now, when you aim with your right hand, you can change the mode from releasing a flying hand to firing an electric charge. By pressing the shot key in this mode, the energy scale is filled. Releasing the key, you fire an electric charge with an energy level equal to the filling of the scale.<br/>There are objects in the game that move depending on the level of energy that is allowed into them. In these cases, you will need to release an electric charge with a specific power. An electric charge can only be fired if the robot has a right hand. It can be used while on the cable.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DarkLight: Platformer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2649040/DarkLight_Platformer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2649040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the world of DarkLight: Platformer, where adventure and fun await you at every step. This exciting 2D platformer promises you an unforgettable journey through 150 unique levels and five diverse biomes.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Collectibles:</strong> Feel like a true collector as you gather 200 unique items scattered throughout the levels. Each item has its own story.<br/></li><li><strong>Character Variety</strong>: Choose from one of 54 unique characters, each with their own traits, strengths, and weaknesses. Collect them all and unlock their potential.<br/></li><li><strong>Progression and Equipment:</strong> Improve your character's attributes and equipment from over 120 different options that will aid you in battles against enemies.<br/></li><li><strong>Magic and Spells:</strong> Immerse yourself in a magical world with 12 powerful spells that will help you solve puzzles and battle bosses.</li></ul><br/>DarkLight: Platformer is not just an exciting game, but also an immersion into a world of magic and adventure. Dive into this unique world and embark on the adventure of your dreams!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Typer Backspace</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2804280/Monster_Typer_Backspace/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2804280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							ENTER a new world, a fresh TYPO experience—an ESCAPE from reality deep within outer SPACE. Welcome to Earth-3.<br>
<br>
Monster Typer Backspace is a fast-paced, zany typing game designed for everyone, featuring simple controls (typing) and easy-to-learn mechanics.<br>
<br>
- Compete against typists around the world on the online leaderboard.<br>
- Learn about the monsters in the Monster Database.<br>
- Every day is a different seed for everyone to compete in.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TheSpoiler</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2761560/TheSpoiler/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							When you come to your senses, you find yourself trapped in a nightmare. <br/>The books scattered around will guide you through your future.<br/><br/>When the clock chimes, everything around transforms with the darkness.<br/>And this place is inhabited by monsters and witches. Escape the nightmare and avoid harm from them.<h2 class="bb_tag">About Game</h2>The Spoiler is an first person escape game infused with psychological horror. <br/>You can progress through the story by solving simple puzzles and finding items.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game elements</h2>Simply puzzle, Chasing enemy<br/>Include short cut scene<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, Language(KR, EN), Sounds<h2 class="bb_tag">Control</h2>W A S D is move , Q E is hang up item, SHIFT is run , CTRL is crouch<br/>Mouse is rotate camera<br/>ESC is open menu<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>About 30 minutes						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pal Up!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2812910/Pal_Up/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Climb to the heavens across worlds, avoiding dangerous enemies in this "Souls-Like" game.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812910/extras/newgif2.gif?t=1707901804"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812910/extras/Gameplay.png?t=1707901804"><br/><br/>⭐⭐⭐<br/>- Climb to the top using jumps and bounces off the wall.<br/>- Dodge arrows and other projectiles of enemies who want to prevent your ascent!<br/>- Open shortcuts to get back from a fall faster!<br/>- Light a campfire to teleport to other precincts!<br/>- Rest by the campfire to replenish the player's health and resources.<br/>- Souls-Like combat system. Enemy Targer-Lock, Dodge, roll, block.<br/>⭐⭐⭐<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812910/extras/newgif1.gif?t=1707901804"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812910/extras/Line.png?t=1707901804"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2812910/extras/newgif3.gif?t=1707901804"><br/><br/>⭐⭐⭐<br/>- You play as "Kyoko" a spirit who needs to climb to heaven to save his people. <br/>- Get there as fast as possible , and compare your results with other players and friends.  <br/>- A wide variety of worlds and obstacles await you, from winter to desert. <br/>- Use your katana to make a series of strikes against your opponent.<br/>- Explore the world to find auxiliary items.<br/>- Bypass your opponents to deliver the fatal blow and ease the climb.<br/>⭐⭐⭐						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirty Rotten Bounders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796280/Dirty_Rotten_Bounders/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">How to play the game</h2>The game has three levels: <strong>Easy, Ok and Ouch</strong>. The names indicate the relative degree of difficulty of each level. To finish a level you must complete each of the 15 boards within the level. After completing the <strong>Easy</strong> level, you move to <strong>Ok</strong> and then <strong>Ouch</strong>. You may start at any level, but a useful tactic is to start at a less challenging level and build up a store of extra lives to sustain you at higher levels.<br/><br/>Gameplay takes place on a series of boards each consisting of nine rows and nine columns of tiles. Each tile may be one of two colours. For example, these tiles are used on the initial Robotica board.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/tiles1and2.png?t=1707898447"><br/><br/>The player is represented by a smiley-faced character on the board.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/players.png?t=1707898447"><br/><br/>The player moves the character from tile to tile by using a gamepad joystick, or the arrow keys (left,right,up,down or W,A,S,D).<br/><br/>When the player lands on a tile, if the tile is already the player's colour, nothing happens and no points are awarded. If the tile was not the player's colour then it will be instantly changed to the player's colour and points will be awarded.<br/><br/>If the tile is changed and, in conjunction with another tile of the player's colour, encloses one or more tiles of the other colour, then those other tiles will flip to the player's colour. Each tile flipped is awarded an increasing number of points, so flipping longer lines is more rewarding than flipping shorter ones. This is the main game mechanic.<br/><br/>The following images should help to explain how it works.<br/><br/>First the player jumps onto another tile:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/explain1.png?t=1707898447"><br/><br/>The tile changes instantly to the player's colour, enclosing one or more tiles of the opposing colour by two player tiles:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/explain2.png?t=1707898447"><br/><br/>The enclosed tiles flip to the player's colour:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/explain3.png?t=1707898447"><br/><br/>Each tile flipped is awarded an increasing number of points:<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/explain4.png?t=1707898447"><br/><br/>Lines may be flipped horizontally, vertically or diagonally.<br/><br/>This mechanism is similar to that used in the strategy board game called Reversi, said to have been invented by an Englishman in 1883.<h2 class="bb_tag">Teleportation</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/teleport.png?t=1707898447"><br/>If the player jumps onto a tile overlaid with a teleport symbol, then the player will be directly transported to another tile at random. At more challenging levels, fewer teleports are available and may disappear at random when used, but will reappear some time later.<h2 class="bb_tag">Adversaries</h2>Each board comes with a number of adversaries. They are called chasers and initially appear in a cage to the left of the board. There is a hole in the bottom corner of the cage, which the chasers can use to gain access to the board. Only a limited number of chasers are allowed on the board at any one time. When the chasers appear on the board they will try to collide with the player's character. If they are successful, the player will lose a life and the board will be restarted. Initially the chasers move quite randomly, but as time passes they begin to hunt the player more zealously. As the chasers move about the board they flip the player tiles to the other colour. The chaser tile flipping occurs in the same manner as the player flipping, except that the flipping is instantaneous, not animated as for the player. The chasers are different for each board, for example the chasers for the Robotica board are:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/chasers.png?t=1707898447"><h2 class="bb_tag">How to complete a board</h2>Jumping around the board scoring points is all very well, but how do you complete a board? To complete a board you must kill all of the chasers. You can kill a chaser by flipping the tile beneath it. When sufficient chasers have been killed the final adversary from the cage, the destroyer, will be released. The destroyer will proceed to jump from tile to tile destroying each tile that it lands upon, reducing the size of the board. You must kill the remaining chasers before the destroyer consumes the board and eventually the player. You cannot kill the destroyer and collision with the destroyer will result in the loss of a life. For the Robotica board the destroyer looks like:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/destroyer.png?t=1707898447"><h2 class="bb_tag">Pick-ups</h2>Whenever a chaser is killed, by flipping the tile beneath it, there is the chance that a pick-up, or hazard, may be generated. The pick-ups that are common to all boards are listed below. In general, a pick-up that is beneficial to the player, will be portrayed by a slowly rotating icon. To acquire the pick-up, and reap the benefits associated with it, the player simply has to jump upon the same tile that the pick-up occupies. The benefits of each pick-up are:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/heart.png?t=1707898447"><br/>The heart pick-up increments the number of lives that the player has remaining. The player starts the game with an initial tally of five lives. If the player loses all lives then the game is over. A heart pick-up will appear when the player flips a chaser having scored 10,000 points, or more. Another heart pick-up will appear after every additional 10,000 points scored.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/shield.png?t=1707898447"><br/>The shield pick-up wraps the player in a protective bubble. If the player collides with one of the four chasers, then the chaser will be killed - the hunters become the hunted. The shield lasts for about 10 seconds, after which time it will flash briefly and disappear. The shield duration is cumulative, so jumping on two shields, one after the other, will afford the player about 20 seconds of protection. Note the shield only protects the player from the four original chasers, not the destroyer or other hazards that may appear.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/speed.png?t=1707898447"><br/>The super-speed pick-up allows the player to move at double speed for about 10 seconds. Again, the super-speed pick-ups are cumulative and are particularly devastating if you are also protected by a shield. You should exercise care when travelling at super-speed, as it becomes more difficult to navigate accurately.<h2 class="bb_tag">Hazards</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/flamer.png?t=1707898447"><br/>There is one particular chaser which poses an additional threat. Sometimes, one of the chasers, always the same type, will pause and breathe flames for a short period. If the player is caught by the flames, a life will be lost.<br/><br/>Occasionally, when a line of tiles is flipped, one of them will shatter, leaving a hole, which randomly moves around the board. The player cannot jump onto a hole, so it provides an obstacle to navigation.<br/><br/>The remaining pick-ups and hazards generated by killing a chaser are specific to each board. To read a full description about pick-ups, refer to the in-game help menu. For the initial Robotica board the hazards are:<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/oil.png?t=1707898447"><br/><strong>The oil slick</strong>. An oil slick  is non-fatal to the player. If the player lands upon it he will slide onto another tile without landing on the tile covered by the oil slick.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796280/extras/saw.png?t=1707898447"><br/><strong>The saw.</strong> A saw  is potentially fatal to the player. The saw moves randomly up and down, or side to side. If the player collides with the saw a life will be lost.<h2 class="bb_tag">Level Completion</h2>When all 15 boards have been completed, the player proceeds to the next level. When the final Ouch level has been completed, the game is finished and any remaining lives are multiplied by 10,000 and added to the total score.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grid Dungeons</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2798420/Grid_Dungeons/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Immerse yourself in the strategic depths of our turn-based dungeon game! Take command of a party of diverse characters, navigating through grid-based maps to outwit and conquer enemies. Your mission: strategically eliminate foes while minimizing damage to your own team. Explore the treacherous depths of dungeons, where every move counts in this thrilling adventure of tactics and skill. Can you emerge victorious against the lurking dangers?<br/><br/>Embark on a strategic journey through a myriad of maps in our turn-based dungeon strategic game! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798420/extras/unit_showcase-500X279.png?t=1707898038"><br/><br/>Command a diverse party of characters, each wielding unique weapons - from swordsmen engaging in close combat to archers picking off enemies from a distance, and mages unleashing powerful spells.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2798420/extras/action_showcase-500X139.png?t=1707898038"><br/><br/>Unlock a plethora of actions, allowing you to tailor your approach to each challenge. Navigate the grid-based landscapes wisely, combining the strengths of your team to defeat foes and uncover the secrets hidden within the dungeons. <br/><br/>Master the art of strategy in a world where every move and action shapes your destiny!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Scourge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2778980/Goat_Scourge/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2778980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Quiet village life is disturbed by the attack of the Ogre Sorcerer, who needs goat bones for his magical experiments. The beloved pet goat of a village boy is stolen - and he risks it all to save the goat's life. Help him retrieve his pet - and explore the village and its outskirts in our game.<br/><br/>The game contains several scenes in which the main character solves quests, explores the level with platformer mechanics, and confronts NPCs. The main goal of the character is to overcome all the obstacles, and save the goat. He will face the antagonist, whose aim is to collect the artefacts for his magic potion.  <br/>You will have a chance to play for both of them.<br/><br/>The entire game is quite short: you will jump on an adventure and will be done in less than an hour. But what an hour it will be!<br/><br/>This game was made with MANU Video Game Maker - no-code game engine!<br/><br/><strong>Controls:</strong><br/>Movement - WASD;<br/>Jump - Space;<br/>Interact - E;<br/>Interface buttons - 1-5;<br/>Menu Interaction - Enter;<br/>Attack/Chop - LAlt;<br/>Goat Minigame - 1-3;<br/>Quest Open/close - Q						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulls and Cows - Wild West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2795840/Bulls_and_Cows__Wild_West/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2795840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the amazing farm where the captivating game "Bulls and Cows: Wild West" takes place! Here, children will embark on a unique adventure, meeting a kind and lovely cow-girl.<br>
<br>
On the farm, amidst green pastures and picturesque meadows, our little heroes will meet Vanessa – a clever and friendly cow-guide. She will enthusiastically explain the rules of the game and help children develop their logical abilities.<br>
<br>
"Bulls and Cows: Wild West" will offer children an endless number of levels that will capture their imagination and ignite the desire to conquer all the puzzles. Thanks to Vanessa, our little heroes will strive for new heights in solving the riddles.<br>
<br>
Immerse yourself in the unique world of the Wild West, accompanied by lively country music. Children will enjoy every level, playing with Vanessa and her friends, and enhancing their logical skills on this captivating farm!<br/>
<br/>
Get ready for an exciting adventure on the farm, uncover number mysteries, and become true sheriffs of puzzles in "Bulls and Cows: Wild West" alongside Vanessa!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hi Eggplant:The Birth of Sprites</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375290/Hi_EggplantThe_Birth_of_Sprites/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							that is, a rich planting experience. At the same time, new concepts such as Sprites have been added to enrich the game, and the details have also been repeatedly polished and improved.<br>
<br>
In terms of planting, we have improved the problem of insufficient guidance at the beginning that was raised a lot in the previous work. Appropriately provide planting methods, while reducing the difficulty, retain the fun of players' own exploration. In addition, pest control and weed control are enriched. The task system has also been newly added, and there will be new tasks waiting for you to challenge in each stage!<br>
<br>
In terms of new content, you are likely to meet some new friends. You can sell the eggplant to NPC Momo, or you can learn a mysterious story from the sprites. And the exploration of this part of the content is also inseparable from your planting ability.<br>
<br>
Oh, in this work, a mechanism that the game will fail when the plant dies is removed, so that you have more space to explore, and you will meet sprites as soon as possible. I hope you will like it.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of The Black Hawk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2664930/The_Adventures_of_The_Black_Hawk/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664930/extras/historia_eng.png?t=1707892859"><h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag">france, Spring 1789.</h2></h2></h2>Social tension rises while nobility, in their convenient and accommodated position, enslaves the common people with their taxes. Meanwhile, Jean Pierre de Saint-Cove, a noble aristocrat, secretly hides behind his mask to fight injustice and inequality, and to give back to the people what they rightfully deserve.<br/><br/>Use your full cleverness to solve the different situations along the way until you fulfill your purpose. Both your sword and eloquence will be your most trusted allies, without forgetting the help of your loyal friend Mathieu and beautiful Violette Hulot, who will get you out of trouble more than once and without whom you would never be able to top this adventure.<br/><br/>Confront aristocracy and the Deputy Chief of police, Baron LeComeau, to  overthrow the Old Regime by finding out about the best hidden secrets of nobility, and using them to your advantage. <br/><br/>Persist in your eagerness to achieve your goal! Be brave, smart and hilariously crazy to achieve victory!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664930/extras/featuring_eng.png?t=1707892859"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>An adventure full of humor, sarcasm and shrewdness, divided in three chapters.<br/></li><li>Control Jean Pierre de Saint-Cove in his two identities, both as an aristocrat and as The Black Hawk. As a plus, your will have to occasionally get aid and control some other character.<br/></li><li>Countless puzzles and riddles of all kinds. Use the objects surrounding you, combine them with each other, talk to every character to get clues and even try to trick them (if you have to).<br/></li><li>Sword duels! Shootings! And lots of emotions in the face of danger!<br/></li><li>Over thirty fully detailed locations, design to bring back that classic adventure style.<br/></li><li>Over sixty characters to interact with.<br/></li><li>Forty-five original music themes which will take you to the past and get you even more in the shoes of The Black Hawk.<br/></li><li>A journey to the 80s and 90s classic adventures, with a style that mimics their predecessors.<br/></li><li>HQ points to get while you solve main and secondary puzzles.<br/></li><li>And villains, too many villains!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Night On The Farm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2598340/A_Night_On_The_Farm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2598340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2598340/extras/ANOTF_Steam_GameLength_Small_3.png?t=1707890445"><br/><br/>A Night On The Farm is an atmospheric, first-person, retro-inspired, horror adventure with deep lore and surprising plot twists. Uncover the mystery surrounding your crashed car and the farm’s inescapable draw. Discover cryptic notes and audio logs as you gain access to [REDACTED] and make decisions that alter the story’s outcome!<br/><br/>Gameplay Features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Interactive, first-person gameplay, focused on story and exploration.<br/></li><li> Unlock doors, access computer terminals, and explore eerie environments to see just how deep the rabbit hole goes.<br/></li><li> Discover fully-voiced cassette tapes, strange toys, and other optional items that flesh out the game's lore.<br/></li><li> Atmospheric lighting, particle effects, and sound design bring eerie Autumn visuals to life.<br/></li><li> Lo-Fi, pixelated, PS1 / early 2000’s-inspired graphics.<br/></li><li> Multiple endings!<br/></li><li> Cloud Saves</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temple of Causality</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2677140/Temple_of_Causality/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Intricate Puzzles:</strong><br/>Each puzzle is a testament to the depth of ancient wisdom and the complexity of causality. Every choice you make reverberates through the temple, shaping the course of your obyssey. Master the unique mechanic: pushing one block triggers an automatic cascase, moving all causally connected blocks.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677140/extras/Gameplay_GIF.gif?t=1707890253"><br/><br/><strong>Immersive Exploration:</strong><br/>Roam through a temple filled with diverse locations, from buddhist statues to Hindu ruins. Unearth long-buried secrets and strands of forgotten history.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2677140/extras/Environments.gif?t=1707890253"><br/><br/><strong>A Journey of Transcendence:</strong><br/>Master the concept of causality and travel to the heart of the temple, where the laws of existence are surpassed. Your decisions hold the key to unlocking the secrets of this temple.<br/><br/><strong>Ancient Wisdom:</strong><br/>Journey through a realm steeped in the wisdom of diverse religious philosophies. Each puzzle carries echoes of Hinduism, Buddhism, Jainism, and more, weaving a tapestry of profound insights.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XELAN FORCE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690610/XELAN_FORCE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							8BIT style vertical scrolling shooting game Zelan Force.<br>
We developed this product with the idea that we want people to remember the excitement of those days and to pass it on to the next generation.<br>
It is a retro-style game that has the same sound as the actual FC machine, limited the number of colors, and eliminates the expressions of modern games as much as possible.<br>
<br>
Equipped with P・L・S (Pilot Level Score) system! The difficulty level changes depending on the player's skill. As the difficulty level increases, the score increase rate also increases!<br>
Challenge your high score in caravan mode!<br>
We aimed to create a game that you can enjoy over and over again, such as the feeling of play that changes between offensive and defensive types, and the ability to search for hidden items.<br/>
<br/>
story<br/>
A galaxy far, far away.<br/>
The inhabitants of the planet Zelan, which was on the verge of extinction due to resource depletion and climate change, were proceeding with plans to develop and colonize other planets in search of a new world.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, an incident occurs in which ships departing from Zeran go missing one after another.<br/>
<br/>
From the communication records, it is revealed that the series of events was caused by an invasion by Alien Muldark.<br/>
Eventually, Moldark's forces take control of Zelan's satellite base.<br/>
Most of the regular army Zeran Force, which was supposed to protect Zeran, had left Zeran to protect the pioneer fleet, so the remaining army faced off against Muldark's army, but suffered a devastating blow.<br/>
<br/>
Pilot Levi Kuzier, who was injured and away from his mission, boards the under-development aircraft ``Riserion'' and flies off into space alone in order to take back the occupied satellite base.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic Arcade Fishing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479670/Classic_Arcade_Fishing/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							2024 newly upgraded classic arcade fishing shooting game, with exquisite graphics and special scenes; unique batteries and wings shake the entire fishing ground, bringing you a different fishing pleasure; more mysterious bosses, innovative events, and upgrade benefits are waiting for you to unlock. This is a casino/shoot them up type of game,take you to experience an unparalleled audio-visual feast!<br/>【The ancient beasts are shocked】<br/>The charming mermaid, the mechanical shark of the future technology, the mysterious and powerful dark dragon, the ancient beast that masters the darkness, the special boss scene interaction and event gameplay, the perfect immersive experience, more mysterious bosses are waiting for you to explore after all!<br/>【Super weapons destroy the world】<br/>The truly innovative experience, the lasers in seconds, the nuclear bombs that bomb everything, the warheads that rampage, the thunder strikes with all their power, etc., will definitely make you feel overwhelmed!<br/>【Random events get rich overnight】<br/>The unique boss awakening event allows you to experience what it means to be lucky! Fun! nice! So exciting!<br/>[Free delivery of super many benefits]<br/>Log in to send massive gold coins, daily tasks, holiday gameplay, and multiple welfare leaders.<br/>【Powerful Fortress Cool Wings】<br/>The exclusive customized turret skin and wing system allows you to stand out and be amazed in the world of fishing!<br/>[Classic arcade super explosion gold]<br/>A mainstream fishing game with classic arcade gameplay, easy fishing, super high explosion rate, and a real hit of 100 million!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War Link - 2111 AD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1489490/War_Link__2111_AD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1489490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step onto the battlefield and answer the call with the title that raised the bar for first-person shooter games with its great graphics, high-powered guns, and intense  action.<br/>Play free anywhere, anytime. War Of Mars delivers the most intense multiplayer action on Virtual Reality. Drop-in, gear up, and compete.<h2 class="bb_tag">Battle Royale features:</h2><br/><strong><u>Game modes</u></strong><br/>3 separate game modes: team, solo, and Robot battle. Try them all!<br/><br/><u><strong>Character variety</strong></u><br/>Tons of different skins and heroes, Pick your target and attack!<br/><br/><strong><u>Weapon variety</u></strong><br/>Choose from pistols, assault rifles, shotguns, miniguns, sniper rifles, rocket-launchers, and grenades, Pick your weapon and attack!<br/><br/><u><strong>Huge map</strong></u><br/>The map is filled with unique nooks, crannies, and structures to hide out in and take cover. Camp out till your heart’s content!<br/><br/><u><strong>Graphics</strong></u><br/>Amazing futuristic graphics in HDR						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amber</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653880/Amber/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an enchanting journey alongside Amber as she ventures through the whimsical realms of Candy, Cake, Story, Rainbow, and Crystal in this captivating action-adventure platformer. Spread love and restore harmony to the vibrant inhabitants as you wield the radiant power of Amber Crystals. Use her Mallet, Chocolate Staff, and Bubblegum Wand to gently pacify unruly denizens. Navigate gracefully through these fantastical lands, running, jumping, and gliding with the Rainbow Umbrella, and even taking a dip in crystal-clear or chocolatey waters. Seek out each kingdom's sovereign and engage them in a transformative encounter, bringing balance and harmony back to this extraordinary world.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Fantasy;</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2699780/Synthetic_Fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2699780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Do you feel lonely?<br/><br/>Observe this story as a member of the audience and witness this tale of love and friendship and find out the answer to the ultimate question:<br/><br/><strong>Can YOU learn to love?</strong><br/><br/>This is the question the protagonist, Dan Garland, will learn the answer to as he is caught between his <strong>fiance</strong> and an <strong>android</strong>. <br/><br/>Hopefully <strong>you</strong> will be able to answer that question too, player.<br/><br/>Features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple endings to obtain<br/></li><li>    Several CG's to enjoy throughout the story<br/></li><li>    Cast Talk-back after obtaining all endings<br/></li><li>    Several achievements to earn<br/></li><li>    You'll learn to love (hopefully!)</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924780/Arzette_The_Jewel_of_Faramore/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/intro_gif.gif?t=1707886813"><br/><br/>After ten years of peace...the evil Daimur has returned! Princess Arzette is the Kingdom of Faramore’s only hope to restore harmony to the land!<br/><br/>In this brand new interactive action adventure game, you control the resourceful princess Arzette. Travel through multiple breathtaking locations filled with scum, villainy and secrets, speak with the locals to uncover mysteries and objectives, and take on the evil Daimur as <strong>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</strong> brings you the best interactive gaming experience since the invention of the CD-ROM!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/mortar_gif.gif?t=1707886813"><br/><br/><strong>Featuring:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hand painted backgrounds and incredible sprite art.<br/></li><li>Fully voice-acted cartoon cinematics with a colorful cast of characters.<br/></li><li>A sprawling world with diverse locations and many secrets.<br/></li><li>Acquire powerful items and abilities by exploring and helping those in need.<br/></li><li>Veteran dev team including artist Rob Dunlavey, Digital Foundry's John Linneman and Audi Sorlie, voice talent Jeffrey Rath and Bonnie Jean Wilbur, and award winning composer Jake "Button Masher" Silverman.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notanote</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687160/Notanote/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2687160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Welcome to the world of Notanote!</strong> <br/>Notanote is a rhythm game that emphasizes visual performance.<br/>It blends melody and beat into the visuals, providing an immersive experience of music!<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong> <br/>Full Keyboard Judgement <br/>     Notanote adopts full keyboard judgement, allowing you to catch notes with any key. <br/>     You don’t need to worry about which key corresponds to which note. Just find the rhythm and press the corresponding number of keys. <br/>     You can hold down one key to catch all drag notes; When faced with multiple long notes, you only need to press the corresponding number of keys at the beginning, and then keep one key pressed down.<br/><br/>Multiple Difficulty Design <br/>     Want to try different performances under the same music? Some tracks have multiple difficulty options, allowing you to choose different difficulty levels according to your needs.<br/><br/>Casual Mode <br/>     Feeling too difficult? You can use the casual mode in the settings to get a more relaxed gaming experience.<br/><br/>Collection System <br/>     During the process of playing the tracks, you will also obtain collectibles and unlock relevant plots.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory of summer flower Ⅱ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2698190/Trajectory_of_summer_flower/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About</h2>Following "Trajectory of summer flower", the official production team SoraPrayer brings you the authentic sequel. This story unfolds ten years after the events of the previous installment. Unlike the portrayal of rural feudalistic customs from an urbanite's perspective in the previous work, this installment takes a different approach. It follows a youth, native to Tangxia Village, providing a perspective rooted in indigenous culture to depict the hidden feudalistic darkness and customs within Chinese villages more profoundly. Additionally, this installment emphasizes the theme of "family", and the humorous and comedic daily life elements from the previous work are preserved authentically, ensuring that you will not find this realistic and poignant subject matter dull. The protagonists and related characters from the previous work will also play crucial roles in this installment, interacting with the new main character, offering you a fresh perspective on the beautiful love story among the youths in the summer countryside.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>Little is known about Tangxia Village, a secluded small mountain village. The scenery here is picturesque, with a perpetual summer-like atmosphere throughout the seasons. For most people, it is like a utopia, but beneath this beauty, this village is rife with feudalistic customs incongruent with its idyllic surroundings. Human trafficking, gender bias, and archaic rituals such as ghost marriage persist in the village, remnants of the old society's customs.<br/>The protagonist of the story, Ma Xiaodong, is the son of the Ma family, local landlords in this village. Living with his father, Ma Qingchen, his two sisters, Ma Minyi and Ma Wenhui, and his childhood friend, Zhu Qianyin, the five of them share a household. As the eldest son, Ma Xiaodong cherishes every day spent with his family, valuing them above all else.  Though his father occasionally treats him harshly, he remains committed to the principle of filial piety. <br/>Despite the seemingly peaceful surface, the inevitable conflict between personal growth and traditional beliefs creates tensions. Like a butterfly breaking free from its cocoon, changes in thoughts and contradictions with traditional values become apparent one summer. In this particular summer, long-hidden family secrets gradually surface. Faced with the impending darkness, the choices between change and tradition, how will the young boys and girls respond? Will the gears of their destiny begin to turn, propelling them towards new horizons? All the answers will be revealed in this summer.<h2 class="bb_tag">Character Introductions</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698190/extras/intro_1.png?t=1707876052"><br/><strong>Zhu Qianyin</strong><br/>Character Voice: 桂圆翊宝<br/>BWH: 82/58/84<br/>Birthday: December 5<br/>Height: 156cm<br/>Weight: 43kg<br/>Of unknown origin, Zhu Qianyin has lived in the Ma family since childhood and is Ma Xiaodong's childhood friend. She is timid, shy, and not good at expressing herself. Despite being responsible for all household chores since she became self-reliant, her clumsy nature often leads to mistakes and punishment from Ma Qingchen. With a low status in the family, she lacks the qualifications to attend school and has the last turn for meals, and she is Ma Qingchen's punching bag when he's in a bad mood.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698190/extras/intro_2.png?t=1707876052"><br/><strong>Ma Minyi</strong><br/>Character Voice: 闲踏梧桐<br/>BWH: 80/54/83<br/>Birthday: October 21<br/>Height: 155cm<br/>Weight: 42kg<br/>Ma Xiaodong's other younger sister, Ma Minyi, is gentle and quiet, who is the opposite of Ma Wenhui in terms of personality. She is the second daughter in the family. She excels in her studies and is good at doing household chores, she is a very perfect girl. Although she is Ma Xiaodong's little sister, she plays the role of "elder sister" among the siblings, intervening in conflicts between her brother and sisters. She is the second person in the family, after Ma Xiaodong, who cares about Zhu Qianyin.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698190/extras/intro_3.png?t=1707876052"><br/><strong>Ma Wenhui</strong><br/>Character Voice: 恪诀<br/>BWH: 65/48/70<br/>Birthday: March 15<br/>Height: 154cm<br/>Weight: 40kg<br/>Ma Xiaodong's younger sister, the lively and curious Ma Wenhui, is playful and carefree during adolescence. She is the youngest in the family. While appearing strong-willed, she has a vulnerable side. Although she often teases Ma Xiaodong, she deeply admires her brother but hesitates to express it openly. She tends to spend money recklessly, exhausting her allowance every month and relying on Ma Xiaodong to "borrow" money, with repayment often forgotten.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698190/extras/intro_5.png?t=1707876052"><br/><strong>Ma Qingchen</strong><br/>Character Voice: 来晓风<br/>Birthday: June 4<br/>Height: 179cm<br/>Weight: 60kg<br/>Ma Xiaodong's father and the head of the Ma family. Stern and unfeeling, Ma Qingchen holds strong feudalistic beliefs, emphasizing the importance of sons over daughters and treating his daughters as tools for collecting dowry. He runs a land leasing company to provides all the economic resources for the family. He believes that children must be filial to their parents and a strict father raises dutiful children, continuously instilling related values in his children. He often mistreats Zhu Qianyin, making her the primary target of his abuse.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698190/extras/intro_4.png?t=1707876052"><br/><strong>Feng Guojian</strong><br/>Character Voice: 马晨星<br/>Birthday: September 6<br/>Height: 176cm<br/>Weight: 55kg<br/>Ma Xiaodong's classmate, Feng Guojian is a poor student who doesn't study well, often loafing around and failing to finish homework. He befriends Ma Xiaodong and considers him as his buddy, but it's just to borrow Ma Xiaodong's to copy. However, even so, he still has a good moral character and readily assists Ma Xiaodong whenever needed.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698190/extras/intro_6.png?t=1707876052"><br/><strong>Lin Jiajun</strong><br/>Character Voice: 茨球儿<br/>Birthday: July 14<br/>Height: 178cm<br/>Weight: 58kg<br/>The headmaster of Tangxia Middle School and the major economic contributor to Tangxia Village, Lin Jiajun is perceived as a great person in the villagers' eyes. Humorous and witty, he maintains a balance between joking and maintaining authority. Despite his high status, he is often seen casually dressed while roaming around the village, and few recognize him. There seems to be an unknown past about him.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2698190/extras/intro_7.png?t=1707876052"><br/><strong>Chen Jiancheng</strong><br/>Character Voice: 昨夜阳光<br/>Birthday: January 5<br/>Height: 179cm<br/>Weight: 57kg<br/>The village secretary of Tangxia, Chen Jiancheng has a strong network in the village and influences the village's development. Despite appearing nonchalant when dealing with village affairs, he is a dedicated village official with high prestige among the villagers. He is masterful at strategizing and masterminding, always showing a calm and confident demeanor, as if everything is within his control.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matchmaker Agency</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2204260/Matchmaker_Agency/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2204260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2204260/extras/banner_about.png?t=1707872431"><br/><br/>Have you ever had a failed date? Are you tired of having awkward moments with strangers you just met from an online application or friends? <strong>Now's your chance to change that.</strong> It's time for <strong>YOU</strong> to become cupid and match couples together in this <strong>immersed, compelling story-based game.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2204260/extras/banner_charles.png?t=1707872431"><br/><br/>Starting as an amateur in the ways of romance, you will quickly learn what it takes to fulfill people's hopes and dreams. <i>Gain reputation points </i>and <i>cash</i> for matching couples successfully, <i>unlock upgrades</i> to enhance events, and <i>enjoy the lovely feline companion</i> <strong>Charles </strong>along the way. But don't forget -- <strong>it's a race against the clock</strong> and you owe the landlord money! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2204260/extras/banner_gamefeatures.png?t=1707872431"><br/><br/><strong>Become The Matchmaker</strong> - Analyze and interview clients, scout the perfect location, select the finest gifts and plan their dates. You might not be the best bachelor/bachelorette, but at least you can be the <i>best matchmaker in the game</i>!<br/><br/><strong>Clients </strong>- <i>Procedurally-generated clients</i> with a (nearly) endless combination of personality types, perk points, and personal tastes. Different kinds of people with different needs for love!<br/><br/><strong>Special Clients</strong> - Meet unique clients each with<i> intriguing backstories </i>and goals (with hot potential lovers). Will you assist them in obtaining their one true love? Or would it be more fun to purposefully sabotage the moment?<br/><br/><strong>Upgrades</strong> - Upgrades people, upgrades! <i>Earn rewards</i> with every successful match, which can be spent to upgrade your skills and improve your office. Unlocking more of your matchmaking capabilities!<br/><br/><strong>Chill and Relax</strong> - Play and enjoy the game at your own pace. After all, love takes time to bloom and shouldn't be rushed.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runestone:Pathfinders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2764080/RunestonePathfinders/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong><i><u>"Runestone: Pathfinder"</u></i></strong> is a 3D adventure platformer game set in the world of Runestone. Players will play as a rookie pathfinder and help the rookie get through his first trial.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/GF_en.png?t=1707900920"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/SC_en.png?t=1707900920"><br/>    Movements, jumps, and dashes are consistent. You can combo them into more complex moves.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/Movements.gif?t=1707900920"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/AC_en.png?t=1707900920"><br/>    You can expect a packed level with collectibles and achievements that take multiple playthroughs to accomplish. <br/>    A fruitful adventure awaits you! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/Collectible.gif?t=1707900920"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/ELC_en.png?t=1707900920"><br/>    You might finish the first playthrough in one hour or two. You will improve the timer drastically the second time. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/Improve.gif?t=1707900920"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/CC_en.png?t=1707900920"><br/>    You can unlock and choose<br/>-7(or more?) styles of feather color<br/>-4 styles of backpacks<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/Custom.png?t=1707900920"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/SL_en.png?t=1707900920"><br/>    Compete against players around the world to see who is the better Pathfinder!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2764080/extras/leaderboard.png?t=1707900920"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skibidi Toilets: Invasion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2550480/Skibidi_Toilets_Invasion/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2550480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Welcome to Skibidi Invasion, a heart-pounding FPS zombie shooter where you must obliterate cyborg toilets and restore order to a world in chaos! Armed with an array of weapons, unleash your fury against the rebellious toilets across seven distinct locations, each offering its own challenges and opportunities for strategic mayhem.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">PLAY ON 5 UNIQUE MAPS</h2>From dilapidated city streets and eerie graveyards to abandoned factories and secret underground bunkers, prepare to battle the cyborg toilet menace in diverse environments teeming with danger.<h2 class="bb_tag">COLLECT ALL WEAPONS</h2>Choose from a vast arsenal of weapons, from traditional firearms to experimental gadgets, each with its own modifications and upgrades.<h2 class="bb_tag">IMPROVE YOUR CHARACTER</h2>But victory won't come easy - pump up your main character with enhancements to accelerate movement, increase damage output, and unlock special abilities. Strategize wisely, hone your skills, and prepare for the ultimate showdown against the Skibidi rebellion.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Fighters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1393680/Supreme_Fighters/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1393680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1393680/extras/About.jpg?t=1707867335"><br/><strong>Supreme Fighters</strong> is a <strong>free</strong> fighting game set in an urban environment. Fight against player or AI in multiple dynamic and destructible maps with 5 different and unique playable characters! Will you be the last player standing?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Gamemodes</strong> </h2><strong>Supreme Fighters</strong> currently features 3 different kinds of gamemodes.<h2 class="bb_tag">- PvP <i>(Teams or Free for All!)</i> <i>(4 Players / AI)</i> </h2>          Fight in a free-for-all or team-based deathmatch until one player or team is the last one standing. Will you become the Supreme Fighter?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1393680/extras/GameplayV2.gif?t=1707867335"><h2 class="bb_tag">- PvE Survival <i>(2 Players)</i> </h2>         Team up together with another fighter to conquer and defeat all enemies across the city. Stand out and you might get noticed by Ghost...<br/><strong>Survival</strong> consists of multiple rounds of beating weaklings, with each round set in another map. At the end of each round you get to pick 1 out of 2 modifiers which can be either positive or negative for your survival. The difficulty will rise each time, but that won't be a problem, right?<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1393680/extras/Survival.gif?t=1707867335"><h2 class="bb_tag">- PvE Streets <i>(4 Players)</i> </h2>         Team up together with 3 fighters to protect a part of the city. You can work together or split up if you are confident enough!<br/>This world consists of one big map where enemies will keep repeatedly spawning. There will be objects scattered around the map that can help you hold them off! Besides, who wouldn’t want to throw a traffic cone at their enemies? Capture hardpoints and get rewarded with positive modifiers! Try to survive and capture as much as possible to reach a new high score!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReRise</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2783380/ReRise/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2783380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Arena of the Steel Gladiator: Robot Warrior's Triumph!<br/><br/>A New Dawn in the Colosseum: The Rise of the Steel Gladiator!<br/>"Step into the future, where the clash of steel and the roar of the crowd set the stage for a remarkable tale. In the Colosseum of tomorrow, a gladiator in the form of a mighty robot wields its deadly weapon, ready to face the challenges that await. W, A, S, D keys are the controls that navigate this metallic warrior as it embarks on a quest to conquer the arena."<br/><br/>The Hunt Begins: Steel Gladiator vs. Monstrous Beasts!<br/>"As the gates of the Colosseum swing open, the Steel Gladiator enters the arena, armed with a formidable robotic weapon. Its mission: to hunt down and eliminate the monstrous creatures that emerge with each victorious battle. With each slain beast, a new challenge awaits in the next round as an extra creature joins the deadly fray. Will the Steel Gladiator emerge triumphant or succumb to the ever-growing swarm of creatures? The fate of the arena hangs in the balance."<br/><br/>Rising Tensions: One Robot Against the Horde!<br/>"With each creature the Steel Gladiator vanquishes, the tension in the Colosseum rises. The crowd's cheers echo as the metallic warrior battles relentlessly, pushing the limits of its robotic prowess. As the horde multiplies, the challenges become more intense. W, A, S, D keys become the lifeline, and the mighty weapon becomes the instrument of survival. The question remains: Can the Steel Gladiator endure the ever-increasing onslaught and emerge as the ultimate champion of the arena?"</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirty Dirty Pirates</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273050/Dirty_Dirty_Pirates/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							--- DEMO WILL EXPIRE FEBRUARY 13 ---<br/><br/>You're a dirty scallywag with nothing to lose. Dirty Dirty Pirates is a fast-paced, chaotic, player versus player fighting game, where fast reflexes and improvisation will help you become victorious. Stab, throw, roll, dance, mount, catch, and smash your way through frenzied battles in a looped battleground and enjoy the hilarious brutality.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL-MULTIPLAYER MAYHEM</strong></h2>Brawl with 2-4 players in a top down, blood-soaked, pirate battleground not for the faint of heart. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273050/extras/DirtyDirtyPirates_Local_Multiplayer.gif?t=1707852004"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHAOTIC LOOPED BATTLEGROUND</strong></h2>You and your thrown weapons wrap around the level, creating chaotic ways to slay your enemies (or yourself)!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273050/extras/DirtyDirtyPirates_Looped_Battleground.gif?t=1707852004"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>POUNCE AND EXECUTE</strong></h2>Mount a downed pirate and choose your killing method. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273050/extras/DirtyDirtyPirates_Mount_Kill.gif?t=1707852004"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GRATIFYING KILL CAMS</strong></h2>Watch the final kill of the match in slow motion and celebrate the brutality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273050/extras/DirtyDirtyPirates_Kill_Cam.gif?t=1707852004"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>WEAPONS WITH A MIND OF THEIR OWN</strong></h2><br/>Not only are the weapons pointy and eager to impale – but they follow you! Better hide, catch, or roll, ya buccaneer.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SLAUGHTER IN DIVERSE LANDS</strong></h2><br/>Slay your foes at ship docks, ancient jungle ruins, desert, caves, and icy tundras.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CUSTOMIZE THE CHAOS</strong></h2><br/>Reduce or increase the blood/gore to your liking (or disable it). Color blind mode is available as well. <br/><br/>Please note: This is a local multiplayer game without online gameplay. For the best experience, find a comfy couch and some friendly mateys in the same room or with Steam Remote Play.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
