<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload: Expansion Pass</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2689210/Persona_3_Reload_Expansion_Pass/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Dive deeper into the world of <i>Persona 3 Reload</i> with this expansion pass featuring new costumes, BGM, and an extended story content scenario “Episode Aigis -The Answer-”, offering over 30 hours of additional gameplay.<br/>Content will be released as follows:<br/><br/><strong>Wave 1 - <i>Persona 5 Royal</i> EX BGM Set and <i>Persona 4 Golden</i> EX BGM Set <br/>Release Date: March 2024</strong><br/>Unlock and listen to additional tracks from <i>Persona 5 Royal</i> and <i>Persona 4 Golden</i> while exploring and battling in dungeons in <i>Persona 3 Reload</i> and <i>Persona 3 Reload: Episode Aigis -The Answer-</i>.<br/><br/><strong>Wave 2 - Velvet Costume &amp; BGM Set <br/>Release Date: May 2024</strong><br/>Unlock Velvet Room themed costumes and BGM to further customize your dungeon experience in <i>Persona 3 Reload</i> and <i>Persona 3 Reload: Episode Aigis -The Answer-</i>. <br/><br/><strong>Wave 3 - New Expansive Story Scenario, “Episode Aigis -The Answer-” <br/>Release Date: September 2024</strong><br/>After unravelling the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fighting epic battles through Tartarus, and all the unforgettable events of <i>Persona 3 Reload</i>, the S.E.E.S. members find themselves trapped in a never-ending March 31st. Journey through the Abyss of Time as Aigis, undertake new challenges, and uncover the cause of this strange fate and the truth of what happened on that day... <br/><br/>Delve into this final chapter now with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, fresh animations and UI, and a rearranged soundtrack. <br/><br/>---<br/><br/><i>Persona 3 Reload: Persona 5 Royal</i> EX BGM Set Track List (8 total):<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Life Will Change<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Beneath the Mask<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Kichijoji 199X<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Gentle Madman<br/>- Dungeon BGM: I believe<br/>- Battle BGM: Keeper of Lust<br/>- Battle BGM: Blooming Villain<br/>- Battle BGM: Victory (Appears on battle results screen）<br/><br/><i>Victory</i> will automatically be applied as the battle result theme when you set one of the tracks in this pack as your battle BGM. It cannot be applied individually.<br/><br/><i>Persona 3 Reload: Persona 4 Golden</i> EX BGM Set Track List (8 total):<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Backside of the TV<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Game<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Junes Theme<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Heaven<br/>- Dungeon BGM: Long Way<br/>- Battle BGM: Revelations: Mitsuo<br/>- Battle BGM: The Almighty<br/>- Battle BGM: Results (Appears on battle results screen）<br/><br/><i>Results</i> will automatically be applied as the battle result theme when you set one of the tracks in this pack as your battle BGM. It cannot be applied individually.<br/><br/><i>Persona 3 Reload</i>: Velvet Costume &amp; BGM Set Contents and Track List (5 total):<br/>- Velvet Room themed costumes<br/>- Dungeon BGM / Battle BGM: Electronica In Velvet Room ("P4D" ver.)<br/>- Dungeon BGM / Battle BGM: Battle Hymn of the Soul (t.komine REMIX "AT 1st" P3D-EDIT ver.)<br/>- Dungeon BGM / Battle BGM: Battle Hymn of the Soul (Daisuke Asakura Remix)<br/>- Dungeon BGM / Battle BGM: Battle Hymn of the Soul -USH ver.-<br/>- Battle BGM: Dance Hymn of the Soul (Disco In Velvet Room) (Appears on battle results screen)<br/><br/><i>Dance Hymn of the Soul (Disco In Velvet Room)</i> will automatically be applied as the battle result theme when you set one of the tracks in this pack as your battle BGM. It cannot be applied individually.<br/><br/>To change your Costume, go to the Main Menu &gt; EQUIP &gt; Select character &gt; Select Outfit.<br/>To change your BGM, go to your Main Menu &gt; SYSTEM &gt; CONFIG &gt; Game System Settings and select Change Dungeon BGM or Change Battle BGM.<br/>You must own Persona 3 Reload with the latest patch downloaded to access expansion pass content. <br/>Some content in this product may overlap.<br/>Names and descriptions in this product are subject to change without notice. <br/>Scheduled release dates are subject to change.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Transmute</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1191660/Rebel_Transmute/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/Rebel_Transmute_Logo_Decorated_Steam.png?t=1710176486"><br/><br/>In this modern metroidvania you play as Moon Mikono, a space scrapper turned adventurer on a mission to uncover the true fate of her missing mother.<br/><br/>To accomplish this mission in your own, unique way you'll be swapping out game changing augments to suit your playstyle.  Aggressive and greedy?  Inquisitive and cautious?  Maybe you just want an army of friendly creatures!  With over 50 unique upgrades, Rebel Transmute allows you to play through a classic sci-fi adventure in YOUR style.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHALLENGING AND CUSTOMIZABLE COMBAT</h2>Use a variety of spells known as Bloodcasts, your trusty Foray-issued Blaster, and a variety of game changing Augments to take on a world of dangerous creatures and space travelers.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/16.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE AND MAP A VIBRANT SCI-FI WORLD</h2>The sprawling world of Rebel Transmute is full of stunning vistas: From vibrant greenery in the Overgrowth, to the fluorescent reefs of the Coral Fissure, to the sparkblood crystal-strewn Surface.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/09.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">Additional Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Encounter over <strong>80 unique enemies</strong> and over <strong>10 formidable bosses</strong>! From mutated worms and electrified beasts, to rogue AI's and gigantic bugs. All offering different and exciting challenges and interactions.<br/></li><li>Discover <strong>game-changing abilities</strong> hidden throughout the outpost.  Spin Bash, Wall Jump, and Void Dash your way across an interconnected network of tunnels, caverns, and research laboratories!<br/></li><li>Augment your playstyle with <strong>48 optional upgrades</strong> that can drastically change how you play the game.  Fight alongside a reprogrammed drone, twist your attacks into spiraling laser blasts, or even summon tentacles to block projectiles!<br/></li><li>Make use of a versatile mapping system to help track your progress.  Use custom markers, track your completion percentage, and find hidden terminals to uncover unexplored areas.<br/></li><li>Experience a <strong>personal and heartfelt story</strong>. As Moon searches for her mother she’ll also encounter various robot life, all with their own stories, personalities, and quests.<br/></li><li>A <strong>hand-painted pixel art</strong> aesthetic lends each and every character, enemy, and sector a personal touch.<br/></li><li>An immersive and atmospheric score, crafted to perfectly match every moment, from bombastic fights to solemn exploration.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of a Wish</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2302080/Death_of_a_Wish/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/DeathWishHeader.gif?t=1710183750"><br/><strong>Death of a Wish</strong> is a vicious action-RPG where <strong>style is salvation</strong>. <br/><br/>Play as Christian as he unites with new comrades to challenge the cult that raised him. By taking down the four Sanctum Faiths: Father, Sister, Cardinal, and Priest, they will upend the order of the world.<br/><br/>Fight your way through a nightmare filled with horrifying monsters and terrifying people. Master brutal attacks and flashy combos as you struggle against the Corruption consuming you with style and grace. Shine your light in this surreal sea of darkness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/keydetails2.png?t=1710183750"><h2 class="bb_tag">ENGAGE IN VICIOUSLY GRACEFUL COMBAT</h2>Unleash Christian’s cursed powers in a demanding and rewarding combat system. Be careful not to succumb to the ever-encroaching Corruption; achieve high ranks in combat and perform graceful combos to hold the Corruption at bay.<h2 class="bb_tag">CUSTOMIZE YOUR MARKED POWERS</h2>Rend your foes asunder with magical combos called Arias. Enhance your abilities with powerful Virtues that alter your approach to battle and the rhythm of combat. With a limitless array of ways to fight stylishly, build your character with passion to destroy your foes.<h2 class="bb_tag">DESCEND INTO THE NIGHTMARE</h2>In the dreamworld of Paradiso, repressed memories and unspeakable feelings come to life as the nightmarish city of Neo-Sanctum. Delve into the secret underworld of the esoteric and abandoned to meet new comrades who will aid you on your journey.<h2 class="bb_tag">SURREAL AND SPECTACULAR</h2>Christian’s world is rendered with a surreal aesthetic like no other. Harsh, pulsating scratches upon a sea of darkness render a thick atmosphere brooding with emotion. Battles come to life in an animated spectacle of light and motion that remains easy to parse in play. <br/><br/>For audio, Nicolo Telesca’s chilling score mixes electronic sounds with live instrumentation and complements the visuals by eliciting feelings of tense anxiety and electrifying catharsis.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/discord2.png?t=1710183750"><br/>Join the official Discord at <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FvJ7JnsAMcK" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/vJ7JnsAMcK</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/ezgif-4-1c4b73cf2b.gif?t=1710183750"><br/><br/><i>Game contains imagery that may be harmful to players with photosensitive epilepsy or similar conditions. See content warnings below. </i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERHOUSE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2533960/SUMMERHOUSE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2533960/extras/summerhouse_new_store_page.gif?t=1709984408"><br/><br/>SUMMERHOUSE is a small-scale building game and a love letter to the feeling of long lost summer afternoons.<br/><br/>Craft a neighbourhood of tiny, beautiful lived-in homes in a variety of settings: the sea, the city, or the mountains. While there are some little secrets to uncover, there are no rules, and you can’t win or lose. Just chill out, build to your heart’s content and soak up the atmosphere.<br/><br/>If relaxation and creation are your thing, this is a game for you :)<br/><br/><i>Please keep in mind that this is a small game with no goals or challenges, created by a single person🙂</i> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORE BLASTERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/BORE_BLASTERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/BLAST.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_blast_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Blast your way through rocks and dirt with your machinegun drill. Carve through the ground to uncover precious ores and defeat menacing foes.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/LOOT.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_loot_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Uncover ancient relics and artefacts hidden in the deep. Amass a fortune in rare gems &amp; ores.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/UPGRADE.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_mortar_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Invest in powerful upgrades and unlock new abilities, turning your humble gyrocopter into a fearsome force to be reckoned with.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/DISCOVER.png?t=1709907021"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_discover_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/>Explore a diverse range of biomes, from treacherous volcanic caverns to lush overgrown underground forests, each with its own unique challenges and rewards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/FEATURES.png?t=1709907021"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Intense mining action with fast-paced blasting<br/></li><li> Constant progress - even failed runs aren't punishing<br/></li><li> Diverse biomes to explore<br/></li><li> Purchase upgrades to overpower your gyrocopter<br/></li><li> Navigate the overworld to unlock new mine shafts<br/></li><li> Collect and loot rare gems, ores, and artefacts to upgrade your gear and abilities<br/></li><li> Endless replayability with procedurally generated levels</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_drones_frame.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/>Drawing inspiration from mining games like Motherload and Galactic Mining Corp, Bore Blasters takes the genre to the next level with high octane action and fast paced gameplay. Fans of digging and collecting will find plenty to love, while the addition of deadly enemies and mysterious artefacts will keep even the most seasoned miners on their toes.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2398170/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/WL_arrow.gif?t=1709907021"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2398170/extras/GIF_missiles_frame.gif?t=1709907021"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Realm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1330000/Stolen_Realm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/GreenDragon.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TURN-BASED STRATEGY MEETS ACTION RPG IN THIS DUNGEON CRAWLING LOOTER</strong></h2><br/><br/>Stolen Realm is a <strong>simultaneous turn-based tactical dungeon crawling looter with action RPG elements</strong> where you control up to <strong>6 heroes, solo or through online co-op</strong>, venturing forth in adventures set in a high-fantasy, low-poly world. <br/><br/>Stolen Realm features an <strong>innovative turn-based combat system</strong> where <strong>simultaneous turns</strong> allow every team to take their actions at once, creating quick combat encounters that blend the tactical depth of titles like Divinity: Original Sin with the thrill of a fast-paced action RPG. Every battle scales based on the number of players involved, so you can easily jump in and out of the game even in the same playthrough!<br/> <br/>With a <strong>highly customisable class system</strong>, Stolen Realm allows you to create traditional RPG classes or break the mold to forge a unique champion of your own as you draw from a pool of hundreds of possible skills. Make a spell-slinging assassin, a priest born of frost, or a shadow-infused knight. Further customize your build by earning and reforging <strong>loot that truly changes the way you play</strong>: wield Abbadon the Soul Crusher, a mythic mace that raises slain enemies as skeletal warriors to fight for you, or unsheath the Bloodletter, a cursed sword that grants additional power at the cost of your lifeblood. D&amp;D-like events where attribute-based rolls will have permanent effects on your character add yet another layer to building a character that is truly your own. Anything is possible in this title that keeps compelling choices at the forefront of your experience.  <br/><br/>Keeping the core appeal of RPGs at its forefront, Stolen Realm ensures you spend all your time, fighting, building your characters and making compelling choices that determine your immediate path or effect your character, rather than getting bogged down in side quests and other RPG-bloat.   After each battle, pick your path between story events, resource gathering, shops and treasure rooms, until you get to the final boss of each <strong>procedurally generated adventure.</strong> If you’re up to a challenge, crank the difficulty up with <strong>6 different difficulty levels</strong> – or pick <strong>Hardcore Mode with permadeath</strong>, where every battle can be the last!<br/><br/>Also features <strong>Roguelike Mode</strong>, a fast paced version of the game where you can mix and match builds that are simply not possible in the traditional campaign!<br/><br/>Carve a place in history with your sword and magic. Rise to honor and glory in the battlefield. <strong>Recover the Stolen Realm.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/CycloneKick.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag">PRAISE FOR STOLEN REALM</h2><br/>“The tactical depth of Divinity: Original Sin” - GamesRadar+<br/><br/>“we’re losing our evenings to… Stolen Realm” - TheXboxHub<br/><br/>“A gorgeous looking game” - PC Gamer<br/><br/>“You can be a fire warrior. You can be a healing necromancer. You can do all sorts of weird s**t.” - <strong>Sacriel</strong><br/><br/>“What I like about this game is it’s straight to the point. You just go in, you’re building your character, you’re getting items…and you just fight. There’s no bulls**t.” - <strong>Shroud</strong><br/><br/>“It’s rad” - <strong>Sequisha</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1330000/extras/Dwarven_Warmachine.gif?t=1709885067"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong></h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play solo or with friends in up to 6 player online co-op, allowing you and your friends to wreak havoc amongst your foes<br/></li><li>Experience thrilling and fast-paced turn-based battles thanks to a simultaneous team turn system<br/></li><li>Full story campaign, roguelike mode and streamer mode<br/></li><li>Use over 300 skills in 10 distinct skill trees allowing for complete and flexible character customization<br/></li><li>Navigate hex-based battlefields where positioning is key due to battle shrines with special effects, exploding barrels and movable crates<br/></li><li>Find and loot over 700 unique items, fully customizable with modifiers, as you explore a wonderful world full of magic, secrets and unexpected dangers<br/></li><li>Co-op focused design keeps gameplay fast paced and strategic for up to 6 players <br/></li><li>Easy drop-in, drop-out design and automatic scaling that allows you to join or drop out mid-quest <br/></li><li>D&amp;D-like attribute-based rolls in special events that have permanent character effects<br/></li><li>Fight against over 200 types of enemies in battles that will be different every time: thanks to the Enemy Modifications feature, every creature you face on the battlefield will be unique<br/></li><li>A world that changes on each expedition, from frosty peaks guarded by the elusive Blue Dragon to overgrown jungles where the rock giants roam. <br/></li><li>Pick your path between battles, choosing where to go between story events, resource gathering, shops, fights, and treasure rooms until you get to the final boss of each adventure<br/></li><li>6 different difficulty levels<br/></li><li>Choose between Normal Mode and Hardcore Mode with permadeath if you want a real challenge!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duelists of Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1664200/Duelists_of_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/DoE_EVO_Trailer_-_steam_gif_short_30fps.gif?t=1710102934"><br/>Duelists of Eden is a card-grid-fighting game set after the events of One Step From Eden. Build your custom deck and battle online in real-time action! There are over 14 unique characters with strengths and weaknesses to encourage creative spell combinations and synergies. Will you combo slashes, fire, or even use bombs to eliminate your competition?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/SaffronWitch_steam_header-features.gif?t=1710102934"><h2 class="bb_tag">Deckbuilding</h2>Fight in a mix of strategy and real-time action! Create your own unique combination of spells to take down the competition. <br/>Save and edit an unlimited amount of decks in the editor!<h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic cardtridge and combo system</h2>Create combos on the fly, adapting the scenario and what spells you and your opponent have.<h2 class="bb_tag">Tutorial and training mode</h2>Learn the ropes in the tutorial mode and deep dive into the mechanics via training mode. <br/>Training mode includes hitboxes, character states, quick deck edits, speed modifiers, and more!<h2 class="bb_tag">Custom rollback netcode</h2>The game was completely rebuilt to support custom rollback netcode, for the smoothest experience possible.<h2 class="bb_tag">Replay mode</h2>Review your matches in replay mode!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1664200/extras/Selicy_OSFE_gif_steam.gif?t=1710102934"><br/><br/>Local multiplayer may require a controller.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sim City 3000™ Unlimited</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2741560/Sim_City_3000_Unlimited/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2741560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Create and control your urban empire with more power than ever before. With SimCity 3000 Unlimited, you get all the great features of the original SimCity 3000 plus much more. Expand your SimCities with 2 new building sets from Asia and Europe. Take on 13 challenging scenarios, or create your own. Unleash 4 new disasters, including an unforgiving whirlpool and plummeting space junk. This is truly SimCity without limits!<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Re-create cities from around the globe with hundreds of new buildings.<br/></li><li>Reunify East and West Berlin in one of 13 scenarios.<br/></li><li>Spruce up your city with over 95 world landmarks.<br/></li><li>Protect your citizens from 4 new disasters.<br/></li><li>Select hundreds of buildings from SimCity 3000 and all-new Asian and European buildings.<br/></li><li>Create unique masterpieces for your metropolis with the Building Architect Plus tool.<br/></li><li>Inflict 9 disasters, including toxic clouds, plague of locusts, space junk, and a whirlpool.<br/></li><li>Play 13 challenging scenarios, or make your own with the SimCity Scenario Creator.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potions: A Curious Tale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/378690/Potions_A_Curious_Tale/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Add Potions: A Curious Tale to your wishlist!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/Wishlist_616.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/LunaCombatGif.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Use your wits to strategize conflict resolution that goes beyond pure combat-- you’ll have to think on your feet and act quickly to sidestep danger and trick, charm, and scare your opponents into dropping valuable resources. <br/><br/>As powerful as your potions are, you’ll find yourself up against monsters that can shrug off your most powerful attacks. Manage your resources carefully and use the environment and even other monsters to defeat your enemies, or you may find yourself with an empty satchel when you need your elixirs the most.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamCraftingVideoFullPotTitleNX.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>On her path to potions mastery, Luna must gather rare ingredients even before she brews her first potion. While her grandmother and friends teach her basic skills and recipes, Luna must fill her vials through experimentation and discovery. <br/><br/>Explore the deep crafting system as you discover new ingredients across 7 biomes to craft over 100 unique potions with different element combinations. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PuzzleGifTitle.gif?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Solve devious puzzles and mysteries with your wits and your arsenal of mystical potions. With a little help from your grandmother (a powerful witch in her own right) and Helios, your cat familiar, you’ll overcome the challenges of these enchanted lands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/StoryTitle.png?t=1709876407"><br/><br/>Growing up is hard, and it’s even harder when you’re a witch! Encounter fairy tale and folklore characters as you guide Luna on her quest to become a potions master. With her sharp-tongued familiar at her side, Luna learns important coming-of-age lessons: Respect is earned, advice can be deceiving, and adults aren't always right.<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FQS2SN55CC4" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/SteamHeaderDiscord616.png?t=1709876407"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/378690/extras/PetCatHeart.gif?t=1709876407"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Saboteur™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/24880/The_Saboteur/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/24880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Not all wars are fought on the open battlefield. Download The Saboteur to visit 1940s Nazi-occupied Paris, as you play tough Irish racecar mechanic Sean Devlin. Working with the French Resistance, Sean is out for revenge against ruthless Nazi Colonel Kurt Dierker, who executed Sean’s best friend.<br/><br/>This open-world action thriller takes you through the seedy streets of Paris as you seek to undermine the German authority and lead a rebellion. Fight across rooftops and through dangerous alleys, and operate a wide variety of vehicles as you navigate your terrain. You can even climb the Eiffel Tower or Notre Dame Cathedral for a sniping mission.<br/><br/>Use stealth and disguise to strike at the heart of the Nazi war machine by disabling trains, destroying bridges, and blowing up enemy facilities. As you work to remove the oppressive forces from parts of the city, the drab black-and-white palette gives way to bright colors, signifying that you’ve inspired the townspeople. The more you incite the people, the more they’ll aid you by intervening in fights or providing a quick getaway from pursuing Germans. The Saboteur presents a fresh take on World War II and features dramatic cinematic elements. The action and intrigue is yours to experience via download on the PC now.<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>First Ever Open-World Paris</strong> — Climb the Eiffel Tour, snipe from Notre Dame Cathedral, and brawl on the Champs d’Elysee as you sabotage your enemies. Fight, climb, and prowl through the dark alleys, rooftops, burlesque houses, and seedy streets of the City of Lights — the ultimate playground for the Saboteur.<br/></li><li><strong>The Art of Sabotage</strong> — Being the Saboteur is all about attacking while staying unnoticed. Get your mission intel at underground clubs and cabarets. Eliminate your adversaries with stealth attacks, disguise, distractions, and explosives. Master a variety of weapons, automobiles, and skills to sabotage enemy operations. <br/></li><li><strong>The Will to Fight</strong> — An action-packed experience and thrilling storyline are made even more engaging by an innovative visual style, characters, and the new “Will to Fight” technology. Experience how the city reacts and changes around you as you free it from Nazi oppression. Only you can restore hope and grandeur to Paris.<br/></li><li><strong>French Resistance Strikes</strong> — Call for support from The Underground in the form of getaway cars, weapon deliveries, distractions, and much more.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1808680/Snufkin_Melody_of_Moominvalley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_1_opt_c.gif?t=1709917468"><br/><br/>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley is a story-rich musical adventure game about Snufkin restoring the valley and helping the quirky and memorable characters and critters who call it home. A series of hideous parks have cropped up in Moominvalley, disrupting the landscape and its harmonious nature. As Snufkin you will distract police officers, pull out signs, and knock over misplaced statues as you vigorously try to restore nature and the inhabitants’ home while putting an end to the industrious Park Keeper’s plans…<br/><br/>Experience a beautifully crafted and quintessentially Nordic game, brought to life with stories, emotions, and a melancholic atmosphere set in Tove Jansson’s vivid and beloved world of Moomin. You are invited to a wholesome experience for every age that combines open-world mechanics with puzzles, stealth, and melodic elements!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_2_opt_c.gif?t=1709917468"><h2 class="bb_tag">GORGEOUS STORYBOOK STYLE BRINGING A WORLD TO LIFE</h2><br/>Immerse yourself in a beautiful and imaginative world that captures the very essence of the Moomin stories; an extensive tapestry of graphical books and cartoons brought to life in a never-before-seen way. <br/><br/>Experience the harmonious symphony with every footfall, elevated by music and melodies from the Icelandic post-rock band Sigur Rós. Befriend Moominvalley inhabitants as Snufkin with a few tunes from his harmonica. Wander Moominvalley with your heart open and your steps light. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_3_opt_c.png?t=1709917468"><h2 class="bb_tag">A CAST OF WONDERFULLY WHIMSICAL CHARACTERS</h2><br/>Get to know a diverse cast of characters with strong yet whimsical personalities, depth, and complexity. Embark on a journey to not only find the cause of the hideous parks but to also discover and interact with the charming Moominvalley inhabitants.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_4_opt_c.gif?t=1709917468"><h2 class="bb_tag">A MUSICAL ADVENTURE</h2><br/>Explore a host of locations where the sun dips below the horizon, casting a warm amber glow across the meadows; where the scent of wildflowers mingles with the crisp breeze, carrying promises of untold stories and hidden wonders; and where you as Snufkin - with your hat pulled low and harmonica in hand - head out. Gain inspiration by exploring Moominvalley and by solving puzzles.<br/><br/>Main features<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Set out on a cozy, story-rich adventure game in a gorgeous storybook art style <br/></li><li> Get the strict Park Keeper and his horrible parks out of Moominvalley with the help of your trusty harmonica, a bit of stealth, and the friends you’ll meet along the way<br/></li><li> Meet over 50 charming characters and creatures calling Moominvalley their home<br/></li><li> Experience narrative gameplay and a myriad of charming stories and quests involving the beloved characters inspired by Tove Jansson’s work<br/></li><li> Explore Moominvalley’s open world and solve musical and environmental puzzles along the way to uncover the happenings in the valley<br/></li><li> Immerse yourself in the beautiful soundscape of music and melodies composed in collaboration with Sigur Rós</li></ul><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.snufkin.game%2Fdiscord" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1808680/extras/Snufkin_Steam_Discord_c.png?t=1709917468"/></a><br/><br/>© Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley. Developed by Hyper Games. Published by Raw Fury AB. © Moomin Characters ™						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Difficult Game About Climbing</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2497920/A_Difficult_Game_About_Climbing/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2497920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Use only your mouse (or gamepad) to control your climber's hands to pull yourself up an enormous, treacherous mountain full of challenges and surprises. Watch out for slippery surfaces as you make your way towards the peak. Eternal glory and a wonderful gift awaits all climbers who manage to reach the top!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Enjoy:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Punishing but not impossible gameplay. Practice makes perfect.<br/></li><li> No filler, every obstacle is designed with intention.<br/></li><li> Focused gameplay with no distracting elements.<br/></li><li> No violence. You can never die or get hurt. But you can lose all your progress with one mistake... perhaps that is worse.<br/></li><li> Climb, slip, fall. Over and over.<br/></li><li> Endless suffering.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>But not:</strong></h2>- Legs... You cannot use your legs for some reason.<h2 class="bb_tag">Note from developer:</h2>This game was created by one person, me (hello).This game is inspired by Getting Over it with Bennett Foddy which in itself is a homage to an even older game, Sexy Hiking by Jazzuo. I was certain that Bennett's game would spawn countless of new types of games in a similar fashion that would present unique, focused and yet simple challenges. I was disappointed to see that trend not materialize fully and so took it upon myself to make this game, hoping to contribute to the spirit of a "Foddian Type" game genre.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy Storm Shadow:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802380/Heavy_Storm_ShadowPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FwmfaDVPKSa" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/dss.png?t=1710177558"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Differences between the prologue and the full version<br/>The prologue opens up a character<br/>The prologue opens up a map</strong><br/><br/><strong>Unlock the true potential of your mech and witness its constant growth and upgrades! In deserts, ice and even satellites, kill thousands of swarms to strengthen your mech!<br/>At the end of each battle you will gain valuable resources to upgrade your mech's weapons and armor, unlocking new skills and powerful equipment.<br/>Through battles, you'll gain the bonds of your mech's pilots, forming modules in different directions to shape your unique fighting style.<br/>Grow and upgrade your mech in real time to make it more and more invincible and become the ultimate weapon against the swarm!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/1z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong>Monsters are coming at you like wave after wave, and as your mech's guns move, the monsters explode into a fog of blood and fall in pieces, painting the earth in scarlet. Operate your mech to dodge attacks, kill through the siege, and find a way to survive among hundreds of enemies!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/2z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong>Explore your own powerful combat combo by unlocking more and more powerful weapons and skills! Become stronger by killing and choosing, picking up resources, choosing the most suitable enhancements, and finally killing the terrifying bosses head-on!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/3Z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong> offers a rich arsenal of multiple primary and secondary weapons, as well as numerous skills with unique features. These weapons and skills will provide endless possibilities for your battles. In the future, there will be even more powerful mechs waiting to be harnessed by you! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4y.png?t=1710177558"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802380/extras/4z.gif?t=1710177558"><br/><strong>The game already offers 3 challenging maps, each with unique enemy combinations and powerful bosses waiting to be challenged for a completely different leveling experience. As the game continues to update, you will meet more new maps and new modes of play to make your Meat Pigeon adventure even more colorful. </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Thaumaturge</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1684350/The_Thaumaturge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Thaumaturge_accolade_616x320_steam.png?t=1709742147"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/TT_claim_EN_small.png?t=1709742147"><br/><strong>The Thaumaturge is an isometric, story-rich RPG with a unique take on turn-based combat, character development features, and investigation mechanics</strong>, facing you with morally ambiguous choices – set in a world teeming with mysterious powers and strange ethereal beings called <strong>salutors</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/City_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>The year is 1905. Warsaw lives under the yoke of imperial Russian tsardom. Its inhabitants constitute a diverse group of different ancestries, views, and beliefs with often conflicting interests: Russian soldiers, Jewish merchants, Polish townspeople, and more. Despite the circumstances, the city is a buzzing metropolis, where one can attend a breathtaking party with the high society, and later get robbed in one of the dark alleys of the Praga district. A city of great hopes and dreams on one hand and dark desires on the other.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Buka_2.gif?t=1709742147"><br/><br/>A <strong>thaumaturge</strong> bears both a gift and a burden at the same time. This parallel holds true for <strong>Wiktor Szulski</strong>, the game’s titular protagonist, who is drawn back to the tumultuous streets of 20th-century Warsaw by family matters. The gift of thaumaturgy is intertwined with family legacy, passed down through one's ancestors. This mystical inheritance significantly shapes Wiktor’s life journey tied around a pursuit of unearthly entities and their hosts. As only a thaumaturge can tame these ethereal entities - known to a select few as <strong>salutors</strong> - utilizing their mystical abilities to discover secrets hidden within the human soul and speak to the Darkness, no one understands quite like Wiktor how everyone suffers their own demons.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1684350/extras/Wiktor_3-01.gif?t=1709742147"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Shape your story</strong> – as a full-fledged RPG, it allows you to alternate your choices and make you deal with the aftermath. <br/></li><li><strong>Develop your character</strong> – creating your own version of the thaumaturge will allow you to approach situations in different ways. <br/></li><li><strong>Experience unique turn-based combat</strong> and defeat your foes using human attacks and skills as well as psychic strikes delivered by salutors.<br/></li><li><strong>Influence and manipulate</strong> the temperaments of other characters to bend their will to your liking. <br/></li><li><strong>Tame the power of salutors</strong> – use the unique set of their skills to gain an advantage while exploring the world and when bringing your adversaries to their knees. <br/></li><li><strong>See the world that’s inevitably gone</strong> – explore the uncommon, heavily researched historic period of the early XX century Warsaw, where crime and luxury are often two sides of the same coin. Meet historical figures and learn about their involvement in the story. <br/></li><li><strong>Created in Unreal Engine 5</strong> to deliver a detailed &amp; beautifully crafted world.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivaland: Dream House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2606170/Vivaland_Dream_House/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1976830</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2606170/extras/ezgif-3-474fd0310c.gif?t=1709804132"><h2 class="bb_tag">Introducing the Vivaland Prologue: Dream House</h2><strong>Build Mode: Craft Your Dreams</strong><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in one of the core game modes of Vivaland: the Build Mode. It's a sandbox where you have control over architectural and design elements, enabling you to construct and decorate a house from the ground up!<br/><br/><strong>Get to Know the First Town of Vivaland</strong><br/><br/>The town of Vivaland offers 8 residential lots, each awaiting your personal touch. Claim your slice of the town, visit your friends' properties, and collaborate on grand projects that will redefine the neighborhood.<br/><br/><strong>Seamless Single and Co-op Experience</strong><br/><br/>Begin your Vivaland adventure either as a lone explorer or with your friends by your side – the choice is yours. You can build together with up to 8 players<br/><strong>Content</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Walls Toolkit:</strong> Build with single wall, curved wall and the room tool!<br/></li><li><strong>Doors &amp; Windows:</strong> Choose entrances and views that reflect your taste.<br/></li><li><strong>Foundations, Multiple Floors, and Stairs: </strong>Build structures that rise to new heights.<br/></li><li><strong>Furniture:</strong> Design with a vast selection of interior items.<br/></li><li><strong>Roofing:</strong> Choose from 10 distinct styles and an array of roof patterns.<br/></li><li><strong>Different styles of items:</strong>  Bohemian, Retro, Victorian, Antique, Cottagecore, Gothic, Modern, Minimalist, Industrial.</li></ul><br/><strong>Functional Freedom</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Resizable Objects:</strong> Adjusting the size of decorative objects.<br/></li><li><strong>Recolorable Furniture and Decor: </strong> Fine-tune your interior design with your color palettes. Save favorite shades and match your items.<br/></li><li><strong>Room Dimension Flexibility: </strong>Tweak the height and width of your rooms.<br/></li><li><strong>Grid Function: </strong>Precise item placement is a breeze with toggleable grid support.<br/></li><li><strong>Intuitive Controls and Snapping: </strong>Seamlessly move and arrange objects.</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeeperRL</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/329970/KeeperRL/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/Peek-2018-11-28-09-43.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL is an ambitious dungeon simulator with roguelike and RPG elements. Take the role of an evil wizard and study the methods of black magic. Equip your minions and explore the world, murder innocent villagers and burn their homes. Build your dungeon, lay traps and prepare for an assault of angry heroes. <br/><br/>When you control your minions the game changes into a classic roguelike, with turn-based and very tactical combat. You can also play as an adventurer and assault dungeons made by you or other players.<h2 class="bb_tag">Dungeon management </h2>You will dig deep into the mountain and build dozens of rooms, corridors and traps. Your minions will train and produce weapons and armor. Prisoners will be tortured. You will research new technologies like alchemy, beast mutation and sorcery.<h2 class="bb_tag">Z-levels</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341">Develop your base across multiple floors by digging down into the earth or building up. Build fantastic dungeon designs or elaborate castles and towers.<h2 class="bb_tag">Roguelike mechanics </h2>The world is simulated on a very detailed level. Creatures use equipment and consumable items. There are dozens of special items, spells, attributes and special attacks. You can cut off heads and limbs and blind or poison your enemies. If you're not careful with fire, you can burn an entire forest or even your own dungeon.<h2 class="bb_tag">Large, procedurally generated maps </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/ezgif.com-animated-gif-maker__2_.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>KeeperRL features a large, procedurally generated world. Explore dozens of locations, from small cottages and shops to major enemies dwelling in castles and dungeons. Uncover secrets, bring back great loot and prisoners back to your base in order to grow in power.<h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple playable factions</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/329970/extras/gif_keepers-ezgif.com-optimize.gif?t=1709280341"><br/><br/>Play as a:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dark wizard researching black magic.<br/></li><li>White knight specialized in horses and angelic beings.<br/></li><li>Necromancer who crafts undead from the body parts of fallen enemies.<br/></li><li>Fragile colony of twelve dwarves.<br/></li><li>Goblin king searching for his lost wives.<br/></li><li>Collective of gnomes with a mechanized army.<br/></li><li>Lone adventurer focused on exploration.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Online map sharing </h2>KeeperRL offers the ability to download dungeons made by other players from Steam Workshop, and places them on your world map as enemies. See how others design their fortresses, fight with their minions, and steal their loot! After winning the game, you'll have the option to share your dungeon online as well.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Grindea</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/269770/Secrets_of_Grindea/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/269770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Secrets of Grindea</i> is an old-school Action RPG with co-op support for up to 4 players. It is a tribute to and sometimes a parody of the old SNES games so many of us grew up with and loved! Journey through fantastical lands, and battle tons of different enemies and bosses in your quest for truth, friendship and, above all, finding the world's rarest treasures!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A rich world filled with 300+ unique, colorful characters and an engaging story to drive your journey forward.<br/></li><li>Co-op support for up to four players! Enjoy the entire storyline with your friends or call someone in to help with the more difficult challenges.<br/></li><li>Customization, customization, customization - design a character that represents you, then mix and match any of the 31 spells and skills across 9 different categories.<br/></li><li>30+ epic boss fights! Overgrown slimes, giant robots, mimics - we have it all!<br/></li><li>Side content - design your own home, fish, craft items, tame pets, partake in mini-games, grow plants - there’s plenty to keep you entertained when you want a break from the main story.</li></ul><br/>And last but not least:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Arcade Mode - Separate from Story Mode, the game includes a <strong>full roguelite</strong> version where you need to battle your way to the top on a single life, building a town of your own as you progress.  How far can you get?</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/678950/DRAGON_BALL_FighterZ/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/678950/extras/GIF_DBFZ_STEAM.png?t=1709230702"><br/><br/>DRAGON BALL FighterZ is born from what makes the DRAGON BALL series so loved and famous: endless spectacular fights with its all-powerful fighters.<br/><br/>Partnering with Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ maximizes high end Anime graphics and brings easy to learn but difficult to master fighting gameplay.<br/><br/>High-end Anime Graphics<br/>Using the power of the Unreal engine and the talented team at Arc System Works, DRAGON BALL FighterZ is a visual tour-de-force.<br/><br/>3vs3 Tag/Support<br/>Build your dream team and sharpen your skills to master high-speed tag combinations.<br/><br/>Thrilling Online Features<br/>Ranked matches, interactive lobby, crazy 6-player Party Match... There is something for every taste!<br/><br/>Exclusive Story Mode<br/>Discover a never-seen-before scenario featuring Android 21, a brand new character whose creation was supervised by Akira Toriyama himself.<br/><br/>Spectacular Fights<br/>Experience aerial combos, destructible stages and famous scenes from the DRAGON BALL anime in 60FPS and 1080p resolution!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robin Hood - Sherwood Builders</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1159420/Robin_Hood__Sherwood_Builders/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fk2N3rpRuB3" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/fc521c8bf21bff775962df4f130bb74eb5577a46.png?t=1709562813"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif01.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Robin Hood - Sherwood Builders is an action-adventure RPG with base-building elements, where you take on the role of a classic hero who stands up to the tyranny and injustice that haunts Sherwood. As Robin, you’ll fight, hunt, craft, steal, and of course help the local people thrive to spite the Sheriff of Nottingham and his ruthless regime – all within an open-world environment that can be freely explored.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif02.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Robin Hood is a famous hero of medieval English folk tales, believed to have during that time roamed the forests of Sherwood with his band of loyal outlaw companions. In the game you’re going to meet those legendary characters as well, such as Lady Marian, Little John, Friar Tuck, Allan-a-Dale, and Will Scarlet. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif05.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Robin's main goal is to help a fledgling community of refugees and rebels advance and expand. Starting with what could be described as a small forest settlement, with a bit of care, hard work, and good luck, it can end up as a town full of people. Recruit local peasants, rebels on the run from the law, and even the citizens and guards of Nottingham themselves as your new outlaw settlers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif04.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>You start your adventure with building a forest camp, which can soon be expanded following the arrival of new residents. You will be responsible for properly managing the space you secured for yourself within Sherwood Forest to build up the village.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1159420/extras/gif03.gif?t=1709562813"><br/><br/>Another important part of taking care of the settlement will be to manage the community members’ professions and tasks, training them to become craftsmen, hunters, or guards, and to manage the settlement’s resources, either gathering them yourself or stealing them from convoys and noble estates.<br/><br/>As Robin's people grow large in number and strong in sword arm, an uprising in Nottingham may just become a reality, ending the Sheriff's tyranny once and for all.<br/>Can Robin Hood and his Merry Men survive and put an end to injustice? Their fate is up to you!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1709723687"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1709723687"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709723687"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1709723687"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1709723687"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1709723687"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS™: Dark Forces Remaster</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2292260/STAR_WARS_Dark_Forces_Remaster/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_8.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/><i>Star Wars</i>™: Dark Forces Remaster has been brought to life by the team at <strong>Nightdive Studios</strong>, fully remastered through its proprietary KEX engine, allowing the game to run on modern gaming devices at up to 4K resolution at 120FPS. New and returning players will enjoy <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces Remaster’s upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<br/><br/>The original 1995 <i>Star Wars</i>: Dark Forces raised the bar for FPS games, offering players a significant degree of movement and interactivity, a large selection of items and power-ups, and engaging environments. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_10.gif?t=1709278523"><br/><br/>In the first <i>Star Wars</i> FPS video game, players assume the role of Kyle Katarn, a defector of the Galactic Empire turned mercenary for hire. Katarn joins the Rebel Alliance’s covert operations division tasked with infiltrating the Galactic Empire, where he discovers the secret Dark Trooper Project. The development of this powerful new series of Imperial battle droids and power-armored stormtroopers stands to strengthen the Empire’s grip on the galaxy unless Katarn and the Rebel Alliance intervene.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>All fourteen original levels, featuring <i>Star Wars</i>™ worlds and capital ships<br/></li><li>Use your ability to jump, duck, and crawl to solve puzzles and defeat enemies<br/></li><li>Your Personal Digital Assistant provides you with in game information such including map, inventory, and mission briefing<br/></li><li>Engaging first-person ground combat featuring ten weapons and twenty types of enemies<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS visuals<br/></li><li>Advanced 3D rendering enables updated lighting and atmospheric effects<br/></li><li>Modern gamepad support adds a new weapon wheel, and rumble<br/></li><li>Controller Support - vibration and gyro controls <br/></li><li>A variety of power-ups are made available to the player, including health, shields, weapons and ammunition<br/></li><li>For combat, the player may use fists, explosive landmines and thermal detonators, as well as blasters and other ranged weapons<br/></li><li>Includes immersive environmental puzzles and mazes </li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2292260/extras/Dark_Forces_horz_1.gif?t=1709278523"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dicefolk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996430/Dicefolk/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FtN3yxBv4tq" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Join_Our_Discord_600x224.png?t=1709379465"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Dicefolk is a tactical roguelite game based on customizable dice and monster-catching mechanics. On your adventure as a Chimera Summoner, you'll meet dozens of unique and powerful creatures that you can recruit to create the perfect team.<br/><br/>Play as Alea, a young Dicefolk hero who discovers her ability to befriend Chimera and fight back against evil forces threatening humanity’s extinction.</strong></h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle_Start.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H2.png?t=1709379465"><br/>Embark on a thrilling quest to save humanity from the grasp of an evil sorcerer. Build a team from over 100 unique, hand-drawn Chimera to suit your playstyle. Unlock all the talismans to uncover the mystical secrets behind the Chimeras’ existence.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Map.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H3.png?t=1709379465"><br/>With a large variety of Chimeras to befriend and command, you'll need to strategize and adapt your playstyle to suit each battle. From tough tanks to speedy attackers, each Chimera brings a unique set of abilities to the table. Your tactical choices will determine your success in battle!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Recruiting.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H4.png?t=1709379465"><br/>It’s all up to you! Customize your dice for maximum influence over your Chimeras’ attacks and abilities. Control the order in which battles play out and choose when parties take action. Dicefolk defies RNG and gives you unprecedented influence on the roll of the dice! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Dicefolk_Battle.gif?t=1709379465"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/H5.png?t=1709379465"><br/>Each playthrough offers its own rewards, and the Chimeras you encounter in one run can be entirely different than those you find in another. With different Chimeras comes different strategies to assemble your team for the perfect run!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996430/extras/Anim_H5.gif?t=1709379465"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator: Dark Fate - Defiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1839950/Terminator_Dark_Fate__Defiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif1.gif?t=1709216510"><br/><strong>Terminator: Dark Fate – Defiance</strong> is a <strong>real-time strategy game</strong> based on the Terminator: Dark Fate universe that follows the war between humanity and Legion's synthetic intelligent machine network.<br/><br/>In the<strong> single-player campaign</strong>, you take the role of a commander in the Founders, a force made up of the remnants of the US military and guide your army in an attempt to foil Legion's plan to exterminate the last remnants of humanity. In skirmish and multiplayer modes, play as three very diverse factions: Founders, Movement and Legion.<br/><br/>Take control of an army carried over from mission to mission on a series of large strategic maps. Make decisions about unit placement, battle tactics and abilities so that you don’t just survive but can become the leader of the resistance against the machines. Hone your skills and military expertise by replaying and achieving the best possible outcomes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic battlefields: realistic tactics and consequences</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif2.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Engage in complex, realistic battles where your <strong>tactical decisions</strong> are vital to your survival and ultimate victory. Use a variety of military equipment, vehicles and ammunition types in your battles against the enemy. Recruit and train new units, assign new skills and acquire new weapons and equipment to continue the resistance.<br/><br/>Encounter tense battles. Your battlefield tactics and choices have deep consequences that will impact through the campaign, with other factions and characters either joining you or fighting against you, and with certain missions being available or not depending on your actions. <br/><br/><strong>Your resources are limited</strong> and you must protect your army. Weapons of war receive damage through a modular component damage system where armour characteristics, component malfunctions and hull structure all affect if your troops survive.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the survival of mankind</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif3.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>Recruit others to your cause and <strong>grow your army</strong>. Mix and match the composition of your troops to fit your preferred battle tactics. Use infantry units, heavy armoured military vehicles, plasma cannon technology, drones and other flying units and even human skirmishers to achieve victory.<br/><br/>Use the battlefield to your advantage! <strong>Physics-based building demolition</strong> lets you generate a realistic set of tactical consequences, especially in urban areas.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem: Skirmish and Online Battles</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif4.gif?t=1709216510"><br/>The excitement amplifies in <strong>skirmish and multiplayer modes</strong>, where <strong>you can play as three distinct factions</strong>: Founders, Movement, and Legion. <br/><br/>Engage in epic battles across vast strategic landscapes, testing your skills and military expertise. Every decision matters, impacting alliances, missions, and the overall survival of mankind.<br/><br/>Challenge your skills in skirmish and online multiplayer matches, facing off against AI or real-life human opponents in intense 1v1 and 2v2 battles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penny’s Big Breakaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1955230/Pennys_Big_Breakaway/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ready. Set. YO! - Join Penny &amp; Yo-Yo in a kinetic 3D-platformer bursting with innovative gameplay! Showcase your catalog of tricks and chain impressive combos to deliver Penny &amp; Yo-Yo's perfect breakout performance. Take the stage with this vibrant pair in Penny’s Big Breakaway.<br/><br/>Penny is a street performer with big dreams; she has her own spin on what it takes to be a star! When Eddie the Emperor calls for new Palace Court Performers, Penny gets herself tangled in an audition she’ll never forget. A strange encounter with a Cosmic String transforms Penny’s Yo-Yo into a living creature with an appetite for snacks— and mayhem! Use Yo-Yo to help Penny clear her name, outrun the Emperor’s penguin army, and unravel the mystery of the Cosmic String. <br/><br/>Burst onto the scene in the fluorescent world of Macaroon, home to this over-and-under escape! Discover your true star power in this easy-to-play, difficult-to-master challenge. Penny’s Big Breakaway is the debut title from Evening Star.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-01-Supertitles.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Key Features: <br/><br/>Walk the Dog: Yo-Yo’s big appetite will earn an even bigger reward with snack power-ups! Use these tasty treats to temporarily transform Yo-Yo, granting it the abilities to improve movement speed, protect Penny from harm, and much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-02-WalktheDog.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Around the World: Flee from Eddie the Emperor’s massive penguin army as they chase you clear across the planet! These clumsy flightless birds patrol the halls, come bursting through walls, and will stop at nothing to seize you! Help out friendly denizens along the way and make use of your spectacular surroundings to evade your capturers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-03-AroundTheWorld.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Encore Stage: Play your way with multiple game modes! Show off your skills as you chain awesome combos and rack up multipliers in Story Mode. Take on the ultimate speedrunning challenge and dominate the leaderboard in Time Attack Mode. Redeem coins for bonus items, secret stages, and more unlockable extras.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-04-EncoreStage.gif?t=1708524042"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1710160593"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708975190"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divine Journey 2: The Five Books of Moses</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2828150/Divine_Journey_2_The_Five_Books_of_Moses/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2828150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"The Five Books of Moses" serves as a compelling sequel to the acclaimed Divine Journey: The Life of Jesus. In this immersive game, players embark on a profound exploration of the foundational stories from the Bible across multiple chapters. Dive into the epic narratives of these ancient texts, experiencing the miracles, laws, and divine guidance that laid the groundwork for a nation. Engage with 13 unique types of minigames, each designed to enhance your understanding of these ancient tales.<br>
As you progress, encounter carefully selected quotes from the Bible, adding a spiritual layer to the gaming experience. Whether you're deciphering ancient texts, uncovering hidden symbolism, or solving interactive puzzles, the biblical quotes offer reflections on the profound themes explored in the game. <br>
"The Five Books of Moses" transcends traditional gaming, providing a contemplative experience that encourages players to connect with the timeless wisdom embedded in these sacred scriptures. Immerse yourself in the sacred narratives in a journey through the Bible's foundational books.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Of Pharaohs</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1515920/Tomb_Of_Pharaohs/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1515920/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Collect keys to unlock the "Pharaohs Tomb" and fight his remains to pass the level!  Dodge traps, scorpions and mummies in a procedurally generated maze with an infinite amount of levels.  Collect coins to unlock characters, upgrade them and increase rewards!  How deep into the tomb you can go?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warped Continuity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2761290/Warped_Continuity/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Warped Continuity is a puzzle platform game based on the Indie game Continuity, but it includes the ability to reverse gravity, create a block, and remove blocks in some levels.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br/>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The witch and the bottle of concepts</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2489670/The_witch_and_the_bottle_of_concepts/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The witch's mage is to pick up the broom and hit hard!</strong><br/><br/>A fantasy pixel-art Metroidvania game. With your reliable companion, discover the island and break the 4th mirror, find the truth under the meta mask!<br/><br/>Villains invade the island, and the only witch on the island has lost her memory and magic power?<br/>You'll wield your broom to swat baddies hard, and the collector in your broom will charge up your partner to cast speciality spells.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/extras/未命名.gif?t=1710225027"><br/><br/>In our fantasy pixel world, you can:<br/>Explore the entire small island with your elf companion at a seamless map, cross fields of wheat and snow, climb the library and magic tower.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/extras/未命名1.gif?t=1710225027"><br/><br/>Hit your enemies and Charge the magic power on your broom: <br/>Will you use a sword or throwing knives? Magic balls are also good! Hundreds of abilities and combinations for you to build!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/extras/IMG_202310176993_600x359.png?t=1710225027"><br/><br/>Together with the charming residents of the island, search for the secrets of the deserted island and uncover the truth behind the demon king!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2489670/extras/Sprite-0005.png?t=1710225027"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Trick: Double Blind</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254710/Death_Trick_Double_Blind/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/Header-2.gif?t=1710225911"><br/><br/>Come one, come all to Morgan’s Traveling Circus, the greatest show in America! Or it was, until its star, Hattie, disappeared. <br/><br/>Take a step back in time to the middle of the mid 20th century, as a magician and a private eye tackle the case of the missing magician. Marvel at lush pulp art visuals and an atmospheric soundtrack that harkens back to the golden days of the traveling circus! But never forget, there’s a murderous mystery afoot.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/MainStage_crazyborder_retime_1.gif?t=1710225911"><br/>Take control of two protagonists tackling the case from different perspectives: one a fellow magician and colleague of the victim, and the other a private eye grappling with a bout of amnesia. Use their unique skills and expertise to befriend and interrogate a huge cast of characters, investigate various locations, and hunt down contradictions in a winding narrative filled with twists, turns, and treachery sure to shock and delight would-be detectives and circus fans alike.<h2 class="bb_tag">Turns &amp; Action Points:</h2> With only limited actions one can take before passing time, plan carefully about which clues to pursue and which locations to investigate.<h2 class="bb_tag">Twin Perspectives:</h2> Alternate between a magician and a private eye: two different characters, with access to different information., and put the pieces together to see the bigger picture! <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/2Perspective_retime.gif?t=1710225911"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unique "Contradiction" Mechanic:</h2> Gather evidence in your collection before combining conflicting reports to create a "contradiction," then challenge the deceptions of those who would deceive a master investigator!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/Contradiction-2.gif?t=1710225911"><br/><br/>🕵️‍♂️ <strong>8</strong> fully animated characters with their own goals, histories, and motives. <br/>🎪 <strong>10</strong> gorgeous locations to investigate and revisit.<br/>🎨 <strong>50+</strong> set of CGs and <strong>300+</strong> panels of comics to bring the circus to life <br/>🔠 A sprawling and non-linear narrative to engross and enchant <br/>🎭 Different unlockable endings for each major character.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2254710/extras/Tarot-card-2.gif?t=1710225911"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254710/Death_Trick_Double_Blind/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2254710/Death_Trick_Double_Blind/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimal Escape</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782420/Minimal_Escape/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fantasy, fairy tale-like, puzzle adventure game<br>
Simple gameplay with difficult puzzles.<br>
Experience a fairy tale fantasy in a puzzle adventure game.<br>
Minimal Escape is a story about a small fairy in a fantasy world.<br>
Is the dark world you travel simply a little nightmare, or our future to come?<br>
Traverse and purify the polluted world and try to restore its former beauty.<br>
<br>
Main Features<br/>
•A mix of arcade, adventure, and puzzle<br/>
•Incorporates the laws of physics<br/>
•24 alluring and addicting stages<br/>
•Advanced puzzles that require all of your brainpower<br/>
•Exquisite 3D animation created with the Unity engine<br/>
•Offers a dreamlike, surreal experience with its highly immersive visuals and audio<br/>
•Diverse and original level designs<br/>
<br/>
How to play<br/>
•Solve complicated puzzles, and escape and survive against all sorts of obstacles<br/>
•Find hidden elements, explore paths, and collect stars<br/>
•Simple controls with directional and jump buttons that require a little bit of luck<br/>
<br/>
Minimal Escape is a top quality indie/arcade/adventure mobile game.<br/>
Listen to the echoes of the environment.<br/>
The world's fateful secrets lie before you.<br/>
Play this beautiful odyssey now!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving Mrs. Hinako</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626240/Saving_Mrs_Hinako/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Whoa... You're Kiichi, aren't ya?!"</i><br/>My next-door neighbor is none other than Hinako, the older girl who I used to know back during my childhood. All the memories from my childhood come flooding back to me. It's just as nostalgic as it is surprising.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A heartfelt visual novel<br/></li><li>Japanese voice acting</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2><br/>When Kiichi moves into a new apartment after transferring from a technical school to a university, his next-door neighbor happens to be Hinako, a former delinquent once feared by many back in their hometown.<br/><br/>Seeing Hinako is still as beautiful and cool as when they were younger digs up long-buried memories, rekindling Kiichi’s forgotten crush. However, there is one poignant difference this time around—Hinako is now a married mom!<h2 class="bb_tag">CHARACTER</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626240/extras/chara01_en.png?t=1710205238"><br/><strong>Hinako Kurose</strong><br/><i>Voice: Kazuha</i><br/>Hinako’s tumultuous journey into delinquency sprouted from cracks in her strained relationship with her father. In her late teens, she entered into a dubious relationship with her current husband and eventually married him.<br/><br/>With her unapologetically wild demeanor, she wields a tongue that could cut glass. However, beneath this rough exterior is a whole lot of heart—which tends to land her in her fair share of overly friendly situations...<br/><br/>Due to her challenging upbringing, she dreams of building a joyful and happy home.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evader</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2839310/Evader/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2839310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Move white square with the arrow keys on your keyboard to dodge red squares.<br>
<br>
This is a game used to test market for those who like challenges and easy gameplay.						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scribble</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2826650/Scribble/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2826650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Feel like a real designer and follow this strange but friendly character in this 2D, monochromatic adventure.<br>
<br>
In a fun game with fluid movement and simple, responsive controls.<br>
<br>
Venture between vertical and horizontal platforms, avoiding traps and cliffs.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exanimum: The Silent Call</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2601030/Exanimum_The_Silent_Call/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2601030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Exanimum: The Silent Call - It is a first-person indie psychological horror game.<br/><br/>The terrifying and bizzare events that happened to Jason and his daughter Jessica on the road to Greenfield town are dragging them into this eerie adventure, leading them into an unknown world. As Jason and Jessica venture deeper into the depths of the forest, an unsettling silence envelops their surroundings, the birds cease their songs, the fog thickens, and the rain intensifies. However, fear is silently approaching with every step they take, relentlessly pursuing them.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2601030/extras/ETSC.gif?t=1710179723"><br/><br/>Creepy Atmosphere: The game immerses players in a creepy atmosphere by drawing them into dark areas with realistic sound effects and graphics.<br/><br/>Psychological Tension: Players experience tension-filled moments in a journey filled with terrifying secrets and threats.<br/><br/>Fear could be approaching at any moment, providing players with constant suspense.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel Transmute</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1191660/Rebel_Transmute/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/Rebel_Transmute_Logo_Decorated_Steam.png?t=1710176486"><br/><br/>In this modern metroidvania you play as Moon Mikono, a space scrapper turned adventurer on a mission to uncover the true fate of her missing mother.<br/><br/>To accomplish this mission in your own, unique way you'll be swapping out game changing augments to suit your playstyle.  Aggressive and greedy?  Inquisitive and cautious?  Maybe you just want an army of friendly creatures!  With over 50 unique upgrades, Rebel Transmute allows you to play through a classic sci-fi adventure in YOUR style.<h2 class="bb_tag">CHALLENGING AND CUSTOMIZABLE COMBAT</h2>Use a variety of spells known as Bloodcasts, your trusty Foray-issued Blaster, and a variety of game changing Augments to take on a world of dangerous creatures and space travelers.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/16.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE AND MAP A VIBRANT SCI-FI WORLD</h2>The sprawling world of Rebel Transmute is full of stunning vistas: From vibrant greenery in the Overgrowth, to the fluorescent reefs of the Coral Fissure, to the sparkblood crystal-strewn Surface.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1191660/extras/09.gif?t=1710176486"><h2 class="bb_tag">Additional Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Encounter over <strong>80 unique enemies</strong> and over <strong>10 formidable bosses</strong>! From mutated worms and electrified beasts, to rogue AI's and gigantic bugs. All offering different and exciting challenges and interactions.<br/></li><li>Discover <strong>game-changing abilities</strong> hidden throughout the outpost.  Spin Bash, Wall Jump, and Void Dash your way across an interconnected network of tunnels, caverns, and research laboratories!<br/></li><li>Augment your playstyle with <strong>48 optional upgrades</strong> that can drastically change how you play the game.  Fight alongside a reprogrammed drone, twist your attacks into spiraling laser blasts, or even summon tentacles to block projectiles!<br/></li><li>Make use of a versatile mapping system to help track your progress.  Use custom markers, track your completion percentage, and find hidden terminals to uncover unexplored areas.<br/></li><li>Experience a <strong>personal and heartfelt story</strong>. As Moon searches for her mother she’ll also encounter various robot life, all with their own stories, personalities, and quests.<br/></li><li>A <strong>hand-painted pixel art</strong> aesthetic lends each and every character, enemy, and sector a personal touch.<br/></li><li>An immersive and atmospheric score, crafted to perfectly match every moment, from bombastic fights to solemn exploration.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 13: Taxidermy Trails</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2492740/Project_13_Taxidermy_Trails/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2492740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Project 13: Taxidermy Trails, a Walking Simulator set in a mesmerizing Taxidermy Museum. In this immersive experience, you assume the role of an kidnapped Probant forced to find a way to escape. Complete all 13 Walks to get out of this Nightmare.<br>
<br>
Your mission is clear: report any anomalies you encounter during your walks. But beware, a single misstep means starting over. Only by consistently reporting accurately will lead to the real Exit.<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
Repeating Museum Corridor: Explore a hauntingly repetitive environment, where each step could lead to discovery or deception amidst the eerie displays of taxidermy.<br>
<br/>
Over 35 Anomalies: Uncover the secrets hidden within the museum as you encounter over 35 unique anomalies. Stay very vigilant, as every detail holds significance.<br/>
<br/>
Confirmation After Each Walk: After each walk, confirm whether you experienced any anomalies. Your precision determines your progress.<br/>
<br/>
Escape on the 13th Walk: Success lies in your ability to navigate the corridors and accurately report anomalies. Reach the 13th walk unscathed, and you may find the exit.<br/>
<br/>
Variable Duration: The duration of your expedition is unpredictable, ranging from 40 minutes to "a lot longer." Sharpen your senses and hone your observation skills to expedite your journey.<br/>
<br/>
Embark on this surreal adventure where reality blurs, and your choices shape your destiny. Are you prepared to unravel the mysteries of Project 13: Taxidermy Trails and overcome the challenges that lie ahead? The museum corridors await – enter if you dare						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnGaCho Dreamy Butterfly</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810380/EnGaCho_Dreamy_Butterfly/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"EnGaCho" is an arcade-style  side-scrolling action game where you advance while defeating enemies and earning money.<br/>The main character "EnGaCho'' goes on a journey to defeat the evil nouveau riche and help the people who are suffering from poverty...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/extras/Dotto.png?t=1710173857"><h2 class="bb_tag">When you are in trouble, money will solve the problem!</h2>EnGaCho's journey will be tough. You should use the money you earn to power up EnGaCho.<br/>It is up to the player to decide whether to be aggressive or focus on durability.<h2 class="bb_tag">100 stages in total!</h2>However, that doesn't mean you have to clear everything. There are many warp zones within the stages.<br/>You can attack the final boss using the shortest route, or you can work hard to earn a score. Again, it's up to the player.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/extras/Dotto2.png?t=1710173857"><h2 class="bb_tag">tips</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Don't miss the power-up items scattered throughout the stage.<br/></li><li>Once you cleared a stage, you can play it as much as you like in Practice mode.<br/></li><li>If you save money instead of spending it, you can get more money and score.<br/></li><li>Also check out the SHOP on the title scene.<br/></li><li>Boss battles should be fought with proper countermeasures.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810380/extras/Dotto3.png?t=1710173857"><br/><br/>Make full use of all options and grab glory!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH ALL - MOUSES</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2853610/SEARCH_ALL__MOUSES/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2853610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">SEARCH ALL - MOUSES</h2> is a hidden object game in which you need to find all the mice in a large location. The mice will be located in a variety of places, from the most prominent to barely noticeable places. The entire game location looks lively because of the animation elements. Find all the mice! Don't let them go unnoticed :)<br/><br/><strong>Key Features:</strong><br/>- Animation elements on location;<br/>- 100 mice to find;<br/>- Pleasant soundtrack;<br/>- The gameplay can be interrupted at any time, and the game will automatically save the result;<br/>- Implemented hints! If you find it difficult to find an item, use the hint!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Backrooms</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1085680/True_Backrooms/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1085680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The most accurate depiction of the backrooms.</strong><br/><br/>Wander an ever growing maze in this horror themed walking simulator. Try to escape before you succumb to madness or before any monsters notice you. You might not be alone. Game length varies wildly dependent on the player, but most can expect a 20-40 minute horror experience.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/>Cool retro graphics.<br/>4:3 aspect ratio.<br/>General controller support.<br/>Unique Scares.<br/>A huge labyrinthine plane of existence.<br/><br/>Too many games miss the mark when it comes to recreating the backrooms. It should be about getting lost, losing hope, and going insane from the monotony. So I have created it. Can you reach the end of the backrooms?<br/><br/><strong>Warning: This game is designed to make you experience insanity, player discretion is advised, and the game contains some flashing lights.</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Empire</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1449550/Chinese_Empire/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1813230/Wild_West_Builder/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1813230/Wild_West_Builder/</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/addtowishlist_gif.gif?t=1710168458"><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FC5KpZ9AEex" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/discord.png?t=1710168458"/></a><br/><br/>Become the Chinese emperor and build your own, great empire! Put more developed buildings up using accessible raw materials. Plan carefully each path and buildings arrangement. Build your own great empire and make new history!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/1.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>BUILDING</strong><br/>The key to creating an economically strong empire is the skillful placement of individual buildings. Plan the location of each of them well and you will certainly use their potential effectively. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/2.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>CROPS</strong><br/>For centuries, cultivation in China has been an extremely important part of the economy. Make the best of what the local areas have to offer!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/3.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>DEVELOPMENT</strong><br/>Starting from a small village, expand your empire to colossal dimensions! Over time, build new buildings available, all the time taking care of not only economic development, but also cultural development.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/5.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>DYNAMIC LIGHTING</strong><br/>The entire production has been dressed in a realistic graphic design to reflect the charms of the lands in which we will be building our empire as much as possible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1449550/extras/4.png?t=1710168458"><br/><strong>ROAD SYSTEM</strong><br/>Thanks to a well-planned network of roads, residents will move faster, which will increase the efficiency of your economy and help keep your empire in order.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats of the Ming Dynasty</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2854690/Cats_of_the_Ming_Dynasty/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to "The Cats of the Ming Dynasty," a delightful game of finding cats. Set against the backdrop of "Along the River During the Qingming Festival," a vibrant genre painting by Qiu Ying, a Ming Dynasty Chinese painter, the game incorporates 600 hand-drawn cats, creating interesting interactions between the cats and historical scenes and characters.<br/><br/>-----Game Features-----<br/><br/>- Relax and enjoy ancient artworks.<br/>- 6 different scenic scenarios.<br/>- 600 adorable hand-drawn cats.<br/>- Comforting and relaxing music.<br/>- Cute cat sound effects.<br/>- Clicking on the game name on the cover allows you to view the complete "Along the River During the Qingming Festival."<br/>- 100 carefully crafted achievement icons.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2854690/extras/1.png?t=1710166609">.<br/><br/>------------------------						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece Link</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690960/Piece_Link/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Drag and Connect the Pieces!</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690960/extras/ezgif.com-video-to-gif.gif?t=1710165404"><br/><br/>Piece Link is a puzzle game that involves arranging blocks of various shapes to fill a playing field. The main objective of the game is to fit the blocks into a designated square so that all the blocks are used and there are no empty spaces. This requires strategic placement of the differently shaped pieces into a grid, aiming to form a complete square without any holes. The game is designed to be both entertaining and educational, challenging players' problem-solving skills and spatial reasoning.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUSFASLEX</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2769380/JUSFASLEX/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2769380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							13 years ago, a man named Joann decided he would bring God back into our world. He couldn't succeed, but his idea lives on through Theodore, an aloof dreamer who's trying to create a utopian society in a new world.<br/><br/>JUSFASLEX is a story about a boy's struggle to stay himself and get along with the new inhabitants of his dimension: Emma, a spirited redhead older than him, and Rebecca, a charming, reserved girl who likes being alone just like him.<br/><br/><strong>Game features:</strong><br/>- Short kinetic story<br/>- The atmosphere of a Victorian manor house<br/>- Ukrainian voice acting						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Road of Heroes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2724960/The_Road_of_Heroes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Hero's Path, a concise hero development system. Every battle offers a unique character development opportunity. With attribute points in hand, you can freely decide which attribute to enhance. With skill points available, you have the freedom to choose which skill to learn or improve.<br/><br/>Skill System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage1.png?t=1710160933"><br/>You are free to decide which skill to prioritize learning or which abilities to enhance when upgrading skills.<br/><br/>Attribute System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage2.png?t=1710160933"><br/>The attribute column on the right allows you to freely choose which attribute to enhance when you have attribute points.<br/><br/>Shop System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage3.png?t=1710160933"><br/>After obtaining gold during battles, you can purchase beneficial BUFFs at the Pig Merchant.<br/><br/>Equipment Crafting System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage4.png?t=1710160933"><br/>When you are in battle, you will obtain 'Molds,' 'Materials,' and 'BOSS Drop Materials.' Only when you have all three types of materials can you craft equipment. Each material has different attributes, and crafting equipment will combine the attributes of the three materials into one piece of equipment.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage5.png?t=1710160933"><br/><br/>Equipment System<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2724960/extras/Eimage6.png?t=1710160933"><br/>When you craft and equip gear, the attributes of the equipment take effect in the combat scenes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FROM ASHES, BLOOM</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2335130/FROM_ASHES_BLOOM/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335130/extras/fab_gameplay.png?t=1710160338"><br/><br/>🌵 <strong>Protect</strong> the oldest tree on Earth from Humanity<br/>🍀 <strong>Tear</strong> through hordes of enemies<br/>🌷 <strong>Sow</strong> trees to help you<br/>🌴 <strong>Active</strong> Tower Defense rogue-like gameplay<br/>🌻 <strong>Personalize</strong> your creature with new attacks<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2335130/extras/fab_features.png?t=1710160338"><br/><br/>🌿 <strong>Huge</strong> amount of upgrades<br/>🏭 <strong>Various</strong> of starting situation with unique skins<br/>👾 A never seen before character with <strong>10/10 procedural animation</strong><br/>😇 Play as an <strong>invincible</strong> mass destruction weapon						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTRL Phreak</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1679360/CTRL_Phreak/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1679360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore a vast network of stolen data, encrypted chatrooms, and backdoor connections as you traverse a shrouded corner of the web only the most elite hackers are able to access. At the end of it all lies The Mainframe, the highest security target known to hacker-kind. You will play as a scrappy hacker penetrating the Deep Web in search of The Mainframe.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1679360/extras/NodeNetNav.gif?t=1710159105"><br/><br/>Grow more powerful to become the LEET H4X0R you were always meant to be: download RAM, discover Keywords, and buy upgrades from the shadowy hacker known as "D34L3R". Fight elite hacker bosses to reach Access Points to deeper levels of the Web.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1679360/extras/Boss.gif?t=1710159105"><br/><br/>Engage in high-octane, keyboard-mashing, hacker-to-hacker combat. Make choices that matter via a retro cyber terminal interface. Can you reach the bottom of the Internet and achieve immortal hacker glory?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1679360/extras/TerminalChatter.gif?t=1710159105"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboSync</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2761130/RoboSync/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/withlist-follow.gif?t=1710161592"> <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FAdZF7EAUC6" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/Join_our_discord.png?t=1710161592"/></a><br/>RoboSync is an immersive puzzle game that puts your logical thinking skills and precision to the test.<br/><br/>In each level, you'll find robots moving in unsynchronized patterns. Your mission? Time the release and blockage of passages just right, coordinating your robots' movements to unlock all the locks simultaneously. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/clip_lvl2-shorter.gif?t=1710161592"><br/><br/>It's crucial to carefully consider every move, executing commands precisely to achieve flawless synchronization. With progressively challenging levels, the game introduces new mechanics to keep the experience engaging.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/Clip_lvl6.gif?t=1710161592"><br/><br/>Solve the challenges swiftly to earn the coveted 3 stars and attain impeccable synchronization for a special medal in each level. Get ready for an exhilarating journey where your mental agility will be constantly challenged."<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2761130/extras/clip_lvl14.gif?t=1710161592"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2689880/Cyber_Story/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2689880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							CyberStory is a cyberbullying intervention game designed to empower players with effective coping strategies. Set in a digital landscape, players navigate challenging scenarios and situations, gaining insights into the complexities of cyberbullying. Through interactive narratives, engaging challenges, and decision-making scenarios, CyberStory provides a safe and supportive environment for players to enhance their coping skills.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Shooter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2843970/Monster_Shooter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2843970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an epic intergalactic battle in "Monster Shooter." This thrilling third-person shooter immerses you in the role of humanity's last hope. Face off against the Roncosferas, voracious aliens originating from the distant planet Ronclumen, on a critical mission to protect the military base and precious resources of the planet Hoperium.<br>
<br>
Take control of a brave space soldier, armed to the teeth with advanced technology. Face endless waves of enemies in a fight for survival, using strategy, skill and an impressive arsenal. Every point adds up in your quest to defend every vital part of the facility, as humanity waits with hope in the balance.<br>
<br>
 The destiny of humanity is in your hands. Accept the challenge, become the last line of defense and defend the future of civilization against the relentless Roncospheres. The planet is counting on you!						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screen Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827410/Screen_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2827410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
<strong>This screen effect program is a software that provides a visually unique and exciting experience.</strong><br/>These programs use graphic elements to provide a visually appealing experience for users.<br/><br/>Following features are supporting now:<br/>1. Twinkle Visual Effect<br/>2. Fire Visual Effect<br/>3. Impact Visual Effect (with Click)<br/>4. 3D sphere Test						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yumpgril</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2835610/Yumpgril/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2835610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Yumpgril is a challenging precision platformer also known as a rage game. Inspired by various rage games that came before Yumpgril is designed to be brutally difficult and punishing.<br>
<br>
*Brutally difficult<br>
*Simple mechanics<br>
*No hand-holding<br>
*No checkpoints<br>
*Very punishing						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suramon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2721300/Suramon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2721300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Explore an open world filled with wild slime monsters. Battle slimes to capture their DNA in cubes, use them for crafting along your adventure. Return home and expand your farm. Plant crops and earn precious gold. Meet the locals and befriend them, giving gifts to earn their love. This is Suramon.</strong><br/><br/>This genre-blending game puts a focus on capturing Slime Cubes, rather than the monsters themselves in typical monster capture games. After inheriting a farm from your uncle and moving to a mysterious valley, the player discovers a world that is filled with colorful slime creatures called Suramon. These creatures roam free and play a part in the day-to-day life in this world. Players will run their farm and try to make a living while exploring the region and fighting the 100 different breeds of slime monsters that wander the land. Each slain Suramon drops a Suramon Cube: a highly sought after element. Each Cube is made up of the organic slime material for each slime, and will differ in color and style to the creature it comes from.<br/><br/>Once the player becomes a Suramon Scout, they will be tasked with collecting the different Cubes for a research lab so they can be used for further scientific discoveries. They will also be tasked with filling their SuraDex: an encyclopedia of all the Suramon that call the region home. Players will quickly learn of a mysterious and shadowy organization called Fuchsia Corp. An organization that wants to capture all of the Suramon for themselves, and use them for devastating purposes. Can the player stop them before it's too late?<br/><br/>Explore a vibrant world filled with colorful slime creatures and colorful villagers who want to get to know you. Battle the Suramon slime monsters and collect Cubes. Grow your farm and renovate your farmhouse. Befriend and gift the local villagers to grow your friendship with them. Fall in love with different romance options and get married. And don't forget to eat and drink to survive! The world of Suramon awaits.<br/><br/><strong>Features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore a large open world.<br/></li><li>Capture slime cubes from monsters and use them to craft.<br/></li><li>Plant seeds, water crops, and pick them when they are ready.<br/></li><li>Time system with passing time and color change as the day passes.<br/></li><li>Mining system with a button mash mini-game. Mine for gold, jewels, and more.<br/></li><li>Play 3 different mini-games in the casino including slots and card games. <br/></li><li>Solve a conspiracy and stop an evil threat.<br/></li><li>Peaceful and soothing soundtrack with a medieval flare.<br/></li><li>Form relationships with NPCs and give them gifts.<br/></li><li>Romance NPCs and get married.<br/></li><li>Expand and renovate your farm, unlocking new equipment.<br/></li><li>Sandbox style gameplay with freedom to explore as you wish.<br/></li><li>Steam Deck support.<br/></li><li>Steam cloud save support.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antipaint</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1418390/Antipaint/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">A Paint-tastic Adventure!</h2><strong>Embark on a quest to become the greatest artist in the world.</strong><br/>The battlefield is your canvas, the enemies are your paint. Literally. The art you make is yours to keep.<h2 class="bb_tag">Paint or Slay Your Way</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/extras/brush_previews.gif?t=1710144089"><br/>Choose from a variety of brushes and characters. From a slow and steady thick brush to a quick and nimble paint roller - we've got you covered.<h2 class="bb_tag">Even The Best Painter Needs A Helping Hand</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/extras/item_previews.gif?t=1710144089"><br/>Finishing a painting rewards you with versatile items. Enlist the help of a friendly painting bucket, install some paint turrets, give your enemies moustaches or become a robot. Find a way to express your true self!<h2 class="bb_tag">Face The Great Works Of Art</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/extras/boss_preview.png?t=1710144089"><br/>You can't be the greatest if there's other art out there. You'll have to defeat various (and dubious) works of art to secure your title.<h2 class="bb_tag">Art to Remember</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1418390/extras/Gallery_Final.gif?t=1710144089"><br/>After the paint has settled and the brushes are cleaned, why not take a step back and admire your masterpieces in the gallery.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of a Wish</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2302080/Death_of_a_Wish/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/DeathWishHeader.gif?t=1710183750"><br/><strong>Death of a Wish</strong> is a vicious action-RPG where <strong>style is salvation</strong>. <br/><br/>Play as Christian as he unites with new comrades to challenge the cult that raised him. By taking down the four Sanctum Faiths: Father, Sister, Cardinal, and Priest, they will upend the order of the world.<br/><br/>Fight your way through a nightmare filled with horrifying monsters and terrifying people. Master brutal attacks and flashy combos as you struggle against the Corruption consuming you with style and grace. Shine your light in this surreal sea of darkness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/keydetails2.png?t=1710183750"><h2 class="bb_tag">ENGAGE IN VICIOUSLY GRACEFUL COMBAT</h2>Unleash Christian’s cursed powers in a demanding and rewarding combat system. Be careful not to succumb to the ever-encroaching Corruption; achieve high ranks in combat and perform graceful combos to hold the Corruption at bay.<h2 class="bb_tag">CUSTOMIZE YOUR MARKED POWERS</h2>Rend your foes asunder with magical combos called Arias. Enhance your abilities with powerful Virtues that alter your approach to battle and the rhythm of combat. With a limitless array of ways to fight stylishly, build your character with passion to destroy your foes.<h2 class="bb_tag">DESCEND INTO THE NIGHTMARE</h2>In the dreamworld of Paradiso, repressed memories and unspeakable feelings come to life as the nightmarish city of Neo-Sanctum. Delve into the secret underworld of the esoteric and abandoned to meet new comrades who will aid you on your journey.<h2 class="bb_tag">SURREAL AND SPECTACULAR</h2>Christian’s world is rendered with a surreal aesthetic like no other. Harsh, pulsating scratches upon a sea of darkness render a thick atmosphere brooding with emotion. Battles come to life in an animated spectacle of light and motion that remains easy to parse in play. <br/><br/>For audio, Nicolo Telesca’s chilling score mixes electronic sounds with live instrumentation and complements the visuals by eliciting feelings of tense anxiety and electrifying catharsis.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/discord2.png?t=1710183750"><br/>Join the official Discord at <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FvJ7JnsAMcK" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/vJ7JnsAMcK</a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2302080/extras/ezgif-4-1c4b73cf2b.gif?t=1710183750"><br/><br/><i>Game contains imagery that may be harmful to players with photosensitive epilepsy or similar conditions. See content warnings below. </i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paragon Pioneers 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2454420/Paragon_Pioneers_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2454420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>» Embark on a Grand Adventure with Paragon Pioneers 2! «</strong></h2>Dive into the captivating world of <strong>Paragon Pioneers 2</strong>, an engaging <strong>city-building idle game</strong> filled with extensive content promising months of immersive gameplay. Discover and conquer customizable islands, carefully shaping your empire to satisfy the needs of your citizens. <strong>Even with limited playtime</strong>, you can delve deep into this simulation, experimenting with various strategies to enhance your realm. Build a magnificent palace and establish your legacy as the most renowned leader in Paragon's history!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>» What Can You Expect? «</strong></h2><strong>BUILD</strong> your empire with over 300 diverse buildings.<br/><strong>PRODUCE</strong> more than 130 goods with intricate production chains.<br/><strong>RESEARCH</strong> over 200 unique perks to tailor your playstyle.<br/><strong>EXPLORE</strong> three distinct regions, each offering unique challenges.<br/><strong>CONQUER</strong> islands using an intuitive and multifaceted combat system.<br/><strong>IMMERSE</strong> yourself in easy-to-learn gameplay, free from ads and online requirements.<br/><strong>RELAX</strong> knowing your empire grows, even when you're not actively playing.<br/><strong>OBSERVE</strong> your scurrying inhabitants in a charming medieval/fantasy world.<br/><strong>SHAPE</strong> every island with a unique map generator to suit your needs.<br/><strong>ADAPT</strong> the game’s difficulty to your preferred play style.<br/><strong>ENJOY</strong> extensive replayability with powerful custodians that grant unique abilities.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>» What’s New in the Sequel? «</strong></h2><strong>NEW MAJOR FEATURES</strong> – Introducing a diverse research system featuring over 200 unique perks that significantly influence gameplay. Explore three distinct regions, each with its own mechanics and exclusive production chains. Tailor your adventure with customizable difficulty levels.<br/><br/><strong>DOUBLE THE CONTENT</strong> – Your islands now have rivers and you can build water mills. Encounter more than double the number of buildings, goods, and units than before. Delve into even more complex production chains for optimization. Boost your crop and livestock production with support buildings as technology advances.<br/><br/><strong>GRAPHICAL OVERHAUL</strong> – Witness the scurrying activity of inhabitants transporting goods and ships docking at islands, all enhanced by dynamic water visuals and more vivid graphics.<br/><br/><strong>IMPROVED INTERFACE</strong> – The menu structure has been refined, and additional shortcuts introduced, ensuring seamless navigation. Trading routes have also been simplified, making their management more intuitive than ever.<br/><br/><strong>ENHANCED PRESTIGE MECHANIC</strong> – Construct your palaces more progressively with new challenges and a focus on long-term happiness of your inhabitants. A new reputation system offers greater freedom in custodian selections.<br/><br/><strong>AND MUCH MORE</strong> – Enjoy numerous quality of life improvements inspired by the awesome Discord community for a smoother gameplay experience. Expect enhanced stability, more device adjustment options and much more…<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>» Thank you for playing Paragon Pioneers 2! «</strong> ❤️</h2>My passion project <strong>Paragon Pioneers 2</strong> is very special for me as it continues my dream of being a game developer. It makes me really happy when my creations bring joy to others and I invite you to join this journey and share your experiences with me :)<br/><br/>Happy Building!<br/><br/>👋 Tobias						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reversi Temple</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2855830/Reversi_Temple/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Play the original Reversi game or play with the Othello starting positions in this highly-acclaimed strategy board game. The rules are simple, but the game is hard to master.<br/><br/>Reversi a strategy board game that involves two players, played on an 8×8 uncheckered board. Play against an AI player with 3 levels of difficulty (Easy, Medium, Hard).<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855830/extras/reversi-gameplay.gif?t=1710140431"><br/><br/>Enjoy the charms of LoFi music whilst you play in various temple-like locations.<br/><br/>Be able to create a giant board to play on, or maticuliously place pieces to roleplay matches or end games.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2855830/extras/reversi-zoom-out.gif?t=1710140431"><br/><br/>Play 2 player local multiplayer with your friends or family. Rather than setting up a physical board, quickly play on your computer with Reversi Temple.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Shadow</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789280/My_Shadow/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Mind can sometimes be too imaginative. While you tuck yourself into your bed and turn the lights off, the creatures of the night begin to appear. As you hide under your bedsheet, they surround you. As you begin to drift away, they take you, down, deep into the depths, of your mind...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789280/extras/SurroundingHands-ezgif.com-crop.gif?t=1710163289"><br/><br/>Welcome to the hauntingly surreal realm of My Shadow, a mesmerizing 2.5D Horror Puzzle Platformer that thrusts players into the enigmatic depths where reality and imagination intertwine. As the night descends, a mysterious world materializes, inviting you to embark on an otherworldly journey through the intricate labyrinth of your own mind. <br/><br/>Traverse the intricacies of the distorted dollhouse, solving puzzles that gradually unveil the truth about your innermost demons.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trash Horror Collection 4</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2846790/Trash_Horror_Collection_4/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/logo_page_steam_trash4.png?t=1710109556"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/c2.png?t=1710109556"><br/><br/>We present a true trash horror experience from the 80s, the golden age of VHS tapes. There are 7 short horror games inspired by the American series "Tales from the crypt", with cult horror and a touch of comedy.<br/><br/><strong>STORY MODE:</strong><br/><br/>Unlike the other collections, in this one we bring a "story mode", which brings together all 7 games in a new bizarre and bloody story.<br/>If you have already played a game, you can skip it and continue with the story mode.<br/><br/><strong>GAMES INCLUDED:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> DEER </li></ul>Samuell lives isolated in his house on the edge of a lake, his great passion is hunting deer. But he will realize that everything he sowed... he will reap now!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/deer02.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Poop Killer 7 </li></ul>A bathroom supply store owner will have to challenge the poop killer to survive. Facing deadly challenges to retrieve the infinite shit jewels.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/peRYlF.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Poop Killer 8 </li></ul>A few years after the Poop Killer's attack on a VHS tape rental store, shitting is officially prohibited.<br/>Alex is on his first night shift at the VHS store, he agreed to work over Christmas because he needed some extra money.<br/>After an inevitable mix-up, the feared poop killer dons a Santa suit for his shit attack.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/poop8_1.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Hello, I came to kill you </li></ul>Lincoln is a single boy and decides to venture online and look for a girlfriend.Yes, he finds a beautiful girlfriend... crazy and psychotic.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/hello02.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Community </li></ul>Marky is a young man who is running from the police, he decides to move to an isolated place with few neighbors.<br/>After moving to a small community, he discovers that his new neighbors are not very normal.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/communitygif_01.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> The lights went out </li></ul>Your car breaks down on an empty and dark road, you look for help... perhaps your only option is to knock on the door of a sinister house isolated from everything.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/thl.png?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Meat </li></ul>After his father's death, Jerry and his brother Cris take care of the restaurant that was their father's great passion. To prevent the restaurant from going bankrupt, they decide to do terrible things.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/meat2.gif?t=1710109556"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2846790/extras/c1.png?t=1710109556"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IIslands of War</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1162470/IIslands_of_War/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=http%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fc3NQd47" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/discord.png?t=1710075461"/></a><br/><br/>Build and battle floating islands in the skies! Fly around the realms of a shattered world and interact with an assortment of islands and factions! Battle procedurally generated enemies, sometimes even more than one at a time!<h2 class="bb_tag">Build</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/editing_small.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>Build your powerful island from loads of blocks and attachments with the island editor. Place your blocks to form your base island, then load up on weapons, shields, reactors, batteries and so much more to try and give yourself the best advantage in combat. Assign weapons and modules to any keybind you desire, all configurable from the super easy to use editor.<h2 class="bb_tag">Fight</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/missile.gif?t=1710075461"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/mortar.gif?t=1710075461"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/laser.gif?t=1710075461"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/ramming.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>As the saying goes, there's more than one way to blow up a floating island! Take out all their floatrons to make them fall out of the sky or destroy their warp core and watch their island explode in a fiery inferno!<h2 class="bb_tag">Explore</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/warp_gate.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>Explore a vast realm, with factions, cities, and pirates! Find abandoned regions and grab some free loot, or a merchant with powerful items to sell! Encounter different enemy classes, with a variety of strengths and weaknesses! Every island is procedurally generated, so each encounter will be unique!<h2 class="bb_tag">Loot</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/loot_collection.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>Collect items to maximize your island's potential! Forge items together to upgrade them from the bronze tier to the crystal tier!  Every single item has the potential to be unique, and almost every property can be upgraded by tech. Infuse tech into items to give them cool buffs like damage penetration, increased health, or reduced cooldowns!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1162470/extras/items.gif?t=1710075461"><br/>With over 150 items, and with over 50 item properties and behaviors, the possibilities are endless!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
