<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711032993"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1710945887"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1710945887"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1710945887"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the Park Baseball 25</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2384620/Out_of_the_Park_Baseball_25/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_banner_1.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/>We are incredibly excited to announce <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong> - the special 25th Anniversary edition of our award-winning baseball strategy series. Can you believe it's been a quarter of a century? Out of the Park Baseball is not just a game - it's a legacy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_henry.png?t=1710574531"><br/><br/>If it happens in real baseball, it happens in Out of the Park Baseball! Discover new talent, draft the next superstar, negotiate with free agents, enter trade talks with other teams, build your dynasty and guide a franchise into an infinite future! As a manager, dive into the more hands-on management and set your team's lineups, pitching staffs, in-game strategy and call the shots from the dugout. You can oversee your league at a high level, or play out each game in the gorgeous 3D game mode, managing play by play or even pitch by pitch. OOTP has it all covered!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/store_text_badge.png?t=1710574531"><br/>Here are just a few of the new features coming to <strong>Out of the Park Baseball 25</strong>:<br/><br/><strong>A game-changing new Player Development Lab!</strong><br/><br/>Shape the future of your upcoming stars! You can channel your inner Player Development Director like never before. A modern new Player Development Lab is here for every team that allows you to give players individual programs to work on, developing them how you like. Do you want your hitter to work on improving their baserunning? Bunting? Contact? Would you prefer your pitcher to work on building up their stamina? Developing a new pitch? Velocity? It's all up to you - for each of your upcoming future stars!<br/><br/><strong>Massive Player Ratings and AI Upgrade!</strong><br/><br/>It’s the most comprehensive player ratings upgrade in the 25 year history of Out of the Park Baseball! Batting, Pitching, and Fielding ratings have been painstakingly modified to capture the essence of baseball, with modifications to Contact and Power for hitters, Movement and Stuff for pitchers, the addition of Catcher Framing and Stealing Aggressiveness, and much more. BABIP is now front and center for hitters and hurlers, while new internal ratings updates allow for even more flexibility for Commissioners around the world to adjust the game to their detailed delight. Plus, the AI throughout the game has been improved dramatically to deliver the most challenging OOTP experience ever! <br/><br/><strong>Even More Detailed Player Development Control!</strong><br/><br/>Delegate how each and every player on your team will spend their time day in, day out with coaches at practice. Want your power hitter to worry less about avoiding strikeouts and put that time and effort into working on his home run swing instead? Want your aging starter to spend more time practicing his control instead of spending that time worrying about his stuff? By allocating their time and focus to the areas you want, over time you can influence how players develop, maintain their skillset, and fight the aging curve.<br/><br/><strong>2024 Rosters and Rules!</strong><br/><br/>As always, Out of the Park Baseball features up-to-the-minute 2024 MLB rosters that get updated all season long, with every franchise represented from its big league club all the way down to the low minors, and everywhere in between! Plus, OOTP 25 features officially licensed leagues from South Korea (KBO) and Europe.<br/><br/><strong>Improved Historical MLB Modes!</strong><br/><br/>Set up historical MLB games in an all new streamlined way - and benefit from vastly improved historical player ratings! It’s never been faster or easier to experience the entire history of Major League Baseball, now producing even more realistic outcomes thanks to those comprehensive ratings and simulation engine upgrades.<br/><br/><strong>New Retro Visual Immersion!</strong><br/><br/>Watch games with a variety of experiences, including retro-style black and white, ‘50s-era, and ‘70s-era television presentations. Choose from all of these to play games, watch highlights, or just catch a ballgame from a bygone era!<br/><br/><strong>New Licensed Leagues!</strong><br/><br/>For the first time ever, Out of the Park Baseball features an officially licensed Honkbal Hoofdklasse league from The Netherlands and the British Baseball Federation from the United Kingdom! Look for their official clubs, players, competitions, and more!<br/><br/><strong>For the first time ever - an official partnership with the Baseball Hall of Fame!</strong><br/><br/>What happens when you combine the only game that has the entire history of baseball and the the greatest Hall of Fame in sports? An incredible, year-long journey! Join us as we partner with the Baseball Hall of Fame all season - and beyond. Explore Hall of Fame Plaques, with the official, accurate text for each Hall of Famer. Discover incredible Hall of Fame artifacts, curated and released in fun "exhibits" over the course of the season in concert with the Hall - and more surprises too. It's going to be amazing! <br/><br/><strong>Dozens of upgrades big and small!</strong><br/><br/>--&gt; Updated in-game engine base advancement and camera movements<br/>--&gt; A new manager decision history screen gives you a look back on your best and worst trades and transactions<br/>--&gt; Improved trade packages for prospect packages <br/>--&gt; Updated two-way functionality with injured players<br/>And much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2384620/extras/pt_store_text_banner2.jpg?t=1710574531"><br/><br/><strong>Perfect Team is back - bigger than ever!</strong><br/><br/>It’s an all-new Perfect Team! There’s nothing in the world like the incredible online competitions of Perfect Team. Featuring by far the largest player pool ever, and taking advantage of all the player rating and balance upgrades, this year’s Perfect Team is a whole new ballgame.<br/><br/><strong>Brand New Perfect Team Combinator Series Cards!</strong><br/><br/>Pulled non-live cards have a chance to be a special Combinator Series version of the card! Use other cards that share a link (for example being teammates) with the player to get a chance to boost the raw ratings of the Combinator Series card.<br/><br/><strong>A Perfect Team Tournament Roster Builder!</strong><br/><br/>Want to design rosters for the incredible array of Perfect Team Tournaments - all on your own? For the first time ever, Perfect Team will feature a Tournament Sandbox! You can tinker to your heart's content with varying rosters for every type of tournament, with no pressure. This long-requested feature makes its debut in Out of the Park Baseball 25!<br/><br/>In addition to the brand-new Tournament Roster Builder and Combinator Series, Perfect Team 25 also features:<br/><br/><strong>Team Chemistry</strong> - Players who played together in real life will get extra bonuses when on your roster together. Players gain bonuses for seasons they played together, as well as simply being part of the same team or from the same decades<br/><strong>Perfect Team competitions starting on the first day</strong>, including a huge Opening Weekend of Tournaments with big prizes and Perfect Team Championship Series qualifying from Day One! <br/><strong>New content all season long - and beyond!</strong> All new programs, missions, competitions, and excitement await you every day.<br/><br/>Out of the Park Baseball 25 runs on PC/Mac and features the American League and National League logos, the World Series trophy, official logos and jerseys for all 30 MLB teams and 15 KBO teams, over 150 Minor League Baseball league and team logos, and historical MLB logos.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skelethrone: The Prey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2139870/Skelethrone_The_Prey/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Wishlist_Follow_ENG.gif?t=1710431377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/About_the_Game_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>You're in for a great adventure inspired by games like Castlevania and Dark Souls.  Bloodthirsty monsters, divine creatures and epic boss battles. The game’s story is shaped by  choices that will define your journey.<br/><br/><strong>PROLOGUE KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Metroidvania</strong> - Unlock unique upgrades for movement and combat to expand the world. Maintaining the game's progression requires you to use different relics, items and abilities.<br/></li><li><strong>Challenging bosses</strong> - Test your skills against multiple bosses and other creatures from the Dark Ages. The game will constantly test your patience as you face challenging battles that require their own unique approach..<br/></li><li><strong>Exploration</strong> - The game features a huge world represented by a variety of hand-crafted levels. From fog-shrouded ruins, where undead corpses cling to any living being passing by, and shambling figures emerge. To the Sun-city that hides in the labyrinthine of an ancient tomb where an unspeakable evil lingers, long forgotten by mankind.</li></ul><br/><strong>AVAILABLE IN FULL GAME:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Weapons and Equipment</strong> – Your character can be armed with bows, scythes, longswords, whips, pistols, rifles, and many more traditional weapons. More exotic weapons will also be available to you, so use any means to achieve success.<br/></li><li><strong>Multiple Endings</strong> – Make key decisions along the way to determine Ericona's fate as you progress through the story.<br/></li><li><strong>Non-linear exploration</strong> – Play through levels and bosses, discover side areas with more secrets and enemies to defeat.<br/></li><li><strong>Combat galore</strong> - You must use an ever-expanding arsenal of weapons and equipment to repel  a wide variety of enemies. Put your courage, skills, and resolve on display for them.</li></ul><br/>"Skelethrone: The Prey" is a free prequel to the main game, setting the stage for the events that will unfold throughout Skelethrone's main campaign.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/Story_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"><br/>The story takes place a few decades before the events of the game's main campaign. Assume the role of Derek Ericona, a lord who escaped the persecution is now trying to get to the borders of the neighboring kingdom to resist the tyranny of Queen Aurora, but he is being chased and faces an uphill battle. Prepare all your skills to overcome all the obstacles and difficulties prepared for our hero. And now the hunt is on!<br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2F89UKE37PuC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2139870/extras/join_the_comunity_628_x_182_bright.gif?t=1710431377"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Shire: Room One</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2517850/Toy_Shire_Room_One/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FkhSxB2MSgD" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/Toy_Shire_-_Discord_Banner.png?t=1710352808"/></a><br/><br/><br/>Play through the <strong>three levels in Kevin's Room</strong> and defend your room against your old toys. Face Memphis-X in the final level and put a stop to his assault as he crushes your soldiers in an attempt to get to your base.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyVengeance.png?t=1710352808"><br/>You received new toys from your family. Isn't that lovely? Oh, it's for sure... <br/>Your old toys, though, aren't getting along as well. They are no longer cared for and have been forgotten. So what follows next? They're going to join together against you and assault your brand-new toys, so be prepared. But never worry! You're in luck since your brand-new toys are troops of green soldiers. They still require your aid though! Control, strengthen, and defeat the opposing forces! However, focus with care, the enemies you encounter might not be your old playthings!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/InteractiveTowerDefense.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Tower building alone won't be sufficient to repel incoming attackers. Build up your own troops in the best feasible positions, then unleash attacks into enemy territory. Never abandon your towers, and deploy your troops in accordance with the traits of the enemy. First, the attacking forces will attempt to get past your defenses. Build and improve towers to aid your army. By using unique abilities, you can support your troops and towers as well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1710352808"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/EpicBattles.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Safeguard your base against waves of attackers. You need to pick the right troops if you would like to prevail. Clean the paths and guard any open routes. Upgrade your troops and unlock new ones to take down the waves and claim victory.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/ToyRealm.png?t=1710352808"><br/>Enter a world and a narrative built around the toys that enriched your youth, including toy soldiers, dinosaur sets, robots, building blocks, and more.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2517850/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1710352808"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2235020/Contra_Operation_Galuga/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2235020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!<br>
<br>
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!<br>
<br>
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now!<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br/>
•The original run-'n'-gun game is back, reimagined and more action-packed than ever!<br/>
•Attack aggressively across eight explosive stages! Infiltrate the jungle, ascend the waterfall, speed through an enemy base on a hovercycle, and more!<br/>
•Multiple playable characters with distinct abilities!<br/>
•Epic, screen-filling boss battles!<br/>
•New and fan-favorite weapons, now with stackable upgrades and incredible Overload abilities!<br/>
•Multiple difficulty options and a wealth of extra content						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchors Blockade Zone:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2819850/Anchors_Blockade_ZonePrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FPZHEvJTz65" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/dss.png?t=1710768496"/></a><br/><br/><strong>Difference between Prologue and Official Edition<br/>Prologue opens up a map</strong><br/><strong>Anchor: Blockade Zone game, is a collection of gun modification, exploring the map, death drop equipment of the Cthulhu theme 2D pixel style shooter. The game puts you in the role of an agent who enters a blockade zone to investigate with the aim of finding out the cause of the strange events in the blockade zone. Your character is trapped in the blockade and has to search for food, water and other supplies in order to survive, as well as completing quests to gather information and find the truth. In the process, don't be too surprised to encounter anything unnatural, whether it's going back in time or to the future. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/1y.png?t=1710768496"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/战斗.gif?t=1710768496"><br/><strong>Experience exhilarating shooting, fight sworn battles with hostile agents, Kraken monsters, and more, and beat the truth out of the world with the weapons in your hands! Poor for tactical penetration, rich for fire coverage, it's all up to you! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/2y.png?t=1710768496"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/改枪.gif?t=1710768496"><br/><strong>We strive to make you feel the thrill of 2d shooting, so that you can feel the real shooting experience.<br/>Up to hundreds of gun accessories, allowing you to freely remodel your exclusive weapon! </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/3y.png?t=1710768496"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/仓库.gif?t=1710768496"><br/><strong>Recruit agents for your exploration operations and train them to grow into excellent agents to help you complete various missions and search various maps.<br/>Each exploration map is a repeated horizontal jump across the edge of life and death for agents, with different maps having different chances of resulting in an agent's outright death. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/4y.png?t=1710768496"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2819850/extras/搜索.gif?t=1710768496"><br/>Explore the map carefully and make sure your agent gets back to base safe and sound every time.<br/><strong>If an agent is unlucky enough to die or return to the city with serious injuries, the items he is carrying and searching for will be dropped with him. Only items placed in the safe will be retained. </strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon's Dogma 2 Character Creator &amp; Storage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674810/Dragons_Dogma_2_Character_Creator__Storage/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare for your grand adventure, Arisen!<br>
<br>
In this app, you can create your characters for Dragon's Dogma 2. Customize the looks of your main character, the Arisen, and the looks and inclination of your companion, your Main Pawn. You can store up to 5 characters of each, the Arisen and your Main Pawn respectively.<br>
<br/>
The character data created in this app can be transferred to the base game of Dragon's Dogma 2, available separately.<br/>
<br/>
In the main game there will be additional graphic options available.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™ 2 and Yuri’s Revenge™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229850/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_2_and_Yuris_Revenge/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The world erupts in conflict as Soviet forces invade American soil in Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert 2. You are the Supreme Commander. Arm yourself to the teeth with top-secret technologies and lead the Soviet or Allied troops to victory.<br/><br/>Plus, defeat an army of mind-controlled Soviet forces in the expansion <strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Yuri's Revenge</strong>.<br/><br/><strong>Game Features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Many ways to play</strong> - Lead Soviet or Allied forces in a gripping single-player game or a Skirmish game, where there's no particular objective other than destroying everything else on-screen. Who will win the war for world domination?<br/><br/></li><li><strong>No need to play nice</strong> - You'll need to pull out all the stops if you're going to win this war. Thankfully, you've got a well-stocked arsenal of legitimate and illicit technologies from Prism Tanks and Terror Drones, to Psychic Mind Control devices and Cloning Vats. Use them.<br/><br/></li><li><strong>Deliver the fury</strong> - Dominate land, air, and sea battles with the help of over 80 units and structures. Plus, you'll benefit from a enhanced veterancy system that turns new forces into battle-hardened war machines -- and brings you closer to victory.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals Zero Hour</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2732960/Command__Conquer_Generals_Zero_Hour/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2732960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals Zero Hour brings you closer to the enemy than ever before. Engage opposing forces at hot spots around the globe as you match strategies and arsenals against the new masterminds of modern war.<br/><br/><strong>Arsenal.</strong> Unleash the next generation of 3D new units and 20 new upgrades including China's ECM Tank, GLA's BattleBus and the USA's Spectre Gunship.<br/><br/><strong>Missions.</strong> Take on 15 new missions and make tomorrow's headlines. Root out a splinter cell in Cairo, steal deadly toxins from a U.S. lab and more.<br/><br/><strong>Generals.</strong> Match strategies and arsenals against 9 enemy commanders with unpredictable personalities and tactics.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Tiberian Sun™ and Firestorm™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229880/Command__Conquer_Tiberian_Sun_and_Firestorm/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Second Tiberium War begins in this legendary sequel to the original Command &amp; Conquer. <br/><br/>With his forces stronger than ever, arch villain and leader of The Brotherhood of Nod - Kane - is pitched in an epic battle against the world's war machine - the Global Defense Initiative. Now you must orchestrate the fate of mankind.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Fight on Dynamic Battlefields. Nature itself provides tactical opportunities - destroyable and deformable terrain, forest fires, treacherous ice fields and many more surprises that help or hinder your strategies.<br/></li><li>Exciting New Strategies and Units. Jump Jet Infantry, Hover Tanks, Tunneling APCs, Hunter Seekers, Laser Fences, Mechanized Battle Units and many more.<br/></li><li>The "Veterancy" Factor. Units can become faster and stronger as they gain combat experience.<br/></li><li>New Kinetic Battlefields. Flying shrapnel, shock waves and crashing debris are just a few of the exciting new technologies developed to enhance the in-game experience.<br/></li><li>The mood and attitude of the battlefield comes alive like never before - covert night missions, searchlights and new defenses intensify the thrill and excitement.</li></ul><br/>Then take the battle further in <strong>Firestorm, the official expansion pack for the game</strong>. Includes all-new campaign missions, cinematics, and units to decide the future of mankind.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Renegade™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229890/Command__Conquer_Renegade/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229890/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer gets up close and personal in this classic First Person Shooter for one of the most iconic franchises.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Wreak Havoc</strong> - Experience the Command &amp; Conquer universe on foot as Havoc, wise-cracking GDI Commando.<br/></li><li><strong>Make Your Own Rules</strong>  - Take on the evil Brotherhood of Nod using your own mix of brute force, stealth, and strategy.<br/></li><li><strong>Assault at Ground Level</strong>  - Dish out the damage in either first or third person.<br/></li><li><strong>Total Access</strong>  - Sneak inside and explore full-scale structures, like immense Tiberium Refineries and the ominous Hand of Nod.<br/></li><li><strong>Grind the Gears</strong>  - Beef up your arsenal by commandeering lethal vehicles, such as Nod Buggies, Flame Tanks, and Mammoth Tanks.<br/></li><li><strong>Weapons of Mass Destruction</strong>  - Choose from a multitude of weapons, including the Tiberium Auto Rifle, Chemical Sprayer, and the devasting Personal Ion Cannon.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ Generals</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229870/Command__Conquer_Generals/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Command &amp; Conquer Generals puts your trigger finger on the pulse of modern warfare. Prepare your forces General... it's time to engage in the next generation of real-time strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Command.</strong> Wage real-time war in more ways than ever with a modern and near-future arsenal. Command the powerful U.S. forces, the vast Chinese war machine, or the resourceful Global Liberation Army.<br/><br/><strong>Conquer.</strong> Battle it out in unprecedented detail on full 3D environments. All-new units and tactics with maximum destructive capability, including Aurora Strike Bombers, Dragon Tanks, and much more.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert™, Counterstrike™ and The Aftermath™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229840/Command__Conquer_Red_Alert_Counterstrike_and_The_Aftermath/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Command &amp; Conquer Red Alert</strong> pushed the envelope for the RTS genre in the mid-1990s and became one of the most iconic strategy games of all time. <br/><br/><strong>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</strong>  gives you the opportunity to be more devious, cunning, and ruthless than ever before. Red Alert puts the fate of the world in your hands!<br/><br/><strong>Counterstrike</strong>, the exciting expansion pack to Red Alert, is full of clandestine activity, experimental technologies, and disavowed tactics. Includes 16 all-new missions, where you decide the ultimate fate of the struggle between the Allies and Soviets.<br/><br/><strong>In The Aftermath expansion pack</strong>, prepare for guerilla tactics, insidious strategies, and forbidden weapons. Includes 18 all-new missions and multiple units in a showdown that will test your mettle.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command &amp; Conquer™ and The Covert Operations™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229830/Command__Conquer_and_The_Covert_Operations/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The legendary RTS game which started it all. Will you side with the humanistic GDI or bring the world to its knees with Kane and the Brotherhood of Nod. Your adversaries are without mercy. And so are you.  <br/><br/>Includes the <strong>The Covert Operations</strong> expansion pack with a range of challenging new missions.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Saboteur™</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/24880/The_Saboteur/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/24880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Not all wars are fought on the open battlefield. Download The Saboteur to visit 1940s Nazi-occupied Paris, as you play tough Irish racecar mechanic Sean Devlin. Working with the French Resistance, Sean is out for revenge against ruthless Nazi Colonel Kurt Dierker, who executed Sean’s best friend.<br/><br/>This open-world action thriller takes you through the seedy streets of Paris as you seek to undermine the German authority and lead a rebellion. Fight across rooftops and through dangerous alleys, and operate a wide variety of vehicles as you navigate your terrain. You can even climb the Eiffel Tower or Notre Dame Cathedral for a sniping mission.<br/><br/>Use stealth and disguise to strike at the heart of the Nazi war machine by disabling trains, destroying bridges, and blowing up enemy facilities. As you work to remove the oppressive forces from parts of the city, the drab black-and-white palette gives way to bright colors, signifying that you’ve inspired the townspeople. The more you incite the people, the more they’ll aid you by intervening in fights or providing a quick getaway from pursuing Germans. The Saboteur presents a fresh take on World War II and features dramatic cinematic elements. The action and intrigue is yours to experience via download on the PC now.<br/><br/><strong>Key features:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>First Ever Open-World Paris</strong> — Climb the Eiffel Tour, snipe from Notre Dame Cathedral, and brawl on the Champs d’Elysee as you sabotage your enemies. Fight, climb, and prowl through the dark alleys, rooftops, burlesque houses, and seedy streets of the City of Lights — the ultimate playground for the Saboteur.<br/></li><li><strong>The Art of Sabotage</strong> — Being the Saboteur is all about attacking while staying unnoticed. Get your mission intel at underground clubs and cabarets. Eliminate your adversaries with stealth attacks, disguise, distractions, and explosives. Master a variety of weapons, automobiles, and skills to sabotage enemy operations. <br/></li><li><strong>The Will to Fight</strong> — An action-packed experience and thrilling storyline are made even more engaging by an innovative visual style, characters, and the new “Will to Fight” technology. Experience how the city reacts and changes around you as you free it from Nazi oppression. Only you can restore hope and grandeur to Paris.<br/></li><li><strong>French Resistance Strikes</strong> — Call for support from The Underground in the form of getaway cars, weapon deliveries, distractions, and much more.</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rental</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2796550/Rental/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2796550/extras/Gif_Final__2___1_.gif?t=1709834139"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Great Deal!</strong></h2><br/><i>Perfect cabin for a family of four. Close to the beach with great vibes!<br/>For more information about this rental, contact the caretaker!</i><br/><br/>For summer vacation, Umi's family rents a cabin near the beach. However, Umi soon realizes that the offer was not as grand as promised...<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Explore the summer cabin in this short game reminiscent of classic survival horror games.<br/></li><li> Meet and talk to a quirky cast of characters as you try to piece together the secrets of the cabin. <br/></li><li> Find items that will help you advance and find out what is wrong with this place. </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Controls</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Arrows or WASD to move<br/></li><li> Space to interact</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 March Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845260/100_March_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_13" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🌸🌹 WELCOME TO 100 MARCH CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌷🐈</h2><br/>Join the cutest adventure in the Lovely world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of romantic 8 march themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game.<br/>Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game. <br/>Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x200.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 March Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁 DLC List for this game 🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Extra.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867620/100_March_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1709955110"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867640/100_March_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=MarchCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Artbook.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/600x1.png?t=1709955110"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845260/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1709955110"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_14" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2827560/100_Romantic_Cats/?utm_source=MarchBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot" id="dynamiclink_15" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2867630/100_March_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=MarchBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outlast Trials</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1304930/The_Outlast_Trials/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Red Barrels invites you to experience mind-numbing terror, this time with friends. Whether you go through the trials alone or in teams, if you survive long enough and complete the therapy, Murkoff will happily let you leave… but will you be the same?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SYNOPSIS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_synopsis_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Set in the era of the Cold War, human guinea pigs are involuntarily recruited by the good folks at the Murkoff Corporation to test advanced methods of brainwashing and mind control. In a world of distrust, fear, and violence, your morals will be challenged, your endurance tested, and your sanity crushed. All in the name of progress, science, and profit.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SURVIVE: SOLO OR COOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_solocoop_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’re all prisoners of Murkoff trapped inside their facility. You can choose to complete the trials by yourself or you can tackle them in a team of 2, 3, or 4 players.<br/>Coop is never forced when it comes to mandatory objectives but working together can be highly beneficial.<br/>Whatever the number of players in your party, it’s about surviving and getting out.<br/><br/>Ultimately, your goal is to complete Murkoff's therapy and earn the right to be released back into society.  In order to do so, you must complete the Trials and the MK-Challenges.  <br/>Trials are immersive story driven therapies that take a certain time to complete.  Mk-Challenges are shorter therapies occurring in modified or redesigned section of an existing map.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>HIDE OR FLIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_hideorflight_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>In pure Outlast fashion, the core gameplay involves avoiding enemies, hiding from them, and trying to run away. Murkoff will provide tools you can use to increase your stealth capabilities, create opportunities to flee, slow down enemies, and more. However, you will have to earn those tools and work hard to improve them.<br/>The tools will allow you to <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Stun enemies<br/></li><li>Blind them<br/></li><li>See through walls<br/></li><li>Heal yourself and people around you.</li></ul>Murkoff will ask you to perform disturbing tasks in each trials or mk-challenges.  Only after completing those, will you be allowed to exit the Trials or the MK-Challenges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_customisation_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>Customize and create your own trial patient.<br/>Your cell is your home while you complete the therapy, you can decorate it however you wish.<br/>Choose your tools, upgrades, and perks to fit your playstyle. <br/>Meet the Denizens of Murkoff’s Sinyala Facility in The Outlast Trials.  Each one of them will try and help you get through the Trials in one piece! Think you’ll make it?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_NOAKS.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_barlow.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/steam_page_doris.jpg?t=1709677975"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>INVESTIGATE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_investigate_616x295.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/>You’ve been abducted by the Murkoff Corporation to undergo unethical experiments that will modify your psyche and behavior throughout the Trials. <br/>Collect documents and items that will help prove Murkoff’s malpractice against its patients.<br/>The Process:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break the Self: Murkoff aims to break down the test subject’s fundamental beliefs. Aspects of self-identity are systematically attacked. Like boot camp or indoctrination, the goal is to force a person to purge themselves of anything held sacred or taboo, the things that limit their behavior. The constant assault on identity, guilt and self-betrayal eventually leads to them breaking down.<br/></li><li>Build the Self: It’s a bad cop, good cop principle. The rejection of the old ideology leaves a vacuum into which the new ideology can be introduced. As the antithesis of the old ideology, it forms a perfect attraction point as the person flees the old in search of a contrasting replacement.  This progress is accelerated as the new ideology is portrayed as harmonious and ideally suited to the person's needs. Collegiality and calm replaces pain and punishment. Just at the point when the person is fearing annihilation of the self, they are offered a small kindness, a brief respite from the assault on their identity.<br/></li><li>Salvation: Faced with the stark contrast of the pain of the past with the rosy glow of the future that the new ideology presents, the person sheds any the final allegiance to the old ideology, confessing any remaining deep secrets, and takes on the full mantle of the new ideology.  This often feels, and has been described by many, as a form of rebirth. It may be accompanied by rites of passage as the person is accepted and cemented into the new order. The rituals will typically include strong statements made by the person about accepting the new ideology fully and completely, swearing allegiance to its leaders. Saluting flags, kissing other artefacts and other symbolic acts, all solemnly performed, all anchor them firmly in the new ground.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1304930/extras/capsule_warning_616x54.jpg?t=1709677975"><br/><u>Content and Photosensitivity Warning:</u></img></h2>The Outlast Trials contain strobing and flashing lights that could cause a small percentage of people to experience seizures when exposed to certain lights, patterns, or images.<br/>This game also contains intense violence, gore, graphic sexual content, and strong language. Please enjoy.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2831340/Rabbit_Hole/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/smaller.png?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Remember you will live.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Rabbit Hole is a fast paced, tough-as-nails 2D Platformer-RogueLike-Shooter inspired by popular roguelikes, made with a love for the genre. <br/>You are Disc, someone who was suddenly brought to the Rabbit Hole. <br/>Collect guns, fight foes and meet strange new characters on your descent to the bottom, all in an attempt to find your heart again.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/1.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“This place is like its own ecosystem. A big living breathing mess.”</i></strong><br/><br/>Every run is different. Enjoy hours of replayable content through randomly generated floor layouts and 50+ weapons to collect and use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/2.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“Hey, hey, hey! How's my favorite anxiety-fueled nutjob!”</i></strong><br/><br/>Unlock new characters with diverse playstyles. Each of the 6 unlockable characters keep gameplay fresh and give a unique perspective on the gameplay loop.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2831340/extras/3.gif?t=1710004888"><br/><strong><i>“There was a blank line, almost as if I had erased it”</i></strong><br/><br/>Discover the truth that lies beneath the surface. Collect books and fill out your library to understand its unseen history. In the end, you may even come to understand yourself?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2811970/MetaGhost_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FuPHvpUDPdZ" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-2.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><a href="https://twitter.com/MetaGhostGame" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/600-140-1.png?t=1710474278"/></a><br/><br/><strong>(Talk to Devs in discord!)</strong><br/><br/><strong>Meta-Ghost: The Breaking Show</strong> is a <i>3D roguelite hack-and-slash action</i> game. Built on the foundation of "cyberpunk" culture, the game provides a thrilling and fast-paced combat experience while telling a profound cyberpunk story.<br/><br/>※ <i>Meta-Ghost: Prologue</i> is the free-to-play version of <i>Meta-Ghost: The breaking show</i>, to showcase some of the gameplay content.<h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue including:</h2><strong>· 3 Characters: "Toxin" Taisuke, "Jeer" Jean, "Yarn" Yan<br/>· Solo Match: Level 1 - Qualifiers, Level 2 - Preliminaries<br/>· Team Match: Level 1&amp;2, up to 3 players online co-op, online matching available<br/>· Off-battle Development: Operating System, Weapon Augmentation, Prosthesis Weaponizing<br/>· Save Inheritance: Save data from the prologue can be inherited into the full version.</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0011_Man-VS-Machine.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0001.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Play as one “breaker” (or several) in Breaking Show, battling intelligent machines with cybernetic enhancements and state-of-the-art weapons provided by the organizers in the future city of "Aeropolis." With each defeat or victory, you will gradually uncover the secrets of "the soul" and the outcome it desires...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0009_Go-live-streaming.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0002.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As a Breaking Show participant with your own personal channel, you must get used to fighting on live broadcasts. Not only do you need to defeat every mechanical opponent in front of you, but you also need to strive for visually stunning performances to please event sponsors and viewers eagerly anticipating your cool moves. Their likes and dislikes will either aid or hinder you on the field.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0006_Diverse-art-elements.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0008.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Combining elements of "glitch art," "street art," "pop art," and other trendsetting styles creates a unique "cyber graffiti style" with a cutting-edge feel and visual impact.<br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0004_Modify_Inherit.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0011.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0004.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Through the participant's lounge modification pod, you can enhance and modify your cybernetic enhancements and weapons, creating a dangerous and diverse fighting style. From event organizers to sponsors, you will have access to a vast array of freely combinable and customizable drivers to equip your cybernetic enhancements with special abilities, making you unbeatable on the field. The relics of other eliminated contestants left on the field will also be a major asset, allowing you to break through with their unfulfilled beliefs.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0002_Choose-wisely.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0006.gif?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0007.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>Breaking Show offers a range of combat styles to suit your preferences, whether you prefer hit-and-run tactics, head-on defense and counterattacks, or precise finesse. The Breakers in the lounge are a diverse group with unique fighting styles, providing a variety of experiences and event performances. Intelligent machines, poised to replace soldiers, agents, and bodyguards, are also preparing for the competition with flexible cooperation, adding to the already diverse lineup and ensuring that every contestant attempting to climb to the top will be successfully blocked.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/未标题-1_0000_Watch-out!.png?t=1710474278"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0010.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>As the venue for Breaking Show, the temporarily closed-off streets may appear normal, but be sure to watch every step you take, even on drainage grates or manhole covers - they could become deadly traps at any moment. Of course, this is only if you can keep your focus while taking down every mechanical opponent in front of you.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/分割线.png?t=1710474278"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2811970/extras/Gif0012.gif?t=1710474278"><br/>So, are you ready to make a name for yourself as a participant in the new season? After all, "the soul" is watching and eagerly anticipating your arrival.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHT-RUNNERS™ PROLOGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707900/NIGHTRUNNERS_PROLOGUE/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_HEADER.png?t=1708958635"><br/><br/><strong>DESCEND INTO THE UNDERWORLD OF JAPANESE STREET RACING</strong><br/><br/>Set in an unknown time between 1990-2009, you will navigate through the corrupt and shady power struggles of local street racing crews, all competing for control of their regions and to top the crew rankings.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extremely detailed customization, including Exterior, Interior, Wheels, Engine, and Handling</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic character dialogue; other racers will comment on your car, your recent races, new local records and your progression</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Full Photomode with VHS, old camera effects and motion blur</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Freely walk around your garage and the car meet (Parking Area) between races</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Adjustable screenshake and camera FOV</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Procedural game event scripting, high replay value</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_2.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Inspired by the real life Japanese used car auctions, you will purchase your first vehicle by visiting the used car auctions and leaving with any decrepit car you can afford.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_3.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Walk around your safehouse and view all your hard-earned cars; change their oil, repair their engines and view their stats. Good maintenance will help your engine last longer after a long night of abuse and overheating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_4.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Take parts off your cars, place them into storage and sell them for some extra cash or transfer them onto another vehicle you own. When you have some spare cash, take a trip to "Top Garage" to buy some new parts for your exterior, interior, wheels, engine and/or handling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_1.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Progress through the underworld by entering a "PA"(Parking Area) and start negotiating wagers with any local crew members who care to race you. You are free to walk around any "PA" and bask in the thick atmosphere of smog and secondhand cigarette smoke.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_5.png?t=1708958635"><br/>The local racers are not impressed with newcomers and will make their disdain known. Impress them by winning and they will change their tone.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707900/extras/N-R_BODY_IMAGE_6.png?t=1708958635"><br/>Earn cash by beating racers in 1vs1 wagers but be warned; these are real wagers and you will lose the money you bet if you lose the race! Some racers will take pity on you and give you a chance to win your money back by suggesting a 'double or nothing' race. It's your choice if you want to take that risk.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2684500/Alpha_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>About us</strong><br/>Beaveroid a new studio, founded in 2022, with 6 members. We will continue supporting the game as long as you are still a part of the community.<br/><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Alpha League is a Roguelike-based Autobattler game. You will choose your favorite hero, build your heroes with 10 different combat genres, and adjust your strategy corresponding to 10+ different maps. There is also drafting and artifacts involved. Download now and try it out!<br/><br/>Patreon page: <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.patreon.com%2FBeaveroidEntertainment" rel="noopener" target="_blank">https://www.patreon.com/BeaveroidEntertainment</a><br/><br/><strong>Pick your hero</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickHeroNew.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Gain powerful skills</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BuySkills.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Draft a genre</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/DraftGenre.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Pick artifacts</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/PickArtifact.gif?t=1709870080"><br/><br/><strong>Be the winner</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2684500/extras/BeTheWinner.gif?t=1709870080"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1710487519"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1710487519"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1709060046"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1709060046"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1710160593"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1710160593"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708975190"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1710258282"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1710258282"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1710258282"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sputnika Game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2730270/Sputnika_Game/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Meet our little friend Sputnik. Help its journey to become the greatest star in the solar system - the Sun!<h2 class="bb_tag">Unique Gameplay With Cosmic Gravity</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/MainMech.gif?t=1710427471"><br/>Cosmic gravity is applied to the planet, which makes it different from the classic Suika-style game.<br/>The ability to target the other side of the planets adds much more strategy and depth to the game!<h2 class="bb_tag">Merge Planets</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/EvoRing2.png?t=1710427471"><br/>Match two identical planets to create bigger celestial bodies.<br/>Discover 10 dazzling planets, each with its own place in the solar system!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/GameOver2.png?t=1710427471"><br/>Watch out for the bubble! If the planet pops out of the bubble, it's game over.<h2 class="bb_tag">Meet the Adorable Planets</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2730270/extras/Adorable2.png?t=1710427471"><br/>Our planets aren't just celestial bodies – they're full of life! <br/>Watch them interact – they might greet each other with a smile or gaze curiously at one another. <br/>Get ready for a whole lot of cuteness as you merge your way through the solar system.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1709666906"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>过劳的爱丽丝Overworked Alice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2829330/Overworked_Alice/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2829330/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> This is a precise platform game modeled after the King of Jumps </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2829330/extras/内容图01.jpg?t=1711037282"><br/><br/><strong>Alice:</strong> A newly graduated worker, is overloaded with work every day<br/>In the process of working overtime, she experienced a magical journey...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2829330/extras/Alice.gif?t=1711037282"><br/><br/><strong>The game is divided into 15 levels </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2829330/extras/play.gif?t=1711037282"><br/><br/><strong> Game system 1: </strong> 5 power jumps<br/><strong> Game System 2: </strong> Unable to adjust direction while jumping<br/><strong> Game System 3: </strong><br/><strong> Useless super free jump (10 times per level) :</strong> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2829330/extras/大炮能量条00.gif?t=1711037282"><br/>Players hit the wall during the jump can accumulate air slot → fill the air slot and then press the jump key → Automatically become a super jump that can adjust the flight direction by itself<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2829330/extras/202402170004_00_00_00-00_00_30.gif?t=1711037282"><br/><br/><strong>OK, let's start our headache-like overtime experience!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Roll</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2817240/Lets_Roll/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817240/extras/Let_s_Roll_gif_0.gif?t=1711035442"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2817240/extras/Let_s_Roll_gif_1.gif?t=1711035442"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Let's Roll</strong></h2>This is a game where you become a pirate and overcome obstacles. <br/>If you work hard, you will reach your goal.<br/>It is a third-person platformer genre.<br/>There is no set save point but you can save using skill.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Controls</strong></h2>Move - w,a,s,d<br/>Jump - space<br/>Attack - mouse left click<br/>Time delay, Aim - mouse right click<br/>Skill - E,R<br/>Option - Esc<br/>Crouch - Alt<br/>Sprint - Shift<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Tips</strong></h2>Don't Fall into the Sea<br/>If the game is difficult, collect a lot of coins<br/>If you press alt right before falling, you will roll forward<br/>Do not try to climb on moving objects<br/>The gun fires only when aiming<br/>Please enjoy the game~						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zeitz Machz √Rhapsody</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2784080/Zeitz_Machz_Rhapsody/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2784080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							No one knows what the future may hold. Just yesterday, Ais was going about her life, enjoying it to the fullest. But out of nowhere, she suddenly finds herself confined alongside a strange girl called "Alice".<br>
<br>
To make matters worse, neither of them remembered anything prior to this incident. Just who is behind this? And why are they doing this?<br>
<br>
A mystery yuri visual novel.<br>
<br>
Features:<br/>
<br/>
30K words<br/>
<br/>
3 Endings<br/>
<br/>
3 CGs<br/>
<br/>
Credits:<br/>
<br/>
Logo Artist: Lazy Polar Bear<br/>
<br/>
Character/CG Artist: Miria Croissant and Sapphire<br/>
<br/>
Editors: Callista, Kristi Jimenez and Julia Martinez<br/>
<br/>
Music: Kamatamago<br/>
<br/>
Background: Minchiri<br/>
<br/>
Special thanks to our wonderful Kickstarter's backer!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parry Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2081230/Parry_Nightmare/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Easy to pick up, and hard to put down! Parry Nightmare is a one-of-a-kind "parry heaven" action game where the best offense is a good defense!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081230/extras/01.gif?t=1711033312"><br/><br/>Use your nightmare's strength against it with your trusty parry move! Stun foes, send away projectiles, and stop threats right in their tracks by chaining parries!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081230/extras/4a.gif?t=1711033312"><br/><br/>Honno-chan will defeat any foes you stun automatically. Leave them to her and focus on the defense!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081230/extras/6.gif?t=1711033312"><br/><br/>Parrying grants your soul more and more courage to face the night! Heal up by continuing to parry! Spend excess soul to unleash a powerful Burst move to wipe out hordes of enemies at once!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081230/extras/5.gif?t=1711033312"><br/><br/>Collect powerups from rare foes to supercharge Honno-chan! Breathe fire, deploy orbital pain, wreak havoc, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081230/extras/8.gif?t=1711033312"><br/><br/>Defeated enemies drop light. Collect light and the darkness of the nightmare abates, giving you a clearer view of the chaos. Max out your light meter to beat the nightmare!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081230/extras/3a.gif?t=1711033312"><br/><br/>Will you be able to escape the nightmare and greet a new day...?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2081230/extras/9.gif?t=1711033312"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prank Heart</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2654360/Prank_Heart/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Phantom Theif vs Detective Slapstick online battle action!!!</strong><br/>You can also have fun with someone or your friends online!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654360/extras/Overview.gif?t=1711033230"><br/><br/>You can play as a Phantom Theif or Detective, and fight with each other.<br/><br/><u><h2 class="bb_tag">Phantom Theif</h2></u><br/>Blend in the crowd.<br/>And, steal lots of treasures!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654360/extras/PhamtomTheif_overview.gif?t=1711033230"><br/><br/><u><h2 class="bb_tag">Detective</h2></u><br/>Find and arrest the Phantom Theivs!<br/>Whatever it takes.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654360/extras/Detective_overview.gif?t=1711033230"><br/><br/><u><h2 class="bb_tag">Various Items</h2></u><br/>Make full use of exciting items!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654360/extras/Items_OverView.gif?t=1711033230"><br/><br/><u><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiple Maps</h2></u><br/>Battle on unique maps!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654360/extras/Maps_overview.gif?t=1711033230"><br/><br/><br/><u><h2 class="bb_tag">Custom Rules</h2></u><br/>Custom the game as you want!<br/>Various customizations are possible.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2654360/extras/RulesCustom_overview.gif?t=1711033230"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon Forbidden West™ Complete Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420110/Horizon_Forbidden_West_Complete_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420110/extras/horizon_forbidden_west_cinemagraph_610x610.gif?t=1711032993"><br/><br/>Join Aloy as she braves a majestic but dangerous new frontier that holds mysterious new threats. This Complete Edition allows you to enjoy the critically acclaimed Horizon Forbidden West on PC in its entirety with bonus content, including the Burning Shores story expansion that picks up after the main game.<br/><br/>Explore distant lands, fight bigger and more awe-inspiring machines, and encounter astonishing new tribes as you return to the far-future, post-apocalyptic world of Horizon.<br/><br/>The land is dying. Vicious storms and an unstoppable blight ravage the scattered remnants of humanity while fearsome new machines prowl their borders, and life on Earth is hurtling toward another extinction.<br/><br/>It's up to Aloy to uncover the secrets behind these threats and restore order and balance to the world. Along the way, she must reunite with old friends, forge alliances with warring new factions and unravel the legacy of the ancient past.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>See every gameplay detail with Ultrawide 21:9 and Super Ultrawide 32:9 resolutions, as well as 48:9 triple monitor support.*<br/></li><li>Witness the Forbidden West coming to life, with NVIDIA DLSS 3 upscaling and frame generation, image enhancing NVIDIA DLAA and latency reducing NVIDIA Reflex. AMD FSR and Intel XeSS are also supported.**<br/></li><li>Customize graphic settings to your preference, with the potential for unlocked frame rates.**<br/></li><li>Take control with full support for the DualSense™ controller, including haptic feedback and adaptive trigger functionality.*** </li></ul><br/>* Compatible PC and 4K display device required. <br/>** Compatible PC required. <br/>*** Wired connection required to experience the full range of in-game controller features.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turbo Tails</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2568700/Turbo_Tails/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Header_TheGame.png?t=1711030374"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/TT_spectatorsAtStartLinje.gif?t=1711030374"><br/>Turbo Tails is a silly arcade animal racer. Consume <strong>Food Pickups</strong> littered across the tracks to power up your critter. Unleash your food power as gaseous turbo boost or leave it behind as a gift to mess with your opponents. Turbo Tails features a unique handling mechanic where taking on food increases your weight, in turn reducing your <strong>maneuverability</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Divider_footsteps.png?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Header_TrickyTracks.png?t=1711030374"> <br/>Compete in a <strong>variety of environments</strong>, from twisty trails to muddy meadows. Featuring challenging <strong>track hazards</strong> such as river crossings, slippery fruit trails, wandering machines and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/TT_scenery.gif?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Divider_footsteps.png?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Header_FoodPower.png?t=1711030374"><br/>Eat food littered around the track to gain <strong>Turbo</strong> boost. The more you eat, the stronger the Turbo! Save up a bunch of food for a long straight and leave the competition behind in a cloud of gas. Use your Turbo boost to create shortcuts or obtain those harder to reach pickups.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/TT_turboPower.gif?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Divider_footsteps.png?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Header_PlanAhead.png?t=1711030374"><br/>Be careful not to consume too much though, as eating will reduce handling. Players will need to be mindful of the track layout when choosing whether to top up on food, else they may find themselves too heavy to make the next turn.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/TT_weightMechanic2.gif?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Divider_footsteps.png?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Header_SpecialDelivery.png?t=1711030374"><br/>Alternatively, if you do find yourself overloaded, you may wish to offload all of your food in a pinch to reduce your weight, which can also serve as a nice gift to your opponents, sending them sliding off the track!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/TT_poopSlip.gif?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Divider_footsteps.png?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Header_CuteCompetitors.png?t=1711030374"><br/>Choose from a variety of animal athletes, such as <strong>Cow</strong>, <strong>Goat</strong> and who could forget <strong>Sheep</strong>. Don't forget to unlock the special critter and show off to your friends!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/TT_startLine.gif?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2568700/extras/Divider_footsteps.png?t=1711030374"><br/><br/><br/>Races can be enjoyed in <strong>multiple modes:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Single Player<br/></li><li>4 Player Versus<br/></li><li>Online Multiplayer</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunt Paradise</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2435310/Stunt_Paradise/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to <strong>Stunt Paradise</strong>, the ultimate destination for <u>extreme driving</u> and heart-pumping stunts! Buckle up and prepare to experience the thrill of a lifetime as you take on the most epic challenges on four wheels.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2435310/extras/stant_paradise_gif_600x200_30_fps.gif?t=1711029651"><br/><br/>Push your driving skills to the limit as you perform insane stunts, including jumping off ramps, flipping through the air, and smashing through explosive obstacles!<br/><br/>Explore <u>extreme tracks</u> in various locations, from industrial cities and dusty deserts to beautiful tropical beaches. With many cool cars to choose from, each level offers a unique challenge that enhances your driving experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">Key features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Extreme driving stunts<br/></li><li>20 unique cars<br/></li><li>50 crazy levels<br/></li><li>Stylish graphics</li></ul><br/>Hit the gas and start your adventure in the world of extreme driving and stunts!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forest Ranger Simulator - Apprenticeship</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802660/Forest_Ranger_Simulator__Apprenticeship/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Forest Ranger Simulator - Apprenticeship</strong> is a free prologue to Forest Ranger Simulator. You have 45 minutes to explore the game, have a glimpse of the story and the game mechanics. If you like it. Here you can get the full game.  <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1185780/Forest_Ranger_Simulator/" id="dynamiclink_6" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1185780/Forest_Ranger_Simulator/</a><br/><br/>Take care of forgotten nature's treasure. Build, craft, feed, clean, and manage your forest in Forest Ranger Simulator. Ensure its long-lasting beauty and become a flawless Forest Ranger!<br/><br/>WHAT CAN YOU DO IN <strong>FOREST RANGER SIMULATOR</strong><br/>⚒️ <strong>Build &amp; Repair</strong> - seatings, benches, feeders, bridges and more<br/>🧰 <strong>Craft</strong> - create something useful out of not useful items<br/>📚 <strong>Learn</strong> - read and learn about real life nature in your notebook<br/>🐦 <strong>Feed</strong> - hungry animals such as ducks or birds need to be fed<br/>⭐ <strong>Unlock Items &amp; Badges</strong> - advance through game to unlock new items and get rewards<br/>🏃‍♂️ <strong>Explore</strong> - walk, run, drive and watch beautiful nature by day and night <br/>🗑️ <strong>Sort &amp; Clean</strong> - help forest and clean it from garbage, lots of different trash need sorting<br/>💰 <strong>Buy and Sell</strong>l - use online store to earn some $<br/>🪓 <strong>Gather</strong> - mushrooms, brushwood, timber, honey and more<br/>🌲 <strong>Take Care of the Forest</strong> - estinguish fires, get rid of traps and more<br/><strong>DO WHAT YOU LIKE</strong> - it's sandbox, play how you like it!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>QUESTS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Quests_small.gif?t=1711029514"><br/>Forest Ranger always has his hands full. The number and variety of quests will not let anyone get bored. Some tasks you can complete without hurry, in others you will have to do a little jogging. Some will require the use of a car. We do not want to reveal too much. See for yourself.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CRAFTING</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Crafting_small.gif?t=1711029514"><br/>What is crafting in Forest Ranger Simulator? It's creating useful things from literally whatever you can find. Sometimes you'll definitely feel like MacGyver.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>GATHERING</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Gathering_small.gif?t=1711029514"><br/>In order to create something you first have to tear it down. Specifically, we need to acquire materials for building and crafting. To build a table we will need wood. In addition, in the forest we can find many other valuable things like mushrooms.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LEARNING</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Learning_small.gif?t=1711029514"><br/>Forest Ranger Simulator is a game, however, we wanted to include as much valuable information from real life as possible in the game. Thanks to the notebook you will learn a lot about the work of a Forest Ranger, you will also find many interesting facts about forests, such as information about mushrooms. Learn by playing. The name simulator obliges.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>WORKSHOP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Workshop_Small.gif?t=1711029514"><br/>Workbench. There's nothing like having everything at hand. Saw, pliers, hammer, paintbrush.... and many more tools ready to go. Why not build a bird feeder?<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>DAY &amp; NIGHT</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Day___Night_Small.gif?t=1711029514"><br/>The profession of Forest Ranger is not a job from 8:00 a.m. to 4:00 p.m. Here you have to be on guard day and night. Remember that the night is dark, and the only light is the glow of the moon and your flashlight. Watching the sunset or the beauty of the moon.... priceless.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CLEANING</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Cleaning_small.gif?t=1711029514"><br/>Forests, it's not just trees, leaves and animals, it's a ton of trash left by people. You will find more than 150 different trash here. Sometimes you will be surprised what you can find in the forest. Remember that everything has to be sorted. You have special trash garbage cans for this. Some skills as well as large garbage bags will be helpful in cleaning up.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>EMERGENCIES</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Emergencies_Small.gif?t=1711029514"><br/>A Forest Ranger has to be alert at all times. You need to observe what's going on in your forest and quickly intervene with a threat. Maybe it's a smoldering fire, or maybe poachers have set up snares again. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Enjoy.png?t=1711029514"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802660/extras/Enjoy.gif?t=1711029514"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Run: Rogue Heroes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2603210/On_the_Run_Rogue_Heroes/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2603210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Awaken your powers and save your friends! Uncover the secrets that the military has been hiding about Activated people, about your family, and about you.<br/><br/><i>On the Run: Rogue Heroes</i> is an interactive teenage-superpower novel by Alyssa N. Vaughn. It’s entirely text-based, 200,000 words and hundreds of choices, without graphics or sound effects, and fueled by the vast, unstoppable power of your imagination.<br/><br/>For decades, everyone with special powers like super-strength or flight has been forced into lifelong conscription in W.I.N.G.S.: the Weaponized Individual National Guardian Services. Most of this military branch’s activities are secret—except for the daring exploits of heroes like Ms. Midnight, Phantom Phaeton, and Sergeant Smash.<br/><br/>You and your older sister grew up living with your grandmother, who cared for you, provided for you, and sheltered you from the truth. She knows what they do at W.I.N.G.S., she knows what happened to your parents, and she knows about the deadly genetic disease that you and your sister both carry.<br/><br/>Now, you and your sister have finally Activated your powers, W.I.N.G.S has arrested and conscripted your sister, and you've fled with your grandmother, on the run from psionic government agents with abilities just as powerful as yours.<br/><br/>But you’re not alone! There are people out there trying to fight back against W.I.N.G.S., people who could be your friend—or more than friends. There's Micah, a long-lost friend with shoulder-length locs and a big secret to protect. Alex, a pickpocket/con-artist has illusion powers and a lot of eye makeup. Then there's Knockout, a vigilante with a red-brown ponytail and homemade costume, including a mask and cape.<br/><br/>While your scrappy little group races against time to save your sister and yourselves, your own powers are growing stronger every day. Outrun cars on the highway with super-speed, pull down telephone poles with your super-strength, let out supersonic cries that can shatter glass—or just turn invisible and sneak away from it all. You’ll need every bit of your power and your smarts as you uncover secrets that could change the lives of every Activated person on earth.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>• Play as male, female, or nonbinary; gay, straight, bi, or asexual.<br/></li><li> Choose your portfolio of powers: super-strength, super-speed, heightened senses, supersonic shouts, or invisibility!<br/></li><li> Befriend or romance a childhood sweetheart, a scrappy con-artist runaway, or a powered vigilante with big golden-retriever energy.<br/></li><li> Discover the truth about your family and rebuild your relationship with your long-lost mother—or leave it all behind and seek support only with your friends.<br/></li><li> Fight back against the government’s control of Activated people, join their secret organization and become even more powerful yourself, or make peace between opposing factions.</li></ul><br/>Who will you trust? Who are your parents? Who will you date?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fida Puti Samurai</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1534340/Fida_Puti_Samurai/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1534340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							What is your happy place?<br/>Maybe it's a bedroom. A calm place in the open. Your bathroom. Or maybe... your personal computer?<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1534340/extras/cozy_place_w.gif?t=1711023451"><br/>During times of need, a programmer developed a virtual cozy experience for his girlfriend.<br/>It was a warm, isolated wood cabin on the snowy alps. With a chill-out music playing on the background, a nice place to say for a while...<br/>... if not by a system bug on the basement, showing a hidden path to another world.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1534340/extras/nuke_wide_w.gif?t=1711023451"><br/><br/>On Fida Puti Samurai, you will incarnate as Liza, digging through a silly kind of rabbit hole:<br/><br/>- Traverse urban environments<br/>- Visit 13 levels on urban settings<br/>- Fight bunny-suit zombies, semi-naked waifus, punk gurls and others on 4 different enemy factions<br/>- Use a wide variety of weapons from sledgehammers to dynamite and even panty-drying miniguns<br/>- Discover the ability to transform into a Mahou Shoujo<br/>- Uncover the secrets that lie on Zanardi's computer and his past<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1534340/extras/minigun.gif?t=1711023451"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1534340/extras/broom_trap_quad.gif?t=1711023451"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soda scuffle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2838960/Soda_scuffle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2838960/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Fight! Upgrade! Every time you upgrade your attributes, you will receive an increase. As time goes by, you will gain some powerful weapons, and of course, monsters will also grow over time. After defeating the boss, you will receive a strong boost! Try to persist for 20 minutes! Come on!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piccadilly's Puzzle Museum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2749730/Piccadillys_Puzzle_Museum/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2749730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2749730/extras/PuzzleCompletion.gif?t=1711017686"><br/>Join Piccadilly and her delightful friends on an enchanting journey through a museum unlike any other. Get ready to immerse yourself in a world of wonder, creativity, and jigsaw puzzles!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2749730/extras/CustomImage5.png?t=1711017686"><br/><strong>🎨 A Gallery of Imagination 🎨</strong><br/>Step into the captivating world of <strong>"Piccadilly and her Magical World"</strong> Children's Picture Book Series. Explore a museum bursting with art, characters, and captions straight from the heartwarming pages of this award-winning series. Every puzzle piece tells a story, inviting you to embark on an artistic adventure like no other.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2749730/extras/CustomImage.png?t=1711017686"><br/><strong>🎵 A Symphony of Sound 🎵</strong><br/>Feel the magic of <strong>Piccadilly's Puzzle Museum</strong> come to life with an original full-length soundtrack. Immerse yourself in a symphony of melodies that complement the beauty of each puzzle, creating an enchanting atmosphere that will transport you to a world of imagination and wonder.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2749730/extras/CustomImage2.png?t=1711017686"><br/><strong>🧩 48 Puzzles, Countless Challenges 🧩</strong><br/>Get ready to test your wits and unleash your inner puzzle enthusiast! <strong>Piccadilly's Puzzle Museum</strong> offers 48 crafted puzzles based on 12 different full-color illustrations. Each puzzle comes in four difficulty levels, ensuring there's a challenge for everyone. Whether you're a beginner or a seasoned puzzler, you'll find the perfect level to suit your skills.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2749730/extras/CustomImage3.png?t=1711017686"><br/><strong>🌟 Hours of Joyful Exploration 🌟</strong><br/>Get lost in the mesmerizing world of puzzles with Piccadilly and her friends. Spend hours of delightful exploration as you piece together these stunning illustrations. From whimsical characters to breathtaking landscapes, each puzzle is a work of art waiting for you to uncover its secrets.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2749730/extras/CustomImage4.png?t=1711017686"><br/><strong>🛍️ No Hidden Costs, No Limits 🛍️</strong><br/>We believe in providing an exceptional gaming experience without any strings attached. With Piccadilly's Puzzle Museum, there are no additional purchases required to complete the entire museum. Enjoy all the puzzles and features to your heart's content, without any interruptions.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaxingTiles</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2663790/TaxingTiles/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2663790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for an extraordinary gaming experience that melds roguelike strategy, deck building, and nostalgic arcade thrills. Welcome to "Taxing Tiles", where you'll embark on a captivating journey through a dynamic world teeming with surprises, challenges, and enigmas waiting to be unveiled.<br>
<br>
Key Features:<br>
<br>
🎲 Deck-Building Mastery:<br>
Craft and fine-tune your card deck as you confront the ever-shifting trials of "Taxing Tiles". Each card you draw holds the power to reshape your destiny.<br>
<br/>
🏰 Forge Your Realm:<br/>
Strategically place an array of tiles to shape your realm. Cultivate lush farms, nurture vibrant flower fields, mine precious gems, and construct majestic buildings. Your world, your rules.<br/>
<br/>
🧙 Mystical Spells:<br/>
<br/>
 Harness the arcane arts with a unique spellcasting system. Unleash "Burning Hands" to obliterate unwanted tiles, conjure spells that fill your coffers with gold, peer into the future to grab cards yet to be drawn, and gain rerolls and skips to craft the perfect hand.<br/>
<br/>
🪓 Tile Interactions: <br/>
<br/>
Engage in tile interactions that bring your world to life. Chop down towering trees for resources, mine valuable rocks for gems, and navigate the perilous challenge of summoning mystical creatures like Ents.<br/>
<br/>
🔥 Tactical Gameplay:<br/>
<br/>
 Navigate the ever-evolving landscape with precision and strategy. Can you outlast the relentless challenges and thrive for five years?<br/>
<br/>
🕹️ Retro Arcade Delights: <br/>
<br/>
Immerse yourself in classic arcade-style gameplay with a modern twist. "Taxing Tiles" offers the perfect balance of challenge and enjoyment, easy to pick up but hard to put down.<br/>
<br/>
🌟 Hidden Wonders: <br/>
<br/>
Dive deep into the game to uncover elusive mysteries and unlock its most coveted secrets. Do you have what it takes to unveil every hidden gem?<br/>
<br/>
🃏 Luck Meets Strategy: <br/>
<br/>
Imagine "Luck be a Landlord" merging with "Slay the Spire", where chance and strategy dance in harmony.<br/>
<br/>
In "Taxing Tiles", your destiny is in your hands as you strive to conquer a dynamic world that's as unpredictable as it is exhilarating. Can you survive, flourish, and unveil all the game's well-guarded wonders? But beware of the mischievous bunnies. The adventure of a lifetime awaits, where your realm is limited only by your imagination!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age of Water: The First Voyage</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2841350/Age_of_Water_The_First_Voyage/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The First Voyage is the very beginning of your Age of Water experience. Jump right into the intense naval combat, craft your first boats, explore the waterworld and get a good idea of what Age of Water is about. Don’t forget to wishlist the full game now!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_ship_anim.gif?t=1711025025"><br/><br/>Become a sea captain on a post-apocalyptic Earth completely covered in water and go on an adventure in a huge open world. Sail through storms, fight and trade, capture other people's boats or build your own, extract resources from the bottom of the ocean, reveal the secrets of the Age of Water world.<br/><br/><strong>Water post-apocalypse</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_1.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>The ocean destroyed a once great civilization, but people survived and adapted. They built settlements on the roofs of tall buildings and the tops of other man-made structures. People travel across the ocean in tiny boats and huge combat vessels. The ocean provides everything they need, including extractable resources on the seabed. And yet, the dream of real land is still alive.<br/><br/><strong>True open world</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_2.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Explore the world at your own pace, discover new settlements and meet their inhabitants. Complete tasks, search for and extract valuable resources from the bottom of the ocean, earn money on trade or simply sell the artifacts you have obtained, and when you get the idea of how this world works, build your own base.<br/><br/><strong>Hundreds of unique ships</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_3.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Build boats from scratch or modify existing ones. Players have access to dozens of hulls and hundreds of parts, from which they can assemble anything ranging from a small boat to a hefty vessel 30 meters long, and then install equipment, armor and weapons. It’s important not to forget to gather a team of good crewmembers so that there is someone to stand behind machine guns and cannons or do other work on board.<br/><br/><strong>Fierce naval battles</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_4.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>Pirates are always waiting for you at sea, and in some cases more aggressive players even start to chase you, so do not forget to install enough guns on your deck.  You can destroy an enemy vessel, or you can capture it in battle and take it for yourself forever. Adventures might also get you into storming enemy fortresses and defending allied settlements!<br/><br/><strong>Personal naval base</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_5.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>This shelter is reliably protected from enemies, and it allows a player to organize the production of everything that the captain may need on it. Build factories for the production of equipment, weapons, hulls for boats of all sizes, as well as the necessary resources.<br/><br/><strong>Flexible balance between PvE and PvP</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2841350/extras/AoF_steam_discr_6.gif?t=1711025025"><br/>At first, you will only meet computer opponents, but later you can challenge other players if you are confident enough in your skills and gear. Always be on the lookout: if your task is to transport illegal goods, then other players may well take the quest to hunt smugglers. In Age of Water, everyone decides for themself who they are today - a peaceful traveler or a bloodthirsty pirate.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largo</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2870910/Largo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2870910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2870910/extras/Frame_1.gif?t=1711009431"><h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to Largo!</h2>Largo is a game in the style of <strong>I'm on Observation Duty</strong>, where you monitor security cameras and spot differences in various locations.<br/><br/>Enter a world with an eerie post-apocalyptic atmosphere where humanity has disappeared without a trace. As a survivor, your task is to examine different abandoned and liminal spaces, and report anomalies.<br/><br/>Stay vigilant for unexpected guests and make it through to dawn!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Report hundreds of anomalies across four dilapidated settings: an arctic log cabin, an office space, a supermarket and an opera house<br/></li><li> Click on objects to file a report<br/></li><li> Select from four levels of difficulty<br/></li><li> Encounter a wide array of anomalies, from the easily noticeable to those that are incredibly subtle<br/></li><li> Face entities in various spine-chilling scenarios<br/></li><li> Earn Steam Achievements for conquering the Nightmare mode and reporting Special Anomalies</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guerra Civil</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2856640/Guerra_Civil/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2856640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Turn-based strategy, based on the Spanish Civil War of 1936.<br>
<br>
You have your Revolutionaries.<br>
Assign your Revolutionaries to produce food, coal, iron, arms and make propaganda.<br>
<br>
You have to manage resources so that no one will starve.<br>
<br/>
With your armed Revolutionaries you will form a resistance block and then regain control over the mother Spain.<br/>
<br/>
Good luck Commandanté!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dampf - The Cozy Tower Defense</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2529290/Dampf__The_Cozy_Tower_Defense/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2529290/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Time to get cozy for the next defense:</strong><br/>Dampf - The Cozy Tower Defense is a tower defense to relax in the meantime. It does not try to be more than that.<br/>It combines a stylistic &amp; futuristic steampunk style with simple tower defense and resource management.<br/><br/><strong>Content:</strong><br/>Manage 3 resources through houses or factories.<br/>Defend your base from enemy attacks.<br/>Build and upgrade 4 different towers to defend yourself from tanks, planes or airships.<br/>Master all 4 levels with 4 different difficulty levels!<br/>Unlock up to 20 different perks to give you more advantages and ways to play.<br/>Allow as much time as you need for preparation. The start of the next wave is up to you!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extraction Force</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2090100/Extraction_Force/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/MasterBanner01.png?t=1711003230"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>WISHLIST TO ENLIST!</strong></h2><br/>Join the <strong>Extraction Force</strong> today and prepare for battle. Head behind enemy lines in this <i>vehicle based combat game</i> and destroy everything in your path as you race against the clock to locate and secure stolen nuclear launch codes. Take to the skies and rain down destruction from above with the fast and agile chopper, or bulldoze your way into enemy territory with the rough and tough tank as you fight your way through a dozen progressively more difficult missions.  <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/PageBreakSmall.png?t=1711003230"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>** THE WORLD IS DEPENDING ON YOU! **</strong></h2> Let nothing stand in your way... <strong>Failure is not an option!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/NuclearBlastGif.gif?t=1711003230"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/PageBreak.png?t=1711003230"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/UpdatedTank.png?t=1711003230"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Heavily armored and the perfect tool for destruction.<br/></li><li> Slow moving but it packs an explosive punch to make up for it.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/Tank2k4gif.gif?t=1711003230"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/PageBreakSmall.png?t=1711003230"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/UpdatedChopper.png?t=1711003230"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Armed with rockets to rain destruction from the sky.<br/></li><li> Fast and agile flight allows the pilot to avoid most incoming enemy attacks.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/ChopperAnim01.gif?t=1711003230"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/ChopperAnim02.gif?t=1711003230"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/PageBreakSmall.png?t=1711003230"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/UpdatedJeep.png?t=1711003230"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Fast but defenseless, the Jeep is used to retrieve the nuclear launch codes and return them safely to your base.<br/></li><li> Driving over ammo crates may provide the driver with grenades to toss out the window.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/JeepAnim01.gif?t=1711003230"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/JeepAnim02.gif?t=1711003230"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/FlagCapture_Small.gif?t=1711003230"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/PageBreakSmall.png?t=1711003230"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2090100/extras/TheEnemy.png?t=1711003230"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAPP: Just Another Precise Platformer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2569910/JAPP_Just_Another_Precise_Platformer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2569910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>JAPP:</strong><i> Just Another Precise Platformer</i> is a mouse based 2D precision platformer that is quite challenging.<br/>But when you have the physics of the game in your fingers, it's a pure bliss.<br/><br/>Climb to the top the fastest possible way is your mission on this game! <br/>You can (for now) play 2 characters, the <strong>Square</strong> &amp; the <strong>Circle</strong>. <br/>Both have their advantages and disadvantages, but you can climb to the top as fast with both. <br/><br/>I hope you will enjoy this as much as I enjoyed making this game. <br/><br/><strong>Have fun :)</strong> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>強運傭兵と宝石の姫騎士 - Fortunate Duo -</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2843200/__Fortunate_Duo/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2843200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"- Fortunate Duo - 強運傭兵と宝石の姫騎士" is a novel game that depicts the lucky Mercenary and the Princess Knight's journey as he becomes a close aide and achieves success along the way.<br>
A Bishojo Game released in 2016 under the "Black Currant" brand has been reworked for the "PandaShojo" platform for players around the world to enjoy.<br>
<br>
<br>
◆Introduction<br>
The day after defeating the self-proclaimed chess king at a tavern...<br>
A group of imposing soldiers arrived to take Alf away.<br/>
"Come with us. Princess Cheryl is waiting."<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
◆Synopsis<br/>
Humanity has allowed the invasion of the Demon King's forces.<br/>
It was later referred to as the era of the 'The Great Human-Demon War'.<br/>
<br/>
While some nations rose to fight against the Demon King, others took the opportunity to start a war.<br/>
The conflict extended beyond the battle between humans and demons, and the entire land was plunged into chaos.<br/>
<br/>
"The lucky mercenary Alf enjoys drinking in a tavern along with his companions...<br/>
nursing an ambition to achieve great feats and become a close aide to the princess knight.<br/>
<br/>
Princess Cheryl of the Kingdom of Ruby, Princess Eve of the Kingdom of Jade, and Princess Mary of the Kingdom of Azure.<br/>
Despite being women, they stood at the forefront of the battle against the Demon King, earning them the title of Savior.<br/>
<br/>
Alf made up his mind and headed to one of the Three Great Nations.<br/>
To become a mercenary aiding the saviors...<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
◆Characters<br/>
・Cheryl Hanover<br/>
"Don’t worry, there's nothing that I can't handle."<br/>
The princess of the Kingdom of Ruby. Dignified and possesses top-tier swordsmanship.<br/>
She hears about Alf's victory over the Chess King and decides to hire him.<br/>
Initially tough and brash, spending time with Alf changes her way of thinking.<br/>
<br/>
・Eve Cecil<br/>
"Your affinity and the magic power circulating inside me is quite remarkable."<br/>
The princess of the Kingdom of Jade. Skilled in both beauty and military strategy.<br/>
Upon the advice of the wizard who has long served Eve, she chooses Alf as her aide.<br/>
Being the daughter of a concubine, she resents her privileged brothers solely for being male and has developed an aversion to men.<br/>
<br/>
・Mary Godwin<br/>
"Onii-chan...? You're my Onii-chan, right!?"<br/>
The princess of the Kingdom of Azure, who takes the sword to avenge her deceased brother.<br/>
However, being unable to accept her brother's death, she refers to Alf as "Onii-chan".<br/>
Being gentle and timid, she's completely unsuited for battle, but alongside Alf she begins to improve as a knight.<br/>
<br/>
・Alf Alcott<br/>
A day-to-day mercenary, dreaming of one day achieving great feats.<br/>
Fortunately, he has survived from numerous battles.<br/>
Perhaps from his luck, he receives an offer to serve as an aide to the princess knight.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planetary Parfait</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2721860/Planetary_Parfait/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2721860/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Based on ASU’s Mars Space Flight Facility JMARS GIS tool, Planetary Parfait is a platform designed to support a wide range of scientific research tasks, including geologic mapping, feature analysis, and mission planning. The platform includes a variety of tools and features to support these tasks, such as 3D visualization, annotation tools, and data layers that can be overlaid on top of the terrain data. It is intended to be used by researchers and scientists working in fields such as planetary geology, geography, and geophysics, as well as by educators and students interested in learning about planetary science.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Whiskers in: the Search for Mr. Fumbleclaw</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1545610/Scott_Whiskers_in_the_Search_for_Mr_Fumbleclaw/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1545610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Join Scott Whiskers on his quest to find Mr. Fumbleclaw – the future star of the legendary cat beauty contest “Ricky’s Finest”.<br/><br/><strong>“Scott Whiskers in: the Search for Mr. Fumbleclaw”</strong> is a modern, funny and family-friendly point &amp; click adventure about cats, Star Trek and life itself. Created in the spirit of the classics of the genre. Classics like Monkey Island, Broken Sword or Zak McKracken.<br/><br/>Visit many colorful, crazy, forbidden, dangerous, scary, and also totally boring locations.<br/>Meet crazy characters and solve tricky puzzles.<br/><br/>Will you find Mr. Fumbleclaw and bring the story to a furry conclusion? It’s up to you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1545610/extras/Jimmy_English.gif?t=1710971486"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A game about our four-legged furry friends</strong></h2><br/><br/><strong>“Scott Whiskers in: the Search for Mr. Fumbleclaw”</strong> is a game about cats and lots of other furry friends.<br/><br/>Furry friends like Buddy, the faithful German shepherd with a rather unhealthy fixation on fine-grained cat litter.<br/><br/>Or furry friends like Steve, the rat. Steve is not to be trifled with – after all, he provides security at the sales stall of the dodgy yet likable crook Bob.<br/><br/>Or furry friends like the hamster Mr. Snuggels, who, if things go badly, could face a fate as a movie monster on the big screen.<br/><br/>Or furry friends like the nameless, extremely dangerous – and certainly deadly – Chihuahua that guards the Longbottom family estate. It is up to you to survive this encounter safely.<br/><br/>And last but not least, we have Mr. Fumbleclaw himself, the award-winning, perennial champion of the legendary feline beauty contest “Ricky’s Finest”, who has inexplicably vanished from the face of the earth. Your mission? Find the cat – save the day!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1545610/extras/Pizza.gif?t=1710971486"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">A game about people</h2></strong><br/><strong>“Scott Whiskers in: the Search for Mr. Fumbleclaw”</strong> is a game about people.<br/><br/>People like Mary, the lonely soul, Scott’s boss, and the caring director of the city’s animal shelter. Help Mary find love – and the bad boy of her dreams!<br/><br/>People like little Susie, Lord Longbottom’s daughter. Susie may be a little crazy, but she is hell-bent on making the perfect monster movie. And she is now looking for a way to turn her hamster Mr. Snuggles into a vicious movie monster! Will you help Susie fulfill her dream – or will you stand by poor Mr. Snuggles? It’s up to you!<br/><br/>People like chain-smoking pet groomer Ricky, host of the legendary feline beauty contest “Ricky’s Finest”. And the keeper of a hairy and immensely profitable secret.<br/><br/>Or people like Alfredo, inventor of a sensational vegan cheese pizza topped with ceiling mushrooms. Never heard of ceiling mushrooms? Alfredo will explain it to you!<br/><br/>Or people like the almost forgotten old-school movie star Vlad Popescu. Help the once so celebrated Dracula actor overcome his depression and make his return to the big screen.<br/><br/>You see – there is a lot to do!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1545610/extras/Street_English.gif?t=1710971486"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A game with tricky puzzles</strong></h2><br/><br/>What would a point &amp; click adventure game be without tricky puzzles? Combine items from your inventory in the right way, unlock further paths of your entertaining journey in dialogues, and interact with numerous objects, characters, and four-legged friends.<br/>All tasks in “Scott Whiskers in: the Search for Mr. Fumbleclaw” can be solved logically with a little puzzling – even if it doesn’t hurt to think outside the box now and then.<br/><br/>To help you not lose sight of the many, many objectives on the search for Mr. Fumbleclaw, an automatically created journal helps you to keep track of everything at all times. In order for you to not miss any interesting events, a “hotspot highlight” can be activated at any time to help you highlight important objects in the current scene.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Features</strong></h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>a gripping story about animals, people, and life itself, told with a big wink<br/></li><li>beautifully hand-drawn, high-resolution backgrounds in combination with three-dimensional characters give the game its very own visual charm<br/></li><li>a captivating soundtrack you won’t be able to get out of your head for a long time<br/></li><li>an automatic journal of your journey and tasks<br/></li><li>hotspot display that can be activated at any time<br/></li><li>free and automatic saving<br/></li><li>unlock many achievements<br/></li><li>duration: approx. 12 hours</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LISA: The First</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2743030/LISA_The_First/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2743030/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Explore Lisa Armstrong’s mind as she tries to cope with the burden caused by her father Marty.<br>
Traverse a slipping reality as you attempt to leave home and recover your memories.<br>
Only, escape is not so easy. <br>
<br>
Features and Gameplay<br>
<br>
- LISA the First is a short and surreal exploration game reminiscent of retro-RPGs.<br/>
- Navigate the twisting world of Lisa’s mind, finding hidden doors and pathways to strange and exotic places.<br/>
- Explore these spaces to uncover Lisa’s memories and unveil the sinister forces laying in wait.<br/>
- Interact with a cast of dark and strange characters who persist across multiple memories.<br/>
- Collect faded thoughts as VHS tapes, and seek a way to replay them in order to gain insight into the sights and sounds you encounter.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking Craze</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2540630/Cooking_Craze/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2540630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cook up a storm serving food from around the world playing our free restaurant game Cooking Craze. Prepare, cook &amp; serve tasty dishes like a professional chef and master the kitchen as you click to grill, bake and cook your way to the top.<br>
<br>
Bake wood-fired pizza in Rome, grill juicy burgers in New York and prepare fine French cuisine in Paris — but be careful, playing fast isn’t enough! You need to keep your customers happy in order to grow your empire. Can you take the heat, Chef?<br>
<br>
Cook classic restaurant dishes from across the globe;<br>
• Make hundreds of delicious dishes including burgers, pizza, sushi, ramen, dumplings and more<br>
• Grill fresh fish, tasty steak, succulent shrimp, and veggie kabobs<br>
• Love desserts? Why not deep fry sweet donuts, bake baklava, serve ice cream, cheesecake or cakes?<br/>
<br/>
Create a Restaurant Empire!<br/>
• Choose from over 100 ingredients cooking up tasty cuisine<br/>
• Create premium dishes with delicious new ingredients<br/>
• Launch new restaurants while learning new cooking techniques<br/>
• Add a new recipe from each city you visit<br/>
• Cook in a variety of settings<br/>
<br/>
Level up with Cooking Quests, Powerful Boosts and features!<br/>
• Serve food fast while managing your time to earn kitchen upgrades<br/>
• Beat over 4000 levels across six continents<br/>
• Master all 3 difficulty levels to get golden comment cards to earn free coins and spoons<br/>
• Dash through service to earn BIG TIPS or work extra shifts to earn money for upgrades<br/>
• Equip your chef with treats for customers, non-stick pans and MORE!<br/>
• Upgrade your kitchen &amp; increase your speed<br/>
• Use a variety of special boosts to cook your way to victory<br/>
• Cook GREEN with an Eco Boost &amp; go organic for more tips<br/>
• Win achievements by completing combos, cooking perfect meals &amp; earning big tips<br/>
<br/>
The best restaurant gaming experience:<br/>
• New levels and cities around the world added regularly<br/>
• Hours of free fun, whenever, wherever you want!<br/>
• Play online or OFFLINE WITHOUT WIFI or internet after initial download!<br/>
<br/>
Download Cooking Craze and create your own kitchen empire!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCP: Descent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2757220/SCP_Descent/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							How many people were lost to the eternal stairwell before it was shut away from the world? What happened to those cursed to walk the liminal spaces for eternity?<br/><br/>Descend the stairwell armed with nothing but a torch and some pieces of chalk while you attempt to keep the monsters at bay. You do not take the journey alone as you are guided by recordings of those who came before. Uncover the reasoning behind the stairwell and look for the exit, if there is one.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>Approximately 60-90 minutes<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757220/extras/PaleOne1.gif?t=1711012846"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2> - Torchlight: Your light is your best way to navigate the dark depths, but use with caution as those who reside below are drawn to it.<br/> - Stealth Indicator: While moving through the stairwell, every action from running, to direct light, to proximity will increase your chances of getting caught. Manage when to make a break for it to avoid capture.<br/> - Limited Saves: The only way to save the game is by marking the walls with pieces of chalk. Choose carefully when and where to save.<h2 class="bb_tag">Solve Puzzles</h2>Those who came before have barred the way, solve their puzzles and prove you are worthy to descend.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2757220/extras/Puzzle1.gif?t=1711012846"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wizard Party</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2688110/The_Wizard_Party/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You awake, accidentally trapped in a surreal world because a bunch of wizards are having a party in the dream realm. Chat to peculiar and delightful characters, mix and combine ideas together to solve puzzles, and explore the dream realm as you try and free your soul by finding the host of, The Wizard Party!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688110/extras/ezgif.com-resize.gif?t=1710979123"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Meet  35+ absurd animated characters! 🍄</li><li> Ask them about 50+ thoughts! 💭</li><li> 'ideas' interact to make new ones! 💡</li><li>Secret rooms and ending! 🔮 </li><li>It's short, surreal and sweet! 🍬</li></ul><br/>Kia ora! I am Jack // nobones. <br/>This is my second game and I am really proud of it. I brought in my skills as a 2D animator, love of making weird little creatures, and compulsion to fill things with silly jokes with lots of heart. Thank you for reading this far and I hope The Wizard Party brings you some joy!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2688110/extras/ezgif.com-resize_1_.gif?t=1710979123"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradox Hr</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2842280/Paradox_Hr/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2842280/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Paradox Hr is a type of Program and Software and is not a game<br>
It automatically generates codes and is unique.<br>
 Designed for Computer Users<br>
<br>
Detailed information is included in the attachment.<br>
The program records the passwords generated by the users and generates separate codes for each Computer User,<br>
Since each computer user produces consecutive codes, the codes created by a different computer user do not match within the program.<br/>
<br/>
Program &amp; Software<br/>
<br/>
Paradox HR<br/>
Added as a timekeeping crafted on a simple<br/>
clock theme<br/>
Rather than displaying it, Paradox Hr will<br/>
always give you a small-digit numerical<br/>
and alphabetical<br/>
gives codes and passwords.<br/>
your passwords as your thoughts, e-mail,<br/>
account, and when creating any<br/>
registration for record<br/>
You can use passwords everything.<br/>
Paradox HR<br/>
Basic operation ,When you start the clock<br/>
work in real life thanks to the codes<br/>
You can save your code reliability if you<br/>
want, or you can build a new code.<br/>
What does it do or is it safe?<br/>
What is the security level of the codes in any<br/>
attack?<br/>
<br/>
Paradox Hr constantly redirects the codes as there is<br/>
software in case of any<br/>
attack.<br/>
This means clicking on the messages sent by any<br/>
attacker or text fraudster.<br/>
does not change.<br/>
because the codes are in the clock setting, the clock<br/>
wheels lock and close the<br/>
codes.<br/>
To attack new offensive code, attackers use the<br/>
network connection path<br/>
contained in the software code and<br/>
It cannot pass its stages, so it must have an advanced<br/>
computer system to decode<br/>
it.<br/>
A computer can only display code as it brings in 1<br/>
million.<br/>
but cannot use it.<br/>
He doesn't have a clue as to how the code is set up<br/>
and where it works.<br/>
Paradox HR or paradox clock (hr-hour) is a cylinder<br/>
that works as a chain.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planetstar Warrior</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2850120/Planetstar_Warrior/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2850120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Planetstar Warrior is a 2D horizontal side-scrolling space shooter game that puts you up against a invading <br>
enemy force trying to take over the galaxy!<br>
<br>
Story <br>
The galaxy is under threat by a mysterious alien force its up to you to stop the onslaught, Equip yourself with <br>
multiple power ups and fight through the increasing enemy waves, Can you reach the mothership and put a stop <br>
to the invasion once and for all?<br/>
<br/>
Key Features<br/>
Collect power ups to destroy invading alien spaceships.<br/>
Battle through 15 levels of space with increasing difficulty.<br/>
Destroy the mothership to save the galaxy.<br/>
<br/>
Tips<br/>
Keep moving to avoid enemy fire!<br/>
Be sure to grab shields power ups!<br/>
Wait for the right moment to use your special!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saw Lab</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2845160/Saw_Lab/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2845160/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Saw Lab</strong>: Test Your Survival Instinct<br/><br/>In a world where every second could be your last, your fate lies in the hands of a mad genius. <i>"Saw Lab"</i> is not just a survival game; it's a test of your mind, willpower, and ability to act under the pressure of unbearable fear.<br/><br/>You wake up in a dark, sinister laboratory, shackled in chains. The only source of light is a flickering television screen that suddenly comes to life, presenting you with a horrifying choice: to cut off your own leg to free yourself. This is just the beginning... Ahead of you lie challenges that will make your blood run cold: searching for keys and codes, running from monsters, dodging spike traps, bear traps, death mazes, rooms filled with lasers, and puzzles requiring you to find a gas mask in a deadly atmosphere.<br/><br/>Every decision here is a matter of life and death. Choosing a door can lead you to salvation... or into a trap with no escape. <i>"Saw Lab"</i> is not just a game; it's a test of your ability to think logically, make decisions under extreme conditions, and trust your instincts.<br/><br/><u>Game Features:</u><br/>- <strong>An unpredictable story</strong> that will make your heart race.<br/>- <strong>A series of unique puzzles and traps</strong> that require creative thinking and quick reflexes.<br/>- <strong>An atmosphere of constant tension</strong>, enhanced by a gloomy soundtrack and visual effects.<br/>- <strong>Decisions that affect the outcome</strong> of the story: every step you take can lead to an unexpected end.<br/><br/>Are you ready to face your fears and find out what you're capable of in the name of survival? "Saw Lab" awaits those who are willing to go through hell to find their freedom. The game has begun... Can you finish it?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project RyME</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2222930/Project_RyME/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2222930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2222930/extras/story_divider.png?t=1710950417"><br/><br/>Six months had passed since Mira's father disappeared and was presumed dead. The other day an old computer of his showed up mysteriously. It's unlike any computer she had seen before and convinced her the answer to his disappearance could be found on it. As the last person with any hope of her father's survival, she eagerly began investigating.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2222930/extras/gamplay_divider.png?t=1710950417"><br/><br/>Project RyME is a puzzle adventure game where you investigate a strange, old computer to get to the bottom of Mira's father's disappearance. With the help of some interesting allies, use a variety of techniques to hack your way into systems that might have clues. Over the course of the investigation you'll experience at least a dozen different game genres.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2222930/extras/features_divider.png?t=1710950417"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Navigate a simulated desktop computer's windowing system<br/></li><li>Use the command terminal to access other computers, run advanced operations and explore the network.<br/></li><li>Hack into various systems using techniques inspired by real cybersecurity vulnerabilities.<br/></li><li>Chat with your allies to discuss strategies, review clues and talk about your favorite anime.<br/></li><li>Play through a variety of digital worlds and minigames that are tightly woven into the story.<br/></li><li>An interactive tutorial and extensive in-game resources make Project RyME accessible even for those without much knowledge about computers.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clocked</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2807110/Clocked/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2807110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2807110/extras/Banner_Desc_1_en.png?t=1710974135"><br/><strong>The adventure takes place in a steampunk universe, within a Great Clock (thought as Big Ben), an unpretentious building where scientific activity takes place, as part of research into new energy sources... or so the story goes.</strong><br/>You take on the role of an automaton, limited to moving, running and interacting, accompanied by a calculator-being that will stick with you until the end of the adventure.<br/>The building is labyrinthine, forcing you to make numerous trips back and forth in order to progress through the story, a classic piece of architecture.<br/>The puzzles are simple, all you have to do is find notes containing activation codes for generators.<br/>The adventure is meant to be short, but it will take longer to uncover all that Clocked hides.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2807110/extras/Banner_Desc_2_en.png?t=1710974135"><br/><strong>The game is simple on the surface, but will be more difficult in this other dimension.</strong><br/>You'll have to use your dexterity to avoid the symbiotic clusters that will surprise you during your health walk.<br/>This is an important dimension, as it will give you access to areas that are normally inaccessible...think about it!<br/>You'll be juggling between the "default" world and this one to navigate the Great Clock.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2807110/extras/Banner_Desc_3_en.png?t=1710974135"><br/><strong>A classic adventure, but a story full of mystery, unclear on the surface.</strong><br/>There's a lot to discover in Clocked, and the adventure revolves more around exploration than escape from the Great Clock.<br/>There are several endings, each offering a unique experience, packed with information about the history surrounding the Great Clock.<br/>Don't forget to chat with your calculator friend, he's very chatty.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easter 2024 Puzzle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2858000/Easter_2024_Puzzle/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2858000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Easter 2024 Puzzle</strong> is an puzzel game with beautiful easter eggs in an stunning synthwave style. You have to assemble a single image from random generated indivdual pieces. <br/>Combine all of the smart singel frames into one big image and unlock the next level.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 Levels<br/></li><li> 25 to 69 frames<br/></li><li> very difficult puzzle adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easter 2024 Memory</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2857990/Easter_2024_Memory/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2857990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Easter 2024 Memory</strong> is an casual memory game with stunning images in the synthwave style. You have to find all of the correct pairs to complete the game. your best round will be count and always be displayed in game, to compare your rounds. try to reduce your turns every game and set up your new record.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 stunning different memory cards<br/></li><li> 24 memory cards in total<br/></li><li> casual memory adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> count of ur best round<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slice &amp; Dice</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1775490/Slice__Dice/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1775490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Slice &amp; Dice is a tactical dice battle roguelike.<br/><br/>Take control of 5 heroes, each with their own unique dice. Fight your way through 20 levels of monsters and try to take on the final boss. If you lose a single fight you have to start over so be careful/lucky!<br/><br/><strong>Gameplay</strong><br/>- 3D dice physics, choose which dice to reroll<br/>- Simple turn-based combat<br/>- Level up a hero or gain an item after each fight<br/>- Randomly-generated encounters<br/>- Ridiculous combos<br/>- Undo actions as much as you like<br/>- Each turn is like a mini-puzzle<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/>- 128 hero classes (+99999?)<br/>- 73 monsters<br/>- 473 items<br/>- Too many modes<br/>- ∞ curses<br/>- Weird modding<br/>- Online leaderboards<br/><br/><strong>Credits</strong><br/>- Created by tann (it took ~7 years)<br/>- Pixel art by a3um<br/>- Music by Ziggurath, Aleksander Zabłocki, Louigi Verona, Cold Sanctum, Ro'sø, Andrew Goodwin<br/>- Trailer by Everdraed<br/><br/>I plan to not participate in any sales/deals/bundles. No AI was used to make this game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1310410/Alone_in_the_Dark/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Alone in the Dark weaves a chilling tapestry of psychological horror and Southern Gothic charm, reimagining the iconic game that set the benchmark for the genre. We invite you to join us on a journey into madness, where each encounter could be your last. With each step you take closer to unravelling Derceto's mystery, the eyes that watch from the darkness grow hungrier. Every bullet means the difference between survival and an unthinkable end. The next door you unlock could lead to a nightmarish realm offering nothing but slashing claws, grasping tentacles, and frayed sanity.  Journey to interbellum Louisiana, where an era of decadence hides a darker tale - of escape from past traumas and an intolerant society, into the waiting grasp of something darker, something that has patiently lurked for impossible eons. This is Alone in the Dark as you've never seen it - a skillfully-woven narrative of Southern Gothic elegance and eldritch madness that pays homage to its legendary origins while taking the next step forward in survival horror storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_VIPIntro_2.gif?t=1710945887"><h2 class="bb_tag">A Haunting Tale of Mystery and Madness</h2>Step inside Derceto Manor, an asylum shrouded in intrigue, guarding a terrible secret. Client Emily Hartwood and private investigator Edward Carnby embark on a harrowing quest for answers; Emily to the mystery of her missing uncle, Edward to the toughest case he will ever face, and both to questions they dare not ask themselves. This re-envisioned classic invites you to explore an unforgettable single player adventure rich with suspense, frights, and revelations that will test the limits of your imagination.<h2 class="bb_tag">Featuring Hollywood Talent</h2>Experience some of the greatest acting survival horror has ever seen through the performances of award-winning actors Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow) in their first videogame roles. Jodie and David’s immaculately captured likenesses breathe life into Emily Hartwood and Edward Carnby, lending a deeply personal aspect to Alone in the Dark’s story that demands it be played twice to get the full experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Tribute to Horror Pioneers</h2>Rediscover the essence of psychological horror in a game that respectfully nods to its 1992 origin, the game that established the survival horror genre. Alone in the Dark is your gateway to an experience steeped in the atmospheric dread of classic horror, with next-generation storytelling and gameplay. A must-play for fans of twisted tales, nerve-wracking exploration, and desperate combat.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Story That Challenges Reality</h2>Envisioned by Mikael Hedberg, acclaimed writer behind modern horror classics “SOMA” and “Amnesia”, Alone in the Dark’s intricate web of mystery delves into themes of trauma, faith, evil, and abandonment. Whether you choose to brave the nightmare as Emily or Edward, you will uncover secrets that defy everything you thought about videogame storytelling.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Atrmo_2.gif?t=1710945887"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore Derceto Manor in this reimagination of Alone in the Dark, a love letter to the 90’s cult classic horror game.<br/></li><li>Return to the roots of psychological horror and experience an atmospheric journey worthy of the game that started the genre.<br/></li><li>Dive into a world full of sounds that make your skin crawl with a haunting, yet mesmerizing doom jazz soundtrack.<br/></li><li>Enjoy the thrill of desperate survival in a world where reality starts to crumble, evil lurks in every shadow and ammunition is scarce.<br/></li><li>Experience this nightmare from either Emily Hartwood’s or Edward Carnby’s perspective and unearth the dark secrets of a gothic mansion.<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in a deep psychological story that goes beyond the realms of the imaginable, by Mikael Hedberg, cult horror writer of SOMA and Amnesia.<br/></li><li>See Emily and Edward brought to live by the Hollywood talent of Jodie Comer (Killing Eve, Free Guy) and David Harbour (Stranger Things, Black Widow), who lend their voices, their appearance, and their formidable acting skills to the protagonists.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1310410/extras/GIF_Riddles_2.gif?t=1710945887"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
