<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Windowkill</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726450/Windowkill/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Something's wrong with the window...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/extras/bar.png?t=1708812124"><br/><br/>Windowkill is a twin-stick shooter, but the game window itself is constantly closing in on you. <br/>This game is experimental, your screen itself is the play area. Windows move and shift around on your screen as you play.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/extras/gif2.gif?t=1708812124"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Twin-stick shooter controls<br/></li><li> Roguelike permadeath<br/></li><li> Shop screens<br/></li><li> Upgrades and Perks<br/></li><li> Hordes of enemies and bosses<br/></li><li> Several unique characters<br/></li><li> Local co-op<br/></li><li> Unlocks<br/></li><li> Secrets</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/extras/gif3.gif?t=1708812124"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unlocks, Stats, and More</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/extras/gif1.gif?t=1708812124"><br/><br/>Mouse and keyboard is preferred, but gamepad is supported.<br/><br/>A game by torcado<br/>Music by keestak						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoversteppers: Zone 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2777190/Hoversteppers_Zone_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2777190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>This is a free prologue for Hoversteppers, and it includes:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>2 stages<br/></li><li>2 Characters, and the starter hoverboard<br/></li><li>10+ Challenges</li></ul><br/>Hoversteppers is a freestyle hoverboard skating game. Explore stages, complete challenges against the clock, or freestyle your own way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2777190/extras/steamGif2.gif?t=1708688865"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>5 unique stages<br/></li><li>Over 50 challenges to complete<br/></li><li>Unlockable characters, boards, and cosmetics<br/></li><li>A rich soundtrack of jungle / drum and bass, by talented artists Mr. Wax, Lunanescence, and Snowdream<br/></li><li>Multiple achievements to unlock</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solium Infernum</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1893810/Solium_Infernum/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare yourself for Solium Infernum, the grand strategy game of politics, intrigue and betrayal, set in the ultimate arena of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingDarkSide2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_IndulgeYourDarkSide_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Satan's mysteriously vanished and Hell is in an uproar. Play as one of eight all-powerful and menacing Archfiends and indulge your Machiavellian dark side. Command legions, enlist champions, cast sinister rituals, and trick, rob, and insult your rivals to be crowned Hell’s new Dark Majesty.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingStrategy2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_StrategyFromHell_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Experience Solium Infernum's legendary devilish political machinations. Requiring nerves of steel and a true heart of darkness, every order you give will have lasting consequences. Get into the minds of your rivals, second-guessing their every move both on the map and on the floor of Hell’s parliament as you sling insults and demands in the only truly political strategy game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Eight playable Archfiends<br/></li><li>Eight single-player Chronicles<br/></li><li>Single-player Skirmish mode<br/></li><li>Revelations Tutorial Scenario<br/></li><li>Sessional and Asynchronous 2-6 player Multiplayer<br/></li><li>Dozens of Infernal Legions, including unique enormous Titans. <br/></li><li>Champion Praetors and dark Artifacts fit for any Archfiend!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingMulitplayer.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_InfernalMultiplayer_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Play 2-6 player multiplayer games with your soon-to-be ex-friends in a single session of deceit and politics, or put your friendships to the test in quick daily bursts with Solium Infernum’s infamous asynchronous multiplayer for a truly harrowing scheme-in-your-sleep experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/Heading_DarkArt2.gif?t=1708670283"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_DivineMadness_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>If you love dark art, you’re in the right place. Brimming with striking visions of Hell unlike anything you’ve seen before, Solium Infernum is an infernal feast for the eyes with multitudes of individual dark paintings to enjoy. Every item of the game is accompanied by mind-blasting artwork, a feat declaring Solium Infernum a winner of the 2022 Game Makers Sketchbook.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/HeadingRessurect.gif?t=1708670283"><br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_CultClassic_eng.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Originally inspired by Milton’s epic poem, Paradise Lost, League of Geeks’ (known for seminal digital board game Armello) sophomore title is a re-imagining and modernisation of Vic Davis’ critically acclaimed cult-classic of the same name, hailed as a masterpiece of strategy game design. <br/><br/>Once again, prepare to lose yourself within ‘the cold glory of a difficult decision’ as we resurrect Solium Infernum from the depths of Hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/label_praise.png?t=1708670283"><br/>Note: The following quotes refer to the original Solium Infernum (2009) by Vic Davis.<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum is a political wargame set in hell… The game is now finished, and none of the friends survived. By which I mean, we all hate each other now.”</i> <br/>- Rock Paper Shotgun<br/><br/><i>“It’s a game about playing other people, in both senses of the word…. This is game design based on psychology as much as rules.” </i><br/>- Quarter to Three<br/><br/><i>“More than any game I've played in years, Solium Infernum nails the sensation of staring at a screen and losing yourself in the cold glory of a difficult decision.”</i><br/>- Game Developer (formerly Gamasutra)<br/><br/><i>“Solium Infernum kicked my knees out from under me ... this game took my past experience with strategy games and threw it, like a pro basketball player, into a bin eighty feet away.”</i><br/>- Eurogamer<br/><br/><i>“One of the best games of the year.”</i><br/>— Three Moves Ahead<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1893810/extras/SI_toReign.png?t=1708670283"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sons Of The Forest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1326470/Sons_Of_The_Forest/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							An entirely new experience from the makers of the ‘The Forest’<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1326470/extras/VirginiaWaterfall.gif?t=1708624856"><br/><br/>Sent to find a missing billionaire on a remote island, you find yourself in a cannibal-infested hellscape. Craft, build, and struggle to survive, alone or with friends, in this terrifying new open-world survival horror simulator.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Survival Horror Simulator</strong></h2><br/>Experience complete freedom to tackle the world how you want. You decide what you do, where to go and how best to survive. There are no NPC's barking orders at you or giving you missions you don't want to do. You give the orders, you choose what happens next.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fight Demons</strong></h2><br/>Enter a world where nowhere is safe and fight against a range of mutated creatures, some who are almost human like, and others who are like nothing you have ever seen before. Armed with pistols, axes, stun batons and more, protect yourself and those you care for.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Build and Craft</strong></h2><br/>Feel every interaction; Break sticks to make fires. Use an axe to cut out windows and floors. Build a small cabin, or a sea-side compound, the choice is yours.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Changing Seasons</strong></h2><br/>Pluck fresh salmon directly from streams in spring and summer. Collect and store meat for the cold winter months. You're not alone on this island, so as winter rolls in and food and resources become scarce you won't be the only one looking for a meal.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Co-op Gameplay</strong></h2><br/>Survive alone, or with friends. Share items and work together to build defenses. Bring back-up to explore above and below ground.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garden Life: A Cozy Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1915380/Garden_Life_A_Cozy_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/MASTER_GIF.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE1_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF1.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>Plant and nurture your dream garden using gardening techniques based in real life and adapted for everyone to enjoy:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Plant seeds, leaving them enough space to thrive<br/></li><li> Water, fertilize, and clip your plants to enhance their natural beauty and nurture them to health<br/></li><li> Discover different colourful varieties and unlock the full potential of each plant<br/></li><li> Pull out all weeds or choose to leave some to protect plants from pests<br/></li><li> Admire your plants in full bloom even through the changing seasons : in Garden Life, all plants thrive no matter the time of year!<br/></li><li> Play the story mode or the creative mode</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE2_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF2.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>You are in charge of an abandoned community garden and decide to roll up your sleeves to restore it to its former glory. Complete tasks given to you by your neighbours to earn rewards, unlock new tools, seeds, ornaments and areas of the garden, and learn more about what lies behind this secluded spot.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE3_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF3.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>Instantly unlock every corner of your garden, including all the seeds and ornaments, and give free rein to your creativity: in this restriction-free mode, you can bring your dream designs to life!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE4_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF4.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>Procedural growth simulation developed specifically for the game ensures each plant grows in its own way! Each and every plant grows procedurally, and some even adapt to their environment by climbing if planted close to certain objects.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE5_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF5.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>In Garden Life, you are not restricted by a grid: place plants and objects freely to create your designs!  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE6_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF6.gif?t=1708616161"><br/> <br/>Head to the village square to sell flowers and bouquets at your stall and use the earnings to buy new seeds, ornaments and tools in the shop. You can also donates flowers to help create huge floral sculptures in the pavilion and win adorable prizes! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/TITLE7_EN.gif?t=1708616161"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1915380/extras/GIF7.gif?t=1708616161"><br/><br/>Add Garden Life to your wishlist, follow us, and join our discord community so you don't miss out on any news!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Drive</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1458140/Pacific_Drive/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Pacific Drive is a first-person driving survival game with your car as your only companion. Navigate a surreal reimagining of the Pacific Northwest, and face supernatural dangers as you venture into the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Each excursion into the wilderness brings unique and strange challenges as you restore and upgrade your car from an abandoned garage that acts as your home base. Gather precious resources and investigate what’s been left behind in the Zone; unravel a long-forgotten mystery while learning exactly what it takes to survive in this unpredictable, hostile environment.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Outrun the storm while facing strange perils in a world that shifts with every journey into the Zone<br/></li><li>Your car, your way – scavenge resources to craft new equipment and configure your wagon how you want. Experiment with different mods and car parts to navigate a treacherous landscape, and look good doing it<br/></li><li>Unravel the mystery of the Olympic Exclusion Zone, an abandoned research site in an anomaly-filled version of the Pacific Northwest<br/></li><li>Original score by Wilbert Roget, II and featuring 20+ licensed songs</li></ul><br/><strong>DRIVE TO SURVIVE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/DriveToSurvive2.jpg?t=1708641540"><br/>It’s you and your station wagon against an unforgiving, vicious world. It’ll take more than a fresh set of tires to keep you alive, on and off the road. Your faithful wagon can be upgraded and reinforced to protect you, but the car is going to take a beating. Keep your gas tank filled and your panels intact to withstand the radiation permeating the Zone. You’ll be pushed to your limit - making repairs on the fly, scavenging materials wherever you can, and adapting your rolling fortress to tackle the many life-threatening dangers that lurk in the shadows.<br/><br/><strong>INVESTIGATE THE ZONE</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Investigatethezone123.png?t=1708641540"><br/>The experimental leftovers of the secretive ARDA organization remain scattered across the Zone, and finding answers won’t be easy. Everywhere you look you’ll find anomalies, surreal forces of a twisted nature that make your journey more difficult... or more interesting. Silhouettes in the dark, rolling piles of scrap metal, and towering pillars of earth - each trip is packed with otherworldly hazards. As terrifying as those may be, nothing compares to the overwhelming power of a Zone Storm. Stomp on the gas and outrun it if you can - these rolling maelstroms rend the landscape and obliterate anything that sticks around too long. Don’t let that be you.<br/><br/><strong>REPEAT</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1458140/extras/Repeat2.png?t=1708641540"><br/>Check the map, pack some gear for the trip, and hit the road. Gather resources and collect data as you go, there’s all sorts of useful stuff inside the walls of the Zone. Make it back safely and use the contents of your trunk to improve your car and garage. Every time you venture out, new trials await: bizarre weather, unforgiving landscapes, and experimental remnants. The golden rule in the Zone is ‘nothing ventured, nothing gained’ — some materials can only be found in the most dangerous places. Be smart out there, and don’t waste time — it’s going to be a long haul.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruindog:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802430/RuindogPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 2 are available in the prologue and 4 are available in the official version.<br/>Maps: 2 in the prologue, 4 in the official version<br/>Weapons: 3 in the prologue, 26 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/11z.jpg?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>A long, long time ago, in a solar system not so far away, alien bugs invaded Earth, but they were soon beaten back home, and by the way, their home planet was blown up. After centuries of being invincible, it became popular for humans to watch live alien hunting shows, participate in alien hunts, save up money, equipment, and use the various loot they found to keep going to new maps and defeating more powerful enemies. </strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/1z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Enemies will come at you from all sides on every level, proceed with caution or you'll be torn to pieces in an instant</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/3z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Each character has a different growth path and active skills, utilize these skills and choose the most appropriate item for the current hero to achieve the mission objective</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5y.png?t=1708706298"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802430/extras/5z.gif?t=1708706298"><br/><strong>Earn more resources and achieve various mission objectives to unlock different maps/difficulties and even new map mechanics!<br/>Each map has very different mission objectives and combat mechanics, so choose the one that better suits the current mechanic to win the game</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myth of Empires</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1371580/Myth_of_Empires/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Embark Upon a Thrilling Journey</h2>Explore a land with diverse landscapes, ecologies, and weather, as well as a realistic day/night cycle. The v1.0 release of Myth of Empires also features a new map – Dongzhou Island, offering new adventures and challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/11111探索之旅，发现新世界的惊险旅程.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build Your Own Empire From the Ground Up</h2>Myth of Empires features sandbox gameplay with a high degree of freedom; the game has 1300+ different crafting recipe, allowing you to build your own empire. The v1.0 release adds new recipes, including mechanical tools and base defenses, as well as a new planting system. The possibilities are endless.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/22222自由创造，打造你的帝国.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Recruit NPCs, Tame Wildlife</h2>In-depth taming and training systems allow players to recruit or subdue additional forces to aid them in combat and production. The v1.0 release adds new boss NPCs and powerful beasts. In addition, smaller types of animals can be used to help power your base’s defenses.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/333333驯服万物，NPC、马匹与野生动物.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Wage Epic Wars on Ancient Battlefields</h2> Myth of Empires features hundreds of different weapons, armor, and large-scale engineering equipment. Pick the weapons that best suit your playstyle, or utilize your strategic capabilities to build an army. The v1.0 release introduces powerful mechanical base defenses, wooden oxen, and other new combat equipment to further enrich the game’s deep war experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/444444史诗战争体验，挑战百变的古代战场.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Engage in Cross-server Battles </h2>Establish administrative regions, fight for the position of county magistrate, and compete to expand your territory through Fortress Battles. Craft the perfect guild and utilize your diplomatic prowess to ensure its long-term stability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/555555跨服征战，共同创造历史.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Write Your Own Legend </h2>With 25 different development paths, a 16-level title system, and more than 100 achievements, you have complete freedom in growing your character. Become a legendary military commander, or content yourself with the life of a simple farmer – the choice is yours.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/666666传奇生涯，定制独特的人生.gif?t=1708657778"><h2 class="bb_tag">Play Multiple Gameplay Modes Offering Endless Possibilities </h2>Myth of Empires supports official servers, custom servers, as well as solo and hosted modes. Creative players are also able to use the game’s robust mod editor to tailor the game to their dream experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1371580/extras/no7多样玩法.gif?t=1708657778"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Epoch</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/899770/Last_Epoch/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Last Epoch combines time travel, exciting dungeon crawling, engrossing character customization and endless replayability to create an Action RPG for veterans and newcomers alike. Travel through the world of Eterra’s past and face dark empires, wrathful gods and untouched wilds – to find a way to save time itself from The Void.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Gameplay.gif?t=1708534852"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>15 Mastery Classes</strong><br/>Embark on your adventure as one of five powerful classes and, through your journey, ascend into a unique Mastery Class that unlocks more specialized abilities and build-options. <br/></li><li><strong>120+ Skill Trees</strong><br/>Every skill has its own augment tree that will allow you to control, alter, and empower your playstyle. Transform your skeletons into archers, your lightning blast into chain lightning, or make your serpent strike summon snakes to fight alongside you!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Nodes.gif?t=1708534852"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Hunt Rare &amp; Powerful Loot</strong><br/>Fill your arsenal with magic items that you may craft to perfection, change the rules of your build with powerful unique and set items, and always have that next upgrade just on the horizon with Last Epoch's deep and randomized loot system.<br/></li><li><strong>Rewarding Crafting System</strong><br/>The items you wield are yours to forge! Last Epoch’s community-revered crafting system allows you to control your character's power progression, featuring robust and deterministic upgrade mechanics.<br/></li><li><strong>Uncover the Past, Reforge the Future</strong><br/>Travel to different moments of time where you will discover the many factions and secrets that exist within the world of Eterra and fight to set the timeline onto a new path.<br/></li><li><strong>Endless replayability</strong><br/>With a wealth of classes and skills to customize, deep game systems, randomized loot, and continuing development, Last Epoch is a game that will keep you coming back for years to come.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/899770/extras/LastEpoch_Monolith.gif?t=1708534852"><br/><br/></img></li><li><strong>Easy to Learn, Hard to Master</strong><br/>We’re committed to making gameplay approachable for new and veteran players alike by allowing you to jump into the fray quickly and providing many in-game resources. Though don’t be fooled, Eterra has many dangers waiting for you that require a mastery of combat and build-crafting.<br/></li><li><strong>Zero Pay-To-Win</strong><br/>Last Epoch will never offer gameplay advantages by being able to spend real money. We believe in creating a fair environment for all players. </li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandle Tale: A League of Legends Story</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1759380/Bandle_Tale_A_League_of_Legends_Story/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							One little Yordle, one humongous problem.<br/><br/>From Lazy Bear, the studio that brought you Graveyard Keeper, comes Bandle Tale: A League of Legends Story™. Jump into this delightful crafting RPG set in the magical world of Bandle City, home of the furry and fun-loving yordles.<br/><br/>You are a shy yordle living in Yarnville, a cozy but isolated island obsessed with all things knitting. When your 101-year-long apprenticeship ends, you want nothing more than to see what lies beyond the portals that connect the rest of Bandle City. But when a party you attend goes horribly wrong, the portals collapse and everything is thrown into chaos!<br/><br/>With your unique knitting magic and unflappable spirit, enlist the help of new friends, restore the portals, and reunite Bandle City once more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Steam-Breaker-Image-616x100.jpg?t=1708719402"><br/><br/>BEYOND THE BANDLEWOODS<br/>In Bandle Tale, experience a never-before-seen look at life beyond the bandlewoods. Encounter curious critters, gather materials to make impossible crafts, and awaken magical portals as you move between five unforgettable new islands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Exploration.gif?t=1708719402"><br/><br/>PARTY ON, BANDLE CITY!<br/>A good life in Bandle City hinges on one thing: beet soup! Wait, no, having fun! Throw festivals to ensure that your fellow yordles are happy and entertained. Cultivate your green thumb and cook farm-to-table dishes for your guests, or flex your engineering prowess and build gadgets to delight them.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Party.gif?t=1708719402"><br/><br/>MEET THE CHAMPIONS<br/>Befriend colorful characters and make League of Legends Champions your allies as you unravel the mysteries around you and mend your community, one magical stitch at a time.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1759380/extras/BandleTale_Champs.gif?t=1708719402"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminator: Dark Fate - Defiance</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1839950/Terminator_Dark_Fate__Defiance/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/header_alt_assets_0.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif1.gif?t=1708701023"><br/><strong>Terminator: Dark Fate – Defiance</strong> is a <strong>real-time strategy game</strong> based on the Terminator: Dark Fate universe that follows the war between humanity and Legion's synthetic intelligent machine network.<br/><br/>In the<strong> single-player campaign</strong>, you take the role of a commander in the Founders, a force made up of the remnants of the US military and guide your army in an attempt to foil Legion's plan to exterminate the last remnants of humanity. In skirmish and multiplayer modes, play as three very diverse factions: Founders, Movement and Legion.<br/><br/>Take control of an army carried over from mission to mission on a series of large strategic maps. Make decisions about unit placement, battle tactics and abilities so that you don’t just survive but can become the leader of the resistance against the machines. Hone your skills and military expertise by replaying and achieving the best possible outcomes.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Dynamic battlefields: realistic tactics and consequences</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif2.gif?t=1708701023"><br/>Engage in complex, realistic battles where your <strong>tactical decisions</strong> are vital to your survival and ultimate victory. Use a variety of military equipment, vehicles and ammunition types in your battles against the enemy. Recruit and train new units, assign new skills and acquire new weapons and equipment to continue the resistance.<br/><br/>Encounter tense battles. Your battlefield tactics and choices have deep consequences that will impact through the campaign, with other factions and characters either joining you or fighting against you, and with certain missions being available or not depending on your actions. <br/><br/><strong>Your resources are limited</strong> and you must protect your army. Weapons of war receive damage through a modular component damage system where armour characteristics, component malfunctions and hull structure all affect if your troops survive.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Lead the survival of mankind</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif3.gif?t=1708701023"><br/>Recruit others to your cause and <strong>grow your army</strong>. Mix and match the composition of your troops to fit your preferred battle tactics. Use infantry units, heavy armoured military vehicles, plasma cannon technology, drones and other flying units and even human skirmishers to achieve victory.<br/><br/>Use the battlefield to your advantage! <strong>Physics-based building demolition</strong> lets you generate a realistic set of tactical consequences, especially in urban areas.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer Mayhem: Skirmish and Online Battles</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1839950/extras/gif4.gif?t=1708701023"><br/>The excitement amplifies in <strong>skirmish and multiplayer modes</strong>, where <strong>you can play as three distinct factions</strong>: Founders, Movement, and Legion. <br/><br/>Engage in epic battles across vast strategic landscapes, testing your skills and military expertise. Every decision matters, impacting alliances, missions, and the overall survival of mankind.<br/><br/>Challenge your skills in skirmish and online multiplayer matches, facing off against AI or real-life human opponents in intense 1v1 and 2v2 battles.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penny’s Big Breakaway</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1955230/Pennys_Big_Breakaway/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Ready. Set. YO! - Join Penny &amp; Yo-Yo in a kinetic 3D-platformer bursting with innovative gameplay! Showcase your catalog of tricks and chain impressive combos to deliver Penny &amp; Yo-Yo's perfect breakout performance. Take the stage with this vibrant pair in Penny’s Big Breakaway.<br/><br/>Penny is a street performer with big dreams; she has her own spin on what it takes to be a star! When Eddie the Emperor calls for new Palace Court Performers, Penny gets herself tangled in an audition she’ll never forget. A strange encounter with a Cosmic String transforms Penny’s Yo-Yo into a living creature with an appetite for snacks— and mayhem! Use Yo-Yo to help Penny clear her name, outrun the Emperor’s penguin army, and unravel the mystery of the Cosmic String. <br/><br/>Burst onto the scene in the fluorescent world of Macaroon, home to this over-and-under escape! Discover your true star power in this easy-to-play, difficult-to-master challenge. Penny’s Big Breakaway is the debut title from Evening Star.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-01-Supertitles.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Key Features: <br/><br/>Walk the Dog: Yo-Yo’s big appetite will earn an even bigger reward with snack power-ups! Use these tasty treats to temporarily transform Yo-Yo, granting it the abilities to improve movement speed, protect Penny from harm, and much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-02-WalktheDog.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Around the World: Flee from Eddie the Emperor’s massive penguin army as they chase you clear across the planet! These clumsy flightless birds patrol the halls, come bursting through walls, and will stop at nothing to seize you! Help out friendly denizens along the way and make use of your spectacular surroundings to evade your capturers. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-03-AroundTheWorld.gif?t=1708524042"><br/><br/>Encore Stage: Play your way with multiple game modes! Show off your skills as you chain awesome combos and rack up multipliers in Story Mode. Take on the ultimate speedrunning challenge and dominate the leaderboard in Time Attack Mode. Redeem coins for bonus items, secret stages, and more unlockable extras.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1955230/extras/PYO_SteamFeatures_Animated-04-EncoreStage.gif?t=1708524042"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balatro</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2379780/Balatro/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Balatro is a poker-inspired roguelike deck builder all about creating powerful synergies and winning big.</strong><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Endless_Possibility.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><br/>Combine valid poker hands with unique Joker cards in order to create varied synergies and builds. Earn enough chips to beat devious blinds, all while uncovering hidden bonus hands and decks as you progress. You’re going to need every edge you can get in order to reach the boss blind, beat the final ante and secure victory.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Jokers_Clean_Thin.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>The definitive poker roguelike experience.<br/></li><li>Endless possibilities - every pick-up, discard and joker can dramatically alter the course of your run.<br/></li><li>In-depth campaign mode complete with 8 difficulties, as well as challenge, daily and seeded runs. </li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Break_The_Game.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><br/>Deftly deploy an array of potent tools: different Decks, Jokers, Tarot cards, Planet cards, Spectral cards, and Vouchers. Use these versatile instruments to ignite a combo frenzy and turbocharge your poker hands, crafting electrifying, adrenaline-fueled synergies.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro_5_Aces_GIF__HQ_.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>150 Jokers, each with their own unique abilities<br/></li><li>15 Decks with distinct modifiers to choose from for each run<br/></li><li>5 potential variants of each Joker which add further abilities<br/></li><li>22 Tarot cards variants that can enhance your regular playing cards<br/></li><li>11 Planet cards that help level up your possible poker hands<br/></li><li>32 Voucher cards to help provide permanent buffs for your current run</li></ul><br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Find_Your_Flow.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><br/>Immerse yourself in Balatro’s distinctive psychedelic world. Let the synthwave soundtrack wash over you -  wind down, escape the daily grind and prepare to enter the ultimate roguelike flow state.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improve your collection and discover new cards and secrets with every single run.<br/></li><li>Make use of the in-depth stats screen to study your best hands, most used Jokers, and more!<br/></li><li>Immerse yourself in the CRT fuzz and enjoy detailed, hand-crafted pixel art.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Spectral_Pack.gif?t=1708683444"><br/><br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2F5mH3dNhjx2" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2379780/extras/Balatro-join_the_discord.png?t=1708683444"/></a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2645580/Free_Stars_The_UrQuan_Masters/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">You are the captain</h2><i>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</i>® is a classic space game that captures the charm of retro science-fiction, space combat, and high adventure. Your story begins as the captain of the last human starship, with Earth trapped under a hostile forcefield. You are the last hope for humanity in a fight for control of the galaxy, as you explore thousands of unknown worlds and get dozens of quirky aliens to help.<h2 class="bb_tag">Meet fascinating alien characters</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_alien_dialog_optimized-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>​The galaxy is thriving with alien species, each with unique mysteries and motives. Meet an eclectic cast of characters, brought to life with full English voiceover. Ask sharp questions, make new friends, and exchange colorful insults.<h2 class="bb_tag">Adventure through HyperSpace</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_explore_hyperspace.gif_scaled-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>Discover a vibrant galaxy filled with wonder, terror, and absurdity. Explore thousands of uncharted worlds across hundreds of stars, and gather important resources and technology.<h2 class="bb_tag">Battle your rivals in starship combat</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_super_melee_scaled-loop-count.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>Build your fleet and battle enemy starships, facing off against friends or the computer-controlled AI. Play action-packed Super Melee as its own mode, or as part of the single-player adventure – or choose automated combat to stay focused on the story.<h2 class="bb_tag">Experience a sci-fi classic – for free!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2645580/extras/free_stars_the_ur_quan_masters_precursors_intro.gif?t=1708358440"><br/>As a celebrated piece of gaming history, <i>Free Stars: The Ur-Quan Masters</i>® has also received wide acclaim for its story, characters, and setting. It was created as a love letter to classic science fiction like Douglas Adams, David Brin, and Jack Vance. In turn, its setting inspired a new wave of game creators, including the visionaries behind <i>Mass Effect</i>, <i>No Man’s Sky</i>, <i>Subnautica</i>, <i>Starfield</i>, <i>Fallout</i>, and <i>Stellaris</i> – to name just a few.<br/><br/>In 2002, the game was released under an open source license thanks to the generosity of Paul Reiche and Fred Ford. It continues to be available to play as a free download, for game historians and fans to enjoy.<h2 class="bb_tag">Game features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience an open-world adventure, venturing through space to defeat the invading Ur-Quan and its hierarchy of battle thralls.<br/></li><li>Travel through extra-dimensional HyperSpace and discover nearly 500 unknown star systems filled with alien worlds.<br/></li><li>Fight enemies in fast-paced space battles with 25 different starships, each with its own unique attacks and powers.<br/></li><li>Befriend, threaten, or fight a diverse cast of aliens with unique personalities, from scary, to funny, to just plain weird.<br/></li><li>Explore thousands of planets, collecting resources and technology to upgrade your flagship and grow your fleet.<br/></li><li>Play standalone Super Melee to practice space combat against AI opponents or to duel against a friend.<br/></li><li>Mod and tinker with freely available, open-source code and content.</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please, Touch The Artwork 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2600140/Please_Touch_The_Artwork_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Disclaimer:</strong><i> This is a short game made in</i> <strong>6 months</strong><i>. It's</i> <strong>100% FREE</strong><i>(no ads, no dlc's), made by a </i><strong>solo dev</strong><i> in honour of James Ensor’s 75 year remembrance.</i> <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2600140/extras/Steam3DRoomGIF_Wide.gif?t=1708440801"><br/><br/>Touch the artwork and help a lost skeleton artist find its way home in a surreal, hand-painted universe. <br/><br/>Collect hidden objects for its quirky inhabitants, solve casual puzzles, and restore cracks in the fabric of the paintings. <br/><br/>This slow paced relaxing adventure was carefully crafted from works by James Ensor, a Belgian pioneer in the world of Modern Art.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> Hidden object adventure<br/></li><li>5 unique worlds<br/></li><li>Hints when stuck<br/></li><li>Casual point &amp; click gameplay<br/></li><li>Zoom-in for extra details<br/></li><li>Real hand-painted art<br/></li><li>Atmospheric relaxing sound<br/></li><li>Silly and quirky<br/></li><li>Slow-paced &amp; relaxing<br/></li><li>Fit for ages 12-99</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Small Mazes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2570630/20_Small_Mazes/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2570630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a puzzle game with twenty small mazes. If you solve the mazes, you beat the game.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>It's about 1-2 hours long, maybe.<br/></li><li>You need a keyboard and mouse to play it. One person played through the whole game on the Steam Deck, but I tried it and think it's better on PC.<br/></li><li> A few puzzles require knowledge of English. No puzzle requires sound or audio to solve it. No puzzle requires being able to recognize different colors.</li></ul> <br/>I hope you enjoy it. <br/> 						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708702172"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat Simulator 3</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/850190/Goat_Simulator_3/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fgoatsimulator" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/GS3_discord_banner_steam_616x140.jpg?t=1708702172"/></a><br/><br/>Pilgor's baaack! Take life by the horns in Goat Simulator 3 today!<br/><br/>Gather your herd and venture forth into Goat Simulator 3; an all-new*, totally realistic**, sandbox farmyard*** experience that puts you back in the hooves of no one's favourite female protagonist.<br/><br/>Join Pilgor and get ready to create your own whirlwind adventure on the island of San Angora. Lick, headbutt, and ruin your way through our open world in the biggest waste of your time since the original Goat Simulator! We won't tell you how to play (except in the tutorial), but merely provide the means to be the goats of your dreams.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/AnnouncementTrailer_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>If your dreams contain more than one goat, that works for us! In Goat Simulator 3, you can invite up to three friends in local or online co-op to create carnage as a team, or compete in mini-games and then not be friends anymore. And don't worry, there are plenty of customisation options so you and your pals don't wear clashing outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Customization_Minigames_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/>Goat Simulator 3 first launched in November 2022, and since then our “game designers” have been hard at work adding even more weird and wondrous stuff. As well as all the original goat-y goodness, Steam players will be able to experience all content from the game’s post-launch updates; including the Mandatory Holiday Update, Operation Crackdown and the Shadiest Update, with more to come!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Steam_Promo_Image_Group_Shot_757.png?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES:</strong><br/>- You can be a goat<br/>- You can be a goat… on Steam!<br/>- Three of your friends can be goats too, and join you in local or online co-op<br/>- No really, there are so many goats. If you want to be fancy you can wear the skins of tall goats, stripey goats, and many more. There's a goat for everyone!<br/>- Dress up your goat in all kinds of nonsense, from toilet rolls to tea trays. Put on a jetpack for all we care<br/>- We have actual 'game designers' who have worked to create 'an okay amount of content'; including events, NPCs to mess with, physics, status effects, collectables, easter eggs, lies, betrayal, heartbreak<br/>- They've added mini-games too, lots of mini-games (seven is a lot, right?)<br/>- They’ve even added a bunch of extra content since the game first launched, aren’t you a bunch of lucky kids?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/850190/extras/Gameplay_GIF_5sec_616x296.gif?t=1708702172"><br/><br/><strong>DISCLAIMER:</strong><br/>Since it launched in November 2022, Goat Simulator 3 has been a completely stupid game. It is still a completely stupid game today, except now it has more stuff! By this point if you're not sure what you're getting into, we can't help you.<br/><br/><strong>NOTES:</strong><br/>* Goat Simulator 3 is technically not completely new, but it is new to Steam users!<br/>** Our game is very realistic, if you happen to be a digital goat with a proclivity for ragdolling.<br/>*** False alarm, this one is actually true.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smalland: Survive the Wilds</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/768200/Smalland_Survive_the_Wilds/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>"Before the time of the giants, we lived freely under the Sun and Moon. Centuries have passed, but those stories of the surface world have been passed down through the generations. Now the giants are gone, and you, Vanguard, must venture out into the wilds once more, on an urgent mission. Be brave, and do not falter…"</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/TreeLookingup.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Explore the vast “Land of the Small" </h2>Traverse lake sized puddles, scale skyscraper sized trees, scramble through cavernous cracks in roads, as you experience a huge open world from a new perspective. Explore dense forests, hazardous swamps and strange ruins left over from the time before. Uncover lore and knowledge from hidden NPCs scattered throughout the world and learn to survive in this vast wilderness. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Land_of_Small.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tame and ride creatures</h2>Uncover recipes that will let you tame and ride an array of critters. Leap huge distances on the back of a Grasshopper, zoom around on a Damselfly, scurry from place-to-place on a Spider. This world and its inhabitants are yours to conquer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Mounts.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive together</h2>Play alongside friends with support for up to 10 players in multiplayer. Explore together, fight together, build together and survive the wilds as a team.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Together.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Build encampments on the ground or amongst the trees</h2>Scavenge or refine resources to build your encampment with multiple material tiers, from leaves and twigs to sturdy stone. Pick your favourite spot in the world and build, or scale vast trees and claim your own settlement at the top.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Housing.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Craft powerful armour sets</h2>Collect powerful armours that provide you with resistances and abilities and mix them up to personalise your appearance. Glide through the skies in winged armour, swing from tree to tree with the grappling hook and many more. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Armors.gif?t=1708514975"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Wilds</h2>Most of the creatures you encounter will see you as lower on the food chain – Ants, Cockroaches, Beetles, Wasps, and Spiders all view you as a potential meal. Weather conditions and seasons are in constant flux so if you want to survive for another day, preparation is key.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/768200/extras/Survive_the_Wilds.gif?t=1708514975"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1708080818"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1708080818"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1708080818"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1708080818"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1708080818"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1708080818"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Tales</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1465070/Legendary_Tales/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_07.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>Are you ready for adventure? Collect loot, destroy enemies, learn magic, craft your own items and head out on epic quests to conquer the evil that lurks beneath the earth. Play Alone or with friends; Legendary Tales is the ultimate fantasy VR experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/00.Steam_MiniTitle_RPG.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Grow your own unique character through gameplay and work your way through an extensive skill tree.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/01.Steam_MiniTitle_Multiplayer.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Supports Up-to 4 player Co-op<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/02.Steam_MiniTitle_Magic.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Master the art of magic and destroy enemies with fire, ice and lightning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/03.Steam_MiniTitle_RNGItems.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Collect an almost limitless amount of items thanks to random number generation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/04.Steam_MiniTitle_Physics.png?t=1707433150"><br/>An amazing physics based fighting system with destructible objects and scenery.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/05.Steam_MiniTitle_Crafting.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Craft your own items,potions and upgrade crafted items with an in depth crafting system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/06.Steam_MiniTitle_AboutLT.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_05.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>Are you ready to step down into the darkness? Explore winding roads and ruined castles that will take you down to the heart of the underworld, to defeat the evil corrupting the land. But be careful down there, the road is dangerous so you best bring a friend. Traverse the landscape, Bludgeon, slice and decimate skeletons with melee weapons, sneak up on a goblin with ranged weapons or destroy a demon from afar with destructive magic.<br/>Physics based melee combat, Improved Ai, an immersive crafting system, a myriad of weapons and up to 4 player co-op; this is an RPG, fantasy, adventure that is waiting for you to create your own Legendary Tales.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/07.Steam_MiniTitle_Generation.png?t=1707433150"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/08.Steam_MiniTitle_VR.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_04.gif?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Built from the ground up for VR; Legendary Tales will throw you into an immersive fantasy world, suitable for any PCVR platform with customisable graphics settings to ensure you get the smoothest possible experience.</ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/09.Steam_MiniTitle_Mutiplayer.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_03.gif?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Up to 4 players can play Legendary Tales in co-op mode. Grab some friends, trade some items, and head down into the dungeon to fight your way through the darkness together.</ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/010.Steam_MiniTitle_Physics.png?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">The physics in Legendary Tales was built to mimic the way real weapons feel and act as close as possible while still being fun to play. Weapons have their own weight so that larger swings will do more damage. Not only that but enemies and destructible items also react to how hard you hit them for a truly engaging experience. </ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/011.Steam_MiniTitle_Items.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_06.gif?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Want to try sneaky kills with a dagger? Hit your enemies from afar with a bow? Or just mash some faces with a morning star? There are a host of different weapon types to suit your play style so find what works for you! And for every weapon type you will find so many variations on their stats thanks to random number generated items. The items are classed into five categories ranging from normal to Legendary. which not only look awesome but have special abilities. What abilities? You’ll have to get one for yourself to find out.</ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/014.Steam_MiniTitle_Skilltree.png?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">As you fight your way through the world, your character will grow based on how you play. But there’s more to growth than just how you fight, work your way through the magic and skills available to truly bring your character to the next level.</ul><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/012.Steam_MiniTitle_Combatskills.png?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Weapons are fun and all but through the skill tree you can improve your abilities with combat skills or find yourself a Legendary item with their own special abilities and even more, you can upgrade their skills! </ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/013.Steam_MiniTitle_Crafting.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_02_new.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>If hunting for weapons in the dungeons isn’t for you then we have good news! You can create your own weapons with ingredients found on your adventures, or by honing the weapons you’ve collected. You can also make potions to prepare deep dungeon crawling and disassemble items you found during your adventures to get ingredients and enhance your crafted weapons or potions with them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_01.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>Get ready for an epic adventure in VR! Put on your headset, find some friends and head into the dungeon to start creating your own Legendary Tales.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707955699"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1708019001"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal Richards (formerly of Echos)</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1708019001"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2774240/Instruction/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/extras/Aboutdevelopment.png?t=1706909482"><br/><br/>Instruction is a story based clicker game where you, an employee of a power plant, are tasked with generating power for your city. The powerplant's built in intelligence mentor program, or I.M.P. for short, will help you generate the necessary amount of voltage to fulfill your quota. I.M.P may have developed a little too much of a personality for the powerplant's liking, but don't worry! It's still more than capable of keeping you on track. <br/><br/>In this game you'll be tasked with using different systems to generate power. Each system works differently and can be upgraded to increase your efficiency. Discover each of the power plant's mechanisms, and uncover the story behind your less than friendly companion. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/extras/Gamefeatures.png?t=1706909482"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Over 300 unique lines of dialogue<br/></li><li>5 different systems to generate power<br/></li><li>Secrets and hidden interactions</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2774240/extras/Aboutdevelopment.png?t=1706909482"><br/><br/>This game was developed as a student project at DigiPen Institute of Technology and was created for educational purposes only. Please check out our publisher page for more information.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotMobile</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2805630/BotMobile/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2805630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							How much are you afraid of heights? Well, the <strong>BotMobile</strong> game tends to put fear even in those who don't have it. Therefore, only the bravest and most fearless are needed here to carry out the missions to conquer the highest peaks. We know that you are a skilled driver, that's why we offer you the fastest cars that are equipped with nitro that will help you jump over the gaps between the supports. Press the accelerator as hard as possible because that's the only way you have a chance to survive. Remember, only one will emerge victorious in this survival race. Courage!!!<br/><br/><strong>Game features:</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>3 cars equipped with nitrogen(Jet,Eagle,Hunter)<br/></li><li>Each level has 5 attempts<br/></li><li>More than 10 levels</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just skill shooter 3: 2d edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2805610/Just_skill_shooter_3_2d_edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2805610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Try on the role of a shooter who opposes the whole world. You will be attacked by hordes of enemies, from whom you will have to shoot back with different weapons. The grenade launcher with its missiles will reduce the number of your enemies pretty quickly. The machine is always full of bullets. Although the shotgun does a lot of damage, it takes a long time to recharge. Enemies come in different types, some have a large supply of health, some throw boxes, others create small copies of themselves after death. Be careful and you will win!<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dynamic gameplay<br/></li><li>Many enemies<br/></li><li>Interesting gameplay</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slime Drop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816420/Slime_Drop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2816420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Main Gameplay Loop</strong><br/><br/>- Drop Slimes into the box .<br/><br/>- Merge two Slimes of the same kind to evolve them to the next tier.<br/><br/>- If a slime drops out of the box, you lose.<br/><br/>- Repeat.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><br/>- Merge three Slimes of the same kind to skip a tier.<br/><br/>- Chain multiple merges in quick succession to gain a combo multiplier for a higher score.<br/><br/>- Change the colors of the box and the background to your liking.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd Control VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776190/Crowd_Control_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776190/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Crowd Control VR, an exhilarating virtual reality adventure that transports you to the lively streets of ancient Greece! Dive into a unique and entertaining experience where your mission is to identify impostors hidden within bustling crowds, each with their own unique behaviors.<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Content:</strong> Embark on a solo adventure through more than 25 levels, presenting several unique impostors and mechanics. From bustling marketplaces to grand amphitheaters, every level brings a fresh challenge and a new set of characters to decipher.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Immersion:</strong> You'll find yourself in various vibrant ancient Greek settings, each hand-crafted to provide a thrilling VR escapade. Sharpen your observational skills as you unravel the mysteries concealed within the crowd, encountering impostors that become progressively challenging to spot.</li></ul><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Accessibility:</strong> Crowd Control VR emphasizes accessibility, making it an ideal choice for both seasoned VR enthusiasts and newcomers. Minimal physical movement is required, ensuring that even those new to VR can effortlessly enjoy the thrill of discovering impostors amid the vibrant energy of ancient Greece!</li></ul><br/>Dive into the virtual mayhem, unmask the impostors, and become the master of the animated crowds in Crowd Control VR!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Morgan: Dilemma</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2680520/Nathan_Morgan_Dilemma/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680520/extras/wishlist_600x132.jpg?t=1708797774"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680520/extras/wish.gif?t=1708797774"><h2 class="bb_tag">NATHAN MORGAN: DILEMMA</h2>Nathan Morgan: Dilemma is a single-player detective game. Detective Nathan Morgan, stationed in the state, is assigned to follow the trail of the mysterious murder at the Bennett mansion. Our goal is to find the killer by making use of the clues.<h2 class="bb_tag">FIND THE CLUES</h2>Try to find clues around you, they will help you find the killer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680520/extras/NathanMorgan_Dilemma2024-01-0221-47-06-Trim-ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter.gif?t=1708797774"><h2 class="bb_tag">QUESTION THE SUSPECTS</h2>The information you get from the suspects is very important. As a detective, keep these in mind.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680520/extras/brad.gif?t=1708797774"><h2 class="bb_tag">FIND THE KILLER</h2>Put together all the information you've collected and decide who the killer is!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680520/extras/asdafdagman-ezgif.com-video-to-gif-converter.gif?t=1708797774"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITHOUT YOU</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2793690/WITHOUT_YOU/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>ADD OTHER GAMES WISHLIST 💋 </strong><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2590770?utm_source=fromSTOREwithoutyou" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793690/extras/stolen.png?t=1708792422"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2590790?utm_source=fromSTOREwithoutyou" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793690/extras/stolen2.png?t=1708792422"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">About</h2>Without you is a story-based non-linear visual novel with live2D sprites. Cute artwork, CGs, BGs, and CGs in chibi style in 4k resolution,original soundtracks, and a interesting story!<br/><br/>"Without You" is a gripping visual novel about the life of Moscowia State University student who has one dream - freedom. There is no room for lies: all the beauty and ugliness of life will appear before your eyes in its clearest form. What to think of it is up to you.<h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>Maels is a student of MSU, Moscowia's finest university. With his sister Alpha Maels has spent his whole life trying to escape from the poverty that surrounds them. But the reality turned out to be much harsher - the world rejected them.<br/>As a result, Alpha fell into depression and went on academic leave. Maels' heart hardened - in response to the anger towards his sister, he refused to accept this unjust world. He stopped attending classes, stopped associating with his classmates. He no longer desired to fit into the system. Apart from his sister, the only person he kept in touch with was Izolda, a caring childhood friend he met back in middle school.<br/>This is the way he lived until he met Astra, the love of his life. Her sincerity and kindness awakened in him long-forgotten feelings and reminded that the world consists of more than just hatred and malice.<br/>He no longer needed to fight the world. When you are truly happy, any hardship in life is vincible...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2793690/extras/ezgif-4-d666f507d5.gif?t=1708792422"><br/><br/>Did you really think it would be that easy? Maels had found love, the world suddenly became a much better place and happiness had replaced the anger in his heart? Then he'll find a 9-5 job, raise three children and take a mortgage on a flat?<br/>Cowardice and turning a blind eye to the abhorrent actions of people around you would only lead to losing everything you hold. So... The only way out was to fight. Fight this cruel and unjust world.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HaHa</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2269530/HaHa/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/extras/Gameplay.png?t=1708790219"><br/><strong>!!! Dev. Warning !!!<br/>Greetings,<br/>Until you get accustomed to the game where we play with the coolest square in the world and empower ourselves with various weapons and passives, or until luck smiles upon you, and you repeatedly curse at me, please don't (Please don't, it saddens me). You find yourselves exposed to small developer jokes while declaring that you've fully completed maps with different concepts. As you sweat profusely during the boss battles at the end of each map, please try to preserve your mental health and take good care of yourselves :)</strong><br/><br/>Dodge bullets coming towards you by jumping between platforms.<br/>Discover your own playstyle with different passive abilities and weapons.<br/><br/>Pay attention to the stones you throw. Unexpected stones can be surprisingly useful.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/extras/ezgif-1-2fd247d75c.gif?t=1708790219"><br/><br/><strong>GUNS</strong><br/><br/>The rocket is a powerful weapon, capable of taking out multiple enemies at once,<br/>but it moves slowly. Play strategically to hit moving targets.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/extras/rocket.gif?t=1708790219"><br/><br/>Use the machine gun to eliminate multiple enemies at once;<br/>it's easier than killing enemies by throwing stones.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/extras/all.gif?t=1708790219"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/extras/ManyCharacter.png?t=1708790219"><br/>There are multiple characters in this game, each with their own strengths.<br/>You can manipulate time to your advantage,<br/>set up portals on walls to ambush enemies,<br/>and play with many other characters like these.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/extras/3Character.png?t=1708790219"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/extras/BossesAndMaps.png?t=1708790219"><br/>Each level features unique end-of-level monsters,<br/>and each level offers a different gameplay experience.<br/><br/>Enemies are multiplying and getting stronger. Best of luck on your journey to become the most powerful square!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/extras/gifHHAA.gif?t=1708790219"><br/><br/>-&gt; Different characters to customize your adventure<br/>-&gt; Numerous spells and weapons to enhance your fun<br/>-&gt; Kill them all and SURVIVE!<br/><br/>HaHa, a fantastic and entertaining horror game with rogue-lite elements, where your choices will quickly have a significant impact against hordes of approaching monsters. The enemies keep increasing in numbers and growing stronger. The circle is closing in, so become strong enough to save not only yourself but also your friends!<br/><br/>Join the fun adventure with your friends in this journey that feels like a bullet hell, where you can move comfortably with simple movement controls and wield customizable weapons.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2269530/extras/upscaleGifRage.gif?t=1708790219"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heraldry Studio</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1152420/Heraldry_Studio/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1152420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Heraldry Studio allows user to create and export a unique coat of arms, according to the rules of heraldry.<br/>Heraldry Studio is not a graphics editor. It creates a coat of arms with given rules, and allows to export the result as a PNG file. The generated arms can be used for personal goals, role-play, historical reenactment, illustration, learning.<br/><br/>Heraldry Studio features field divisions with different directions, field covered with charges (semé), honourable ordinaries, combinations between ordinaries and other charges. The program has simple inputs - all available functions always are found on the screen. Composition of the arms is displayed in a graph on the left panel.<br/><br/><strong>Users of Heraldry Studio are allowed to use created arms for other projects, including commercial ones.</strong><br/><br/>Historically, at some time between the First and the Second Crusade knights started to mark themselves and their property with simple contrasting designs. That is considered to be the beginning of heraldry. With time arms started to be used by all classes and institutions of society and heraldry acquired strict rules. Nowadays arms are still accompanied with myths and untruths but there always have been a need to create new arms.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUNR END</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1908350/RUNR_END/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1908350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1908350/extras/IceCave01_gif_optimized.gif?t=1708785663"><br/><br/>RUNR END is a challenging platformer set in a dreamish world.<br/><br/>Pull off cool movements while dodging traps and making precise jumps.<br/>Discover secrets through your journey by paying attention to every detail the world has.<br/>Oh, and I forgot to mention, there are <i>no checkpoints on levels</i>, who needs them anyway?<br/><br/><strong>Be careful,</strong><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1908350/extras/fallensoul.png?t=1708785663"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1908350/extras/TutLevel_grass_gif_optimized.gif?t=1708785663"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A challenging campaign - No checkpoints on levels so you gotta be careful</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Make awesome movements</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Compete with your friends on Leaderboard</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Even compete with the DEV itself on Leaderboard :) </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Discover secrets and earn Achievements through your journey</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tipsy Rescue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2717600/Tipsy_Rescue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2717600/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br>
"Tipsy Rescue Game" is a puzzle game designed to unlock the phone's various locks. Your objective is to safely guide our friend, who has fallen asleep after drinking, home by navigating through the apps on the phone.<br>
<br>
Gameplay<br>
This puzzle game is available for both PC and mobile devices, requiring players to use a mouse (or touch screen) and keyboard to solve the challenges presented. The game is centered around the phone's screen, where you must uncover passwords for locked sections by gathering clues from the content within various apps. Players are free to explore nine different apps on the phone to gather hints. Once you discover her address, you can call a taxi to ensure she safely reaches home.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papercut Art Gallery-Nature</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782400/Papercut_Art_GalleryNature/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to "Paper Art Gallery," an artistic puzzle game inspired by the art of paper cutting. Your task is to piece together fragments of paper cutouts to restore the nature-themed artworks in the gallery.<br>
<br>
----- Game Features ------<br>
<br>
- 32 nature-themed paper cut artworks<br>
- Immersive puzzle experience<br>
- Comfortable and relaxing ambient music<br>
- Simple controls<br/>
- Moderately challenging levels<br/>
<br/>
----- Game Controls ------<br/>
<br/>
- Hold the left mouse button to move a puzzle piece<br/>
- Click the right mouse button to rotate a puzzle piece<br/>
- Press the R key to rotate the held puzzle piece<br/>
- Press the ESC key to hide or show the game UI<br/>
<br/>
------------------------						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Survivors: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2706570/Midnight_Survivors_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2195510/Midnight_Survivors/?beta=0" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2195510/Midnight_Survivors/?beta=0</a><br/><br/>It's Time to Spit Out All Bullets!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706570/extras/bossFight.gif?t=1708772296"><br/>Take control of the bullet-spitting cat and take down waves of enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706570/extras/tpsFixed.gif?t=1708772296"><br/>Upgrade your cat and get various weapons and skills to defeat your enemies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706570/extras/TopView.gif?t=1708772296"><br/>Find a more efficient strategy by combining various skills.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2706570/extras/tpsFree.gif?t=1708772296"><br/>Let your enemies know who will be the last one standing.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood On The Streets</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2748530/Blood_On_The_Streets/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2748530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Call it a third-person shooter<br>
It can also be called a racing game<br>
I would call it the city of freedom<br>
Stepping into this open city, you will find a game world full of challenges and opportunities waiting for you to explore. In this free and open realm, engage in fierce gang wars with gangsters and mafia, challenging your strategy and leadership. Get ready to start a new life and experience an endless world where you make the rules.<br>
<br>
In this virtual city, you will meet real players from all over the world to compete, cooperate, and even break the rules of the game. Choose the weapon you need and choose from a variety of firearms to best suit your unique tactics. Time is running out and every moment is an opportunity to fight against the crime family.<br>
<br>
Join this engaging game and become a legend of the city. In this world of endless possibilities, every decision you make will shape your destiny. Challenge the limits, create legends, and let this city become the stage for your endless adventures.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sprite Wars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2690570/Sprite_Wars/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690570/extras/img_SpriteWars.png?t=1708763578"><br/>Sprite Wars is a top-down arena shooter roguelite. Use, develop and purchase any of 8 unique weapons and 4 different skills. Fight bosses and show your enemies who the real boss is at the end of 40 levels.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2690570/extras/img_Features.png?t=1708763578"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>8 unique weapons and 4 different skills</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Variety of enemies and bosses</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Choose weapons, upgrade skills, unlock masteries</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Bonus objectives for more rewards!</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Long playing time and challenging levels</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Auto save system</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cute graphics and colourful atmosphere</strong></li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Shot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2789430/Accurate_Shot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2789430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Accurate Shot is a 3D adventure game with a first-person perspective. You are a young traveler who has decided to become an archer, your task is to pass the entrance exam and prove to everyone that you are the best shooter!<br>
<br>
Stretch the bowstring, aim and shoot! Control the arrow and hit all the targets on your way! Many exciting levels of varying difficulty await you! Whether you can pass this test is up to you!<br>
<br>
You have to make quick tactical decisions and destroy targets with a precise shot! Use your bow and arrows and show off your lightning-fast reactions! Use your care and creativity to move forward, otherwise you'll have to start all over again! Develop your skills through mistakes and careful training and become the greatest archer!<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br/>
- First person archer simulator with incredible bow mechanics.<br/>
- In the game you have to plan every shot<br/>
- Lots of levels						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tower Of Wishes 3 : Japan</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2634940/Tower_Of_Wishes_3__Japan/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2634940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Tower of Wishes 3: Japan is a match 3 game that tells the story of Ryu, a skilled ninja who is on the run, being pursued by his own clan. Unable to shake off the relentless pursuit, Ryu decides to seek his destiny in climbing the Tower Of Wishes.<br/><br/>An ancient legend speaks of a tower that grants wishes to those who can climb it. For Ryu, the Tower of Wishes may be the only hope left.<br/><br/>The stunning Japanese style artwork and immersive soundtrack transports players to a world of ancient Ninja lore and mystical powers.<br/><br/>With 100 challenging match 3 levels, a rich storyline, fun minigames and customizable gameplay options, Tower of Wishes 3: Japan offers a unique blend of match 3 puzzles, strategy, and fun.<br/><br/>Do you have what it takes to reach the top of the tower and make your wish come true?<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/>✪ Engaging Storyline<br/>✪ Unique Match 3 gameplay<br/>✪ Hidden Object, Solitaire, Jigsaw, and Slider minigames<br/>✪ 100 levels of fun match making<br/>✪ Customizable gameplay options<br/>✪ Beautiful Japanese style artwork<br/>✪ Immersive Japanese style music						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPY-der PIG</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802110/SPYder_PIG/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is Obstacle course game. Agent Spy-der Pig with the mission of finding and destroying the most powerful thing in the dark world. The higher you go, there will be more obstacles and challenges from Will-o'-the-wisp, black cats, poisonous spiders to ghostly witches' fire pans... <br/><br/>Along the way, don't forget to collect gold coins to upgrade cases and guns, these are two powerful tools for you. This lonely adventure to reach The Top will demand full mastery of the technique of jumping, shooting, swing... Let's fight together with Mr.derPig to see who will get to the best position in this journey.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>:::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::: - <u>GAME FEATURES</u> - ::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::</strong></h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Diverse gameplay strategies</strong><br/>You can shoot rope guns, swing, jump on terrain, jump in the air, dodge traps, collect coins, kill ghosts and more.<br/></li><li> <strong>Support tools</strong><br/>Cases and guns for spies to upgrade that improve the ability to jump and kill enemies.<br/></li><li> <strong>Cute art style</strong><br/>Many characters built-in with cute blocky style, snappy animations. From the spy Spyder Pig, to the scenes, to the enemies, you will definitely enjoy the adorable characters and background designs. Don't miss the sound in the game, it will make you laugh out loud.<br/></li><li> <strong>Challenge and perseverance</strong><br/>fun entertaining game, helping you and your friends increase perseverance, especially when playing together. Challenge your friends to play this game to see who gets the higher score!<br/><br/>This Game is appropriate for all ages. </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fittest Fire</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2537510/Fittest_Fire/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537510/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a ruined world, overrun by evil robots, a disabled cyborg named Blaze rests. Send a spark of energy from your world to Blaze’s to wake him up. <br/><br/>Help Blaze take revenge against the robots in this fast paced 2D platformer where you workout to level up. The Fittest Fire game features:<h2 class="bb_tag">Powerful melee attacks that devastate enemies and recharge your ammo</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537510/extras/giphySwordNew.gif?t=1708746399"><h2 class="bb_tag">Fast ranged attacks to dispatch enemies from a distance</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537510/extras/giphyGunNew.gif?t=1708746399"><h2 class="bb_tag">Tight movement controls with variable jumping, dashing, and wall jumping</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537510/extras/giphyNewPlatformer.gif?t=1708746399"><h2 class="bb_tag">An explorable world with 12 unique areas, 8 bosses, and 20+ enemy types</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537510/extras/giphyBoss.gif?t=1708746399"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Fittest Fire comes with a mobile app</strong></h2><br/>Fittest Fire is both a game and mobile app. The Fittest Fire mobile app allows you to log exercises and get points based on the weight, reps, time, and/or distance. These points can be used in the Fittest Fire game to:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Increase sword and gun damage as well as the attack speed<br/></li><li>Unlock powerful special attacks for both the sword and gun<br/></li><li>Increase health points, movement speed, and power up durations</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537510/extras/giphyLevelup.gif?t=1708746399"><h2 class="bb_tag">Power up with Fire mode once it’s unlocked</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537510/extras/giphyFireMode.gif?t=1708746399"><br/><br/>It's possible to play the game without downloading the mobile app. However, you will not be able to level up without the mobile app and will face significantly more difficult gameplay.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich everyone</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2615230/Rich_everyone/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The game simulates the life restoration of ancient Chinese farmers in scientific farming, vegetable planting, animal husbandry, and various handicraft workshops. Free simulation of construction and extensive reference to the earliest and most complete agricultural masterpiece Jia Sixie's 《Qi Min Yao Shu》.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615230/extras/FSNS_mujiangfang_616.jpg?t=1708750362"><br/>In the game, seasonal content is quoted as follows: "When the weather is favorable and the quantity and location are favorable, less effort will be exerted and more success will be achieved. When one returns to the path, effort will be lost." The following types are generally divided into upper time, middle time, and lower time, which will directly affect the harvest.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2615230/extras/FSNS_jianjie_zhonggu_616.jpg?t=1708750362"><br/>Intensive cultivation and meticulous cultivation are like when plowing, "When barren mountains and fields are opened, they are cut with wormwood in the seventh month. When the grass is dry, it is set on fire. It blooms in spring, and the roots are rotten, saving energy<br/>To excel in one's work, one must first sharpen their tools; to please others, one must forget their labor. In agricultural activities, there are inevitably some agricultural tools that can improve productivity, which requires the production of various agricultural tools in workshops. There are many characteristic agricultural tools such as plows, plows, hoes, land axes, and waterwheels.<br/>In the game, many agricultural products can be produced, including planting, breeding, workshops, and other three categories, including grains, fruits, vegetables, meat, fish, and so on.<br/><br/>Game features:<br/>Government affairs mainly provide services such as managing administrative construction and improving agricultural production technology. For example, warehouses can store materials, merit steles can help improve the source of reputation, memorial archway can improve commuting efficiency, and schools can train senior craftsmen.<br/>【Industrial Chain】 It has a rich industrial chain, showcasing production technologies such as agriculture, forestry, animal husbandry, sidelines, fishing, and various workshops.<br/>Seasons, especially during crop cultivation, provide an interesting and vivid representation of the gameplay of seasons.<br/>【Product】 integrates a very rich variety of commodities, including grains, vegetables, fruit trees, meat, workshop processed products, agricultural tools, etc., with detailed descriptions.<br/>[Construction] It contains rich architectural content, basic residential buildings, and characteristic buildings with various functions. For example, the Merit Monument can help improve reputation, the Temple of Nong can reduce construction costs, the memorial archway can improve people's commuting ability, the teahouse can improve farmers' enthusiasm for work, and the school can cultivate various craftsmen and improve production capacity.<br/>【Planting】 When planting crops, it is important to follow the natural and favorable conditions, with less effort and more success. If you are willing to return to the path, you will find no gains through hard work. "Similarly, in the game, it is important to pay attention to the planting season, such as when planting grain." In early February, for those who grow mahogany poplar, it is the first season; in early March, for those who start peach blossom during the Qingming Festival, it is the middle season; in early April, for those who grow jujube leaves and mulberry flowers, it is the second season<br/>There are various varieties of cultivation, such as rice, millet, sorghum, soybeans, adzuki beans, sesame seeds, melons, gourds, taros, okra, woad (green vegetables), radish (radish), garlic, scallions, and Sichuan mustard.<br/>Planting grain every year, planting trees every ten years "includes rich fruit tree planting content, such as planting jujube, peach and plum, plum and apricot, pear, chestnut, persimmon, etc.<br/>【Animal husbandry】 includes raising chickens, ducks, pigs, sheep, cows, horses, and how to care for them<br/>The workshop is mainly used for the processing of agricultural products, the production of agricultural tools, and the processing of infrastructure materials, which can generate more commodities.<br/>【Trading】 The world is prosperous, all for profit; The bustling world is all for profit. The game includes rich cargo trading systems, such as bazaars, cargo stations, docks, and going out for business.<br/>【Agricultural tools】If you want to do something good, first sharpen your tools; Pleasure makes people forget their labor.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eugenia's Pursuit: The Hidden Legacy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2809770/Eugenias_Pursuit_The_Hidden_Legacy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2809770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a suspense-filled first-person survival horror game. <br>
<br>
As a player, you will assume the role of Eugenia, a 27-year-old woman who is an intern reporter, infiltrating an abandoned building of the OHJIN Group. <br>
You will explore the building interior, solve a variety of puzzles, and uncover hidden truths. <br>
You will need to navigate all accessible floors of the building, surviving potential dangers through intelligent decision-making. <br>
<br>
This game delivers a vibrant and tense experience with high-quality graphics and sound, testing your strategic thinking and decision-making skills.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Survivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2336730/Dungeon_Survivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dungeon Survivors is a top-down fantasy roguelite where you can choose between 5 different classes, and use your class abilities to fight off a horde of fantasy monsters. Choose from a variety of abilities and items to create unique builds and survive as long as you can. Build out unique comps with up to 3 other players in online co-op.<h2 class="bb_tag">1-4 PLAYER CO-OP</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336730/extras/Sequence_01_1.gif?t=1708739903"><br/>Play solo or choose up to 3 additional friends to play with. Strategize with different class combinations as well as different stat combinations.<h2 class="bb_tag">BOSS WAVES</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336730/extras/Sequence_01_4.gif?t=1708739903"><br/>Every 25 waves, you will be hit with a boss wave. Boss waves are all different, and you will have to learn the different mechanics of each of the bosses.<h2 class="bb_tag">HUNDREDS OF CARDS</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2336730/extras/Sequence_01.gif?t=1708739903"><br/>At the end of each wave, you will be able to pick between 3 different cards. These cards have 5 different rarities (common, rare, epic, legendary, mythic). These cards can consist of player items, abilities, stat increases, mounts, etc.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2></strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Quick runs<br/></li><li> Hundreds of items, weapons and abilities to choose from<br/></li><li> 5 Classes to choose from (Warrior, Rogue, Archer, Priest, Wizard)<br/></li><li> Each class has their own set of cards and abilities<br/></li><li> Survive 30 second waves, which gets increasingly harder<br/></li><li> 4 Boss waves, after which you fight as long as you can (for a leaderboard spot)<br/></li><li> 100+ Waves<br/></li><li> Leaderboard for achieving the highest wave on certain classes/comps<br/></li><li> Random "cards" to choose from each round. Cards can vary in rarity and type<br/></li><li> Play by yourself or with 1-4 player co-op<br/></li><li> Create hundreds of unique characters. Choose from different hair, facial hair, hair color and race</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jinni : Haunted House</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2674240/Jinni__Haunted_House/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2674240/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>"Jinni: Haunted House" is a horror experience designed to lure brave players deep into the spirit world. In this dark and haunted atmosphere, you will experience moments of fear and suspense as you escape from the shadow of a mysterious creature stalking you. </strong><br/><br/><strong>Atmosphere:</strong> Get ready for a true horror experience with the game's stunning sound design and impressive soundtrack. You'll get lost in the chimes of the call to prayer and the whispers of the jinn.<br/><br/><strong>Mysterious Storyline</strong>: An in-depth horror story will draw players into mysterious events as your character's past and the secrets of this dark house are revealed.<br/><br/><strong>Horror Houses and Labyrinths:</strong> Designed to complicate your escape, the houses of horror and labyrinths will give you a constant sense of tension and danger.<br/><br/><strong>Constant Danger:</strong> As a player haunted by a constant stalker, you must be on your guard at all times. As the shadow approaches you, your breath will be taken away and your heartbeat will speed up.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panoptia</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2604880/Panoptia/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In a small peaceful town, there is a mysterious building called Panoptia by the townsfolk. No one knows what it is for, but it is heavily protected for some unknown reason. But when a girl gets past the security, she finds herself in an ever-expanding subterranean world, where thoughts and desires, both good and bad, come to life.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604880/extras/00gameplay.gif?t=1708731379"><br/>Panoptia is a narrative-driven adventure and features a rich world with a variety of environments to explore. Explore areas such as the subway, offices, or mall to discover the mystery behind the creation of this strange building.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604880/extras/00features.gif?t=1708731379"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"> <li> A haunting, ambient original soundtrack <br/> </li><li> A story-rich world<br/> </li><li> Choices that affect the player and story</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2604880/extras/00developersnote.gif?t=1708731379"><br/>This game was wholly made by me, Enrico. I've done all the programming, music, art, and writing, so I hope you can support me in any way you can! Whether it be buying the game, recommending it, or just adding to your Steam Wishlist, anything helps! I've been working on it for the past two years and this game means so much to me. Making this game and its world and characters is a true passion of mine and I hope you enjoy!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icy Incline</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2797900/Icy_Incline/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2797900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Icy Incline" is a experience where you control a penguin sliding through 24 icy trails. Race against time, avoid obstacles, and find the best route for the fastest time and reach the end of each trail. See your performance with stats like best score, worst score, and crashes.<br/><br/>As the penguin, your goal is simple yet thrilling: reach the end of each trail in the shortest time possible. The icy trails are filled with obstacles that demand quick reflexes and strategy. Feel the rush of the chilly wind as you gracefully navigate the 24 trails, avoiding crashes and collecting powerups. The obstacles consist of candy canes, cones, rocks, and ice patches. Candy canes, cones, and rocks will end your run, while ice patches will slow you down.<br/><br/>Controls: A, D - turn left, turn right<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2797900/extras/credits2.png?t=1708726835"> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation “Kyiv”</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2681230/Operation_Kyiv/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2681230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Operation "Kyiv" thrusts players into the heart of one of the most intense and pivotal battles of our time. Set against the backdrop of the Ukrainian landscape, the game unfolds the gripping narrative of the struggle for key locations like Irpin, Bucha, Gostomel, Сhernihiv, and the crucial M0-6 highway.<br>
<br>
As a player, you'll be immersed in the chaos and strategic intricacies of modern warfare, navigating the challenges of urban combat, coordinating troop movements, and making crucial decisions that can sway the course of the entire conflict. The meticulously designed landscapes and dynamic scenarios provide a visceral experience, capturing the tension and adrenaline of the battle for Kyiv.<br>
<br>
Operation "Kyiv" isn't just a game; it's a journey into the heart of a geopolitical crisis, challenging players to confront the harsh realities of war						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seasonal Soccer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/818380/Seasonal_Soccer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Xmas special: Winter Wonderland -level added with 1 new achievement!</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/pixelstyle.png?t=1708729707"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/steamkauppalogo1.png?t=1708729707"> is pixel stylished game, which respects the traditions of good old style soccer-games! The object of the game is to score by moving the ball beyond the goal line into the opposing goal and defend own goal. This game may cause happy moments, frustration, nostalgic memories and more. Choose your team from 8 different choices and play on single player mode against CPU... and beat the opponent AI team! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/pallo.png?t=1708729707"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/somesoccer.png?t=1708729707"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/steamkauppalogo2.png?t=1708729707"> good old times soccer games with easy controls and amazing pixel graphics? Have you ever wanted to dive into those memories again and enjoy 100% pixel style and simple game play? With no need to follow the complicate plot? Looking for a time to relax and let your mind wander? Or perhaps a game with simple game controls and amazing pixel graphics? Or a game that includes speed and requires accuracy? Well, believed it or not, this game have it all. Seek no more, you have found what you have searched.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/mypa.png?t=1708729707"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/original.png?t=1708729707"> idea for Seasonal Soccer has started and inspired by the passion of football in a town of Myllykoski. That village, located in the final frontier Finland, surrounded by a thick forests and fertile oat fields, has a truly passion for football. Together with legendary worldwide paper industry pioneer Myllykoski Paper decision to build a a football pitch with spectator stands in 1947 and continuous support, football club Myllykosken Pallo −47 (or MYPA, formerly MyPa) did many miracles in football history. In addition to regular football, the village was also in the fashion of playing legendary Amiga soccer games. Inspired by this spectacular passion to the football, Seasonal Soccer is here for you to play. And we also hope that we can "ignite the candle" and inspire people all around the world to start a career in football.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/8teams.png?t=1708729707"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/flags__1_.png?t=1708729707"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/youcan.png?t=1708729707"> play against CPU by selecting one of these teams: Russia, Belgium, France, England, Finland, Switzerland, Spain or Honduras. If you win (or lose..), you can choose new opponent. On this Early Access version you can't win World Cup tournament (yet), but you can play 2 levels and win the match against CPU and have fun! You can also let AI play your team players and only "manager" a team, but in hard situations you will need to take control. Of course you can also play all time with 100% control of your players.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/pixelgraph.png?t=1708729707"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/thisis.png?t=1708729707"> is a pixel-style retro AAA-game (graphically). The game does not take the whole screen, so it is easy to play also at the work place, school etc (of course at a break time). Screen resolution is excellent 900x640 size and you can also choose Full Screen! (New!). Full Screen mode is still experimental and while playing in full screen mode, it is possible that you cant see incredible graphics frames which appear when you or enemy made a goal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/gives.png?t=1708729707"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improved Full Screen mode <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A new Windows runtime using DirectX 11<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Improved performances with new engine optimizations<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Faster loading times<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hunt Achievements (currently 1)<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You can play against CPU (We promise that it is challenging.)</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You can choose from 8 different teams (Russian, Belgium, France, England, Finland, Switzerland, Spain or Honduras.)</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>You can change your team and opponent from the options menu.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each team has its strengths and weaknesses</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>How long will you play, it is up to you. We believe that this game can entertain you as many hours as you wan't, because if your moves are different so will be every match. So you can spend minutes or even hours by playing this game without getting bored. How much gameplay will this game give you, it is up to you. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>This game do include music and you can also listen applauses and cheers yells from the audience while playing against opponent team.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>On this stage on Early Access, you can play 2 football fields/levels, but as it is said every match can be different..</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>There is no referee in the football field (yet), so this game might not be totally realistic in every aspect.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/ai.png?t=1708729707"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/former.png?t=1708729707"> football player have been used to test play &amp; consult to plan opponent team strategies and movements, strengths and weaknesses, in order to offer players the most genuine experience. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/macmini.png?t=1708729707"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Available for PC &amp; Mac</strong></h2><br/><i>"Seasonal Soccer is a small top down soccer game in the genre of SNES soccer games. there is no online multiplayer or local, just singleplayer. but for a moment of your time its a moment of fun"</i> -Press Start To Begin Curator<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/818380/extras/poster.png?t=1708729707"/></img></img></img></li></ul></li></ul></li></ul></li></ul></li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of Melody Memorial</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/804230/Mystery_of_Melody_Memorial/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/804230/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Throughout his life, Joseph Teddie has been dead set on one singular goal: Uncover the depths of Melody Memorial. Why? He doesn't know. All he knows is that he needs to.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/804230/extras/Sitting.png?t=1708742547"><br/>In this musical adventure game, Joseph will travel and sing through creepy caverns, mischievous marshes, and even a casino to get to the legendary locale. But for the first time since he was a little kid, he won't be alone. After an encounter with local celebrity Angeli Lovely, she decides to piggyback on his journey in hopes of digging up the rumored treasure of Melody Memorial.<br/><br/>Are you ready to believe?<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Meet charming and quirky characters! </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore places to solve puzzles!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Sing along to the rhythm!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Laughs and emotions aplenty!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Set high scores in Arcade mode!</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Featuring an original soundtrack by Alexander Lyons and artwork by Alice Tan!</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windowkill</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2726450/Windowkill/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Something's wrong with the window...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/extras/bar.png?t=1708812124"><br/><br/>Windowkill is a twin-stick shooter, but the game window itself is constantly closing in on you. <br/>This game is experimental, your screen itself is the play area. Windows move and shift around on your screen as you play.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/extras/gif2.gif?t=1708812124"><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Twin-stick shooter controls<br/></li><li> Roguelike permadeath<br/></li><li> Shop screens<br/></li><li> Upgrades and Perks<br/></li><li> Hordes of enemies and bosses<br/></li><li> Several unique characters<br/></li><li> Local co-op<br/></li><li> Unlocks<br/></li><li> Secrets</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Multiplayer</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/extras/gif3.gif?t=1708812124"><h2 class="bb_tag">Unlocks, Stats, and More</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2726450/extras/gif1.gif?t=1708812124"><br/><br/>Mouse and keyboard is preferred, but gamepad is supported.<br/><br/>A game by torcado<br/>Music by keestak						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wizzerd Quest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2785800/Wizzerd_Quest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the mysterious land of Wayword!<br/><br/>Wizzerd Quest is a bite-sized open-world RPG with full splitscreen co-op. Its aesthetic and gameplay sit somewhere between DOOM and Daggerfall, and it's designed to be a fun little excursion without wasting your time. The full game, which is totally free, includes:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A main story quest that takes you all around the open world (Takes ~3 hrs to beat the game)<br/></li><li>6 classes, assigned dynamically based on leveling<br/></li><li>8 enemy types plus two bosses<br/></li><li>12 hand-crafted dungeons<br/></li><li>3 towns with facilities such as banks and traders<br/></li><li>Over 40 NPCs, all with unique, witty and funny (according to the devs) dialogue<br/></li><li>A full day-night cycle<br/></li><li>A voiced opening cutscene with cringe voice acting straight out of 1995<br/></li><li>The ability to ATTEMPT BARTERING WITH FARM ANIMALS <br/></li><li>Absolutely <strong>ZERO </strong> microtransactions, network telemetry or invasive DRM</li></ul><br/>Kondoorsoft offers this game to you totally free of charge. But make no mistake: this is no mere marketing demo. It's a full game, given freely to the community in the hopes that it will bring entertainment to those that play it. But if you like it and wish to support us, consider looking at the rest of our game catalog.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TerraCodex: The Stolen Relics</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2457350/TerraCodex_The_Stolen_Relics/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2457350/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The plot</strong><br/>The year is 1935. In the opulent city of Monte Carlo, the TerraCodex foundation is robbed of its powerful relics. All signs point to the infamous criminal group known as the 40 Thieves. Now, it's up to you to assemble a team of unique agents and track down these criminals to recover the stolen relics.<br/><br/><strong>The player, agents and thieves</strong><br/>As the mastermind of the operation, you direct agents around the globe, hunting for clues about the relics' whereabouts. Along your journey, you'll encounter diverse characters and unique scenarios. Challenges present themselves as engaging mini-games, each tied to different attributes. The thieves, each equipped with unique evasion skills, will not be caught easily. But rest assured, your agents have their own set of abilities too.<br/><br/><strong>The game board</strong><br/>Experience a first-person, single-player modern board game brought to life in VR. The game board, components, and miniatures come alive as you engage with them, collecting scattered clues to progress in your investigation.<br/><br/><strong>The experience</strong><br/>"TerraCodex: The Stolen Relics" stands out in the VR market with its unique approach to the board game genre. It offers a comfortable, accessible, and visually appealing strategy game experience. As the game constantly evolves to enhance the player's journey, you'll get to travel around the world of the mid-30s, visiting 60 unique venues across 20 different iconic cities, and interact with a dynamic array of characters.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunstorm</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2787740/Gunstorm/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2787740/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Your chance to defeat Xodar of Gorn! Gunstorm is a single-screen space shooter loaded with playability. Wave after wave of alien craft attack your agile ship. Face various end of level motherships and other special levels.<br>
<br>
Use the mouse to control your ship at the speed of thought, or use the keyboard or game controller. Set your own difficulty level and choose between a fixed or random game for infinite playability. Play the main campaign, or try an Onslaught against foes of increasing speed and number.<br>
<br>
Includes a variation of the classic arcade game Asteroids.<br/>
<br/>
Years of work has gone into perfectly balancing the gameplay to make a progressive game that never becomes impossible.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex's Hope &amp; Alex's Solitude</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2537750/Alexs_Hope__Alexs_Solitude/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2537750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Stories from the troubled pasts of two young adults, Alex's Hope &amp; Alex's Solitude will take you through their darkest days and immerse you in their deepest emotions.<br/><br/><strong>Alex's Hope</strong><br/>The difficult story of a boy with a bleak future and a critical lack of love finding a reason to regain hope. A dark atmosphere, a cold journey, and a soft warmth will change his fate.<br/><br/><strong>Alex's Solitude</strong><br/>The story of a stubbornly good-hearted girl finding rejection and struggling to fit in. A change in persona, a new friend, and a serious wake-up call will lead her to make a life-changing resolution.<br/><br/><strong>Content Warning</strong><br/>This visual novel contains themes that may be distressing to many individuals, including:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Depression<br/></li><li>Anxiety<br/></li><li>Suicidal Thoughts<br/></li><li>Self Harm<br/></li><li>Substance Abuse<br/></li><li>Drug Overdose</li></ul><br/>It does not contain any written or visual depictions of death or any graphic depictions of injury or self harm.<br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Two individual short stories (Combined length of about 7,400 words)<br/></li><li>Immersive and intensely emotional storytelling<br/></li><li>Original hand-drawn characters and backgrounds<br/></li><li>Original, immersive, and very emotionally driven soundtrack with 12 unique songs<br/></li><li>Three CGs in each story<br/></li><li>A cute cat</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bunny-girl with Golden tummy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2780880/Bunnygirl_with_Golden_tummy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2780880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2780880/extras/vvv.gif?t=1708711070"><br/>What could be cuter than a girl bunny? That's right! A girl bunny with a golden tummy! Our bunny loves to serve customers, she is just waiting to be asked to make a cocktail or dance. Don't keep her waiting and ask for something too! ♡<br/><br/>Easy win: Keyboard <u><strong>Сtrl+D</strong></u> - Complete Level<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2780880/extras/she.png?t=1708711070"><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>⭐   Beautiful artwork<br/></li><li>⭐   Animation scenes<br/></li><li>⭐   Relaxing music<br/></li><li>⭐   CG Gallery Mode<br/></li><li>⭐   Puzzle game</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penni's Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2479020/Pennis_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare to embark on a thrilling adventure as the mischievous Lightbearers invade your tranquil home, reshaping it with their enigmatic technology! It's time to rally your courage, rescue your friends, and send those bears packing in this action-packed platformer that's perfect for the entire family! <br/><br/>Immerse yourself in a visually captivating world with retro-inspired graphics that'll transport you to a bygone era of gaming nostalgia. Get ready for an epic quest filled with excitement and endless fun! <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479020/extras/GIF_1.gif?t=1708710988"><br/><br/><br/>Unleash your inner sorcerer as you engage in whimsical yet engaging combat. Wield a wide array of magical powers to thwart the Lightbearers, and get ready to grin from ear to ear as you unleash your creative arsenal of enchanting weaponry!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479020/extras/GIF_2.gif?t=1708710988"><br/><br/><br/>Embark on a dazzling journey through a tapestry of vibrant and diverse landscapes, from enchanting forests to mysterious caves, sun-kissed beaches, and beyond! Each level is a new adventure waiting to be explored! <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2479020/extras/GIF_3.gif?t=1708710988"><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Experience classic action/platforming gameplay across a multitude of mesmerizing biomes.<br/></li><li>Take on fun bosses, ranging from imposing tanks to the legendary Kraken!<br/></li><li>Harness the power of magical wands, including fire, lightning, and even love, throughout your epic adventure.<br/></li><li>Discover new weapons and unlock exciting features as you traverse the enchanting lands of Penni's Adventure!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowkin</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2212410/Shadowkin/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2212410/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You play as two lowly minions to the Dark Lord, tasked with becoming stronger and conquering worlds.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2212410/extras/steam_gif1.gif?t=1708734809"><br/><br/>You may play Singleplayer and be accompanied by your Ally (AI controlled), or play with a friend in <strong>2 Player Local Coop via Steam RemotePlay</strong>. Together, you will synergize your builds and work together to vanquish those who would stand in your way.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2212410/extras/steam_gif2.gif?t=1708734809"><br/><br/>Annihilate your foes with a variety of auto-attacking abilities, ranging from fireballs and boomerangs to exploding ice sculptures and pushable boulders. Throughout your quest, you will be offered unique relics to further empower your abilities. Gifts from the Dark Lord. Use them well.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2212410/extras/steam_gif3.gif?t=1708734809"><br/><br/>From the creator of <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1929870/Nomad_Survival/" rel="" target="_blank">Nomad Survival</a>, this is a Bullet Heaven unlike any you've seen before.<h2 class="bb_tag">TAKE OVER THE WORLD</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Auto-attacking Horde Survival Roguelite with a unique twist, 2 characters means 2 builds, and many skills interact with the other player directly.<br/></li><li>Play with an AI-controlled Ally, or with a friend using Local Co-Op (compatible with <i>Steam RemotePlay</i>)!<br/></li><li>Unique skill level ups - most filler is removed in favor of giving skills more interesting effects when leveling them up!<br/></li><li>Each run is unique, with each room presenting various risks and rewards!<br/></li><li>Acquire relics to aid you in various ways throughout your playthrough, modifying the behavior of your abilities and more!<br/></li><li>Take on a boss fight that awaits you in the final area of every zone. Each boss has their own special attacks and abilities!<br/></li><li>Many elemental skills interact with each other. For example, some Water skills make puddles, and Storm abilities electrify them!<br/></li><li>Become stronger between runs through meta upgrades in the form of a skill tree!</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bots Color Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2803470/A_Bots_Color_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2803470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Get Ready for the game of your Life: ABotsColorAdventure!<br>
Within this beautiful world, each level has its own color palette. The landscape is not merely a backdrop; it's a living, pulsating entity that sets the stage for thrilling challenges and unforeseen adventures.<br>
Your quest begins with the pursuit of blue orbs scattered across all levels. Collect them and move on to the next level. <br>
Battle against herds of enemies, each with its own set of challenges and strategies. The combat system is not only dynamic but also rewards strategic thinking, encouraging players to adapt their approach and evolve with each encounter.<br>
Whether it's rescuing a friendly NPC, solving intricate puzzles, or facing off against powerful enemies, every mission propels you forward in your quest to become the ultimate adventurer.<br>
Use the stat and ability upgrade system to empower you on your journey, and unlock new abilities to turn the tide of battle in your favor. <br>
As you navigate through the game, companionship takes on a new dimension with the ability to summon an adorable pet. They will help you progress through the game more easily.<br/>
Are you prepared for the adventure of a lifetime? Jump into ABotsColorAdventure and get the adventure started!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
