<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor - Supporter Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2782850/Deep_Rock_Galactic_Survivor__Supporter_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2782850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							If you simply can't get enough of Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor then the Supporter Pack is for you. Your support fuels further development of the game, and gives you this small satchel of exclusive in-game goods as a nice bonus:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A prestigious golden skin for all four dwarf classes!<br/></li><li>A fancy supporter badge on the main menu game logo<br/></li><li>Our heartfelt and eternal thanks and gratitude &lt;3</li></ul><strong><u>Important note</u></strong>: By buying this DLC you are first and foremost showing your support for the game and for Funday (developers) and Ghost Ship (publishers). The bling-bling in the list above is really just icing on the cake!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tomb Raider I-III Remastered Starring Lara Croft</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2478970/Tomb_Raider_IIII_Remastered_Starring_Lara_Croft/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2478970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Discover Lara Croft’s Original Adventures, Lovingly Restored</h2> <br/>Play the Original Three Tomb Raider Adventures: For the first time ever, play the complete experience with all expansions and secret levels on modern platforms in this definitive collection.<h2 class="bb_tag">Included Game Titles</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tomb Raider I + Unfinished Business<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider II + Golden Mask<br/></li><li>Tomb Raider III + The Lost Artifact</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2><br/><strong>Solve Ancient Mysteries</strong>: Uncover treasures of the ancient world by solving puzzles and unraveling mysteries lost to the ravages of time.<br/><br/><strong>Globe-trotting Adventure</strong>: Follow Lara Croft around the world and face off against deadly foes and dangerous myths.<br/><br/><strong>Lovingly Restored</strong>: Experience the classics boasting upgraded graphics, with the option to switch to the original polygon look at any time.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1924780/Arzette_The_Jewel_of_Faramore/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/intro_gif.gif?t=1707886813"><br/><br/>After ten years of peace...the evil Daimur has returned! Princess Arzette is the Kingdom of Faramore’s only hope to restore harmony to the land!<br/><br/>In this brand new interactive action adventure game, you control the resourceful princess Arzette. Travel through multiple breathtaking locations filled with scum, villainy and secrets, speak with the locals to uncover mysteries and objectives, and take on the evil Daimur as <strong>Arzette: The Jewel of Faramore</strong> brings you the best interactive gaming experience since the invention of the CD-ROM!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1924780/extras/mortar_gif.gif?t=1707886813"><br/><br/><strong>Featuring:</strong><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Hand painted backgrounds and incredible sprite art.<br/></li><li>Fully voice-acted cartoon cinematics with a colorful cast of characters.<br/></li><li>A sprawling world with diverse locations and many secrets.<br/></li><li>Acquire powerful items and abilities by exploring and helping those in need.<br/></li><li>Veteran dev team including artist Rob Dunlavey, Digital Foundry's John Linneman and Audi Sorlie, voice talent Jeffrey Rath and Bonnie Jean Wilbur, and award winning composer Jake "Button Masher" Silverman.</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwatch® 2 - Ultimate Battle Pass Bundle: Season 9</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2707800/Overwatch_2__Ultimate_Battle_Pass_Bundle_Season_9/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2707800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Explore the cosmic unknown!<br>
<br>
Includes:<br>
- Premium Battle Pass + 20 Tiers<br/>
- Beholder Sigma and Harbinger Lifeweaver Legendary Skins<br/>
- 2,000 Overwatch Coins<br/>
<br/>
With your Overwatch Coins, you can purchase in-game cosmetic items to customize your heroes. Owners of the Premium Battle Pass can also use Overwatch Coins to unlock Tiers and instantly access Legendary and Mythic content. Tier skips will not apply to any battle pass level beyond level 80 and will not unlock prestige tiers. Any excess tier skips you purchase past level 80 are banked and will be automatically redeemed at launch of the following season.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caribbean Legend: Sandbox</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1782680/Caribbean_Legend_Sandbox/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782680/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Caribbean in 1654 AD, a place teeming with opportunities and mysteries. Assume the role of one of the three adventurers: youthful French aristocrat, a formidable Spanish mercenary, or a savvy English entrepreneur. Explore, trade, plunder, complete quests and enjoy the Caribbean Open World. This game has the most of improvements and a good portion of new content from the upcoming Caribbean Legend. <strong>Based on Sea Dogs series and inspired by Sid Meier's Pirates!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782680/extras/steamchar2.jpg?t=1707850966"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782680/extras/Без_имени-3.png?t=1707850966"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Freeplay</strong>: The Caribbean is your domain, offering everything from exploring ancient pyramids to capturing entire towns.<br/></li><li><strong>Hundred Recurring Quests</strong>: Engage in a myriad of quests, each with multiple potential outcomes, including freight jobs, bounty hunting, trading contracts, and more!<br/></li><li><strong>Unique Quests:</strong> Embark on twenty distinctive quests, each with its own compelling narrative.<br/></li><li><strong>Land and Naval Warfare</strong>: Transition from confronting thugs in jungles and pirating a small game to leading full-scale sieges and commanding an armada of warships.<br/></li><li><strong>Extensive Customisation</strong>: Tailor your experience with character builds, dozens of ships, and a vast array of over a hundred items and weapons.<br/></li><li><strong>Side Activities</strong>: Immerse yourself in a wide range of activities, including crafting, trading, duels, gambling, smuggling, romance, ship upgrading, and treasure hunting.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782680/extras/Без_имениdd-3.png?t=1707850966"><br/>Caribbean Legend: Sandbox is at the beginning of its journey as we aim to create the ultimate pirate freeplay game. This game is still under development, and while we haven't finalized all the main future milestones, our general vision is already taking shape. The old Sea Dogs approach primarily focused on expanding quest content. When a player completed all available side quests, their journey in the game would come to an end. This approach wasn't necessarily flawed, but we're excited to explore a new direction. <br/><br/>What if the game consistently generated one-of-a-kind situations for players, ensuring each playthrough remains captivating and distinctive, from the early game to the very end? Let's discover the possibilities! Based on sales of the full game and community feedback, the following roadmap may undergo adjustments, to the lesser or (hopefully!) the bigger scale. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1782680/extras/en-roadmap.png?t=1707850966"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islands of Insight</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2071500/Islands_of_Insight/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Islands of Insight: a sublime shared-world puzzle game set in a fantasy realm of ancient wonders and natural beauty. Brimming with mysterious puzzles to solve, secrets to uncover, and vibrant landscapes to explore, this peaceful world of floating islands is the perfect place to unwind. Embark on a puzzle adventure of your choice, all at your own pace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_1-Title-Journey_EN.png?t=1707847143">‎‎‏‏‎<br/>Play as a Seeker on a peaceful journey rich in exploration and puzzle-solving. Embark on the Path of Discovery and let your curiosity guide you through a breathtaking open world where the answer is always in sight.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Journey_HD.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_2-Title-Puzzles_EN.png?t=1707847143"><br/>Seek out and solve an unparalleled collection of over 10,000 puzzles divided across 24 puzzle types. Every corner of the world holds a new eureka moment for you to discover. From enigmas of perspective to logic problems, environmental challenges and more, the puzzles you’ll encounter vary in difficulty and have been crafted by some of the best minds in puzzle design to create an engaging experience for both newcomers and seasoned puzzle fans.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_Gifs_Puzzles_HD.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_3-Title-Exploration_EN.png?t=1707847143"><br/>Freely explore the main island’s expansive open world where most of the puzzles and secrets are found. Wander the vibrant landscapes and architecture of its 5 distinct biomes or spread your wings to glide above them. Navigate the environment’s verticality and take your game to new heights. Unlock puzzle types and new areas in the campaign by completing 20+ Enclaves housing curated puzzle challenges. Go where you want. Solve what you want. The only path here is the one you make.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/3.IOI_Steam_Gif_Exploration___Discovery_2.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/IOI_Steam_About_the_Game_Banner_5-Title-Experience_EN.png?t=1707847143"><br/>Customize your character. Increase your puzzle masteries to level them up while earning sparks to unlock new abilities. Complete daily quests. Seamlessly interact with other players in our shared world to gain or offer a bit of guidance, or choose to figure things out entirely on your own. With puzzles that refresh over time, a new discovery awaits with every visit to the islands.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2071500/extras/4.IOI_Steam_Gif_An_Evergreen_Experience_2.gif?t=1707847143"><br/><br/>Age restrictions may apply to access this game.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2436570/DRAGON_QUEST_BUILDERS/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Build.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>The first title in the BUILDERS series, DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS, is bringing its handy crafting features to Steam!<br/>Gather, craft and build to defeat defeat the evil Dragonlord and restore Alefgard to it's former glory!<br/>In a world made out of blocks, everything that you see can be materials used to create! Farm ingredients, craft various items and build your base to unite the people roaming the ruins. From buildings to entire towns, you have the freedom to make your village your very own.<h2 class="bb_tag">■ Story</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Lightning.gif?t=1707862917"><br/>BUILDERS is set in the realm of Alefgard, the setting for the first ever DRAGON QUEST game.<br/>The world of Alefgard has been plunged into darkness, its light stolen by the evil Dragonlord, and this story begins with the appearance of a young hero with a mysterious ability to build things... And so the stage is set for an epic tale in which the dark world of Alefgard is returned to life with the power of creation!<h2 class="bb_tag">■ The first DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS title, helpful crafting features include:</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_3.png?t=1707862917"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Place blocks remotely, or destroy blocks with ease, with just a single click of the mouse!<br/></li><li> Now Includes a helpful Undo feature, which allows you to put things back to how they were before!<br/></li><li> Now Featuring Big Bash, a useful feature introduced in DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS 2 that allows you to break all objects in a particular area in one go!<br/></li><li> Terra Incognita, BUILDERS’ free build stage, the stackable block height is doubled!<br/></li><li> Includes fun side content, like collecting figurines of NPCs and monsters, or gathering pixels and exchanging them for a variety of handy items!<br/></li><li> Use Build Cards to share buildings with other players and bring their buildings to life on your island!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">■ Includes all DLC from previous versions of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/intextbanner_4.png?t=1707862917"><br/>The Steam version of DRAGON QUEST BUILDERS includes all of the DLC from past versions including the free build mode, Terra Incognita: Magic Carpet, Boss Monster Model Set, Astronomy Set and Pixel Ring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2436570/extras/Toybox_Announce_Stack.gif?t=1707862917"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lysfanga: The Time Shift Warrior</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161620/Lysfanga_The_Time_Shift_Warrior/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/LYS_LOGO_STEAM.png?t=1707919615"><br/>After half a millennium of peace, a new danger hangs over Antala. Its fate depends on you, Imë, <strong>Lysfanga</strong> of the New Kingdom, protector of the realm. The ancient cities, previously locked in time, are now free again, and an old evil has escaped, threatening the peace. <br/><br/>But you won’t be alone. Gifted with <strong>temporal powers</strong> from the Goddess of Time herself, something no other Lysfanga has had before, you have the ability to <strong>rewind time in combat</strong> to summon <strong>clones of your past-selves</strong> to help you. Master your power to become legion, and crush hordes of the escaped demons, known as the <strong>Raxes</strong>.<br/><br/>With your <strong>army of past-selves</strong>, progress through the ancient cities to extend your arsenal of weapons and learn new spells, preparing for the much greater threat ahead... <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/MUSTER_AN_ARMY_OF_YOURSELF_V2_EN.png?t=1707919615"><br/>Use Imë’s godlike powers to rewind time a few seconds in the past and summon clones of yourself – remnants – to create an army and overpower your enemies. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/Lysfanga_gif_steam_v4.gif?t=1707919615"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/PUSH_YOUR_LIMITS_V2_EN.png?t=1707919615"><br/>Challenge your skills and your wits to outdo yourself. Master and replay each arena to beat your high scores, and challenge yourself by changing the difficulty settings and adding combat modifiers to unlock new rewards.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/TAILOR_EACH_FIGHT_V2_EN.png?t=1707919615"><br/>Each arena can be approached in countless ways. Adapt your strategy and use all the tools at your disposal to emerge victorious. Success will only depend on your combination of remnants, spells and weapons.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/Lysfanga_gif_steam_Fight.gif?t=1707919615"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161620/extras/INVESTIGATE_GIGANTIC_ANCIENT_CITIES_V2_EN.png?t=1707919615"><br/>The old time-locks are gone. The Raxes are now free to create chaos again. Explore the abandoned cities of the old continent previously locked in time and uncover the truth behind the resurgence of the Raxes.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blacksmith. Song of two Kings.</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2531370/Blacksmith_Song_of_two_Kings/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Text_Welcome.png?t=1707832591"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Stuff1.png?t=1707832591"><br/>Take your hammer and get the coals burning! It's time for fire, metal and magic! In this game you will: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Forge, bend, cut and sharpen metal. Work with wood and bone.<br/></li><li>Weave chainmail. Use potions and spells.<br/></li><li>Take blacksmithing orders, creating unique weapons, armor and other curious items.<br/></li><li>Upgrade your dwelling and forge.<br/></li><li>Find useful items and new friends who are willing to help. <br/></li><li>Explore high fantasy world while diving into the story of the game.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Text_Gameplay.png?t=1707832591"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Final1_small_1.gif?t=1707832591"><br/>You'll have to work in the forge literally by hand - grab the hammer and hit the workpiece with it, sending out sparks. Strike after strike to flatten or bend metal. Cut wooden boards, sticks and branches by grasping the saw handle and moving it back and forth. Tie ropes, attach chains. Push the levers of the tongs. Bring flasks to the blanks, spill potions. Use magic books to enchant blades, shields and armor! There are over 100 unique and repeatable schemes, as well as a free-to-play forge mode.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Gallery_Overview_Small.gif?t=1707832591"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Text_SmithyManagement_eng.png?t=1707832591"><br/>Much of what you find during your wanderings will prove useful in the forge. The properties of items and character skills are revealed in combinations with each other. It's no secret, for example, that dwarves are more willing to work in the forge if you put a couple of kegs of beer in the house!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Managment_Small.gif?t=1707832591"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Description_Text_Adventure.png?t=1707832591"><br/>You have a journey ahead of you, blacksmith. You have seen it in your dreams. And now they lead you. So embrace it. Embark on your adventure and face your destiny!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2531370/extras/Adventure_Small.gif?t=1707832591"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultros</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2386310/Ultros/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You wake up stranded, after seemingly crashing your ship on The Sarcophagus — a giant, space-drifting, cosmic uterus holding an ancient demonic being known as ULTROS. Trapped in the eternal loop of a black hole, you will have to explore The Sarcophagus and meet its inhabitants to understand the part you play. <br/><br/>Are you the gruesome breaker of this cycle, or can you become a link from destruction to rebirth? <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat1.png?t=1707822049"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat1.gif?t=1707822049"><br/>ULTROS is set in a multifaceted realm - a vast alien landscape teeming with life. Grounded in science fiction, ULTROS comes wrapped in an eccentric art style and a mystical soundtrack from the visionary El Huervo, renowned for his work on Hotline Miami. ULTROS explores meta-themes of mental health, life, death, and karmic cycles through deep lore and environmental storytelling.       <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat2.png?t=1707822049"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat2.gif?t=1707822049"><br/>Experience brutal, intimate, close-quarter combat with cosmic lifeforms, driven by a sense of urgency – where precision is paramount and every cut of your blade counts. Yet this intense combat is juxtaposed with cultivating the greenery and tending to plant life in The Sarcophagus, providing precious moments of contemplation and peace. In turn, this grants deeper access to obscured paths.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/EN-Ultros-feat3.png?t=1707822049"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2386310/extras/steam_feat3.gif?t=1707822049"><br/>The rich world of ULTROS holds many secrets for those curious enough — and fearless enough — to seek them out. A unique loop-based mechanic will allow you to start over at key moments in the story, providing opportunities to unfold such secrets, unlock different areas of the world and new abilities on a branching skill tree. Experiment with and master your own specific fighting style as you explore the world of ULTROS. Each loop brings you closer to the truth...						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Will:Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2802530/Space_WillPrologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>The difference between the prologue and the official version<br/>Characters: 10 in the prologue, 59 in the official version<br/>Galaxy: 2 in the prologue, 6 in the official version</strong><br/><br/><strong>Sixty basic cores, hundreds of base station equipment, and thousands of chips, you can freely cooperate and shoot through the dual-angle joystick operation in a survival Roguelike game! Explore the sci-fi space and build your strongest battleship!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/1y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Step 1: Choose a "core" as your basic role<br/>Step 2: Choose a "crew" as your initial weapon<br/>Step 3: Select a galaxy for exploration</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/2y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game will continuously collect new "units" or "chips" during the exploration process<br/>Using "crew" can expand weapons and enhance combat effectiveness for your warship<br/>Using "chips" can enhance various abilities of your warship</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/3y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>Each "core" or "unit" has a maximum of 4 interfaces. When the interfaces are used up, you cannot equip more parts, but you can also infinitely increase the number of your interfaces!<br/>Each "crew" can use the right mouse button to rotate and adjust the optimal angle for combat</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.png?t=1707882542"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2802530/extras/4y.gif?t=1707882542"><br/><strong>The game features dual joystick shooting, with the keyboard moving and the mouse aiming at the enemy. Of course, there are many weapons that can automatically attack or be placed in the scene as traps for use~</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_TITLE_FULLSCREEN.gif?t=1707823167"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_1.png?t=1707823167"><br/> <br/>In New Eden, 1695, communities of settlers are plagued by a dreadful curse. As Banishers, step into their lives, investigate the source of evil, unravel chilling mysteries, explore diverse landscapes, and interact with unforgettable characters whose fate lies in your hands.<br/><br/>Banishers: Ghosts of New Eden is an all-new title crafted by renowned studio DON'T NOD, known for their acclaimed titles such as Life is Strange and Vampyr. Immerse yourself in an intimate narrative Action-RPG, taking you on an exhilarating journey between life, death, love and sacrifices.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_2.png?t=1707823167"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_FANTASY.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Play as a couple of Banishers, Red and Antea, experienced spirit hunters entrusted with the daunting task of dispelling a malevolent curse through powerful rituals. Protect the living from the threat of lingering ghosts and specters, and become a beacon of hope in a world consumed by darkness.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_3.png?t=1707823167"> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_NARATION_LOVE.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Experience a heart-wrenching love story between Antea Duarte and Red mac Raith. When Antea is killed and turned into a spirit, you find yourself facing a choice. Will you uphold your oath and ascend her soul, or will you sacrifice the living in the hope of bringing her back? Your decisions will shape the fate of New Eden’s inhabitants - may they be living or dead, and determine the end of your journey.<br/> <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>BLAME</strong> the living and sacrifice their lives, holding them responsible for their actions<br/></li><li><strong>BANISH</strong> souls of the departed, condemning them to eternal suffering<br/></li><li><strong>ASCEND</strong> souls, liberating them from eternal sorrow and granting them serenity</li></ul><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_4.png?t=1707823167"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_COMBAT.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Banishers are specialized in combat against undead creatures, such as specters or ghosts. Combine Red's physical arsenal with Antea's supernatural powers in a dynamic combat system. Find your own style by mixing weapon attacks and spiritual abilities. Powerful synergies will lead you to defeat New Eden’s most dangerous enemies and bosses.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_6.png?t=1707823167"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_SKILL.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Unleash the full power of the Banishers by unlocking new gear and supernatural abilities. By exploring New Eden, you will find ancient artifacts, trinkets and valuable resources to enhance your equipment in preparation of future fights. In addition to your arsenal, progress in Antea’s skill trees to upgrade her devastating spectral powers and unseal new combos.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_5.png?t=1707823167"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/BANISHERS_GIF_EXPLORATION.gif?t=1707823167"><br/>Investigate haunting cases in a mystical world full of dark secrets. Discover New Eden, a North America settlement marked by terrible stories and secrets of its tormented inhabitants. Understanding each resident’s motivations will be essential to guide your decisions throughout the game.<br/><br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1493640/extras/Title_Card_7.png?t=1707823167"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1493640/Banishers_Ghosts_of_New_Eden/?utm_source=Steam&amp;utm_medium=VampyrSteam&amp;utm_campaign=Permanent</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 Ninja Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<table><tr><th><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop" id="dynamiclink_9" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=WidgetTop</a><h2 class="bb_tag">🐱🥋🐾 WELCOME TO 100 NINJA CATS – THE BEST HIDDEN OBJECTS GAME! 🌆🗡️</h2>🗡️Join the cutest adventure in the Ninja world full of cats! Explore the charming hand-drawn artwork of ninja themed locations as you embark on a quest to find 100 adorable cats hidden throughout the game. 🎨<br/>😸Test your attention and observation skills in this cozy and delightful hidden object game.<br/>😊Each cat is more charming than the last, and every discovery brings a smile to your face.<h2 class="bb_tag">🐈🕵️‍♂️ Can you find them all? 🕵️‍♂️🐈</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x200.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">⚙️ Key Features ⚙️</h2></img></th></tr></table><ul class="bb_ul"><li>🎮 1 Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎮 1 Extra Level<br/></li><li>🐈 100 Extra Hidden Cats<br/></li><li>🎵 Awesome Soundtrack<br/></li><li>🎨 High Quality Resolution Artworks<br/></li><li>🌗 Brightness Settings<br/></li><li>💾 Progress Saves<br/></li><li>🔍 Zoom<br/></li><li>😺 Real Meow Sounds!<br/></li><li>💥 Combo Counter!<br/></li><li>💡 Hints<br/></li><li>🌐 No Text</li></ul><table><tr><th><h2 class="bb_tag">🏆 START YOUR AMAZING JOURNEY IN THE WORLD OF CATS RIGHT NOW 🏆</h2><strong>Don't miss out on the cutest and exciting puzzle game ever! Come to 100 Ninja Cats and start your amazing adventure today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">😻🎁DLC List for this game🎁😻</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815970/100_Ninja_Cats__Extra_Content/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Extra.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2816000/100_Ninja_Cats_Soundtrack/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Soundtrack.png?t=1707834357"/></a><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2815980/100_Ninja_Cats__Artbook/?utm_source=NinjaCats_Bot" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Artbook.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/600x1.png?t=1707834357"><h2 class="bb_tag">✅😻 Follow our Dev Page! 😻✅</h2><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/publisher/100CozyGames" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2776810/extras/Following_Small.png?t=1707834357"/></a><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot" id="dynamiclink_10" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2687200/100_London_Cats/?utm_source=NinjaBot</a></img></th></tr></table><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot" id="dynamiclink_11" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2776810/100_Ninja_Cats/?utm_source=NinjatBot</a> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Tales</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1465070/Legendary_Tales/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_07.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>Are you ready for adventure? Collect loot, destroy enemies, learn magic, craft your own items and head out on epic quests to conquer the evil that lurks beneath the earth. Play Alone or with friends; Legendary Tales is the ultimate fantasy VR experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/00.Steam_MiniTitle_RPG.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Grow your own unique character through gameplay and work your way through an extensive skill tree.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/01.Steam_MiniTitle_Multiplayer.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Supports Up-to 4 player Co-op<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/02.Steam_MiniTitle_Magic.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Master the art of magic and destroy enemies with fire, ice and lightning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/03.Steam_MiniTitle_RNGItems.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Collect an almost limitless amount of items thanks to random number generation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/04.Steam_MiniTitle_Physics.png?t=1707433150"><br/>An amazing physics based fighting system with destructible objects and scenery.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/05.Steam_MiniTitle_Crafting.png?t=1707433150"><br/>Craft your own items,potions and upgrade crafted items with an in depth crafting system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/06.Steam_MiniTitle_AboutLT.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_05.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>Are you ready to step down into the darkness? Explore winding roads and ruined castles that will take you down to the heart of the underworld, to defeat the evil corrupting the land. But be careful down there, the road is dangerous so you best bring a friend. Traverse the landscape, Bludgeon, slice and decimate skeletons with melee weapons, sneak up on a goblin with ranged weapons or destroy a demon from afar with destructive magic.<br/>Physics based melee combat, Improved Ai, an immersive crafting system, a myriad of weapons and up to 4 player co-op; this is an RPG, fantasy, adventure that is waiting for you to create your own Legendary Tales.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/07.Steam_MiniTitle_Generation.png?t=1707433150"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/08.Steam_MiniTitle_VR.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_04.gif?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Built from the ground up for VR; Legendary Tales will throw you into an immersive fantasy world, suitable for any PCVR platform with customisable graphics settings to ensure you get the smoothest possible experience.</ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/09.Steam_MiniTitle_Mutiplayer.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_03.gif?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Up to 4 players can play Legendary Tales in co-op mode. Grab some friends, trade some items, and head down into the dungeon to fight your way through the darkness together.</ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/010.Steam_MiniTitle_Physics.png?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">The physics in Legendary Tales was built to mimic the way real weapons feel and act as close as possible while still being fun to play. Weapons have their own weight so that larger swings will do more damage. Not only that but enemies and destructible items also react to how hard you hit them for a truly engaging experience. </ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/011.Steam_MiniTitle_Items.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_06.gif?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Want to try sneaky kills with a dagger? Hit your enemies from afar with a bow? Or just mash some faces with a morning star? There are a host of different weapon types to suit your play style so find what works for you! And for every weapon type you will find so many variations on their stats thanks to random number generated items. The items are classed into five categories ranging from normal to Legendary. which not only look awesome but have special abilities. What abilities? You’ll have to get one for yourself to find out.</ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/014.Steam_MiniTitle_Skilltree.png?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">As you fight your way through the world, your character will grow based on how you play. But there’s more to growth than just how you fight, work your way through the magic and skills available to truly bring your character to the next level.</ul><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/012.Steam_MiniTitle_Combatskills.png?t=1707433150"><br/><ul class="bb_ul">Weapons are fun and all but through the skill tree you can improve your abilities with combat skills or find yourself a Legendary item with their own special abilities and even more, you can upgrade their skills! </ul> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/013.Steam_MiniTitle_Crafting.png?t=1707433150"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_02_new.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>If hunting for weapons in the dungeons isn’t for you then we have good news! You can create your own weapons with ingredients found on your adventures, or by honing the weapons you’ve collected. You can also make potions to prepare deep dungeon crawling and disassemble items you found during your adventures to get ingredients and enhance your crafted weapons or potions with them.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1465070/extras/Steam_About_01.gif?t=1707433150"><br/>Get ready for an epic adventure in VR! Put on your headset, find some friends and head into the dungeon to start creating your own Legendary Tales.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLDIVERS™ 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/553850/HELLDIVERS_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SuperEarthSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><br/>The Galaxy’s Last Line of Offence.<br/><br/>Enlist in the Helldivers and join the fight for freedom across a hostile galaxy in a fast, frantic, and ferocious third-person shooter.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/BugAssaultSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">URGENT BROADCAST – SUPER EARTH ARMED FORCES</h2>Freedom. Peace. Democracy. <br/>Your Super Earth-born rights. The key pillars of our civilization. <br/>Of our very existence. <br/>But the war rages on. And everything is once again under threat.<br/>Join the greatest military force the galaxy has ever seen and make this a safe and free place to live.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StratagemSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">BECOME A LEGEND</h2>You will be assembled into squads of up to four Helldivers and assigned strategic missions.<br/>Watch each other’s back – friendly fire is an unfortunate certainty of war, but victory without teamwork is impossible.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/EagleExplosionsSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">LOADOUTS</h2>Rain down freedom from above, sneak through enemy territory, or grit your teeth and charge head-first into the jaws of combat.<br/>How you deliver liberty is your choice; you’ll have access to a wide array of explosive firepower, life-saving armor and battle-changing stratagems… the jewel in every Helldiver’s arsenal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/ChargerChargeSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">REQUISITION</h2>Super Earth recognises your hard work with valuable Requisition. Use it to access different rewards that benefit you, your squad, your destroyer ship and our overall war effort.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/StriderSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">THREATS</h2>Everything on every planet wants you dead. That’s what we’re dealing with.<br/>Each enemy has distinct and unpredictable characteristics, tactics, and behavior – but they all fight ferociously and without fear or morality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/553850/extras/SquadRunningSTEAM.gif?t=1707382710"><h2 class="bb_tag">THE GALACTIC WAR</h2>Capturing enemy planets, defending against invasions, and completing missions will contribute to our overall effort. <br/><br/><br/>This war will be won or lost depending on the actions of everyone involved.<br/><br/>We stand together, or we fall apart.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KONOSUBA - God's Blessing on this Wonderful World! Love For These Clothes Of Desire!</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2349140/KONOSUBA__Gods_Blessing_on_this_Wonderful_World_Love_For_These_Clothes_Of_Desire/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/KonoSuba_KeyArt_Landscape_WithLogo.png?t=1707479148"><br/>Follow Kazuma and company, as they discover a mysterious "Black Slab" which curses them with desires contrary to their personality. The gang must now find and feed ingredients to the slab to create outfits which match and fulfil their new desires, and thus break their curse. Are you ready to meet Darkness as a ruthless dominatrix? How about Aqua as a prim and proper goddess? Or Megumin as the proud leader of the Lolita League?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/new-narrative-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/01._Black_slab!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Witness a new story in visual novel form! Featuring a full cast of fan-favourite characters from the series, this wild adventure gives you the chance to build up affection with up to seven heroines!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/get-to-work-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/02._Schedule_overview!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Fill out a weekly planner for each character based on their strengths to earn funds and resources which can be used for making outfits.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/make-decisions-orange-1.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/decision_making_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Each of them has her own story endings and special dress-up CGs, so pick your words wisely and avoid invoking their wrath! Your choices matter! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/Manage-resources-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/04._Resources_schedule_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Collect resources to create outfits by completing tasks and quests. Manage your finances carefully to afford the materials you are missing, and prioritise gathering the outfit-specific ingredients you will need.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/play-dress-up-orange.gif?t=1707479148"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/05._Make_more_clothes!_resized.jpg?t=1707479148"><br/><br/>Once the mystical outfits have been made it’s time to play dress-up! Be ready for twists and turns as your favourite characters’ personalities change with each curse and desire-fulfilling piece of clothing.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2349140/extras/DANCE-smaller-no-boaarder.gif?t=1707479148"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III - BlackCell (Season 2)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2731840/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III__BlackCell_Season_2/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2731840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Get Call of Duty® Points* and in-game content for Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III and Call of Duty®: Warzone™.<br>
<br>
Offering includes:<br>
<br/>
- Battle Pass for Season 2<br/>
- 20 Battle Token Tier Skips<br/>
<br/>
Exclusive BlackCell Sector on the Battle Map:<br/>
<br/>
- 1100 Call of Duty® Points<br/>
- BlackCell Operator<br/>
- Assault Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Battle Rifle Weapon Blueprint<br/>
- Finishing Move<br/>
<br/>
- BlackCell Bonus Topper with 11 additional reactive Operator skin alternatives and 6 Weapon Blueprints with Tracers.<br/>
<br/>
Activision may update, replace, or remove this in-game content at any time.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WitchHand</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2420880/WitchHand/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-01.gif?t=1707898632"><br/><br/>In <strong>WitchHand</strong>, you use cards to build your empire of witches. Maximize the production of your villages and use your resources strategically to upgrade and expand. Focus on trade, alchemy research, or war in order to secure your coven's place amongst the Council of Fates, influencing the destiny of all. Work with your neighbors to secure a better future or crush them and use their bones to fuel your spells. When the witching hour comes each night, your witch's powers are at their strongest, while unseen forces work against you. You must expand and manage your coven to new heights if you are to withstand the coming darkness. No rest for the wicked.<h2 class="bb_tag">A CIVILIZATION OF WITCHES</h2>WitchHand folds the 4X strategy formula into card-based gameplay. You'll perform strategic actions like exploring, expanding, and exterminating through real-time card placement. Manage worker placement, village production, and research in order to advance the strength and reach of your coven.<h2 class="bb_tag">WIELD THE POWERS OF THE WITCHES OF THE REALMS</h2>Each witch has a unique selection of spells, buildings, and units that defines them. Empower your villages and production with the Celestial Witch. Overpower your enemies with the might of the Chaos Witch. Cook delicious, stat-boosting meals with the Chef Witch. Choose the witch that best suits your playstyle and have full control over your research paths to further personalize your playthrough.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/spellbook_and_wonder_crop.gif?t=1707898632"><h2 class="bb_tag">EXPLORE THE MYSTERIES OF THE NINTH</h2>The Council of Fates does not have faith in your expedition to the Ninth. Make alliances with rival factions or declare war and take their resources for your own. Manage your relationships through trade and gifts or with a well-placed fireball spell. Grow your coven to new heights and prove the Council wrong.<h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES:</h2>🧭 <strong>Explore</strong> the Ninth Realm to discover new sites for your villages, necessary reagents to fuel your spells, and clues to the mystery of the Ninth's sudden appearance.<br/><br/>🏘️ <strong>Expand</strong> your coven by building new villages, perfecting production, and trading with the local factions.<br/><br/>🔥 <strong>Exterminate</strong> the beasts of the void, whose relentless assaults on your coven jeopardize your mission.<br/><br/>🧙‍♀️ <strong>Choose</strong> the witch to lead your coven, each with unique spells and playstyles.<br/><br/>⌛ <strong>Impress</strong> the Council of Fates and benefit from their powerful boons.<br/><br/>🕊️ <strong>Peaceful Mode</strong> - The option to play without the constant threat of extinction.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/combat-crop.gif?t=1707898632"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2420880/extras/store-gif-04.gif?t=1707898632"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheepy: A Short Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1568400/Sheepy_A_Short_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Help Sheepy, an abandoned plushy brought to life, as he explores a forgotten and broken world. Sheepy: A Short Adventure is the first short game from MrSuicideSheep.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/V1400.gif?t=1707785084"><h2 class="bb_tag">An Original Soundtrack</h2>Weaved into the world is an incredible original soundtrack created by Seeking Blue artists <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F4IuWSIEfIed8aZb49YA4Cj%3Fsi%3DAGrFrA3PTvudKKKR1yMfbw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Yoe Mase</a>, <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6rTFfPwNNFIpBOdBShd47e%3Fsi%3DAlBCvD6kTIilKbz-NgBg1w" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Hahlweg</a> and <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fopen.spotify.com%2Fartist%2F6SnMMbLQ4iS8WIyt3ksmCR%3Fsi%3DqDFw8B3HTIO2z0F9cIbg8Q" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Tal from ECHOS</a>, currently in development.<br/><br/><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fmrsuicidesheep.ffm.to%2Fsheepygamestsml.wnm" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1568400/extras/MList.jpg?t=1707785084"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Mailing List</h2>Join the Mailing List and be the first to learn about the future of Sheepy, limited edition merch and more.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXIT KUN</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2781370/EXIT_KUN/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2781370/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This game is a game of finding differences and observing. Our game challenges players to carefully observe and spot the distinctions that lead them to the elusive "Exit KUN."<br>
<br>
Game Overview:<br>
<br>
You find yourself trapped in an enigmatic underground labyrinth, and your only goal is to reach "Exit KUN." The journey demands keen observation of your surroundings. Every detail matters, and anomalies could be your key to progress.<br>
<br>
How to Play:<br>
<br/>
Observe Carefully: Scrutinize your surroundings to uncover anomalies that may guide your way or pose a threat.<br/>
Turn Back if Needed: If anomalies are detected, swift decision-making is crucial. Turn back immediately to avoid unforeseen consequences.<br/>
Forward Momentum: Should your observation reveal no anomalies, press forward. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
Developer Notes:<br/>
This game is inspired by Exit 8. You are free to create, upload, and monetize videos and any other content featuring Game on platforms such as YouTube, Twitch, and other video-sharing websites. The characters, places, and elements involved in the game are fictitious. Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or events is purely coincidental.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soak &amp; Splash</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2051500/Soak__Splash/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2051500/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to the Soak &amp; Splash! Get ready to sweat, socialize, and have a blast with your friends in this unique game that combines the best of traditional sauna culture with modern party fun.<br>
<br>
First, step into the steamy sauna and feel the heat and humidity envelop your body.<br>
<br>
Once everyone is inside, it's time to start the fun. You can start by whisking each other with broom.<br>
<br>
Feeling competitive? You can also fight with other players with sauna equipment. Or you can simply relax and enjoy the company of your friends, chatting, singing, or telling jokes.<br>
<br/>
Finally, when you've had enough of the sauna, you can cool off in the nearby pool or shower.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, this game is all about having fun, bonding with your friends, and experiencing the unique benefits of sauna culture. So why wait? Download game and get ready to sweat, laugh, and enjoy life to the fullest!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/315210/Suicide_Squad_Kill_the_Justice_League/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							From Rocksteady Studios, the creators of the Batman: Arkham series, Suicide Squad: Kill the Justice League is a genre-defying third-person action shooter where the ultimate band of misfits must do the impossible to save the world: Kill the Justice League.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/SSKTJL_Intro.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Join the newly “recruited” members of Amanda Waller’s infamous Task Force X (aka the Suicide Squad), Harley Quinn, Deadshot, Captain Boomerang and King Shark, as they set out on an impossible mission to Kill the Justice League. Drop into an expansive and dynamic open-world Metropolis ravaged by Brainiac’s invasion and terrorized by the heroes who once protected it. <br/> <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/315210/extras/Traversal_2.gif?t=1707761424"><br/>Each Squad member brings their own traversal mechanics to help them navigate a sprawling and battle-torn Metropolis, combining free-roaming exploration and combat verticality for an unforgettable experience. Players are free to experiment with a variety of different play styles to unleash maximum damage on their enemies. Whether in single player or online with up to three of your friends, players can take on this suicide mission their own way.<br/><br/>Post-launch, players can expect a continuously evolving Metropolis with free new playable villains, environments, weapons, in-game events, and more, all included with purchase of the base game.						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Together</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2788630/Nothing_Together/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2788630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The hardest game you're ever going to play together. Maybe.<br/><br/>Just do Nothing as the timer goes up and climb the leaderboards. If you do Something, you lose.<br/><br/>Play in <strong>Together </strong>mode, where up to 20 players unite to do Nothing, or compete with other players in <strong>Battle Royale</strong> to find out who's the best at doing Nothing!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 3 Reload</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2161700/Persona_3_Reload/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2161700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Step into the shoes of a transfer student thrust into an unexpected fate when entering the hour "hidden" between one day and the next. Awaken an incredible power and chase the mysteries of the Dark Hour, fight for your friends, and leave a mark on their memories forever. <br/><br/>Persona 3 Reload is a captivating reimagining of the genre-defining RPG, reborn for the modern era.<br/><br/>Key Features: <br/>- Experience the pivotal game of the Persona series faithfully remade with cutting-edge graphics, modernized quality-of-life features, and signature stylish UI. <br/><br/>-Fully immerse yourself in an emotional, gripping journey with new scenes, character interactions, and additional voiceover.<br/><br/>- Choose how to meaningfully spend each day through various activities, from exploring the Port Island to forging genuine bonds with beloved characters.<br/><br/>- Build and command your optimal team to take down otherworldly Shadows and climb closer to the truth.<br/><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Deluxe Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook: Filled with 64 pages of character art, concept art, backgrounds and other illustrations from the game!<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack: Listen to newly arranged tracks from the original Persona 3 plus all-new tracks from Persona 3 Reload, presented by the Atlus sound team for a total of 60 new songs.</li></ul><br/>---<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Persona 3 Reload Digital Premium Edition includes:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Base Game<br/></li><li>Digital Artbook<br/></li><li>Digital Soundtrack<br/></li><li>Persona 3 Reload DLC Pack:  P5R Phantom Thieves Costume Set, P5R Shujin Academy Costume Set, P5R Persona Set 1, P5R Persona Set 2 , P5R BGM Set, P4G Yasogami High Costume Set, P4G Persona Set</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLCARD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1201540/HELLCARD/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Hellcard</strong> is a <strong>cooperative roguelike deckbuilder</strong> that can be played in both <strong>Singleplayer </strong>and <strong>Multiplayer </strong>modes. The game takes place in the paper dungeons known from Book of Demons, and its main mechanics revolve around deckbuilding and fast-paced tactical card battles. <br/><br/>If you are excited about <strong>HELLCARD</strong>, be sure to <strong>wishlist </strong>the game on Steam. Otherwise, consider wishlisting anyway - who knows, we might surprise you yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif5_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/>What makes <strong>HELLCARD</strong> unique and different from other deck-building games is that <strong>monster placement actually matters</strong> and can be used to your advantage.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif4_600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> supports <strong>co-op battles</strong> with up to three heroes facing the Archdemon's hordes. In <strong>singleplayer mode</strong>, you can descend into the dungeons solo or recruit computer-controlled companions. In <strong>multiplayer mode</strong>, your friends or strangers can help you battle the hordes of hell. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/Hellcard_gif1-2-3-600.gif?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/r2g_logo_fixed.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>Return 2 Games</strong> is a series of unique mid-core games inspired by the golden days of PC gaming. Each R2G title is a tribute to a single hit game from the '90s: a reimagining of a single universal story for a brand-new audience, using modern means and innovative, often vastly simplified gameplay mechanics.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1201540/extras/pillars.png?t=1706878477"><br/><br/><strong>HELLCARD</strong> was first envisioned as a new game mode inside the Book of Demons universe, but we soon realized that its design is huge and that it should be executed as a stand-alone spin-off game. If you want to learn more about Return 2 Games or support us in the development of the series, visit the <strong>Supporter Pack</strong> store page. On release, <strong>HELLCARD </strong>will be a part of it.<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/" id="dynamiclink_2" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/706770/Return_2_Games_Supporters_Pack/</a><br/><strong>Book of Demons</strong>, the first part in the series is already here, be sure to check it out as it includes a free demo. <br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/" id="dynamiclink_3" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/449960/Book_of_Demons/</a><br/>Also, be sure to check out <strong>Book of Aliens</strong>, the second book in the series and a tribute to MicroProse’ UFO: Enemy Unknown that’s also in the works:<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/" id="dynamiclink_4" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1196230/Book_of_Aliens/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominion</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1131620/Dominion/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Expand a small kingdom to a mighty Dominion!  <br/><br/>Play the Spiel des Jahres winning boardgame beloved by millions around the world. This is the officially licensed implementation.  <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Reigning.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Discover the game that defined a genre, Dominion was first to popularize deck-building and remains a staple of tabletop. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/GrowYourKingdom.png?t=1707010484">Collect as many Victory Points as you can by building a powerful deck. Your deck starts out a small sad set of Estates and Coppers, but you hope that by the end of the game it will be brimming with Gold, Provinces, and the inhabitants and structures of your kingdom.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/BuildEngine.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Choose wisely among the 10 cards available in the tableau to create the strongest combos to dominate your opponent.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CollectAllExpansions.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Make your games more exciting with additional cards and rules from up to 15 expansions including the recent Plunder expansion! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/NearInfiniteVariety.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Over one hundred thirty-two septillion possible Kingdom combinations, 500+ cards, 15 and counting expansions, and ongoing promo packs make Dominion one of the most extensive and replayable boardgames in the hobby. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CompeteComputer.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Sharpen your skills with solitaire style solo play against a robust AI, with four levels of difficulty. Our innovative AI learns through self-play. Earn Achievements and win in Recommended Sets against each AI level. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/PlayWithFriends.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Join up to 6 players online through your device or pass and play among your friends. Play ranked or unranked matchmaking, with realtime and asynchronous modes. Set up a private table for a family game, challenge a stranger in the lobby, or invite a friend!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Daily.png?t=1707010484"><br/>A daily ritual to relax with over a cup of coffee. Try the Daily Dominion, a free puzzle level available to players around the world. Practice your strategy to keep up a winning streak and climb the leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/CrossPlatform.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Play from any supported device, whenever you want, after verifying your email in-game. Join games with opponents on platforms other than your own to enjoy the largest possible multiplayer pool and speedy matchmaking. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/JoinCommunity.png?t=1707010484"><br/>With an active Discord and online community, make new friends or challenge new people to a game. Export and share kingdoms and game summaries to compare strategies.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/FreeToPlay.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Download the game that started it all for free! The base set of Dominion is available at no charge. Try the rotation of expansion cards in the Daily at no cost once per day. Jump into a lobby game with expansions enabled to try before you buy. Only the host needs to own the expansions.    <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Intro.png?t=1707010484"><br/>Learn the ropes in this easy to pick-up, hard to master title. Play one of the most highly regarded strategy tabletop games of all time through our simple tutorial.  The core loop is easy to follow, but offers a wealth of strategy to explore.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>1-6 player</strong> support<br/></li><li><strong>500 </strong> plus <strong>cards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Solo play</strong> against four AI difficulties<br/></li><li><strong>Async </strong>&amp; <strong>real-time</strong> multiplayer<br/></li><li><strong>Ranked</strong> &amp; <strong>unranked</strong> matchmaking<br/></li><li><strong>Lobby</strong> &amp; <strong>Private game</strong> tables<br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform multiplayer</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Cross platform purchases</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Daily challenge</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Challenging AI</strong> that learns through self-play<br/></li><li><strong>Recommended Sets</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Customize</strong>, save &amp; share <strong>Kingdoms</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Achievements</strong>, <strong>Stats </strong>&amp; <strong>Leaderboards</strong><br/></li><li><strong>Pass &amp; Play</strong> mode<br/></li><li>Automated <strong>score-keeping</strong> &amp; hints<br/></li><li><strong>Smart-play</strong> options to streamline gameplay<br/></li><li><strong>Jumbo mode</strong> for readability on phones<br/></li><li><strong>Turbo mode</strong> to zoom through games quickly<br/></li><li><strong>Tutorial</strong> &amp; <strong>Rules</strong><br/></li><li><strong>4 languages</strong>: English, Japanese, German, French<br/></li><li><strong>15 expansions</strong> plus three promo packs </li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Awards for the Boardgame</h2><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1131620/extras/Awards.png?t=1707010484"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granblue Fantasy: Relink</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/881020/Granblue_Fantasy_Relink/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/881020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Story<br/>
Granblue Fantasy takes place in the Sky Realm, a world where myriad islands float in a great blue expanse. Take your role as captain of a skyfaring crew, joined by a scrappy little dragon named Vyrn and a young girl with mysterious powers named Lyria. Together you sail with a colorful cast of crewmates, including kings and misfits alike, for Estalucia, a fabled island beyond the end of the skies.<br/>
<br/>
In the Zegagrande Skydom, islands are guarded by powerful creatures known as primal beasts and winds carry tales of a secretive organization known as the Church of Avia. Unveil a web of intrigue reaching far beyond the borders of Zegagrande and engage in a battle for the fate of the Sky Realm itself.<br/>
<br/>
Gameplay<br/>
Engage in real-time combat with a party of four in this character action RPG—choose from a diverse roster of skyfarers, each with their own unique weapons, skills, and combat styles. Teamwork makes the dream work with party-based mechanics such as Link Attacks and Chain Bursts to help you crush foes in spectacular fashion. Tackle quests solo or with the help of others for up to 4-player co-op and take down treacherous foes to score rare loot to further enhance your gear. Every enemy and party formation has its own strengths and weaknesses—the key to victory lies in working out how these pieces fit together.<br/>
<br/>
Fast-paced combat not your thing? Assist modes can provide accessibility for gamers of all skill levels. Toggle on Full Assist to have all actions performed automatically during battle!<br/>
<br/>
The Sky Realm is rich in lore and history. Browse Lyria's journal at any point during the game to access a trove of writings on the world's peoples, places, and more. In addition to the wealth of side quests available, Fate Episodes allow you to delve into the backstories of each member of your crew!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlazBlue Entropy Effect</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2273430/BlazBlue_Entropy_Effect/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/原创声明-英语.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗EN_.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超华丽动作战斗.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Charismatic character designs with unique aesthetic styles and dramatic animations create a flamboyant, awesome combat experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快的动作连招EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/极致爽快动作连招.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>Smooth controls, infinite possibilities of combos, and realistic combat feedback. This is the roguelite game with the best action experience yet!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/超多角色豪华制作EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/全员图618x346.jpg?t=1707811616"><br/>Ten playable characters with vibrant personalities, unique combat styles, and immersive voice-acting.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式自由定制EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/百种招式，自由定制en.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>There are hundreds of moves for you to build around, plus countless elemental effects and legacy skills passed between characters. The possibilities are infinite. Time to make the best fighter of your own!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/抉择拯救世界EN.png?t=1707811616"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2273430/extras/GIF-抉择拯救世界EN.gif?t=1707811616"><br/>In the future where the world has been plunged into chaos, people enter a cyberspace called ACE, seeking their last chance to resolve the crisis.<br/>If you are the only person in this world who knows the truth, how will you react?<br/>The ending is also the beginning. Your decision will decide humanity's future.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Simulator: Prologue</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772560/Supermarket_Simulator_Prologue/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This Prologue is a limited version of the full game to stop waiting and jump into running your supermarket already. Don't forget to wishlist the full game to continue your most fun supermarket experience.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Design your store, optimizing for efficiency and aesthetics. Determine where products are displayed, manage your aisles, and ensure a smooth shopping experience for your customers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Store_Management.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Order stock using an in-game computer and anticipate the arrival of your next delivery. Unpack goods, organize them in your storage room and display them on shelves, fridges, and freezers.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Supply_Goods.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Read product barcodes, handle cash and credit card transactions, and ensure customers leave satisfied with their shopping and checkout experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Cashier_Raw.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.png?t=1706285874"><br/>Navigate the complexities of a real-time market. Buy products when prices dip and determine the best-selling prices to balance customer satisfaction with profit margins.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772560/extras/Free_Market.gif?t=1706285874"><br/><br/>Wishlist the full game "Supermarket Simulator" where every decision matters. Will you rise to the occasion, transforming a modest establishment into a retail powerhouse, all while balancing customer satisfaction, finances, and mafia expectations?						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper Lily - Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2220360/Paper_Lily__Chapter_1/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<i>Something terrible has happened. You can’t bear to think about it - but you can’t live like this anymore. You stopped attending school, you haven’t left your house in months, you have no reason to get out of bed anymore. There are no choices left.<br/><br/>No choice except... that strange golden letter.<br/><br/>It’s time to get your life back together. <br/><br/>One last try.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/divider.png?t=1706724298"><br/><br/>Paper Lily is a story-driven, psychological horror RPG where each puzzle has multiple solutions and outcomes. <strong>There is always another way.</strong><br/>Follow Lacie's story as you explore a dangerous hidden world, solve puzzles in multiple different ways, and face strange enemies. The game is playable in about 4 hours and contains multiple endings depending on your actions.<br/><br/>Paper Lily - Chapter 1 is the continuation to the prologue, <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1698960" rel="" target="_blank">Project Kat</a>, but it can also  be enjoyed without having played it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2220360/extras/lacie_sai_walk.gif?t=1706724298"><h2 class="bb_tag">Out of Context Features</h2><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Multiple ways of solving puzzles!<br/></li><li>Touch grass, and trees<br/></li><li>Minigames where you press buttons and push boxes around<br/></li><li>Call your mother<br/></li><li>Harmless Snack™<br/></li><li>Various things made of paper<br/></li><li>Bunnies (or whatever those things are)<br/></li><li>Demons<br/></li><li>Fast demons<br/></li><li>Social anxiety simulation<br/></li><li>Table salt<br/></li><li>...Is that Kat? Nah, probably not<br/></li><li>Bathroom etiquette<br/></li><li>Death</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEKKEN 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1778820/TEKKEN_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/header_alt_assets_3.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>GET READY FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER IN THE LEGENDARY FIGHTING GAME FRANCHISE, TEKKEN 8.</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">• 32 FIGHTERS FOR A NEW GENERATION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_32-Fighters-for-a-new-Generation.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Completely redesigned character visuals.</strong> Elaborate, highly-detailed models built from the ground and high-fidelity graphics break the limits of new-generation hardware by <strong>adding a new weight and atmosphere to TEKKEN’s signature battles</strong>. <strong>Vivid environments and destructible stages</strong> combine to create an overwhelming sense of immersion, creating the ultimate play experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">• NEW GAME, NEW RIVALRY</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_New-Game-New-Rivalry.gif?t=1707465369"><br/><strong>Fist Meets Fate in TEKKEN 8.</strong> Holding a record for the longest-running video game storyline, <strong>the TEKKEN series begins a new chapter</strong> as TEKKEN 8 continues the <strong>tragic saga of the Mishima and Kazama bloodlines</strong>, and their world-shaking father-and-son grudge matches starting from 6 months after the closure of the last match. The story of Jin Kazama's growth and determination <strong>marks a new chapter in the timeless saga</strong>.<h2 class="bb_tag">• THRILLING OVER-THE-TOP BATTLES EMBODYING AGGRESSIVENESS &amp; DESTRUCTION</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Thrilling-onver-the-top-battles.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>The <strong>new battle system, Heat</strong>, dials up the <strong>aggressive nature of battles</strong>, while maintaining the <strong>play feel and tactics unique</strong> to the TEKKEN series. The intensity of battles is greatly enhanced by the destructable stages. Unleashing super move-like Rage Arts is sure to enthrall both players and spectators alike. All of these hard-hitting mechanics come together to make TEKKEN 8 the most exciting installment in the series to date!<h2 class="bb_tag">• ENJOY YOUR TEKKEN LIFE!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1778820/extras/GIF_Enjoy-your-Tekken-life.gif?t=1707465369"><br/>In the <strong>new single-player mode Arcade Quest</strong>, craft your own unique avatar and embark on your new TEKKEN life. Battle your way through a variety of rivals across multiple arcades as the story unfolds, all while mastering the basics and practical skills in TEKKEN 8. <strong>Unlock a variety of customization items for characters and avatars</strong> as you progress.<br/><br/><i>*In addition to this edition, Deluxe Edition and Ultimate  Edition are also available. Please be careful not to purchase the same content twice.</i> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072450/Like_a_Dragon_Infinite_Wealth/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/Accolades_616.png?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>EPIC EMOTIONAL DRAMA</strong><br/>Two larger-than-life heroes brought together by the hand of fate, or perhaps something more sinister…<br/><br/>Ichiban Kasuga, an unstoppable underdog who’s no stranger to crawling up from rock bottom, and Kazuma Kiryu, a broken man facing down his last days.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/2_Epic_Emotional_Drama.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>BEST-IN-CLASS RPG ACTION</strong><br/>Experience one-of-a-kind combat with dynamic, fast-paced RPG battles where the battlefield becomes your weapon, and anything goes. Adapt your party’s skills to the situation with outlandish jobs and customizations to strategically subdue enemies with over-the-top moves. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/3_Best_In_Class_RPG_Action.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong>INFINITE ADVENTURE</strong><br/>Live it up in Japan and explore all that Hawaii has to offer in an adventure so big it spans the Pacific. Unforgettable moments await at every step of the journey with a unique mix of quests and activities to enjoy at your leisure.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072450/extras/4_Infinite_Adventure.gif?t=1707132191"><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Deluxe Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"><u>Ultimate Edition Content</u></h2></strong>- Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth game<br/>- Master Vacation Bundle: Explore a bonus dungeon, get special Sujimon, resort guests, outfits, new game+ &amp; more<br/>- Assorted Outfit Bundle: Customize your party's look with outfits &amp; swimwear<br/>- Sujimon &amp; Resort Bundle: Get legendary Sujimon, resort guests and special boosters<br/>- Yakuza CD Collection Set: Increase your in-game playlist with classic karaoke tracks						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2187220/Apollo_Justice_Ace_Attorney_Trilogy/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2187220/extras/13_Apollo_CustomImages_600x338.png?t=1706177279"><br/><br/>Apollo Justice's Legal Journey Begins Anew!<br/><br/>Join rookie attorney Apollo Justice and his mentor, the legendary Phoenix Wright, in this collection of 3 games! This title features the 14 episodes of "Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney", "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Dual Destinies", and "Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney - Spirit of Justice", and the 2 previously DLC-only Special Episodes for a total of 16 episodes!<br/><br/>Also included is a mountain of extra goodies that's sure to satisfy any Ace Attorney fan!<br/><br/>Orchestra Hall - Listen to the in-game background music and select orchestral arrangements!<br/><br/>Art Library - View illustrations, design specs, commissioned pieces, and even the special Spirit of Justice Prologue anime!<br/><br/>Animation Studio - Play around with character animations and recreate your favorite scenes!<br/><br/>This collection supports Japanese, English, French, German, Korean, and Traditional and Simplified Chinese. Mix and match to play in whichever languages you'd like!<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in this beautiful collection as you shout "Objection!" in these newly renovated halls of justice!<br/><br/>Some of the contents of the games in this collection are presented as initially released to preserve the games as originally created.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDER NIGHT IN-BIRTH II Sys:Celes</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2076010/UNDER_NIGHT_INBIRTH_II_SysCeles/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sys:Celes sinks towards ruination.<br/>For the Immortalize, the collapse of all that is, looms on the horizon.<br/>The curtain rises on the final chapter of the Hollow Night. Catastrophe beckons...<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store1b.gif?t=1707122865"><br/><br/>Experience the Dramatic Stylish 2D Fighting Action in the latest entry of the UNDER NIGHT IN-BIRTH series!<br/><br/>The first numbered sequel in the series!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Choose from a roster of 24 total characters, with renewed visuals!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store2.jpg?t=1707122865"><br/>3 new characters join the battle: Moonlight Dancer "Twin Barrel Beauty" Kaguya, Indomitable Rampart "Steel Guardian" Tsurugi, and Endless Entity "Eternal Re-Birth" Kuon.<br/>You won’t be able to take your eyes off the intense battles between these 24 fighters with the highly detailed HD pixel art graphics!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Simple inputs make it easy to jump into the fray!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store3.gif?t=1707122865"><br/>New to fighting games? Not a problem – simple inputs mean even beginners can pull off moves with a single button!<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Now supporting rollback netcode for an improved online experience!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store4.jpg?t=1707122865"><br/>With the addition of Casual Matches, it’s easier than ever before to dive in and enjoy online battles.<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ Introducing new moves and game mechanics!</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2076010/extras/uni2_store5.gif?t=1707122865"><br/>All characters now boast new moves, such as Hyde’s Blaring Outrage and Linne’s Soaring Dragon.<br/>The new game mechanics Creeping Edge and Celestial Vorpal open up additional depth to gameplay.<h2 class="bb_tag">▼ The final chapter! A new tale of the Hollow Night…</h2>Sever the cycle. An end to the endless.<br/>May the tale of these countless Nights be concluded, on this eve, the moment of destiny.<br/>A long-awaited continuation to the tale of the Hollow Night unfolds!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plasma Orb</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2794250/Plasma_Orb/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2794250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							*** Dive in the beautiful and mysterious world with your Plasmorb! ***<br>
<br>
Plasma orb is a marble-like game.<br>
Plasmorb is a ball shaped creature that you are going to control<br>
Roll your ball and go through different levels with mini-puzzles and narrow paths. And try not to break it and fall down!<br>
You will encounter many hindrances, mazes and mysterious constructions<br>
All the game levels look beautiful. You have to travel through an old forest, dangerous swamps and even explore the depths of underground!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iragon</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2229300/Iragon/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2229300/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About the Game</h2><br/>We think the best way for us to explain this game is to tell you how we came up with this idea. Everybody who works at Repulse loves fantasy anime. We are huge fans of shows like Attack on Titan and Full Metal Alchemist.  And we also like to play visual novels, especially the ones with erotic and lesbian content.<br/><br/>When we finished our last game, we asked ourselves:  What if we could combine the elements we love most about anime and visual novels in an interactive VR experience that you could also play without VR. And that is exactly what Iragon is about.<br/><br/>You play the game as Darick, a poor kid from a small village.  Everything for him changes when he meets a bisexual girl who gets ambushed by soldiers of the Empire. To help her, you must learn to use your magic, but on your quest to bring her home safe, you will have to journey into a dangerous frozen world.  Along the way, you will battle enemy soldiers, undead skeletons, and perhaps cross paths with seductive creatures of the frozen land while you unlock new erotic adventures with her.<br/><br/>So this is ultimately a game about living out a high fantasy adventure, with a strong emphasis on putting the player in control.  The game is meant to be experienced in VR, but we dedicated an equal amount of care to deliver a standard version that will work for players who do not have a VR headset.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>Whether you play in VR or not, you can expect us to deliver:<br/><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 3 Main storyline romance routes<br/></li><li> 4 Side romance routes<br/></li><li> 12 Monster girls you can romance<br/></li><li> Interactive experiences with your love interests<br/></li><li> Different outfits<br/></li><li> Voice acting<br/></li><li> Motion captured animations<br/></li><li> A dynamic combat system that features both magic and melee;<br/></li><li> Destructible environments;<br/></li><li> A dialogue choice system that influences the response you get.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">STORY</h2>Be the hero, live the story, and go on an adventure of a lifetime while you immerse yourself fully in the world of Iragon, with a complete animated story and full voice acted cast.  (skip options are also available for those who prefer to just get on with the action.)<h2 class="bb_tag">GAMEPLAY</h2>And yes, of course, this is not just a story you watch it is a game. Battle enemies, cast spells, collect loot, upgrade, interact with NPC's, go on quests. It has everything you would expect from a fantasy RPG game.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lords of Exile</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1329360/Lords_of_Exile/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1329360/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In ancient times of war in the Far East, the lands of Exilia were overrun by creatures of the night and samurais. Amidst this cruel conflict, only a bloodthirsty cursed knight can bring hope and vanquish the darkness.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1329360/extras/LoE_June_Gif_2.gif?t=1707928338"><br/><br/><strong>Key features </strong><br/><br/><u>Levels </u><br/><br/>	Explore 8 levels of classic linear design, each featuring challenging obstacles and enemies to overcome. At the end of each level, you'll face off against a powerful boss that will put your skills to the test. And as Gabriel, you'll receive an extra skill after defeating each boss, allowing you to progress even further and take on greater challenges.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1329360/extras/LoE_June_Gif_1.gif?t=1707928338"><br/><br/><u>Gameplay Variety </u><br/><br/>	Experience a range of mechanics, from throwing weapons to melee combat, down stabs, jumping, and dashing. Unlock the powers of Gabriel's curse to enhance your abilities. Play as both Gabriel and Lyria, each offering a unique and distinct gameplay experience for endless replayability.<br/> <br/>	Plus, once you've beaten the game with Gabriel, unlock two additional game modes: Speedrunner mode and Boss Rush mode. And the best part? You can play both of these modes with either Gabriel or Lyria for even more variety and fun!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1329360/extras/LoE_June_Gif_3.gif?t=1707928338"><br/><br/><u>Retro-aesthetic and sound design </u><br/><br/>Relive the glory days of classic gaming with retro-inspired 16-bit physics and perfectly polished controls. The game's stunning handcrafted 8-bit pixel art and fast anime-style animations, the 8-bit SFX and OST, enriched with sounds from the Megadrive sound chip, complete the immersive retro experience.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1329360/extras/GIF3_Opti.gif?t=1707928338"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Hitter</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1335940/Circle_Hitter/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1335940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Warning</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>This game may be more difficult than it looks, so please use caution before playing for your mental health.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Main gameplay</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Dodge: Slide the mouse to control the protagonist’s movement and dodge increasingly dense barrages.<br/></li><li>Counterattack: Click the mouse at the right moment to bounce back the enemy’s bullets, and use the rebounded bullets to eliminate the enemy.<br/></li><li>Stamina: Attacks consume stamina, which is restored when enemies are eliminated. Stamina also slowly recovers on its own. </li></ul><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1335940/extras/Gameplay.gif?t=1707926480"><h2 class="bb_tag">Pick power-ups</h2>Staying within the power-ups range can trigger powerful effects.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1335940/extras/Power-ups.gif?t=1707926480"><h2 class="bb_tag">Global leaderboard</h2>Survive and get amazing scores, occupy a place on the global leaderboard, and show off to your friends!<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1335940/extras/Leaderboard.gif?t=1707926480"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many characters</h2>By the way, remember to pick up the dropped coins and use them to unlock more unique characters.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1335940/extras/Players.gif?t=1707926480"><h2 class="bb_tag">Trial mode</h2>Are you strong enough? Through trials, characters can gain stronger abilities!<h2 class="bb_tag">More feature introductions</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Easy to get started, just slide the mouse and click the left mouse button to enjoy the game.<br/></li><li>Difficult to master, hone your mouse skills and become a master of mouse control!<br/></li><li>Minimalistic graphics, interesting circular interface design.<br/></li><li>Supports multiple languages (other than Chinese/English, other languages are machine-translated).<br/></li><li>Steam achievements.<br/></li><li>Steam cloud. </li></ul> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Void Shaper</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2637050/A_Void_Shaper/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2637050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Shape the void with the power of your <strong>cursor</strong>! <strong>A Void Shaper</strong> is an <strong>arcade</strong> game about avoiding shapes and killing them, while you collect <strong>upgrades</strong>. <strong>Unlock</strong> new enemy shapes and upgrades as you progress through the game and complete your <strong>collection</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2637050/extras/Heading-CursorControls.png?t=1707926142"><br/>Your only task is to <strong>avoid </strong>the shapes and <strong>survive </strong>as long as possible. And all you have to do is to move your <strong>cursor</strong>.<br/><br/><i>You're controlling "<strong>Null Sphere+</strong>", a special probe sent by humanity to find a proper new planet.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2637050/extras/Heading-EnemiesAndBosses.png?t=1707926142"><br/>There are lots of <strong>enemies</strong> and even a first <strong>boss</strong> you can encounter in the void. Each enemy shape has a specially <strong>adjusted behaviour</strong> and stats to keep the game fresh and exciting. Each enemy shape has <strong>different variations</strong> called "Champion" and "Giant", these have adjusted stats and can possibly even drop <strong>special upgrades</strong>. You will unlock new enemies and therefore new upgrades as you progress!<br/><br/><i>Your task as Null Sphere+ is to collect data, while you kill enemy shapes, the "Planetary Void Allocation Agency" (the organisation that sent Null Sphere+ into the void) researches new upgrades for your Null Sphere+ in the background.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2637050/extras/Heading-Upgrades.png?t=1707926142"><br/>Collect <strong>upgrades</strong> to get stronger. Each upgrade makes it easier to survive in the void. There are a lot of different upgrade types that you can unlock and collect as you progress. For example: <br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Attack Speed Increase (ASPD+)<br/></li><li> Magnetism<br/></li><li> Homing <br/></li><li> Projectile Count Increase</li></ul>I'm sure that you will find upgrades that you like!<br/><br/><i>Each upgrade either improves an existing component or even adds a new module to the Null Sphere+. This probe is the only chance for humanity to find new planets to inhabit, so all resources are invested to analyze the data that Null Sphere+ sends. This analyzed data is used to develop new improvements or modules.</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2637050/extras/Heading-Soundtrack.png?t=1707926142"><br/>It's time to shape the void! <strong>A Void Shaper</strong> features a masterfully <strong>handcrafted soundtrack</strong>, composed by <strong>K1ngKapra</strong>. The soundtrack is a combination of <strong>electronic</strong> and <strong>metal</strong> music. You will bang your head to this!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Library Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2808770/Library_Fantasy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2808770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are a powerful sorcerer working in a vast library of magic known as Fantasia. You need to unravel its secrets and restore order. Fantasia was known for its unparalleled collections of magical books, artifacts and knowledge, but in recent days, something has gone wrong.<br>
<br>
The game is a 2D platformer with quest elements. You need to complete various tasks at the location and move further through the levels.<br>
<br>
The pages of magical books began to riot, dark wizards hungry for knowledge and power began to attack the library, and dark magical rifts began to open in various places in the library.<br>
<br>
You have to explore the library, uncover secrets, and stop dark wizards.<br/>
<br/>
Game Features:<br/>
- Pixel graphics<br/>
- Various tasks<br/>
- Good soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search of the Source</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2808790/Search_of_the_Source/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2808790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Search of the Source is an exciting role-playing game in which you take on the role of a young squire venturing into a dangerous and mysterious magical forest. You have to complete many different tasks, explore mysterious places and fight mystical enemies.<br>
<br>
Each task and battle will present you with new challenges, requiring your dexterity, determination and ability to make the right decisions.<br>
As you travel through the magical forest, you will discover new places, meet different characters and reveal the secrets of this mysterious world. Your goal is to find the source of the evil that threatens the forest and defeat it to save this magical corner of nature.<br>
<br>
Are you ready to venture into this exciting world and become a hero saving the magical forest?						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPERATION TEMPLE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2808780/OPERATION_TEMPLE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2808780/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You have to take on the role of a mercenary going on a dangerous mission, you are sent to an abandoned city to restore magical totems and destroy enemy invaders. On your way you will be threatened by dangerous enemies, monsters and traps, bravely overcome the greetings on your way and achieve your desired goal.<br>
<br>
The game is a classic 2D platformer with action elements. Destroy enemies in the location, restore totems and complete assigned tasks.<br>
<br>
Game Features:<br>
- Pixel graphics<br>
- Various enemies<br/>
- Good soundtrack						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knight's Saga Evil Goblins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810110/Knights_Saga_Evil_Goblins/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Knight's Saga: Evil Goblins is an exciting fantasy game where the world has been invaded by evil goblins and you take on the role of a brave warrior on a dangerous journey to destroy them. Exciting adventures and battles await you in the name of saving the kingdom. The game offers you the opportunity to plunge into a fascinating world where you will explore mysterious locations. Are you ready to walk this incredible path?<br>
<br>
Your fighting skills and strategies will be tested in various battles, and your courage and bravery will be tested in dangerous adventures.<br>
You will embark on an epic journey through mysterious lands, exploring colorful locations, meeting powerful enemies and gaining fame among the inhabitants of the kingdom.<br>
<br>
Are you ready to take on the challenge and go on a dangerous journey to save the kingdom from evil?						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SameShadow: Fernando's Journey</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2641050/SameShadow_Fernandos_Journey/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Prepare to embark on 'SameShadow: Fernando's Journey,' a third-person action RPG Roguelike set within an ever changing besieged Ukrainian city. As Fernando, your mission is to prevent a repeat of history, ensuring that Russian dominance doesn't extend further into European territory.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Master the Art of Combat:</h2></strong><br/><br/><strong>Choose your combat style: </strong>Will you wield a razor-sharp sword with unmatched precision, unleash barrages of bullets, or confront enemies with bare fists? As you Awaken new powers within the skill tree, your choices will define your approach to combat and shape Fernando's journey.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641050/extras/SSFJ_SkillTree.gif?t=1707924528"><br/><br/><strong>Unleash your powers:</strong> Awaken extraordinary abilities, including Rapid Regeneration, allowing you to trade energy for rapid healing; Particle Acceleration, for blowing away and ragdolling enemies; and Time Dominion, slowing down time to dismantle foes without resistance. Harness these powers, but be cautious—extreme exertion can drain your health and energy.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641050/extras/SSFJ_SwordAttacks_Gif.gif?t=1707924528"><br/><br/><strong>Precision and devastation: </strong>Become a Sword Master, significantly improving your sword fighting style and speed. Execute Bullet Rush to unleash barrages of bullets, or use Rage to deal massive area damage based on your remaining energy.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Shape History:</strong></h2><br/>'SameShadow: Fernando's Journey' combines the intensity of ARPG, RPG, Hack and Slash, and Third Person Shooter genres. Explore a world teetering on the brink of transformation, confront shadowy forces, and overcome challenges that will define Fernando's path.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641050/extras/SSFJ_TeleMissile_Gif.gif?t=1707924528"><br/><br/>Fernando's quest for answers leads to revelations that shape not only his journey but the fate of the future. Step into the darkness and become a legend in 'SameShadow: Fernando's Journey,' where the story unfolds amidst chaos and intrigue.<br/><br/>Are you ready to awaken your powers and ensure that history doesn't repeat itself?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2641050/extras/SSFJ_GameOverGif.gif?t=1707924528"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HealQuest</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2713040/HealQuest/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2713040/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Dive into an immersive and revitalizing experience with HealQuest, a revolutionary VR game that redefines the concept of playful physical activity. Transport yourself to a breathtaking tropical island, where idyllic landscapes invite adventure and well-being.<br>
<br>
At the heart of HealQuest lies an innovative goal: to get moving in order to explore and interact with the environment. As you stroll through the island's winding trails, discover entry points that trigger dynamic and entertaining sports exercises. Whether performing jumps, stretches or cardio exercises, each activity is seamlessly integrated into the exploration of this paradise world.<br>
<br>
One of the most captivating aspects of HealQuest lies in its interaction with the island's inhabitants: colorful, cheerful characters who invite you to play and progress. Forge bonds with local animals, overcome creature-specific challenges and improve your skills as you discover the island's secrets.<br>
<br>
Thanks to visually stunning environments, total immersion in virtual reality and a variety of playfully integrated sports activities, HealQuest offers a unique gaming experience. Stimulating body and mind, this game invites players to escape on an enchanting adventure where fun, exploration and fitness meet.<br/>
<br/>
Developed by the studio Voskalia, HealQuest is much more than a simple VR video game; it's an invitation to discover the pleasure of physical exercise and exploration in a heavenly setting, offering a revolutionary and refreshing gaming experience.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pulsar, The VR Experience</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2714260/Pulsar_The_VR_Experience/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2714260/extras/About_This_Game_Custom_Image_616x353__4_.png?t=1707923520"><br/><br/>PULSAR is an award-winning 40-minute Immersive Art Installation with occasional interaction: a tribute to the imaginative spirit of six-year-old Eloise who lost her battle with leukemia. <br/><br/>Three portals into deep space. Three unique, music-driven journeys. <br/><br/>PULSAR invites you to enter an artistic representation of Eloise’s final birthday wish. You are now a Galactic Observer and a Virtual Astronaut. You can transcend the fragility and physical restrictions of human existence and experience another dimension. Witness galactic events, the birth and demise of stars and planetary systems. Soak up the sights and sounds. Enjoy the slow discovery. Hear the captivating melodies of the Universe. Harness the energy in the pit of a Black Hole. Affect the flow of linear time. Venture on an unusual spacewalk. Demolish fierce asteroids to protect a planet from destruction. Co-create solar systems based on the rhythms, textures, and colors of universal frequencies. Extras offer you a 3D volume of scientific facts and animations. <br/><br/>PULSAR promises you delight, awe, wonder, and the freedom to create your own interpretation. <br/><br/>(Note: Headphones are recommended to experience the full audio immersion of Pulsar, The VR Experience)						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MimiCries</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2542110/MimiCries/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							MimiCries is a Victorian-inspired, narrative-driven puzzle room game where players investigate the devastated remnants of the tragic Griswald family, and escape from <br/>the horrors of their accursed residence.<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features</h2></strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive Pixel-art</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542110/extras/Steam_Immersive_PixelArt_600_Faded.gif?t=1707924446"><br/><br/>Drawing creatively from the Victorian period, all pixel-art in MimiCries has been meticulously curated to craft time-accurate environments, with astonishing designs that may literally take your breath away.<h2 class="bb_tag">Interactive Puzzle-solving</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542110/extras/Steam_Interactive_PuzzleSolving_600_Faded.gif?t=1707924446"><br/><br/>Emulating your playable character's point-of-view, MimiCries offers a plethora of object <br/>and character interactions, which evolve as you make progress with its variety of unique <br/>and challenging puzzles.<h2 class="bb_tag">Duality Of Light</h2><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2542110/extras/Duality_of_Light_600_Faded.gif?t=1707924446"><br/><br/>As you traverse the dark rooms and corridors of the Griswald mansion in MimiCries, <br/>the light sources you have on hand will both help and hinder your exploration. In the <br/>engulfing darkness, will light be the key for your freedom?<br/><br/>All mysteries lay in wait for your unravelling. The Griswald mansion beckons...						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiding Star</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2643470/Hiding_Star/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Single player game with puzzle elements and survival in a mysterious building, where you are chased by a mad attraction - Toothy Jack, who serves Hostess. Use Ball Gun to solve puzzles and move forward<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643470/extras/1s.gif?t=1707923195"><br/><br/>Using the Ball Gun is not so easy, you need to calculate the distance to the target and the speed of the projectile. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643470/extras/2s.gif?t=1707923195"><br/><br/>Take cover, move cautiously along the narrow path, trying not to fall into the abyss, visiting strange rooms and memory-lost creatures. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643470/extras/4s.gif?t=1707923195"><br/><br/><br/>Don’t let Toothy Jack see you! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643470/extras/3s.gif?t=1707923195"><br/><br/>The old amusement test room is full of secrets and dangers. <br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2643470/extras/5s.gif?t=1707923195"><br/><br/>"Toothy Jack will bring you back. To the Hostess, to the Hostess... "						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devilish League</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2759910/Devilish_League/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2759910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Swing, hit, and bounce! Blast enemies with your heavy bat in this hilarious cartoon roguelike!</h2><br/><strong>About the game</strong><br/>Devilish League is a cartoon roguelike with heavy bat-swinging action!<br/>You play as the badass Bash and face off against the evil Durahan's team!<br/>Enjoy cool battles, tons of items to collect, and an addictive adventure as you blast away enemies!<br/><br/><strong>Game Features</strong><br/>[1] A charming playing stage with a casual cartoon style<br/>[2] Heavy charging attacks that hit hard with each blow<br/>[3] Play and grow differently each time with various items<br/>[4] Challenging boss and elite monsters to keep you on your toes						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undulations</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2768150/Undulations/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2768150/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							This is a survival escape action game from a huge wave that will make you feel fear and despair within the first minute.<br>
<br>
The setting is an exoplanet where waves of over 3,000 feet (about 900 meters) are constantly hitting the surface of the planet, due to the gravity of a giant red dwarf star and its orbital period of about 60 minutes.<br>
The objective of the player is to escape from the waves and survive.<br>
<br>
This game is an escape game, but there are no complicated puzzle elements; all you need is the courage and strength to overcome fear.<br>
<br/>
Overcoming this fear, thinking and acting in order to survive, continuing to challenge without giving up, and the scenery you see after surviving will surely leave a strong impression on the minds of those who play the game.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crush Link TD</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2636990/Crush_Link_TD/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2636990/extras/Crossroads_gif.gif?t=1707922755"><br/><br/>Don't waste your chance!<br/><br/>Your task is to protect your base preventing spam from getting into your inbox. Build towers in marked places to stop spam.<br/><br/>Crush Link TD is an unusual Tower Defense strategy game where you will meet unexpected mobs, defeat various bosses, upgrade virtual towers, earn in-game achievements and arrange a date with your crush.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Nutritious Boyfriend</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2555910/A_Nutritious_Boyfriend/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2555910/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Amazing! <br>
<br>
You have just started a new position as the first female human professional trainer at the prestigious Squirrel Fitness Club, a club for dedicated squirrels. Motivate and coach squirrel members until you stumble upon love with fun obstacles along the way. Finding your nutritious life partner won't be a crawl in the park but where there is hope, there is love! Enjoy this adventurous and adorable squirrel dating sim respectfully and heavily inspired by the avian dating sim Hatoful Boyfriend.<br>
<br>
This rodent visual novel/dating sim includes 8 dateable squirrels all with unique traits and personalities, training your favorite squirrel may help him win his big race at the end of the game, and making the right choices may leave you with a big diamond acorn on your finger, but over-training any of the squirrels or making the wrong choices can lead to some pretty nutty consequences.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godsvivors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2441080/Godsvivors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441080/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441080/extras/logo.png?t=1707920129"><br/>Prepare for an <strong>epic</strong> experience that will leave you <strong>breathless</strong>! In <i>Godsvivors</i>, dive headfirst into a battle of <strong>divine proportions</strong> between the gods of Olympus and the relentless <strong>Hades</strong>. He's threatening the balance of the universe, and it's up to you, fearless player, to take action!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441080/extras/Animação_frenetico.gif?t=1707920129"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>SLAY THE DEMONS</strong></h2>Prepare for <strong>epic</strong> showdowns with fearsome underworld enemies like the sinister ferryman <strong>Charon</strong> and the god of death himself, <strong>Thanatos</strong>. Improve your skills, unlock divine powers, and face the formidable <strong>Hades</strong>!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441080/extras/Animação_caronte.gif?t=1707920129"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>DIFFERENT GODS TO PLAY!</strong></h2>Choose from seven powerful gods - <strong>Ares, Apollo, Athena, Hephaestus, Hermes, Poseidon, and Zeus</strong> - each with unique abilities and distinct playstyles. Master their tactics, unleash devastating combos, and unleash the true divine power that runs through your veins!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441080/extras/Animação_personagens.gif?t=1707920129"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>POWERFUL WEAPONS</strong></h2>The action never stops! In a top-down <strong>roguelite</strong> frenzy of shooting, face endless hordes of demons as you dive into the depths of hell. Arm yourself to the teeth with an impressive variety of weapons, such as pistols, shotguns, rifles, and more. Every strategic choice matters as you face death head-on, fighting to survive for <strong>15 minutes</strong> of pure adrenaline!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2441080/extras/Animação_armas.gif?t=1707920129"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features and Resources</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>7 <strong>Playable</strong> Gods<br/></li><li><strong>Unique</strong> Abilities and Playstyles<br/></li><li>Devastating <strong>Combos</strong> and Divine <strong>Power</strong><br/></li><li>Top-Down Roguelite <strong>Frenzy</strong> of Shooting<br/></li><li>Endless Hordes of <strong>Demons</strong><br/></li><li>Impressive Variety of <strong>Weapons</strong><br/></li><li>Meaningful Strategic <strong>Choices</strong><br/></li><li>Epic <strong>Confrontations</strong> with Underworld Enemies<br/></li><li>Skills Enhancement and Unlocking <strong>Divine</strong> Powers<br/></li><li>Epic Battles between Gods and <strong>Hades</strong><br/></li><li>Elimination of Infernal Creatures<br/></li><li><strong>15 Minutes</strong> of Adrenaline<br/></li><li>Restoration of Order in the Underworld<h2 class="bb_tag">Get <i><strong>GODSVIVORS</strong></i> now and embark on an <strong>unforgettable</strong> journey of action and mythology!</h2></li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cipher Monk</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2772900/Cipher_Monk/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2772900/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Cipher Monk!<br/><br/>Tease your brain in this number logic game where you have to use an old numeric system do decipher the answers!<br/>Drag, rotate and drop the pieces to get the correct number!<br/><br/><strong>Key features</strong><br/><br/>Handcrafted Levels<br/>The game comes with handcrafted levels that will tease your brain.<br/><br/>Simple controls<br/>The game is played simply by dragging, rotating and droping the pieces.<br/><br/>Relaxing music<br/>Originally composed music to help you focus and relax while solving the puzzles.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will The Man Get Frog</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2658990/Will_The_Man_Get_Frog/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Will The Man Get Frog is a semi-random writing game in which you compose haikus (japanese short poems) in a cute and soothing atmosphere. Carefully crafted constraints will help you be creative regardless of your writing skills. The minimal design gives you space to focus, explore and express yourself. No achievements, no scoring, no leaderboard. It's about you and the words spending quality time together.<br/><br/>A game session can take from 5 minutes to... well, hours. It all depends on how carried away you get. Sometimes you just want a little distraction, and sometimes it gets more introspective. Both are great ways to enjoy the game!<br/><br/><table><tr><th>Pick words!</th><th>Compose!</th><th>Enjoy and Share!</th></tr><tr><td><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658990/extras/1.gif?t=1707919635"/></td><td><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658990/extras/2.gif?t=1707919635"/></td><td><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2658990/extras/3.gif?t=1707919635"/></td></tr></table><h2 class="bb_tag">FEATURES</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Thousands of words</strong> to choose from!<br/></li><li> <strong>Four beautiful pixel art backgrounds</strong> available, one per season!<br/></li><li> <strong>An Inspiring chip-tune soundtrack</strong> made by the talented c.diffin!<br/></li><li> <strong>Gif recording system:</strong> share your art with the world!<br/></li><li> <strong>Streamer-friendly!</strong> Ask your viewers for advice, or have a writing workshop all together!<br/></li><li> <strong>Asynchronous multiplayer-ish!</strong> "Shared Game" mode allows players to compose with the same word set using a clever password system. Get together, play and compare your works, or play by yourself, send your friends a poem and wait for theirs!<br/></li><li>    ... That's it, really. It's a small game.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Ok, my poem is ready. What do I win?</h2>Well, you win… a .gif of your creation, to use however you see fit!<br/><br/>Maybe you'll be so proud that you'll post it on every social media.<br/>Maybe it'll remind you of a loved one. Why not send it like a digital postcard?<br/>Maybe it'll be personal, so you'll simply keep it close. As a souvenir.<br/>Maybe it won't make much sense. That's okay, things don't always have to make sense.<br/>Maybe you just won't like it. That's okay too, writing is hard. You can try again later.<br/><br/>Point is, I can't tell what you'll get out of it.<br/>But it's probably worth exploring!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FROGUE</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1936990/FROGUE/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1936990/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark in a procedurally generated journey in FROGUE, a Roguelike Bullet Hell Platformer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1936990/extras/steam_gif_2.gif?t=1707919231"><br/><br/>Dash to avoid bullet and kill your enemies!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1936990/extras/steam_gif_.gif?t=1707919231"><br/>​​​<br/>Throw knifes to kill them at a distance.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1936990/extras/steam_gif_1.gif?t=1707919231"><br/><br/>Out of options? No problem, freeze time and make your own solution!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1936990/extras/steam_gif_3.gif?t=1707919231"><br/>​​						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane Mechanic Simulator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/803980/Plane_Mechanic_Simulator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/803980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FxtPbZ6tN9b" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/803980/extras/PMS_discord_Steam.jpg?t=1707919036"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/803980/extras/PMS_Features.gif?t=1707919036"><br/><br/>Plane Mechanic Simulator puts you in a role of an RAF ground crew technician at the start of the Battle of Britain. You will face various tasks ranging from simple refueling to engine repairs and gun harmonization. In order to bring you the best possible experience we have meticulously recreated 3 legendary British aircraft of that era:<br/><br/><strong><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Supermarine Spitfire Mk.1<br/></li><li>De Havilland Tiger Moth<br/></li><li>De Havilland Mosquito<br/></li><li>Hawker Hurricane<br/></li><li>Bristol Blenheim<br/></li><li>And more to come!</li></ul></strong><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/803980/extras/pms_timeline_bristol.png?t=1707919036"><br/><br/>Plane Mechanic Simulator offers <strong>81 </strong>missions, almost <strong>800 </strong>parts to tinker with and an unprecedented attention to detail.<br/><br/>The game also features a unique campaign where you are assigned to a specific squadron with your own machine and pilot. Make a mistake and he might not return from a mission. Perform well and he will become an ace.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/803980/extras/MOSHED-2019-1-28-15-32-26.gif?t=1707919036"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/news/group/35983346/view/3318612066841486740" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/803980/extras/banner3.jpg?t=1707919036"/></a> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worldcrusher - a survival clicker game</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2633110/Worldcrusher__a_survival_clicker_game/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Worldcrusher" is a simple clicker game that involves destruction of worlds, farming and a bit of space travel. Your world has been lost. Luckily, you've been given a chance to restore it. Travel through space, destroy other worlds piece by piece and collect the items in order to recover your own home.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2633110/extras/steam_gif.gif?t=1707916285"><br/><br/>Features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Travel between planets, destroy plenty of objects on every one of them<br/></li><li> Collect resources to restore your home planet<br/></li><li> Grow plants in your homeworld</li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlexanderBall: A Countryball Tale</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1944660/AlexanderBall_A_Countryball_Tale/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1944660/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">JOIN OUR DISCORD:</h2><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FjCagQqpMxd" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1944660/extras/pixelatedResizedDiscordBanner.png?t=1707916153"/></a><br/><br/>Ascend to the Macedonian throne as Alexander the Great and relive his conquests. Fighting alongside redoubtable and quirky commanders, recruit numerous types of balls for your army, construct countless cities called Alexandria, and build an empire that stretches to the ends of the known world.<h2 class="bb_tag">Main Features:</h2><br/><strong>Complex Turn-Based Battles</strong><br/>Employ intricate tactics! Outflank your opponents for bonus damage! Instruct your infantry to fortify against attacks! Charge your cavalry into your foes! Keep your ranged units out of trouble and feather your enemies with arrows! Utilize your limited action points in any manner of your choosing each turn to command your army. A infinite range of possibilities await on the battlefield!<br/><br/><strong>The Living, Breathing World of 4th Century BC</strong><br/>Navigate the complicated world of 4th century BC. The world is inhabited by various ‘Balls’, each with their own martial traditions, and each needing to be cajoled to join the Macedonian army. AlexanderBall must choose whether to win over these Balls through gold or glory.<br/><br/><strong>Highly Customizable Army</strong><br/>Our expert ancient Greek mathematicians have discovered that players will be able to choose from billions of possible army combinations for their playthroughs of the campaigns. Add the wide variety of Alexander’s companions to boot and these numbers keep getting bigger. This wide range of possibilities will apply to PvP offline multiplayer battles as well, where your all-Bactrian army can smash your friend’s Hellenic League contingent!<br/><br/><strong>Empire Management</strong><br/>Just as the historical Alexander the Great struggled to unite his disparate and unwieldy empire, AlexanderBall will face countless challenges to keep his empire from falling apart. Placing governors from amongst his companions in important seats of power, while maintaining high opinions with subjects will become a tricky balancing act that will test the players’ management skills. <br/><br/><strong>Story-driven Experience</strong><br/>Relive and refight some of Alexander’s most iconic battles. As the journey progresses, Alexander’s legendary companions will grow and develop alongside their young king as the story takes them from their Greek homelands to the ends of the known world. Dozens of cutscenes crafted by a devoted art team will bring to life the most iconic moment’s from Alexander’s life and more!<br/><br/><strong>Local PvP Multiplayer Battles</strong><br/>Challenge your friends to a duel that will test both players’ army management skills and their knowledge of turn-based tactics. Build a well balanced army with archers, infantry and cavalry, or try out ridiculous combinations such as all-Archer builds just to troll your opponents. Try out various combinations of units and generals and uncover a playstyle that could shake up armchair generalship for years to come!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPG Plus - Virtual Tabletop</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2072070/RPG_Plus__Virtual_Tabletop/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2072070/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							RPG Plus is the <strong>all-in-one solution </strong>for Tabletop RPG players.  Thanks to its campaign manager tool, chat, character sheets, 2D and 3D map builder system, you can:<br/><br/>- Create your campaign as a Game Master or join your friends as a player<br/>- Design your story by adding rooms (chats, maps, sheets) and selecting your players<br/>- Make your map for each adventure using the <strong>3D map</strong> maker system, and add setting items and miniatures for the characters<br/>- Use advanced 3D dynamic lighting on the map<br/>- Keep track of the initiative and who can move with an intuitive turn manager<br/>- Upload and share an image to create 2D Maps<br/>- Upload 2D images or 3D models (.stl files) to create custom 3D tokens<br/>- Interact with the other players via chat: posting messages, rolling dice, sending stickers, and sharing links  <br/>- Record your character's features in a digital sheet. You can select an advanced template for pathfinder 2nd edition and D&amp;D 5th edition, or a simple and flexible table system<br/>- Enjoy the flexibility of a fully cross-platform with a similar experience in both mobile and desktop versions<br/>- Access to a simple schematic How To guide for the different panels.<br/><br/>Thanks to its customizable design, RPG Plus can be used for any of your favorite RPGs. Fans of Pathfinder and D&amp;D can enjoy a library of specific character sheet templates and characteristic miniatures, and many more features and graphic elements are uploaded periodically.<br/><br/>The 3D map includes almost <strong>700 high-quality tokens</strong>. In addition, you can create your token library using 2D images or upload 3D models as STL files.<br/><br/>The 3D map also includes:<br/>- an advanced and realistic dynamic lighting system<br/>- 68 special light effects<br/>- 18 types of walls<br/>- a flexible multi-level system<br/>- 118 grid textures<br/>- a simple 3D distance measuring system<br/>And much more!<br/><br/>Escape Flatland! Add a new dimension to your virtual tabletop encounters with RPG Plus!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Times</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2223820/Supermarket_Times/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223820/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Supermarket Times offers the player the chance to take on the exciting role of a <strong>normal person</strong> going shopping. <br/><br/><strong>Key Features</strong><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Shopping</li></ul>Browse a selection of <strong>surreal</strong> and <strong>thrilling products</strong>, including the renowned <strong>fat fat fatty’s fat powder™</strong> - get fat for a laugh, <strong>Marl-bros </strong>cigarettes – a slippery slope indeed, and the captivating <strong>thick and milky mother’s magazine</strong>. <br/> <img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223820/extras/Text_Products_Image_longer_32.png?t=1707913745"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Chatting</li></ul>Meet a cast of <strong>peculiar people</strong> for the first time (and for some<strong> hopefully the last time</strong>). Sid wants you to know he is<strong> not a pervert</strong>, Carol wants to make sure there is <strong>absolutely no</strong> processed meat in her son’s soup, James’ Dad bought him a skateboard with no wheels 15 years ago and<strong> he’s still sad about it</strong>.<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223820/extras/Text_Character_Image3_chenal_and_norf_face_32.png?t=1707913745"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Legendary Tasks</li></ul>Complete <strong>Legendary Supermarket Tasks</strong> such as <strong>buy alcohol for the teenagers</strong>, <strong>hit the seagull with the rock</strong> and <strong>stamp on the rat</strong> .<br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223820/extras/Small_Seagull_and_whiskey_31.png?t=1707913745"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Exploring</li></ul>Discover <strong>strange</strong> and <strong>intriguing secrets!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2223820/extras/Secrets_image_for_sdescription_45.png?t=1707913745"><br/><br/>Explore, shop and chat and eventually you may discover <strong>the super-secret of the supermarket!</strong> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traveler Eternal Night</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2810120/Traveler_Eternal_Night/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2810120/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							In the game "Traveler: Eternal Night" you will embody a brave fighter who goes on a dangerous journey to destroy the evil that threatens the world. You have to explore different locations, fight monsters and complete quests to become stronger. Your hero will have to endure many trials, but his courage and determination will help him overcome any obstacles. An exciting adventure awaits you, full of dangers and battles that will show what a true hero is capable of.<br>
<br>
Various enemies await you along the way, each of which has its own unique abilities and weaknesses. You will have to use a variety of tactics and strategies to defeat your enemies and overcome all the challenges.<br>
<br>
The game offers an interesting plot, colorful pixel graphics and exciting battles that will immerse you in a world of fantasy and adventure.						</br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unknown Signal</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2808760/Unknown_Signal/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2808760/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Unknown Signal is a 3D adventure game. You have received a mysterious signal and you have to find out what or who sent it. Arm yourself with the best weapons and explore the mysterious planet! Fight with unknown mechanical creatures, go through dangerous situations that await you on this mysterious planet! Find out what is hidden behind the mysterious signal and become a real hero!<br>
<br>
Features<br>
- Nice soundtrack<br>
- Colorful graphics.<br>
- Dangerous opponents						</br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrowstorm Ascendant</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2785750/Arrowstorm_Ascendant/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785750/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">About This Game</h2><br/>Arrowstorm Ascendant is a rogue-like shoot 'em up based on "Seraph's Last Stand" and "Vampire Survivors". Defeat hordes of dragons and wyverns with your outstanding archery skills. With each new wave you fight more enemies with more power, while also selecting one new upgrade. Create the most interesting, powerful or game breaking build and try to reach the top of the leaderboards.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785750/extras/gameplaynew-ezgif.com-resize.gif?t=1707912076"><br/><br/>Everytime you restart you lose your previous powerups, but you can acquire gold coins while playing to buy new upgrades:<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785750/extras/upgrades-ezgif.com-resize.gif?t=1707912076"><br/><br/>You can choose 4 green cards and 4 blue cards after each wave. Find the best build possible and reach the highest level you can!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2785750/extras/cards-ezgif.com-speed.gif?t=1707912076"><h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 50 different cards with green, red or blue upgrades. Create your build using a combination of 4 blue and 4 green cards (red card are infinite).<br/><br/></li><li> 11 different skins to choose from, with each skin having its own advantage.<br/><br/></li><li> A leaderboard system divided by score, enemies defeated and coins obtained.<br/><br/></li><li> A boss fight once you reach a certain number of waves.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tale of (Your Name)</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2746270/The_Tale_of_Your_Name/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2746270/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Embark on an exploration through a procedurally generated dungeon, brimming with ferocious monsters, perilous traps, and challenging puzzles. Dive into a distinctive 2D roguelike shooter experience, where each game unfolds as a unique journey.<br>
<br>
In "The Tale of (Your Name)," take control of a character's role in a tabletop RPG setting, shaping their attributes and narrative. Collaborate with a group of friends to craft an epic medieval fantasy tale, featuring a protagonist armed with weapons ahead of their time.<br>
<br>
Select your hero from three remarkable adventurers, each endowed with unique abilities, and set out on a journey filled with perils and discoveries. Venturing through a dungeon fraught with monsters, traps, and puzzles, your objective in each room is to locate a key to progress to the next challenge. As you advance, encounter narrative events that unfold your story—make critical choices in these events to proceed, decisions that might lead to wealth or pit you against a formidable monster.<br>
<br>
Progressing through the dungeon, utilize your accumulated wealth to purchase and enhance your weaponry (yes, firearms in this setting—thanks to the campaign master's whimsy), as well as other resources.<br/>
<br/>
Prepare for an exhilarating journey where, with each move, a new chapter emerges, and the fate of the protagonist rests in your hands. In "The Tale of (Your Name)," your unwritten story awaits. Confront challenges, make strategic choices, and become the unforgettable hero or villain of this captivating tale.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFENDUN : Hero Defense</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2323810/DEFENDUN__Hero_Defense/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2323810/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2323810/extras/defendun_620x180_.gif?t=1707908907"><br/><br/><strong>Defenden is a strategy merge defense game!</strong><br/><br/>There were two very powerful beings in the world, Bael and Deus, who were very close brothers, but for some reason their relationship deteriorated and they began to fight. Their fight had unacceptable negative consequences, and the dark energy that spread during the fight awakened long forgotten dungeon guardians and monsters, demons in volcanoes, and yetis in snowy regions. The angels and demons who came as reinforcements to stop the monsters from invading the villages and kingdoms of the uninhabited, gave the heroes the ability to merge with the monsters and use this ability to help them stop the onslaught of monsters. Help the heroes, Guardians!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2323810/extras/defendun_-1.gif?t=1707908907"><br/><br/><br/><strong>Combine units according to a recipe. </strong><br/>Mix and match your favorite units to a set recipe. Build your own team by combining over 100 different units, each with unique traits and skills. Sometimes units are stronger uncombined, but higher tiers are usually better.<br/><br/><strong>15 classes to differentiate units. </strong><br/>Build efficient teams with units that are categorized into 15 different classes. If you have a lot of units of the same class, you can use class enhancement cards effectively. (Individual characters do not have classes.)<br/><br/><strong>Defeat over 200 themed monsters. </strong><br/>To clear the stages, you need to know the characteristics of each monster. Whether it's physical or magical damage reduction, multiple births, or the ability to summon monsters, know the characteristics of each monster to clear the wave.<br/><br/><strong>Understand and utilize your unit's skills. </strong><br/>Understanding the skills of your units will help you organize your team. Try to balance physical and magical attack units, think about the ratio of damage over time, instant damage, and area of effect attacks, and combine units that stun, bind, and slow monsters.<br/><br/><strong>Earn different passives each game to create different combinations.</strong><br/>Fill up the monster kill gauge or defeat boss monsters to earn the chests in the bottom right corner and spend them to upgrade individual units and earn class upgrade gold.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2323810/extras/defendun_-2__about_this_game_.gif?t=1707908907"><br/><br/><strong>Clear the stage by understanding the boss's abilities. </strong><br/>Defeat bosses by recognizing their abilities to freeze or stun units, reposition units, or restore health.<br/><br/><strong>Understand the structures that embody the concept of the stage. </strong><br/>Understand the features of maps that match the stage's concept, such as lava on the ground to give debuffs and water at the bottom to match the sea concept, and place your units correctly.<br/><br/><strong>Use the diamonds you're rewarded for playing to become stronger. </strong><br/>Diamonds are rewarded for play and can be used to take units to the next game or to permanently strengthen a player's Passive. They're awarded after you play, so play a lot to customize your look by purchasing custom skins from the Shopkeeper and in-game event skins.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monument village</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2553250/Monument_village/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2553250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Monument village is a peaceful turn-based medieval city-builder.<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2>Start on a pristine island, and grow your village, building by building. You can build exactly one building per turn. At the end of each turn, all your buildings produce some resources.<br/><strong>The focus of the game is on building placement</strong>. Each building has bonuses and penalties depending on its neighbors, so take your time to choose where to place them and plan ahead.<br/><br/>As your village produces resources, you will gain knowledge and discover new innovations. Each one gives you a choice of bonuses and/or new buildings to unlock. You cannot get everything, so each playthrough will be different.<br/><br/>Every now and then, you will receive a request for some resources to be delivered. You have to do it, but you will have some time to adapt and prepare.<br/><br/>Finally, when your village and your economy has grown enough, you will be able to build your dream monument. Four monuments are available to choose from, each with its unique requirements and resources.<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> <strong>Simple yet deep building placement system</strong>: find the right place for each building to optimize its production and that of its neighbors, present and future<br/></li><li> <strong>Innovation system with many choices</strong>: choose unlocked buildings and bonuses from a large pool, making each playthrough unique<br/></li><li> <strong>Many game options</strong>: choose from different map types and monuments</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2>You are a talented architect, eager to prove your skills and build the grand monument which sketch has been sitting on your desk for far too long. But you need a place to build it, and land isn't cheap.<br/><br/><br/>After many days of searching, you finally make a deal with a wealthy merchant named Tessa. She owns an island on which there is enough space for your project. You accept her conditions without much thought.<br/><br/>Maybe you should have read the fine prints:<br/>First surprise, the island is remote and pristine. You will have to find a way to attract workers and to gather resources from the island. Guess it's time to learn how to manage a village!<br/>Moreover, until the monument is finished, Tessa can request any resource from you, and you will have to comply. Fail to do so and she will kick you out of the island. The longer you take to complete your project, the more you will have to deliver.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Yellow Moon's School: The Ghosts Day</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2813970/The_Yellow_Moons_School_The_Ghosts_Day/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2813970/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Yellow Moon's School: The Ghosts Day is a top-down shooter game in which you <br>
must shoot ghosts and destroy them to save the school.<br>
<br>
You control a student with a gun and have to shoot and eliminate hordes of Ghosts <br>
while avoiding contact with them. Some ghosts have guns and will shoot you.<br>
<br>
When you destroy hordes, a new stronger horde will appear, so you may have to<br>
upgrade to win.<br/>
<br/>
When you kill a ghost, you earn money. Use the money to upgrade and get stronger.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Patagonians</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1665170/The_Patagonians/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1665170/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The events of this terrible night began ten years ago.<br/>However, today they will overtake you and make you remember the promise made once.<br/>Rushing to find your missing daughter, you will become participants in terrible events.<br/>But this time it won't be possible to retreat.<br/><br/>The Patagonians is a 2D horror adventure inspired by horror movies from the 80s and 90s.<br/>You have to explore creepy and unpleasant locations filled with disgusting monsters.<br/>At the beginning of the journey, you will only have a torch in service.<br/>So sometimes the best solution to save your own life is to run away.<br/>To top it off, huge guardian bosses will stand in your way.<br/>Their main task is not to let you into the lair of the Patagonians.<br/>To win you will have to show ingenuity and patience.<br/>Get ready! It will be very difficult.<br/>What awaits you at the end of this story?<br/>I'll leave it up to you to find out for yourself.<br/><br/>Waiting for you:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Original 2D graphics.<br/></li><li> Atmospheric environment.<br/></li><li> 3 zones and more than 20 locations.<br/></li><li> 11 types of deadly enemies. <br/></li><li> Simple controls.</li></ul><br/>Explore locations, look for clues, solve puzzles, fight dangerous enemies or flee, destroy obstacles.<br/>Do whatever is necessary to reach your goal.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Multitool</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2723690/Robot_Multitool/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2723690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>Robot Multitool</strong> is a puzzle adventure about a multifunctional robot.<br/><br/>In your arsenal, you have the opportunity to cling and swing on a cable, release an electric charge of a certain power, shoot, remotely control a flying hand capable of pressing levers and buttons.<br/>All the mechanics open up gradually as you progress through the game.<br/>Thanks to all the robot's capabilities, you can interact with the environment to solve puzzles and skill tasks.<br/><br/><strong>Story</strong><br/><br/>At the beginning of the game, the drone connects the missing part to the robot and revives it. Due to the fact that the robot is broken, it is leaking energy. You must pick up a part for the flying arm and use it to get to the part that stops the leak as soon as possible.<br/>During the game, you will find electronic notes from an unknown robot that will give you information about the place where you are and give you hints. He wants to help you get to the place where he is being kept locked up so that you can free him. You will have to complete all the puzzles, skill tasks and battles that you will encounter on your way.<br/>It will not be easy to go all the way, as many robots will try to destroy you. Some of them you can just dodge, and some will have to fight. Also, puzzles require good ingenuity to solve them.<br/><br/><strong>Mechanics</strong><br/><br/>Controlled flying arm:<br/><br/>You can aim and shoot your right hand at the right place. Then you can switch between hand control and robot control. The hand has an energy scale. The arm is able to fly until the energy runs out. As soon as the hand falls and touches the surface, its energy is fully restored.<br/>With the help of a controlled hand, you can reach levers and buttons that cannot be reached just like that. For example, the lever that opens the door you need is located behind a wall in which there is a small hole that only a hand can fit through.<br/>The ability to be in one place in the form of a robot and in another place in the form of a hand is extremely useful in passing. As soon as you need two hands to open a large door or activate a large lever, you can return the hand to the robot.<br/><br/>Cable:<br/><br/>Your other hand is capable of releasing a cable that can cling to certain flying objects. Hanging on the rope, you can swing, go up and down, shortening or lengthening the rope.<br/>You don't need a flying arm to hook, so you can control the flying arm by hanging on a rope. For example, you can hook a rope to a special object, and with your controlled hand press the lever that controls the movement of this object.<br/><br/>Weapon:<br/><br/>In the game you have to fight with some robots. To do this, you have a weapon that has a delay after each shot.<br/>By pressing a certain key, you can switch the arm/weapon aiming mode. In the first mode, you aim to release the flying arm. In the second, to fire a weapon.<br/><br/>Electro-shot:<br/><br/>When you pick up a certain part, the right hand will have a new mode. Now, when you aim with your right hand, you can change the mode from releasing a flying hand to firing an electric charge. By pressing the shot key in this mode, the energy scale is filled. Releasing the key, you fire an electric charge with an energy level equal to the filling of the scale.<br/>There are objects in the game that move depending on the level of energy that is allowed into them. In these cases, you will need to release an electric charge with a specific power. An electric charge can only be fired if the robot has a right hand. It can be used while on the cable.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
