<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Overwatch® 2 - Ultimate Battle Pass Bundle: Season 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2618580/Overwatch_2__Ultimate_Battle_Pass_Bundle_Season_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2618580/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Team up and go on the hunt!<br>
<br>
Includes:<br>
- Premium Battle Pass + 20 Tiers<br/>
- Magma Mauga and Wild Tracker Widowmaker Legendary Skins<br/>
- Magma Moira Epic Skin<br/>
- 2,000 Overwatch Coins<br/>
<br/>
With your Overwatch Coins, you can purchase in-game cosmetic items to customize your heroes. Owners of the Premium Battle Pass can also use Overwatch Coins to unlock Tiers and instantly access Legendary and Mythic content. Tier skips do not apply to Prestige Tiers.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwatch® 2 - Starter Pack: Season 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2618570/Overwatch_2__Starter_Pack_Season_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2618570/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							This bundle includes:<br>
<br>
- 1000 Overwatch Coins<br>
- Magma Moira<br/>
<br/>
With Overwatch Coins, you can unlock the Premium Battle Pass, buy in-game cosmetic items or skip tiers in the Premium Battle Pass. Tier skips do not apply to Prestige tiers.						</br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Anacrusis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1120480/The_Anacrusis/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Battle for survival against endless alien hordes with your friends! From the lead for Left 4 Dead and L4D2, The Anacrusis is a 1-8 player, sci-fi first-person shooter. Experience intense 4 player co-op action or play as the aliens and stop your friends in Versus mode. Now with Steam Workshop support!<h2 class="bb_tag">Fight Aliens Using Fantastical Weapons </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Weapons.png?t=1701799902"><br/>Battle the alien menace using an astounding arsenal of classic sci-fi weapons. Buy yourself some time with a stasis grenade, toss a shield grenade to provide instant cover while you pop off a heal, and bring your friends back to life using the Respawner. Or throw caution to the wind and burn friend and foe alike with the laser rifle.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play As The Aliens in PVP Versus Mode!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Design_Steam_Versus_Header.png?t=1701799902"><br/>PVP comes to The Anacrusis! The goals are simple, Survivors need to reach the end of the level and the Aliens must keep them from their goal. Take control of the Brute, Flasher, Grabber, Gooper, and Spawner (with more special Aliens to come) and keep your friends from escaping the level. Tuned for intense co-op PVP play with teams of 2, 3, or 4 players, or take on the bots in a private match to practice playing the aliens.<h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Alien Infestation!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Horde.png?t=1701799902"><br/>In the distant future, mighty corporations have carried humanity to the fringes of the galaxy. After expanding unfettered across tens of thousands of systems--all devoid of intelligent life--humanity has grown complacent, until disaster strikes. Work together and survive the alien hordes!<h2 class="bb_tag">A Fight For Survival Is Just the Beginning</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Survivors.png?t=1701799902"><br/>The first season of The Anacrusis tells the story of four unlikely survivors--Nessa, Guion, Liu, and Lance--who are unwilling combatants in the battle to defend humanity from the alien menace. Play more and unlock more of the unfolding mystery of the alien attack.<h2 class="bb_tag">Never Fight the Same Battle Twice</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Director.png?t=1701799902"><br/>In The Anacrusis, the AI Driver controls every aspect of the game. It spawns every enemy, directs each boss, and places every weapon, gadget, and health kit. No matter your skill level, you'll find the perfect level of challenge. More than that, the AI Driver creates the kinds of video game moments that you can’t wait to tell your friends about.<h2 class="bb_tag">Join the Community</h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fstraybombay" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Community.png?t=1701799902"/></a><br/>We've posted 35 updates to The Anacrusis since launch, and we couldn't have done it without our incredible community of Early Access players. <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fstraybombay" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join the Discord</a> and share your feedback with us. Or check the <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Ftrello.com%2Fb%2FjcUa92HH%2Fthe-anacrusis-roadmap" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Roadmap</a> to see what's coming next!<h2 class="bb_tag">We Love Mods! </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Mods.png?t=1701799902"><br/>We think co-op games are better with mods, which is why The Anacrusis includes Steam Workshop support for new campaigns, holdout maps, character skins, character accessories, gun charms, and animations, with more to come. Even better, the mods you load are automatically displayed for your friends to see when you play the game. Want to create mods for The Anacrusis? <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fstraybombay" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our Discord</a> for updates and conversation about mod support.<h2 class="bb_tag">Earn New Perks and Change the Way You Play</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Perks.png?t=1701799902"><br/>Matter compilers spread throughout the game give you access to dozens of perks that will change the way you play. Stack all of your upgrades to power up the last-resort pistol or boost your defense by supercharging your shield pulse. Unlock new perks as you play, and share your unlocks with everyone on your team!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company of Heroes 3: Hammer &amp; Shield Expansion Pack</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2068342/Company_of_Heroes_3_Hammer__Shield_Expansion_Pack/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2068342/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							The Hammer &amp; Shield Expansion Pack introduces two contrasting new Battlegroups for Multiplayer,   Co-op and Single Player Skirmish.  For solo strategists, an all-new Campaign Company allows you to tackle the Italian Campaign with bold combined arms tactics. In addition, Hammer &amp; Shield also includes four cosmetic packs, one for each army in the game.<br/><br/><strong>USF  -  ADVANCED INFANTRY BATTLEGROUP</strong><br/><br/>The elite Rangers are one of the key elements of the Advanced Infantry Battlegroup. Riflemen in the field can be upgraded to Rangers and become an option in the Barracks build menu. These devastating troops can call down their own weapon drops, and can wield up to six upgraded weapons in total, ranging from flamethrowers to BARs. <br/><br/>Advanced Infantry Battlegroup is also heavily focused on artillery support. Upgrade your Scouts into Artillery Observers, who can build Artillery Radio Beacons. These hidden structures can be used to call down light artillery barrages in their vicinity, causing chaos in the enemy ranks.<br/><br/>The 105mm M1 Howitzer provides your troops with dedicated on field medium artillery support, and can even be upgraded to auto fire on the enemy, leaving you more time to focus on the assault at hand.<br/><br/>Finally, if the situation calls for a concentrated heavy artillery solution, the 155mm Rapid Artillery strike will provide exactly that. This ability is perfect to smash the lines of entrenched foes, or to tip the scales in large scale engagements.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2068342/extras/COH3_XP1_US-Forces_Steam_616x346px.jpg?t=1701808829"><br/><br/><strong>WEHRMACHT - ITALIAN COASTAL DEFENSE BATTLEGROUP</strong><br/><br/>The Coastal Reserves Infantry are  versatile, and defensive, opening up myriad strategies for cunning commanders. These reservists are experts in field defenses and can build anything from tank traps to concrete bunkers. The Coastal Reserves also gain combat bonuses when fighting from cover or near defensive bunkers, making them an extremely difficult nut to crack. <br/><br/>The Artillery Officer is the perfect unit to punish the enemy as they stall against your fortifications and dogged line infantry. The officer can call down artillery and smoke barrages, supervise production, and inspire nearby infantry to greater feats in combat. <br/><br/>Support Bunkers allow for even more utility in the defensive line. The Anti-Tank Bunker will dispatch enemy vehicles from long range, while the Command Bunker will improve the performance of nearby bunkers, and act as a retreat point for infantry. <br/><br/>The Obice da 210/22 is a heavy howitzer, and a statement piece in any defensive general’s armament. Its ominous boom heralds the impact of 101KG shells that will eviscerate infantry, armor, and fortifications alike. As if the Obice was not terrifying enough, it will fire additional shells when in proximity to friendly bunkers, due to its Rapid Resupply ability.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2068342/extras/COH3_XP1_Wehrmacht-Italian-Coastal_Steam_616x346.jpg?t=1701808829"><br/><br/><strong>BRITISH AIR AND SEA - CAMPAIGN COMPANY</strong><br/><br/>The British Air and Sea Company for the Italian Dynamic Campaign allows for a varied and flexible combined arms playstyle. <br/><br/>In missions, Airborne Commandos will enable you to lay deadly ambushes, or strike fast and hard in all out assaults. These Elite troops are among some of the finest in the theatre, and can be used to devastating effect. <br/><br/>As this company often operates behind the lines, the Air and Sea ground troops often rely on mobile team weapons to deal with the threats they encounter. For instance, CWT towed anti-tank guns (including the legendary 17 pounder) can be deployed rapidly to engage armor. Similarly, airdropped Pack Howitzers are an option should field artillery support be a priority. <br/><br/>When more drastic solutions are required, the Air and Sea Company can call in a range of devastating aerial support, such as Incendiary Saturation Bombing, Anti-Tank Strafing Runs, and more. The boots on the ground can also rely on Naval Bombardments to smash defensive lines and keep the enemy on their heels.<br/><br/>On the Campaign Map, the Air and Sea company is an exceptional deep strike option. Able to paradrop to target locations, this company offers the British a more aggressive archetype than the other available Campaign Companies. What’s more, in keeping with their combined arms theme, the British Air and Sea Company will attain sizeable on map combat bonuses when engaging enemy companies while overwatched by aerial reconnaissance.<br/><br/>With Company Upgrades that are managed via the Campaign Map, the British Air and Sea can make upgrade selections that further enhance their already formidable abilities and units. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2068342/extras/COH3_XP1_British-Air-Land-Sea_Steam_616x346.jpg?t=1701808829"><br/><br/><strong>PREMIUM COSMETICS</strong><br/><br/>Hammer and Shield also includes 4 premium cosmetic packs, one for each army in the game. The packs are listed as follows:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Wehrmacht - Fallen Leaf Panzer IV and Stug III Pack<br/></li><li>Deutsches Afrikakorps Blocking Force Infantry Pack   <br/></li><li>British Nature’s Vanguard CwT &amp; Dingo Pack<br/></li><li>USF Board Room Half-Track and Hellcat Pack</li></ul><br/>In total,  Hammer &amp; Shield Expansion Pack owners will have access to 10  new premium cosmetics. Win at all costs and look good doing so.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born of Bread</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1555140/Born_of_Bread/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beings from another age are causing havoc across the land! And with their mischief comes a great threat to everyone. The unlikeliest hero, a golem born of bread, will find himself and his newfound buddies in the middle of a drama that's thousands of years in the making. Together, they will visit incredible locals and meet fascinating characters. Although he may not look like much, Loaf might be the hero this land kneads.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Sentient Bread on a Quest</h2><br/>Play as a flour golem who possesses a never-ending childlike wonder and a set of odd abilities in this 2.5D adventure game!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Cinematic_opti.gif?t=1701805959"><br/><br/>Explore the different regions of a wonderful world ripe with mysteries and team up with a colorful cast of fleshed-out characters. With the help of your buddies, face off against menacing and weird baddies and engage in a fun and quirky turn-based combat system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Enviro_opti.gif?t=1701805959"><br/><br/><strong>A home-cooked battle system</strong><br/>Born of Bread puts a twist on turn-based combat tropes with a fun interaction system that will test your reflexes.<br/>This interactive system also features a weaknesss and resistance system that makes battles more strategic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Combat_Opti.gif?t=1701805959"><br/><br/><strong>Team up with your buddies</strong><br/>Loaf can't do it alone. Meet new characters during your adventure, each with their own abilities and personnality. Use their unique skills to overcome threats and obstacles whether in fights or when exploring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Buddies_opti.gif?t=1701805959"><br/><br/><strong>Stream your fights to a fake audience!</strong><br/>Your dragon buddy Dub will let you save your progression but also stream your fights to a fake audience with his little laptop! Gather more viewers and answer their demand to get rewards!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley: A Rift in Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2632050/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley_A_Rift_in_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2632050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Content</h2>
							Once an ancient kingdom full of treasures and magical artifacts, Eternity Isle has become lost in time as a result of Jafar’s meddling in magic. Journey to this faraway land and utilize a mysterious new Royal Tool—the Hourglass—as you discover new secrets and uncover lost treasures. Stop Jafar’s scheme to steal the Spark of Imagination, an ancient relic that holds the fabric of Dreamlight Valley together. With the help of the Hourglass, you are the key to fixing rifts in time and putting an end to Jafar’s evil plan!<br/><br/><strong>Unravel a Whole New Story on Eternity Isle</strong><br/>Help foil the plans of the nefarious Jafar as you meet new friends and find treasures lost in time in a new story unfolding in three acts. Secrets from Dreamlight Valley’s past can be uncovered using a new Royal Tool, the Hourglass, as you reveal what happened long before the Forgetting…<br/><br/><strong>Discover a New Island </strong><br/>Delve into three new Biomes, each with new areas to explore and make your own. From Ancient’s Landing to the Glittering Dunes and the Wild Tangle, each has a fully customizable layout to decorate with lost treasures and exclusive Disney- and Pixar-inspired furniture.<br/><br/><strong>Spend Time with Four New Villagers</strong><br/>Reunite EVE with WALL·E, help Rapunzel start an art class, take lessons in heroics from Gaston, and decide if you can really trust Jafar. Explore Eternity Isle with your new friends… or move them back to live in Dreamlight Valley!<br/><br/>Play Scramblecoin, a new board game that your Villagers are waiting to play with you.<br/><br/><strong>Wield the Royal Hourglass</strong><br/>Find a new Royal Tool, the Hourglass, and use its magic to find Relics lost in time. Build Ancient Machines to help automate Activities such as gardening and cooking, which makes it easier than ever to run your island. Take your new Hourglass back to Dreamlight Valley and explore the Realms to see what other treasures you can find!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picayune Dreams</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2088840/Picayune_Dreams/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2088840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FvEnpxNJxxx" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2088840/extras/PDstorediscord.jpg?t=1701805326"/></a><h2 class="bb_tag">Picayune Dreams</h2>Lost in the endless expanse of s̴p̵a̶c̵e̵, you must fight off endless hordes of inter-dimensional beings t̷o̶ ̸c̵l̵a̷i̵m̵ a few more brief moments of life. <strong>P̸̯͛i̸̲͌c̶̖͝a̵̙̔ý̵̥u̷̱̒n̸͖̓ḛ̸̔ ̷̣̕D̵̢͑r̵̰̕e̶̘̓ã̴̧m̶͉̈s̶͓̄</strong> will challenge your skill, endurance, and perseverance through a m̸i̴n̷d̴ ̵w̴a̶r̶p̷i̶n̵g̸, psychedelic, bullet hell nightmare.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2088840/extras/PDsteamtitles01.gif?t=1701805326"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2088840/extras/PDsteamgif02.gif?t=1701805326"><br/>Survive hordes of nightmarish creatures. This game does not favor passive builds, and will require you to stay on your toes, weaving through enemies and incoming attacks, while collecting resources and upgrades when and where you can. Modify your runs with limited elements of roguelite progression.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2088840/extras/PDsteamtitles02.gif?t=1701805326"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2088840/extras/PDsteamgif01.gif?t=1701805326"><br/>A gauntlet of Bullet Hell bosses will test both your defenses and offenses. These high-octane, punishing battles are be driven by a pulse-pounding, glitchcore soundtrack from Milkypossum.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2088840/extras/PDsteamtitles03.gif?t=1701805326"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2088840/extras/PDsteamgif03.gif?t=1701805326"><br/>Immerse yourself in a psychedelic atmosphere, filled with secrets, that will keep you guessing at every turn. The more you think you know of the story, the more layers you'll find to peel back. The story elements are largely option, but will provide depth and context for players who wish to explore every corner of Picayune Dreams.<h2 class="bb_tag">Inspirations</h2>Taking inspiration from a varied collection of our favourite games: <strong>Vampire Survivors</strong> (roguelike horde survival), <strong>Touhou</strong> (true bullet hell), <strong>Yume Nikki</strong> (surrealist visual stylings and secrets), and <strong>Diablo</strong> (power scaling and item visualization).<br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2088840/Picayune_Dreams/" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2088840/Picayune_Dreams/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Svarog's Dream</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2004640/Svarogs_Dream/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2004640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Ever-changing world</h2>In Svarog's Dream, you will have absolute freedom to explore the world and make decisions.<br/>However, freedom comes with consequences; over time, your actions will shape the world around you, either for the better or worse.<h2 class="bb_tag">Soul lost between worlds</h2>You start as a lost soul, and you will inhabit human hosts who are desperate enough to accept you. With each death, you will revisit the underworld and return through new characters with their unique backgrounds and talents.<h2 class="bb_tag">A pawn in the game of Gods</h2>While humans are waging their wars on Earth, the Gods are battling each other in the sky.  <br/>Their power is immense; however, everyone is bound to the threads of destiny, except for you. <br/>You possess a valuable power—the power of free will—and because of that, <br/>the gods will see you as an important piece and will try to persuade you to join their side.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2004640/extras/BogoviBaner14.png?t=1701811367"><br/><br/><strong>The old prophecy:</strong> <br/><i>"Svarog, the first god, created six worlds and fell asleep.<br/>In his dream, he created the seventh world, Earth.<br/>Once he wakes up, Earth will cease to exist."</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Immersive gameplay</h2>In Svarog's Dream, you will discover over a hundred quests, more than a hundred unique abilities, and over five hundred unique items. <br/>You will have to eat, cook, sleep, craft potions, upgrade gear, buy houses, take loans, and even evade debt collectors or headhunters, and much more.<br/>We have done our best to make the world around you feel alive and responsive to your decisions.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Die in the Dungeon: Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2428770/Die_in_the_Dungeon_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Die in the Dungeon is a <strong>deck-building, turn-based roguelite</strong> where your deck is not made out of cards, but <strong>DICE</strong>!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/dicegif.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/>In Die in the Dungeon, each dice represents a different action, from basic ones like attacking or healing to boosting other dice or copying their abilities.<br/><br/>Improve the quality of your dice, combine them and acquire powerful relics to defeat the monsters that dwell in the dungeon! Find great synergies by combining dice with unique abilities to create powerful and bizarre decks!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/gameplay_v2.gif?t=1701702754"><h2 class="bb_tag">Prologue Features</h2><strong>Create unique and powerful dice sets the Relics and Events System</strong><br/>Decide how to proceed when faced with short events and be on the lookout for their juicy rewards:<br/>Powerful artifacts called “relics” will help you create unique combinations, strengthening your dice even more! But watch out, some of them might be cursed!<br/><br/><strong>Discover the Origins of Die in the Dungeon!</strong><br/>Play as Lisver - a new character whose story takes place in a supposedly safe and thoroughly explored dungeon, but something seems off here… Hold your ground while overcoming new and unexpected threats and make every dice roll count!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2428770/extras/Lisver.gif?t=1701702754"><br/><br/><strong>Various Battles and Dicey Enemies</strong><br/>Fight your way through hordes of monsters with increasing difficulty: facing enemies with unique mechanics and new special events. Go through a series of trials, defeat the great evil that lurks in the depths, and venture into the Endless Mode, the ultimate test of strategy.<br/><br/><strong>Way of a Dice!</strong><br/>Collect dice, make them stronger with special properties, and craft the ultimate deck. All dice can be combined with powerful modifiers to reduce their energy cost (Hollow) or make them stay longer on the board (Heavy), among many others!<br/>What fate awaits you within the dungeon walls? Face familiar foes, learn the truth about this endless cycle, and dare to step even farther with a brand-new game mode!<br/><br/>And the best part is, you're getting a massive amount of content completely for free!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2608050/Cats_Hidden_in_Jingle_Jam/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Cats Hidden in Jingle Jam is a <strong>free </strong>hidden object game made for the charity event Jingle Jam 2023 in collaboration with The Yogscast.<br/><br/>🎨 The game features custom artwork created specially by Nina-Serena and given away completely free for everyone to enjoy! <br/><br/>🐱 100 cats are waiting to be discovered in a custom hand-drawn background. Relax thanks to a chill soundtrack.<br/><br/>🐈 Found a cat? Click on it! <br/><br/>🎁 And please consider donating to the Jingle Jam this year - supporting a range of great charities across the world!<h2 class="bb_tag">Features</h2>🐾 1 Level, 100 cats<br/>❔ Easter Eggs<br/>💡 Hint System<br/>⏰ Timer mode with leaderboard<br/>⚙️ In-game Settings<br/><br/><strong>TRAVELLIN CATS GIFT COLLECTION</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/divider__1_.png?t=1701703324"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/32209/Travellin_Cats_Gift_Collection/" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2608050/extras/gift_bundle_jingle_jam.png?t=1701703324"/></a> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SteamWorld Build</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2134770/SteamWorld_Build/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-Homestead.png?t=1701599791"><br/>One final landrush! The planet is dyin', Astrid, and it's dig or die trying! <br/><br/>That mine under our town is sitting empty, and wouldn't you know there's rumours of ancient tech down there that might help us out of this predicament. Round up the posse, circle the wagons, and let's get to buildin' a new home! Collect resources above ground and ores down below so we can get those wealthy bots in here to help us build bigger, and we can get the heck out of here!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_1.gif?t=1701599791"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_manage.png?t=1701599791"><br/>As your borders expand, new steamfolk will find their way to you! Every bot is crotchety in their own way, and it's up to you to keep them steaming along. Barter to boost efficiency, keep goods flowing to and from the mines and keep everyone happy to make them work their darndest and hardest.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_2.gif?t=1701599791"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/steam_description_features-DIG-DEEP.png?t=1701599791"><br/><br/>Stare into the abyss long enough and it might just stare back... we're going looking for riches and something down there doesn't want to share! Have gun, dig gravel, and make sure the mines don't collapse upon you as you defend yourselves from the creepy crawlies that lurk within...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_GIF_3.gif?t=1701599791"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2134770/extras/SWB_steam_description_features.png?t=1701599791"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Break ground on a bustling SteamWorld town, inspired by the Old West.<br/></li><li>Keep your steambots from getting cranky by ensuring their complex needs get met<br/></li><li>Dig deep and spread wide to produce resources to aid your search for ancient technologies<br/></li><li>Defend your mine from the creepy varmints that lurk deep below your town<br/></li><li>Trade resources at the local train stop and welcome special visitors who'll lend a hand<br/></li><li>Five distinct maps littered with secrets for the discerning SteamWorld explorer to find<br/></li><li>Developed from the ground up for both mouse and controller, whichever takes yer fancy.<br/></li><li>Four difficulty levels, including a sandbox difficulty for when you just want to Build!</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalypse Party</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2351560/Apocalypse_Party/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">The moment of "Apocalypse" approaches, this time... ...you fight for yourself!</h2><br/><strong>「Apocalypse Party」</strong> is distinct from the former 「Project Zero」<br/>In this installment, you will delve deeper into this long-standing battle, with the story gradually becoming incredible! Time travel? Apocalypse? Saving the world? You will face many more unknown challenges... ...<br/>But it still retains our beloved RogueLike + mowing-down-enemies combo, and you will face this catastrophe online with your friends (of course, you can also face it alone)!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Engaging and Deep Mechanics ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT01_Skills_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/><strong>Talent pool expanded to 450! And most of them are mechanics that can change the course of battle</strong><br/>Additionally, there are:<br/>- Hundreds of distinct ranged and melee weapons!<br/>- A plethora of divine ultimate skills!<br/>- 35 varied hero characters, hundreds of unique hero skills<br/>The richness has increased by <strong>more than 10 times compared to the former installment</strong>! Can you build the strongest combo?<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Supports Multiplayer, shall we join the hunting party tonight? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT02_MutiplePlayerMode_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>Support <strong>up to 3</strong> multiplayer online! <br/>Massive hordes of zombies, exhilarating mowing-down action, why enjoy it alone?<br/>Imagine the joy of roaming through a sea of zombies with your friends!<br/>Call them, support each other, move forward or retreat together, survive here!<br/><strong>Of course, we kindly remind you, a "friendship-ends" scenario is not excluded :)</strong><br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ You crave some real challenge, don't you? ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT04_Boss_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>In this game, you will face the ultimate challenge.<br/><strong>9 highly challenging Bosses!</strong><br/>Only rapid growth can help you withstand the fierce attacks from the Bosses, accept the challenge, defeat them, and show them who’s boss now!<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ Perhaps we can do some time traveling! ■</h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT05_Medivel_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>A brand new storyline takes you into this familiar yet strange world, continuing a tale of redemption amidst time traveling:<br/>The tragic death of loved ones<br/>The desperate nuclear explosion<br/>The eerie rebirth<br/>The deathly quiet town<br/>The dark dungeons<br/>... ...<br/><br/><strong><h2 class="bb_tag"> ■ We are continuously focusing on your gameplay experience! ■ </h2></strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/gifT03_Combat_EN.gif?t=1701678706"><br/><br/>We have keenly listened to the feedback from the players of our former installment, reworked the combat system of the game, continuously bringing more fluid gaming experiences to players.<br/>-<i>Mix and use combat methods like melee weapons, firearms, spells, summoning, witchcraft... ...</i>! They will bring you a fun experience.<br/>-<i>Drive vehicles, summon planes, dragon flying, use otherworldly ninjutsu, even use the mysterious Dual-vector Foi</i>, and more easter eggs await your exploration.<br/>-This game encourages an online experience, but undoubtedly, the single-player part can still experience all the systems and joy of this game.<br/><br/>Smooth operation (handling) is also an important part we continuously focus on！<br/>We have made the game’s operation &amp; flow experience more user-friendly.<br/><strong>Easy to get started, yet "easy to learn, hard to master"!</strong><br/><br/><strong>"Since the apocalypse is here, join us for the last revelry."</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2351560/extras/Library_Hero_EN.jpg?t=1701678706"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronzebeard's Tavern</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2422870/Bronzebeards_Tavern/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bronzebeard's Tavern is a goofy and playful restaurant manager sim where 1-4 players can work as a team with multiplayer co-op. Fulfill a number of different roles, serve a diverse range of customers and cook up delicious dwarven cuisine.<h2 class="bb_tag">4-Player Multiplayer!</h2>Work together (or try) to keep the tavern running for as long as you can with three other dwarves in online multiplayer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/UpTo4Players.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Serve Customers!</h2>Properly manage customer seating and orders and deliver them the correct foods to reap rewards!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/ServeCustomers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Cook Up and Blend Delicious Food and Drink!</h2>Prepare food for the customers upon receiving orders from your teammates, being careful not to burn anything!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/CookUpBlend.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Customize your Menu!</h2>Your daily customers are always different! Design your menu however you like based on the day's forecast and food sales!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Menus.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Customers to Discover!</h2>There's always an unfamiliar face showing up when you're working in a tavern... can you satisfy them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Customers.gif?t=1701703276"><h2 class="bb_tag">Upgrade your Tavern!</h2>Build up your tavern with upgrades! These decisions change the way you play and are crucial for progressing into tougher days. Opt for more customer capacity with a shiny new expansion or utilities like more blenders or more stoves to increase your output!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2422870/extras/Upgrades.gif?t=1701703276"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1996770/Turok_3_Shadow_of_Oblivion_Remastered/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/raptor_jumps.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is a faithful restoration of the classic first-person shooter originally released in 2000 for the Nintendo 64, upgraded through Nightdive Studios’ proprietary KEX Engine for play on modern gaming devices with up to a 4K resolution at 120FPS. <br/><br/>It joins Nightdive Studios and Universal Games popular Turok and Turok 2: Seeds of Evil remasters, capping off the trilogy. <i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> features upgraded gameplay, high-resolution textures, enhanced lighting and rendering, and support for gamepads.<h2 class="bb_tag">FINISH THE HUNT</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/sniper_one_eye.gif?t=1701367237"><br/><br/><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> is the first title from Nightdive Studios to be remastered using the latest version KEX engine, which utilizes an improved renderer to achieve a higher tier of visual fidelity across 3D models, textures, and graphical effects.<h2 class="bb_tag"><i>Turok 3 Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</i> Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>A remastered version of the 2000 classic, available for the first time since its Nintendo 64 release<br/></li><li>Up to 4K 120FPS performance<br/></li><li>Advanced rendering features, including anti-aliasing, bloom, ambient occlusion, dynamic shadows, and motion blur	<br/></li><li>Remastered environment art, character models, and updated weapon models<br/></li><li>Brand new Achievements</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1996770/extras/robot.gif?t=1701367237"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pinball M</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2337640/Pinball_M/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-1.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>The new horror-inspired pinball platform for fearless players. Prove your skills on the most sinister, gory, and badass tables ever brought to life. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-2.png?t=1701703297"><br/><br/>- Wrath of the Elder Gods: Director’s Cut - experience the eldritch horror unrestricted for free<br/>- A library of brand new, never-before-seen tables filled with fear and carnage<br/>- Thrilling competition<br/>- Zen Studios’ ultimate pinball simulation<h2 class="bb_tag">Sink your teeth into these tables as purchasable DLC: </h2><h2 class="bb_tag">- Chucky's Killer Pinball:</h2> Step into a twisted realm where the innocent becomes sinister, and the playful turns menacing. Navigate through an eerie playfield where Chucky lurks in the shadows, ready to pounce.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Dead by Daylight™️ Pinball:</h2> Become the hunter or even the hunted in a thrilling fusion of classic pinball and the excitement of one of the most popular horror games ever created.<h2 class="bb_tag">- Duke Nukem's Big Shot Pinball:</h2> Enjoy the biggest, grooviest, most BADASS pinball table ever made packed with guns and babes. Push start and play with balls of steel!<h2 class="bb_tag">- The Thing Pinball: </h2>Use your pinball skills and battle against the shape-shifting alien through the arctic chill of U.S. Outpost #31. Can you trust anyone, even yourself?<br/>- Even more coming...<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2337640/extras/Pinball_M_Steam_banner_616x72px-4.png?t=1701703297"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEVI</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2230650/TEVI/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FZ9KrdFvNRK" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/JoinUsOnDC.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Action-Packed_Combo_System.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/戰鬥動圖.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>The protagonist Tevi is nimble and agile, wielding both her trusty dagger and an oversized wrench for dishing out melee damage in style. Alongside her, companions Celia and Sable manifest as two floating orbitars, ready to unleash a variety of ranged offensive and supportive magic in battle. Adapt your combat style to suit any situation and bring down foes with flashy, dazzling combos!<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Thrilling_Boss_Battles.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Boss.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Every boss fight is a unique challenge requiring different strategies to tackle, all while you dodge their attacks and look for openings to counter-attack. <br/>As bosses change phases, their attack and bullet patterns become increasingly challenging, and they can even unleash devastating ultimates. Continual offense can submit bosses into a vulnerable BREAK state, during which you can deal massive bursts of damage.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/Myriad_Abilities,_Equipment,_and_Exploration.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/badge.jpg?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Scattered across the the expansive world, there are over 300 different items and pieces of equipment waiting to be discovered. These items can enhance your abilities or introduce new ones, allowing you to find more methods of navigating the world and finding secrets. A cornucopia of equippable sigils can be freely configured to create builds tailored to your preferences and playstyle.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/A_Rich,_Expansive_Fantasy_World.png?t=1701314590"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/場景6.png?t=1701314590"><br/><br/>Dive into the vibrant world of Az, in which you will discover various towns, regions, peoples, histories, and civilizations, each with their own tale to tell. Along the way, you'll meet a large cast of strange and colorful characters. As their tales unfold and intertwine, you'll be drawn into a tale full of adventure, friendship, mysteries, and danger... <br/><br/>Get ready to embark on an unforgettable adventure, writing your own epic journey alongside Tevi!<br/><br/><a href="https://youtu.be/psxior_WswQ" rel="" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2230650/extras/角色介紹.png?t=1701314590"/></a><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Tevi（VA: Lynn）<br/></li><li>Celia（VA: Yoko Hikasa）<br/></li><li>Sable（VA: Natsumi Fujiwara）<br/></li><li>Zema（VA: Tomokazu Sugita）<br/></li><li>Vena（VA: Rie Kugimiya）</li></ul> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Exit 8</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2653790/The_Exit_8/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2653790/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.<br/>Observe your surroundings carefully to reach "The Exit 8".<br/><br/><strong>Don't overlook any anomalies.<br/><br/>If you find anomalies, turn back immediately.<br/><br/>If you don't find anomalies, do not turn back.<br/><br/>To go out from Exit 8.</strong><br/><br/><br/>The Exit 8 is a short walking simulator inspired by Japanese underground passageways, liminal spaces and back rooms.<br/>The game is only available in Japanese and English, but if you understand the above description of the anomaly, you can probably play it all the way through.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play Time</h2>15-60 minutes<h2 class="bb_tag">About Video Distribution</h2>・Distribution is available to both individuals and corporations without permission.<br/>・Monetization is only possible when using the functions provided by the video distribution site.<br/>・We would appreciate it if you include the name of the game in the title of your video or live broadcast, or include a link to the Steam page in the summary section.<br/><br/>We will not be liable for any damages caused by the distribution of videos of this game.<br/>The contents of these guidelines are subject to change without notice.<h2 class="bb_tag">Option</h2>Graphics settings, mouse sensitivity, camera shake, and other settings can be configured from the options.<br/>If you are easily intoxicated, changing the following settings may help.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera shake】</strong><br/>The camera shakes when you walk or run, but if you set the value to 0.0, the camera will not shake.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Acceleration】</strong><br/>If you set the maximum value to 30.0, the camera will move without delay.<br/><br/><strong>【Camera Sensitivity】</strong><br/>If the sensitivity is high, the camera will move significantly when the mouse is moved. <br/>Adjust the value if you find it difficult to operate the camera with the default value of 1.<br/><br/><strong>【Motion Blur】</strong><br/>Afterimages will appear when the camera is moved. Recommended to disable at 30FPS<br/><br/><strong>【Preset】</strong><br/>Set the overall graphic settings.<br/>If you do not have sufficient specs, it is better to set it to "Low" to avoid sickness.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Train Home</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1469610/Last_Train_Home/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/LTH_GIF2.gif?t=1701758817"><br/><br/>Embark on a desperate mission through the depths of a war-torn wasteland. Your goal is to guide Czechoslovak soldiers back home onboard an armored train, but the path ahead is fraught with peril. Caught in the middle of a brutal civil war between Russia's Red and White Armies, your unit must remain in fighting shape, managing what little resources you have and maintaining morale at all costs. Venture through the bleak and unforgiving landscape of Siberia, where the freezing cold and the merciless environment will push you to your very limit. Resources are scarce and your crew is exhausted, but you must keep pushing forward. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_RTS_Optimized.gif?t=1701758817"><br/><br/>As you journey through the heart of the conflict, the horrors of war will surround you. The fate of your legion rests on the actions of a few key soldiers, as you engage in real-time battles that will determine the outcome of your mission. You must choose your tactics wisely, using every skill at your disposal to safeguard your troops and complete your mission. With careful training and development, your squads will become a seasoned legion of comrades, brothers and sisters, ready to face any challenge that comes their way.<br/><br/>The decisions you make along the journey will determine the fate of your comrades. Inspired by historical events, of the Czechoslovak Legion and their determination to return to their newly formed republic following The Great War,  this mission will test your courage and your will to survive. The Last Train Home is in your hands.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1469610/extras/Last_Train_Home_Management_Optimized.gif?t=1701758817"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>PICK YOUR BATTLES: Deploy your squad and complete diverse objectives in a series of real-time missions where specialist combat skills, planning, and superior tactics will lead you to victory.<br/></li><li>EQUIP YOUR SOLDIERS: Level up your men by unlocking new skills and gathering better equipment – discover their stories, assign medals, and help them rise up through the ranks.<br/></li><li>MANAGE YOUR CREW: Direct your soldiers in their non-combat roles onboard the train. Craft items, heal your wounded, and restore morale for the arduous journey home.<br/></li><li>UPGRADE YOUR TRAIN: Unlock your armored train’s full potential by upgrading the carriages and locomotive and oversee important maintenance work to keep it running.<br/></li><li>JOURNEY THROUGH SIBERIA: Stockpile and trade supplies, make new allies, and overcome crisis after crisis as civil war rages across the vast snowfields of Siberia.<br/></li><li>BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS: Last Train Home, is a compelling narrative that portrays the experiences of the Czechoslovak Legion and their valiant fight on behalf of the Entente powers during World War I.</li></ul> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats and Seek</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2672090/Cats_and_Seek/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							😻 100 Cats!<br/>🔍 Hint system<br/>🎨 Choose your favorite color<br/><br/>Let's play hide and seek with 100 cats!<br/>Can you find them all?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/game_play.gif?t=1701587609"><br/><br/>And if bored with black and white doddles you can choose <strong>your own favorite color</strong>.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2672090/extras/change_color.PNG?t=1701587609"> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Stars And Time</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1677310/In_Stars_And_Time/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2FZzFSRUBXEC" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/discordbanner620.gif?t=1701180941"/></a><br/><br/><strong>What would you do if you were forced to relive your failures over and over again?</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam5_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> tells the story of Siffrin and their adventurer friends—a found family bound together by fate in order to end the tyrannical reign of an evil king. But as victory is just within the party’s grasp, a tragedy occurs, the clock resets, and <strong>they have to do it all again</strong>. <br/><br/>As Siffrin’s the only one who notices this loop, each new start wears away at his cheerful veneer, yet he keeps going in hopes he can end this temporal tragedy once and for all.<br/><br/><strong>In Stars and Time</strong> is a <strong>time-looping RPG adventure</strong>. With each loop, Siffrin gains a new perspective on the world around them, opening up new solutions to puzzles and allowing them to make better choices in conversation. Equip memories as armor, pray to the Change God to improve your team’s capabilities each loop, and challenge deadly foes to Rock, Paper, Scissors as Siffrin seeks the truth.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam4_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Our Adventurers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Siffrin (he/they):</strong> Stressed, depressed, and under duress. (Don’t worry about it. They’re doing fine.) The punmaster protagonist of our neverending tale.<br/></li><li><strong>Mirabelle (she/her):</strong> A caring and nervous housemaiden mysteriously blessed by the god she so ardently follows.<br/></li><li><strong>Isabeau (he/him):</strong> Defender with a heart of gold. Cares dearly for his people and his friends.<br/></li><li><strong>Odile (she/her):</strong> The mature and nonsensical researcher studying…something. (No, she will not tell you what it is.)<br/></li><li><strong>Bonnie (they/them):</strong> Wait a minute, who brought this kid along???</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">✦ Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Save the world through the power of Rock, Paper, Scissors in <strong>strategic turn-based RPG</strong> combat encounters.<br/></li><li>Ignore the limits of time and space to <strong>fix your past mistakes</strong> by repeating the same two days over and over again.<br/></li><li>Equip the <strong>memories you have of your friends</strong> to make your party stronger in combat. <br/></li><li><strong>Watch the fate of this world unfold</strong> as you escape the twists and turns of this endless(???) loop.<br/></li><li>Eat <strong>samossas</strong> with your friends!<br/></li><li>Get heckled by a <strong>cheeky ethereal being of infinite starlight</strong>.<br/></li><li>Pray to a god for good luck in your travels. <strong>You’re gonna need it.</strong></li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1677310/extras/steam2_600px.gif?t=1701180941"><br/><br/>If any of this interests you, you might also want to play the game’s initial prototype, <u><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1691420/START_AGAIN_a_prologue/" rel="" target="_blank">START AGAIN START AGAIN START AGAIN: A Prologue</a></u>. While you don’t need to play it to understand In Stars and Time, it’s fun to see the game’s roots.						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Arcade Full of Cats</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2368470/An_Arcade_Full_of_Cats/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsbanner.png?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Frr8zmYk9VH" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/devcatsdiscord.gif?t=1700441481"/></a><br/><br/>Prepare for a gaming journey with a time-traveling twist in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." Join Leo and Fofiño as they navigate a feline-infused version of the arcade era, spanning from 1980 to the year 2000, all while attempting to find their way back to the present!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2368470/extras/1985gif.gif?t=1700441481"><br/><br/>Embark on a quest to discover hidden cats in five distinct scenarios, each representing a catified rendition of classic arcades. Get ready for the ultimate pet'em up! <br/><br/>"AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS" Features...<br/><br/>Time-Traveling Fun: Explore a charmingly reimagined arcade era, from the nostalgia of 1980 to the dawn of the new millennium, as you assist Leo and Fofiño on their journey back home.<br/><br/>Hidden Cat Hunt: Search high and low for hidden feline companions across five captivating scenarios, each with its unique surprises.<br/><br/>Whisker-Worthy Arcades: Visit five classic arcades, transformed into delightful cat-themed versions!<br/><br/>Get ready to traverse time and enjoy endless hours of cat-seeking amusement in "AN ARCADE FULL OF CATS." The ultimate pet'em up and our tribute to the Arcade Era!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bopl Battle</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1686940/Bopl_Battle/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Bopl Battle is a couch/online game where you battle your friends as a goofy slime.<br/>Squish and splatter each other using a combination of wild and unique abilities/weapons.<br/>Last slime standing wins!<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/celebrationFinal_yellow.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Here are some things you can do in the game:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Attach a rocket engine to platforms to send them flying away<br/></li><li>Cover the stage in flammable smoke<br/></li><li>Create a black hole and make it swallow the whole stage.<br/></li><li>Use a growth ray to permanently enlarge anything, including arrows, grenades, other players, even the stage itself<br/></li><li>Stop time and setup a deadly situation for all of your enemies as they are frozen<br/></li><li>Grab the stage and move it around</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1686940/extras/Bopl_Battle_2023.01.01_-_20.09.10.04_8fps.gif?t=1701286289"><h2 class="bb_tag">Invent your own strategy with a unique ability combination</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>create <strong>platform </strong>+ control <strong>platform</strong> + attach big sword onto <strong>platform</strong><br/></li><li><strong>flammable </strong>smoke + throw <strong>grenade</strong> + turn into an <strong>invincible</strong> rock</li></ul>The combos get even wilder in the team vs team mode, as you cooperate with someone to really push the game to its limit.<h2 class="bb_tag">Disclaimers</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Warning</strong>: This game contains flashing lights that may make it unsuitable for people with photosensitive epilepsy or other photosensitive conditions. Player discretion is advised.<br/></li><li>Only one player can use keyboard + mouse per computer. So playing locally requires controllers for the other players.<br/></li><li>Bopl Battle is a multiplayer game. There is no singleplayer mode and no bots. Make sure to bring a friend!</li></ul> </img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Makeover</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626940/Life_Makeover/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Life Makeover is a liberating fashion game where you have the freedom to express your unique style. Customize your virtual persona, experiment with various fashion choices, and dive into the joy of unlimited dress-up possibilities with fashion dye and do-it-yourself (DIY) options. It's your chance to create your own fashion show! Plus, you can even design and build your dream home for free.<br/><br/>[Unleash Your Unique Persona] - Customize Every Detail<br/>Take command of your virtual character and let your style shine. Customize facial features, body shape, and skin tone to break free from conventions and express yourself in your own extraordinary way.<br/><br/>[Elevate Designs with Limitless Wardrobe] - Powered by UE4 Engine<br/>Experience an extensive wardrobe for every occasion, each design flawlessly detailed. Fueled by the cutting-edge UE4 engine and a range of 3D materials, your creations will be impeccably crafted, down to the smallest stitch and embroidery.<br/><br/>[Express with Color, Lead with Style] - The Power of Fashion Dye<br/>Unleash your creativity through the fashion dye feature. Color different parts of your outfits with hundreds of combinations, from dazzling iridescence to perfectly coordinated hues. Be a trailblazer in setting new trends and embody the essence of beauty.<br/><br/>[Your Designs, Your Brand] - DIY Garment Studio<br/>Step into the shoes of a fashion designer. From fabric selection to pattern making, cutting, and printing, oversee every aspect of the creative process. Your designs, your choices, your brand.<br/><br/>[Beyond Fashion, Craft Your Ideal Home] - Unleash a Dream Lifestyle<br/>Personalize your living space with a diverse selection of furniture. Embrace a lifestyle of reading, dancing, working out, hosting parties, raising pets, and much more in your ideal home.<br/><br/>[Uncover Mysteries and Memories] - Immersive Stories with Live2D Cards<br/>Delve into captivating stories and memories brought to life with Live2D cards. Concealed beneath exquisite costumes lie mysteries and clues waiting to be unraveled. Are you prepared to uncover the truth?<br/><br/>[Connect, Create, and Celebrate] - Thrive in a Community of Designers<br/>Join a dynamic community of designers in a boundless universe. Share makeup and outfit ideas, visit friends' homes, host afternoon tea gatherings, and enhance house decor for stunning photos. Forge new friendships and connect with others in the world of Life Makeover.<br/><br/>[Your Journey to Infinite Possibilities] - Beauty, and Freedom<br/>In Life Makeover, you're not just a player; you're a creator. Come and infuse your life with inspiration and imagination. Embrace a world where diversity and freedom reign supreme!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Hero</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/Backpack_Hero/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1970580/</a><br/><strong>The inventory management roguelike!</strong><br/>Collect rare items, organize your backpack, and vanquish your foes!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/overview_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><strong>Backpack Hero is a twist on your standard deck-building roguelike. It isn't just about what you carry, but how you organize the items within your bag!</strong><br/><br/>Placement has a huge impact on your items – find the right spot in your backpack to increase their power! Explore ancient dungeons, caves, swamps, and more! Meet colorful friends and fight deadly foes! Don't get lost!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/backpack_gif1.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/story_mode_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><strong>When you aren't putting your life in danger, you can make good use of the resources you have gathered and rebuild your hometown of Haversack Hill!</strong><br/><br/>Turn it into a charming and efficient hamlet to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests. By organizing the perfect village, you will restore the world of Orderia and rescue the animals who live there!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/town_gif3.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/features_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Experiment with your strategy</strong> and create game-breaking solutions<br/></li><li><strong>Collect 800+ distinct items</strong>, with ingenious powers and synergies to harness<br/></li><li><strong>Battle with over 100+ enemies.</strong> Learn their attack patterns and vanquish your foes<br/></li><li><strong>Dive into the endless dungeons!</strong> Start every run with randomly generated levels and discover unpredictable items, unique layouts, events, and challenges<br/></li><li><strong>Explore 5 unique play styles</strong> by selecting different heroes<br/></li><li><strong>Play standalone runs or experience the full adventure</strong> and meta progression in Story Mode<br/></li><li><strong>Rebuild Haversack Hill </strong>and help its inhabitants<br/></li><li><strong>Turn the village into an appealing and efficient hamlet</strong> to attract new residents. Buy and sell items, conduct research, and unlock heroes, challenges, and quests</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/dungeon_gif2.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1970580/extras/extra_features_banner.gif?t=1701712994"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Enrich your game with mods</strong> created by the community<br/></li><li>Enjoy the game on <strong>PC or Steam Deck</strong><br/></li><li>Play with <strong>full controller support</strong></li></ul><br/><strong><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fv7dJYk6gtw" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our community</a> and share your feedback - our developers visit every day!</strong> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astral Ascent</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1280930/Astral_Ascent/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Astral Ascent is a 2D platformer rogue-lite game set in a modern fantasy world. As one of 4 Heroes with very different personalities, you must escape from <i>the Garden</i>, an astral prison guarded by 12 powerful and vicious bosses, the Zodiacs.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>CREATE YOUR OWN PLAYSTYLE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Gif_playstyle.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Unlock dozens of unique spells for your 4 distinct characters. Optimize your own build or try out new ones to take down 12 powerful bosses. Get stronger with time to match up with your foes. Each run will test your skills and your reactivity.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>TWELVE ALMIGHTY BOSSES TO FACE</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Zodiacs.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The Zodiacs are 12 experienced guardians dispatched over 4 gorgeous worlds. They’ll bring to the battlefield unique attacks, abilities, and patterns, backstories to uncover, and reasons to be fighting you. Get yourself warned!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>4 PLAYABLE CHARACTERS</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/4_Character_banniere_steam7.png?t=1700851162"><br/><i>Unique characters. Unique weapons. Unique ways to play.</i><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Ayla:</strong> The sole survivor of her guild of assassins, she uses her twin daggers to eliminate her enemies before they can react. Her speed and proficiency are unmatched.<br/></li><li><strong>Kiran:</strong> This orphan learned life the hard way. He uses his strength to deliver attacks powerful enough to create shockwaves. Brutal.<br/></li><li><strong>Calie:</strong> This talented sculptor wants her freedom back. She will use her magical gemstones to pierce enemy defenses and shred them to bits. She is unforgiving.<br/></li><li><strong>Octave:</strong> Trained by a powerful witch, this young fighter summons ethereal guns to attack his foes. When needed, he can conjure bigger weapons as well. Lethal in all cases.</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A STORY THAT OPENS UP, ONE PIECE AT A TIME</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/ZimZim2.png?t=1700851162"><br/>Astral Ascent is a rogue-lite infused with narration. Replayability is part of our story which will be unraveled piece by piece. As you get stronger, you will discover more about the characters, their motivations, and the secrets of the world they’re trapped in.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>LOCAL CO-OP</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Coop.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>The weight of destiny is too heavy to carry by yourself? Don’t worry and bring a friend to play in our <strong>two-player co-op</strong> mode. Fight and crush your enemies together in local co-op or online using the <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/remoteplay?snr=1_614_615__1601" rel="" target="_blank"><strong>Steam's Remote Play Together</strong></a> feature.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A VAST, COLORFUL FANTASY WORLD WAITING TO BE EXPLORED</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1280930/extras/Panning.gif?t=1700851162"><br/>Dash across gigantic landscapes. Explore original and hand-crafted areas. Discover the world created by our artists, with a gorgeous art and frame-by-frame animation.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral Island</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1158160/Coral_Island/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/header_alt_assets_1.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/ChickenSteam.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_About.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>It’s time to leave big-city life in Pokyo behind and start a new chapter of your life on Coral Island! <br/><br/>Be who you want and create the idyllic farm of your dreams, where you’ll tend crops, nurture animals, and build a bond with the natural world around you. Help revitalize the nearby town and its surrounding coral reefs, and forge relationships with a vibrant community of more than 70 fellow people who call Coral Island home. <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/UHD_Resize.gif?t=1699982807"><br/><br/>Farm. Decorate. Craft. Explore. Relax. Your future—and the future of Coral Island—is what you make of it.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1158160/extras/Store_Page_-_Features.png?t=1699982807"><br/><br/><strong>Build Your Dream Farm</strong><br/>Transform your overrun land on Coral Island into a lush and lively dreamscape—you decide what to build, what crops to grow, and which animals you’d like to tend. <br/><br/><strong>Write your own story</strong>:  <br/>The story changes with each season, but life goes with the flow. Spend your days exploring, or build a life with someone special. Save the seas, brave the caves, or focus on your farm. It’s up to you!<br/><br/><strong>Be yourself</strong>: <br/>Choose from a wide variety of outfits, accessories, and physiques—you’ll find plenty of options to express yourself, find your style, and be whoever you want to be. <br/><br/><strong>Befriend a diverse cast of islanders</strong>: <br/>Get to know the 70+ characters from all walks of life who live on Coral Island. Converse with them, find out more about their interests, and try to impress them with just the right gift.<br/><br/><strong>Find that special someone</strong>: <br/>Meet 25 singles who are ready to mingle! Build relationships, sweep them off their feet, and find the one—and when you’re ready, embark on a new chapter of your story together at the farm.<br/><br/><strong>Restore an island once paradise</strong>: <br/>Make Coral Island a better place for everyone! Take part in community projects to liven up the town, expand the local museum, and discover how to restore heritage sites. Increase the town's rank and  your community will thrive!<br/><br/><strong>Catch of the day</strong>: <br/>Island living has a lot of perks, including being just a stone's throw away from fun activities like hunting for insects and catching fish.<br/><br/><strong>Dive the ocean &amp; mine the caverns</strong>: <br/>Go diving to restore the coral reef, or mine precious gemstones in the cavern. Whatever you decide to do, you’ll find loot to hone your tools and upgrade the quality of your livestock and crops.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Infinite by PokerStars</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/886250/Vegas_Infinite_by_PokerStars/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.com%2Finvite%2Fpokerstarsvr" rel="noopener" target="_blank"> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/886250/extras/transition.gif?t=1701808865"> </img></a><br/><br/>PokerStars presents Vegas Infinite, a world of entertainment with no limits. Leap into virtual reality or sit back and play on PC with no headset required.<br/><br/>Take on the house at action-packed blackjack and roulette. Light up the dice with your friends at craps. Choose from a dazzling selection of slots, and challenge real opponents in cash, Spin &amp; Go, Sit &amp; Go, and multi-table tournament poker. <br/><br/>From luxury casino floors, private suites, and galactic space stations to soaring skylines and exclusive rooftop escapes, lose yourself in stunning environments while you play.  <br/><br/>Be yourself with a giant collection of customizable accessories and apparel, and add a touch of magic to your gameplay with an endless supply of props. <br/><br/>Your seat is open.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Access to IAP may be restricted by location<br/>Vegas Infinite VOIP is monitored by ToxMod<br/>Vegas Infinite is not a gambling product and does not present an opportunity to win real money. 18+ only. Please play responsibly.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gatekeeper: Infinity</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2391710/Gatekeeper_Infinity/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2FHkrp6AUa5S" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Discord_banner_gatekeeper.png?t=1700646226"/></a><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/infinity_gif_steam_1.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper" id="dynamiclink_1" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/2106670/Gatekeeper</a><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Wishlist_Arrows.png?t=1700646226"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Get ready to embark on an epic quest to recover the stolen Heart of the Universe on two different planets across twelve challenging locations.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>With 4 unique and playable characters to choose from, you can customize your gameplay experience and play to your strengths. </li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Each character offers a unique set of skills that can be upgraded through 45 different upgrades to help you on your journey.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>But beware! You will face fierce resistance from 20 different types of enemies, each with its own unique abilities and weapons that will challenge you at every turn.</li></ul><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Join forces with friends to fight against the machines in co-op mode.</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2391710/extras/Hybrid_Infinity.gif?t=1700646226"><br/><br/>Join the battle to recover the Heart of the Universe and become the ultimate Gatekeeper!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2519060/Call_of_Duty_Modern_Warfare_III/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2519060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Purchase any edition and receive:<br>
<br>
- Available in Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® III, Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II and Call of Duty®: Warzone™:<br>
-- Soap Operator Pack*<br>
-- Zombie Ghost Operator Skin*<br>
<br>
ADAPT OR DIE IN A FIGHT AGAINST THE ULTIMATE THREAT<br>
<br>
In the direct sequel to the record-breaking Call of Duty®: Modern Warfare® II, Captain Price and Task Force 141 face off against the ultimate threat. The ultranationalist war criminal Vladimir Makarov is extending his grasp across the world causing Task Force 141 to fight like never before.<br>
<br>
IT’S TIME TO SETTLE OLD SCORES AND START NEW ONES<br>
<br>
Modern Warfare® III celebrates the 20th anniversary of Call of Duty® with one of the greatest collections of Multiplayer maps ever assembled - both fan favorites and all new ones. All 16 launch maps from the original Modern Warfare® 2 (2009) have been modernized with new modes and gameplay features and will be available at launch to get everyone started, while over 12 all-new core 6v6 maps will fuel post-launch live seasons.<br>
<br/>
ALL NEW OPEN WORLD ZOMBIES<br/>
<br/>
For the first time, team up with other squads to survive and fight massive hordes of the undead in the largest Call of Duty® Zombies map ever. Modern Warfare® Zombies (MWZ) tells a new Treyarch Zombies story with missions, core Zombies features, and secrets to discover.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wanna Maker</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1114940/I_Wanna_Maker/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							I Wanna Maker is a precision platformer with a robust level editor and online level sharing, based on I Wanna Be The Guy fangames.<br/><br/>Create complex levels using a wide variety of objects, a powerful events system, and customizable visuals. Browse levels online, traverse a hand-crafted campaign, take on challenge modes, and more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Item_showcase.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">Level Editor Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Intuitive but powerful level editor with 70+ objects<br/></li><li>A flexible events system which enables endless possibilities<br/></li><li>Dozens of visuals for blocks, spikes, and backgrounds, each color-customizable<br/></li><li>150+ songs to choose from<br/></li><li>Props, lights, and particles to visually enhance your levels<br/></li><li>Add optional objectives to your levels with collectible gems</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay Features</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Play 240,000+ user-created levels made for a variety of skill levels<br/></li><li>Speedrun leaderboards for each level with watchable replays<br/></li><li>Campaign mode with dozens of high-quality levels<br/></li><li>Incredibly precise and responsive controls<br/></li><li>Take on challenge modes consisting of randomly chosen levels<br/></li><li>Save levels to custom playlists and share them online<br/></li><li>Follow your favorite makers so you don't miss their new levels<br/></li><li>Customize your character's appearance</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1114940/extras/Page_break.png?t=1699649497"><h2 class="bb_tag">No monetization</h2>I Wanna Maker is free to play, with no monetization of any kind. We hope you enjoy making levels and participating in the community!						</img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Rain Returns</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1337520/Risk_of_Rain_Returns/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/01_risk_of_rain_is_back.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Carefully designed, beautifully remastered, and loaded with new ways to play—Risk of Rain is back and better than ever! Dive into the iconic roguelike full of unique loot combinations, entirely new Survivors, overhauled multiplayer, and more!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/02_Before_and_after_revised.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/03_Uncover_New_Ways_to_Play_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Hone your skills and abilities, discover new Survivors, and dive into progressively stronger runs! Discover secrets of ancient design lying dormant beneath the surface of Petrichor V. Search under every log, stone, and Gup to find new ways to play!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/04_unlock_notification_popping_up.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/05_Header_Play_solo_or_gather_your_crew.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Many Survivors fled the mysterious attack on your ship. Slice, dice, and serve justice cold with the return of Chef, hold the front line and shield your team as Enforcer, or lay down a path of toxic sludge as everybody’s favorite purple monster: Acrid! Forge new paths to explore with 15 unique Survivors, each with new abilities to master. Two entirely new Survivors are making their debut in Risk of Rain Returns.<br/><br/>Also introducing The Drifter! This resourceful brawler gathers scrap from conquered foes and can spawn items that temporarily empower teammates. She can also take them for herself and unleash an unbridled blaze of area-wide destruction. The Drifter is the perfect addition to any group of Survivors. Her ability to support the team while laying down her own brand of hurt will prove she’s more than just a stowaway.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/06_place_holder_gif.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/07_Play_Solo_Or_Gather_Crew_615x200.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Drop to the surface solo or with your crew! Choose Survivors that complement each other’s strengths and weaknesses, or go wild and choose whoever has the largest guns (spoiler: it’s Loader). With up to four-player online and couch co-op, you’re not alone in this fight. <br/><br/>Risk of Rain Returns features new and improved multiplayer services to ensure the only thing that gets between your crew’s survival are the ever-growing hordes on Petrichor V.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/08_Gif_of_survivors_jumping_out_Desolate_Forest_zoomed_in.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/09_Potent_Pick-Ups_Header.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Fight your way to the surface while uncovering precious cargo. These items serve as your redemption, helping you move faster, deal more damage, or jump a little higher. Still others empower you in more dramatic ways—like the rare Ukulele, which empowers your attacks with electrifying music. <br/><br/>If explosions are what you’re after, hunt down the Brilliant Behemoth and watch as even your most mundane attacks erupt in a barrage of beautiful blasts. The magic comes in the unpredictable combinations you create. Exploding chain lightning is only the beginning of your frenetic masterpiece!<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/10_Potent_Pick_Ups___fireboots_2.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/11_Header_The_Dangers_of_Petrichor_V.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>The denizens of Petrichor V are as diverse as the many planets they once called home. As these monsters approached extinction on their own worlds, a mysterious force brought them to Petrichor V. The planet quickly grew to be a menagerie of the most dangerous monsters in the galaxy, and they’re not thrilled by interlopers (aka YOU).<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/12_Diversity_of_Environment.gif?t=1699995226"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/13_rule_bending_artifacts.gif?t=1699995226"><br/>Variety is the spice of destruction. Select from more than 10 Artifacts that each mutate your run! Perhaps you’d like to start with a random equipment item that changes every time it’s used, or maybe you’d like to experience a rampant Imp invasion every 10 minutes. Play around with combinations of Artifacts and discover exciting new ways to play.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1337520/extras/14_place_holder_gif_3_possible_artifact.gif?t=1699995226"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Core</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2179850/Cobalt_Core/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_1.gif?t=1701600866"><br/><br/>Cobalt Core is a sci-fi roguelike deckbuilder with a unique single-axis combat system that will throw you for a loop. Many loops! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/Cobalt_Core_Battle_Sequence_GIF_2.gif?t=1701600866"><br/><br/>Give orders to your crew by playing cards: Will you <strong>raise shields</strong> to protect your ship, <strong>dodge</strong> incoming missiles and cannon fire to avoid damage outright, or <strong>strike</strong> preemptively to disable your enemy’s weapons? Outmaneuver your foes to stay just ahead of impending calamity, and reach the Cobalt Core!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/characters.png?t=1701600866"><br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>Fresh new spin on tactics –</strong>  dodge attacks and target weak points in this unique single-axis take on tactics combat. Outwit the enemy in a high stakes game of cat and mouse!<br/></li><li><strong>Customize your deck –</strong> hundreds of cards and split upgrade paths means no two runs will be the same. Find that perfect combo that brings your deck from powerful to overpowered.<br/></li><li><strong>Get to know your crew –</strong> each character comes with a completely unique playstyle and their own personal story. Bring 3 along, mix and match their decks, and see how these little goobers get along with each other.<br/></li><li><strong>Tons of replayability –</strong>  hundreds of different character+ship combinations before you even hit “start run”. Crank up the difficulty and really test your skills!<br/></li><li><strong>Forward momentum –</strong> untangle a narrative and unlock more playstyles as you go. Is there any escape from this time loop?</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2179850/extras/grandma_cookies.gif?t=1701600866"><br/><br/>By the makers of <i>Sunshine Heavy Industries</i>, recipient of IGF's <strong>Honorable Mention for Excellence in Design 2022</strong>.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2375550/Like_a_Dragon_Gaiden_The_Man_Who_Erased_His_Name/?snr=1_239_new__145</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">DELUXE EDITION INCLUDES:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name<br/></li><li>Legendary Fighter Pack</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Legendary-Fighter-Pack-Steam.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Floating in the bay, away from the prying eyes of the public, is a mysterious container ship known as the Castle. At its center lies the Coliseum, and three legendary yakuza have entered the battle arena as playable characters.<br/><br/>Enter the Coliseum and play as or alongside:<br/><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Goro Majima – The Mad Dog of Shimano<br/></li><li>Taiga Saejima – The Slayer of Eighteen<br/></li><li>Daigo Dojima – 6th Chairman of the Tojo Clan</li></ul><br/>Claim victory with these allies in the ultimate showdown!<br/><br/><strong>ERASE YOUR PAST TO PROTECT YOUR FUTURE</strong><br/>Once a legendary yakuza, Kazuma Kiryu faked his own death and abandoned his name for the sake of protecting his family. Now, he is thrust into conflict by a mysterious figure attempting to drive him out of hiding.<br/><br/>Under the codename “Joryu,” Kiryu embarks on a gripping action narrative with bone-shattering combat in vibrant locations filled with exciting characters and activities.<br/><br/><strong>ULTIMATE COMBAT WITH TWO HIGH-IMPACT FIGHTING STYLES</strong><br/><br/>Dynamically switch between the Yakuza and Agent fighting styles in visceral melee combat.<br/><br/>With the Yakuza style, strike fear into enemies by unleashing wildly aggressive moves powered by Kiryu’s unparalleled strength and flair.<br/><br/>Or up the ante with the Agent style by delivering blows with absolute speed and precision, while using an array of high-tech gadgets like electrified bind wires to stun enemies then send them flying.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Ultimate_Combat_2.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Strategically adapt to the situation and leverage both styles to dominate and destroy hordes of enemies.<br/><br/><strong>ENDLESS ENTERTAINMENT</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2375550/extras/Endless_Entertainment.gif?t=1700648373"><br/><br/>Whether you're brawling in the secret Battle arena, singing a new karaoke song, enjoying a drink at the live-action cabaret club, or racing in the pocket circuit, the world offers a variety of immersive experiences. <br/><br/>An intriguing informant named Akame also provides thrilling sub-missions, drawing you into an epic showdown that unfolds the more you explore and enjoy Sotenbori and Yokohama.<br/><br/><strong>LIKE A DRAGON: INFINITE WEALTH SPECIAL TRIAL VERSION ALSO INCLUDED!</strong><br/>After completing Like a Dragon Gaiden: The Man Who Erased His Name game, a Like a Dragon: Infinite Wealth Special Trial Version will be unlocked for you to enjoy!<br/><br/><br/><i>This game may be updated over time and have paid for and free additional content released for it. Please be aware that this may increase the minimum requirements for running the game above the specification stated here</i><br/><br/><i>English voice will be implemented in a post-launch patch distribution</i> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Resistors</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2066490/Robot_Resistors/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2066490/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Robot Resistors is an action-packed survival rogue-lite that pits you against hordes of enemies who want nothing more than to rip out your circuits and send you to the scrap heap.<h2 class="bb_tag">Join the Resistance! </h2><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Explore strange and exotic locales and get a glimpse of the dark future that awaits robot-kind should you fail.  Featuring 5 unique stages, each procedurally-generated, with wildly different mechanics, hazards, moods, and objectives. <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2066490/extras/locales.gif?t=1701818644"> <br/></img></li><li>Over 100 unique enemies to outgun and outmaneuver, each with their own custom abilities, stats, and art.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2066490/extras/gif1.gif?t=1701818644"> <br/></img></li><li>Confront challenging bosses with unique designs and movesets<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2066490/extras/bosses.gif?t=1701818644"> <br/></img></li><li>Beautiful, 100% original pixel art abounds.  Step back in time to the glorious 90s, and enjoy the retro-style art and graphics.   <br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2066490/extras/gif3.gif?t=1701818644"> <br/></img></li><li>17 unlockable characters and counting, all with custom stats, abilities, and art.<br/></li><li>Collect salvage and purchase permanent upgrades to customize your characters and power them up for each run.<br/></li><li>More than 17 weapons with over 20 ultimate variations to unlock through gameplay challenges.<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2066490/extras/gif2.gif?t=1701818644"><br/></img></li><li>Absolutely ZERO microtransactions or DLC.  All future content will be free. </li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Survivalist</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2664260/Rogue_Survivalist/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2664260/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Choose your class - Knight, Mage, or Rogue - and embark on an epic journey! Take on hordes of enemies across 6 distinct maps as you level up, improve your character, and unlock unique abilities for each class. Level up, enhance your skills, and become the ultimate hero in this thrilling action RPG!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hans</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2671730/Hans/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671730/extras/Untitled_design.png?t=1701810947"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671730/extras/Untitled_video__3_.gif?t=1701810947"><br/><br/><i>Hans</i> is a visual novel baking simulator in which you play as an alien dropped off on Earth during World War 1, who bakes magical pastries to help the people in your small town. You can also choose not to make what they ask for, because sometimes their requests are not as thought out as they may think. Just be prepared, because your actions have eight endings worth of consequences!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671730/extras/Untitled_design__2_.png?t=1701810947"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671730/extras/Untitled_video__1_.gif?t=1701810947"><br/><br/><strong>Bake magical foods for the local townsfolk</strong><br/>In this moody handdrawn game, you have the power to help the townsfolk by baking magical pastries! Will you accept their requests?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671730/extras/Untitled_video.gif?t=1701810947"><br/><br/><strong>Summon aliens to obtain magical ingredients</strong><br/>Enter the mysterious cat shrine and tap into your magical powers as an alien to obtain a special ingredient to use in your baking. <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671730/extras/Untitled_video__2_.gif?t=1701810947"><br/><br/><strong>Help two friends fall in love</strong><br/>Addler is interested in their friend, Karl! Will you bake them some magical muffins to give them a boost of confidence and ask Karl out?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671730/extras/Untitled_design__1_.png?t=1701810947"><br/><br/>Hans is a passion project made in a few months by a handful of college students. Art is pencil on watercolor paper, colored and edited in Photoshop.<br/><br/>Designed together by Clei Barnhart and Elaine Toh. Produced by Clei Barnhart and David Contarino. Coding by Elaine Toh. Art and narrative by Clei Barnhart. Music by Fay Xu and Jacob Naumoski. Sound design and audio implementation by David Contarino. UI by Elaine Toh. Special thanks to Nicholas Linares and Marianne Zhou!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2671730/extras/USC_Games_Yellow_Logo.png?t=1701810947"> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowmen</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2325770/Snowmen/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325770/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Summary</h2><br/><strong>Snowmen </strong>is a <strong>fairy tale</strong> like short horror game where you must <strong>escape </strong>a hellish snowy environment by <strong>collecting </strong>unusual ingredients and avoiding otherworldly <strong>dangers</strong>!<h2 class="bb_tag">Gameplay</h2><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325770/extras/Signjump-Freeze-Steam.gif?t=1701805978"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Keep <strong>MOVING</strong>, as time is short and <strong>DANGER </strong>is close by!<br/></li><li><strong>COLLECT, COLLECT, COLLECT</strong> and... <strong>RUN</strong>!!!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325770/extras/Note-2-Steam.gif?t=1701805978"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>EXPLORE </strong>a seemingly infinite realm you are trapped in!<br/></li><li><strong>SEARCH </strong>and navigate with the help of <strong>LANDMARKS </strong>and <strong>AUDIO</strong> cues!</li></ul><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2325770/extras/TTS-2-Steam.gif?t=1701805978"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li><strong>INTERACT</strong> with the environment and its strange, yet familiar looking inhabitants to retrieve useful information!<br/></li><li><strong>CHOICES </strong>matter, so be wary about your actions!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Story</h2><br/>A fairy tale like short horror game where you get kicked out of your <strong>HOME</strong> for being very <strong>naughty</strong>!<br/><br/>You prepare for a journey to start a new life after the unfair and irresponsible treatment you witnessed!<br/>But things don't turn out as expected, as it is usually the case in life...<br/> <br/>This is different though... But it surely can't be <strong>bewitched</strong>, right? <br/>Especially not at this holy and blessed time full of love where you spend time with your close ones!!<br/><br/>...Oh wait. <br/><br/>That time is already behind you and so is your <strong>PATH</strong> ahead, as you are already lost. <br/>You are not alone though, for better or for worse.<br/><br/>...Probably worse.<br/><br/>Even the good old stories about the kind gift bringer seem to be all <strong>lies </strong>and can't be trusted either. <br/>So who can you trust in this <strong>cold nightmarish realm</strong>?<br/><br/>The only thing left is to <strong>keep MOVING</strong> forward and finding a way back. <br/>Hope just can't be all lost, right?!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sofi Origins</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695730/Sofi_Origins/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695730/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Sofi Origins is an adventure game of suspense and terror where you become Sofi, a girl with a very sad past, yet possessing powers in her world.<br>
<br>
With Sofi, we will experience tense and terrifying moments where we'll need to focus, using special mechanics of accuracy to unleash her powers. But that's not all; you'll have to be very clever and skilled to escape, jump, and solve puzzles. This will lead us to uncover the story of a girl who lived through a hellish experience.<br>
<br>
Do you dare to face the past?<br>
<br>
Features:<br/>
<br/>
■ Skill mechanics for walking, running, jumping, and dodging.<br/>
■ Special accuracy mechanics.<br/>
■ A unique way to experience a sad and captivating story.<br/>
■ Moments and gaming styles that will surprise.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Box VR: Escape The Room</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2700460/Mystery_Box_VR_Escape_The_Room/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/h1.png?t=1701804585"><br/>Interact with bizarre mechanisms, think out of the box to gain your freedom, and discover historical mysteries<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/1.gif?t=1701804585"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/h2.png?t=1701804585"><br/>You will experience a real-life adventure while playing this puzzle game! Lots of intriguing puzzles are waiting for you, ensuring an immersive experience that will keep you engaged for hours<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/h3.png?t=1701804585"><br/>Examine several mechanisms to unlock each box and gain your freedom<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/level.png?t=1701804585"><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/h4.png?t=1701804585"><br/>For an unforgettable experience, immerse yourself in the adventure by playing the game with your headphones on!<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/h5.png?t=1701804585"><br/>Get hints that will help you through the game. If you really can't make it, you may still get in touch with the developer, who will be happy to help ;)<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/h6.png?t=1701804585"><br/>This is an extra challenge that will keep your brain busy for days. Open the letter inside the Enigmas Box and crack a new riddle every day. How far can you go?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/eb.gif?t=1701804585"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/h5.png?t=1701804585"><br/>Available in English, French, Italian, German, Spanish, Russian, and Japanese.<br/><br/><i>The game language will change automatically based on the language settings of your device</i><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2700460/extras/xslogo.png?t=1701804585"><br/>XSGames is a solo indie game developer from Italy. I self-published the first Mystery Box chapter on the app stores in 2021 and was amazed by the awesome success it had with mobile game players.<br/>Such results changed my life, so I hope you'll enjoy playing the Mystery Box escape room adventures as much as I love making them!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Anacrusis</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1120480/The_Anacrusis/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Battle for survival against endless alien hordes with your friends! From the lead for Left 4 Dead and L4D2, The Anacrusis is a 1-8 player, sci-fi first-person shooter. Experience intense 4 player co-op action or play as the aliens and stop your friends in Versus mode. Now with Steam Workshop support!<h2 class="bb_tag">Fight Aliens Using Fantastical Weapons </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Weapons.png?t=1701799902"><br/>Battle the alien menace using an astounding arsenal of classic sci-fi weapons. Buy yourself some time with a stasis grenade, toss a shield grenade to provide instant cover while you pop off a heal, and bring your friends back to life using the Respawner. Or throw caution to the wind and burn friend and foe alike with the laser rifle.<h2 class="bb_tag">Play As The Aliens in PVP Versus Mode!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Design_Steam_Versus_Header.png?t=1701799902"><br/>PVP comes to The Anacrusis! The goals are simple, Survivors need to reach the end of the level and the Aliens must keep them from their goal. Take control of the Brute, Flasher, Grabber, Gooper, and Spawner (with more special Aliens to come) and keep your friends from escaping the level. Tuned for intense co-op PVP play with teams of 2, 3, or 4 players, or take on the bots in a private match to practice playing the aliens.<h2 class="bb_tag">Survive the Alien Infestation!</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Horde.png?t=1701799902"><br/>In the distant future, mighty corporations have carried humanity to the fringes of the galaxy. After expanding unfettered across tens of thousands of systems--all devoid of intelligent life--humanity has grown complacent, until disaster strikes. Work together and survive the alien hordes!<h2 class="bb_tag">A Fight For Survival Is Just the Beginning</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Survivors.png?t=1701799902"><br/>The first season of The Anacrusis tells the story of four unlikely survivors--Nessa, Guion, Liu, and Lance--who are unwilling combatants in the battle to defend humanity from the alien menace. Play more and unlock more of the unfolding mystery of the alien attack.<h2 class="bb_tag">Never Fight the Same Battle Twice</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Director.png?t=1701799902"><br/>In The Anacrusis, the AI Driver controls every aspect of the game. It spawns every enemy, directs each boss, and places every weapon, gadget, and health kit. No matter your skill level, you'll find the perfect level of challenge. More than that, the AI Driver creates the kinds of video game moments that you can’t wait to tell your friends about.<h2 class="bb_tag">Join the Community</h2><a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fstraybombay" rel="noopener" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Community.png?t=1701799902"/></a><br/>We've posted 35 updates to The Anacrusis since launch, and we couldn't have done it without our incredible community of Early Access players. <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fstraybombay" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join the Discord</a> and share your feedback with us. Or check the <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Ftrello.com%2Fb%2FjcUa92HH%2Fthe-anacrusis-roadmap" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Roadmap</a> to see what's coming next!<h2 class="bb_tag">We Love Mods! </h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Mods.png?t=1701799902"><br/>We think co-op games are better with mods, which is why The Anacrusis includes Steam Workshop support for new campaigns, holdout maps, character skins, character accessories, gun charms, and animations, with more to come. Even better, the mods you load are automatically displayed for your friends to see when you play the game. Want to create mods for The Anacrusis? <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fdiscord.gg%2Fstraybombay" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Join our Discord</a> for updates and conversation about mod support.<h2 class="bb_tag">Earn New Perks and Change the Way You Play</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1120480/extras/Steam_Detail-Headers_Perks.png?t=1701799902"><br/>Matter compilers spread throughout the game give you access to dozens of perks that will change the way you play. Stack all of your upgrades to power up the last-resort pistol or boost your defense by supercharging your shield pulse. Unlock new perks as you play, and share your unlocks with everyone on your team!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Praise Dead</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2459180/Praise_Dead/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459180/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Praise Dead is a roguelike auto-battler where you create minions from the parts of dead villagers and monsters. Collect relics that power up your zombies. And defend the town from the nightly demonic incursions that threaten to slay us all.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459180/extras/Battle.gif?t=1701799564"><br/><br/>Place your minions on the perfect squares to maximize returns on resources - their stats dictate how much iron they mine, food they produce and villagers they can recruit!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459180/extras/WorkerPlacement.gif?t=1701799564"><br/><br/>Create the perfect minion for fighting, farming, or recruiting more villagers - each part has unique attributes that you can combine together.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459180/extras/CreateZombies.gif?t=1701799564"><br/><br/>Purchase powerful Relics that will greatly empower your minions for fighting and resource gathering<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2459180/extras/Relics.gif?t=1701799564"><br/><br/><strong>Help defend the village as a semi-evil-semi-good necromancer today!</strong><h2 class="bb_tag">Planned road map</h2><br/>1.0.5 - Balance updates, bug fixes, extra polish, QOL updates based on community request.<br/><br/>1.1 - Power to the player: new relics, new weapons, new armor, and new spells.<br/><br/>1.2 - Free DLC - Demonic uprising - new bosses, new demons, new demon parts to add to zombies, more ritual levels.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born of Bread</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1555140/Born_of_Bread/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Beings from another age are causing havoc across the land! And with their mischief comes a great threat to everyone. The unlikeliest hero, a golem born of bread, will find himself and his newfound buddies in the middle of a drama that's thousands of years in the making. Together, they will visit incredible locals and meet fascinating characters. Although he may not look like much, Loaf might be the hero this land kneads.<h2 class="bb_tag">A Sentient Bread on a Quest</h2><br/>Play as a flour golem who possesses a never-ending childlike wonder and a set of odd abilities in this 2.5D adventure game!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Cinematic_opti.gif?t=1701805959"><br/><br/>Explore the different regions of a wonderful world ripe with mysteries and team up with a colorful cast of fleshed-out characters. With the help of your buddies, face off against menacing and weird baddies and engage in a fun and quirky turn-based combat system.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Enviro_opti.gif?t=1701805959"><br/><br/><strong>A home-cooked battle system</strong><br/>Born of Bread puts a twist on turn-based combat tropes with a fun interaction system that will test your reflexes.<br/>This interactive system also features a weaknesss and resistance system that makes battles more strategic.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Combat_Opti.gif?t=1701805959"><br/><br/><strong>Team up with your buddies</strong><br/>Loaf can't do it alone. Meet new characters during your adventure, each with their own abilities and personnality. Use their unique skills to overcome threats and obstacles whether in fights or when exploring.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1555140/extras/Buddies_opti.gif?t=1701805959"><br/><br/><strong>Stream your fights to a fake audience!</strong><br/>Your dragon buddy Dub will let you save your progression but also stream your fights to a fake audience with his little laptop! Gather more viewers and answer their demand to get rewards!						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingpin: Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1224700/Kingpin_Reloaded/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1224700/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Welcome to Kingpin: Reloaded</h2><br/>In a stylized noir art deco gangland that never was, the Kingpin rules above all else with a bloody fist. When his lieutenant Nikki Blanco leaves a no-name thug battered and broken, the upstart criminal rises from a puddle of blood pipe in hand and revenge in mind. <br/><br/>Kingpin: Reloaded brings new life to the Quake II engine classic. 4K resolution and improved graphics in Enhanced mode enable the beautifully-depicted metropolitan nightmare to shine. Controller support makes the game more accessible for anyone wanting to explore the depths of Kingpin’s depravity. Improvements like new quest and conversation systems make Reloaded even better than the original.<br/><br/>Stalk lamp-lit streets and take down rival gangs to let the Kingpin know his end is nigh. Kingpin’s immersive sim elements allow you to recruit other gangsters and increase your influence through multiple hub-based missions. Run with the gang on a violent warpath with upgradeable weapons. Location-based damage leads to bloody, thrilling battles: kneecap, maim, or go for the head.<br/><br/><strong>Kingpin: Reloaded includes a range of new features:</strong><br/><br/>- Re-balanced and Polished gameplay<br/>- New Quest System<br/>- Ultrawide and 4k Support<br/>- Classic and Enhanced modes<br/><br/>And so much more!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ungate</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2601620/Ungate/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2601620/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>UNGATE</strong><br/>In this narative, first-person, survival horror game, the action is about a young man named Jason, who follows the steps of his friends to find them and to get them out of a mysterious cave that has its own ecosystem and is known by the locals of the West Village as the gate of hell. By doing so, he will find himself trapped into a dark place that is the home of the dark creatures and dark presences that will try to kill him and turn his soul into a servant of darkness. Along his way of gathering more clues, he will face constant horror scenes and unbearable tension, that are meant to block him from getting to the source of the evil and put an end to the nightmare. After he will face the dark creatures both on the surface and underground, Jason will finally find out if he can survive one last terror.<br/><br/><strong>STORY</strong><br/>IN THE PAST, a group of scientists discovered that the center of the world’s energy is in the cave of the Black Mountains. The government decided to send a military research team to investigate but instead of getting to the core, they found another world hiding in the dark. The cave was strangely big and it had its own sky and a lake of blood that was burning your skin. The event was unusual and after they decided to navigate on the lake, they found a mysterious cabin at the other side of the shore, like someone was actually living there. Everything was so bizarre that the government decided to build a military base to study that strange occurence. Within 66 days, all the people involved in the project disappeared along with that cave except one. Dr. John Ellis was outside the cave at that time trying to reach the research team but he couldn’t find the entrance anymore. Following the disappearance he found that the black mountains represents the point where other worlds collide. Also, the locals of the West Village located at the base of the mountains told Dr. John Ellis that the cave found inside the Black Mountains is a gate of hell. Even if you escape from that cave your soul will be taken sooner or later. According to the legend, it appears once every 66 years for 66 days and everyone that gets trapped in, is not getting back. After several days, the doctor died in strange circumstances and nobody went to that cave again for 66 years.<br/>IN THE PRESENT, as tourists in the West Village, you and your friends found about the legend of the gate of hell. Despite the warnings of the locals and your disapproval, your friends decided to go visit that place without you. The last time you saw them, they were heading to the cave to find out if the rumors are true. After extensive research about the legend, you discovered that there is only 1 day left until the cave will disappear. Desperate, you tried to get someone’s help but the locals are afraid of searching for your friends and the authorities are not coming. Knowing the danger that awaits them, you decided to go get them back before it's too late.<br/><br/><strong>KEY FEATURES</strong><br/>TERRIFYING CREATURES: There are many dark creatures within the game. Some of them are sensitive to light and some of them are sensitive to sounds. You should use your skills to avoid them and survive.<br/>THERE'S NO COMBAT: Instead of engaging in combat, you must rely on your skills to avoid the creatures and survive. You'll have only your headlamp and supplies you'll find along the way to help you outrun and escape from the creatures.<br/>STEALTH: You can use your tactics to avoid being noticed or detected by some creatures, enhancing your chances of survival.<br/>STRATEGY: You should strategize to light your way and orient yourself within the dark.<br/>SURVIVE AND EXPLORE: The game also promises bone-chilling scenes that will evoke fear and challenges for you to overcome. Can you survive until the end?						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While the Iron's Hot</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1906830/While_the_Irons_Hot/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/WTIH_Steam_Banner_Game_Header__1_.png?t=1701795624"><br/><br/>In the faraway land of Ellian, legendary artisans have gathered for ages to perfect their craft. Now it’s your turn to join them.<br/><br/>Step into the boots of a journeyman blacksmith on a quest to become a master in While the Iron’s Hot, a crafty adventure assembled with mystery, wit, and charm. Forge, smelt, and combine works of metal to grow your smithing skills and discover exquisite new items to create. Explore an island filled with resources, treasures, puzzles, and fellow artisans with their own motives and designs. Rebuild the ruins of Ellian’s long-abandoned blacksmiths’ village to restore its former glory and grow your own crafting capabilities—and ultimately become a true master smith.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/Village_Upgrade_Gif_-_640x360.gif?t=1701795624"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/WTIH_Steam_Banner_Features__1_.png?t=1701795624"><br/><br/><strong>Forge, smelt, assemble</strong><br/>Master every step of the smithing process. Smelt ore and metal into ingots, and shape them into useful parts. Grind each piece to perfection, then use your creativity, knowledge, and finely honed observation skills to assemble alloyed works of art.<br/><br/><strong>Smith a solution</strong><br/>In a land of artisans, you can forge your own key to almost any challenge. Repair machinery to open up pathways. Overcome puzzling environmental conundrums. Win over the isle’s most hardened personalities with your crafty smithing wiles.<br/><br/><strong>Unearth a whimsical adventure</strong><br/>The land of Ellian is a bright, even a little mystical, world populated by charismatic and quirky characters. Explore tunnels with puzzles and resources, and embark on a combat-free journey to reforge the links of a world where crafting connects everything.<br/><br/><strong>Discover the island’s secrets</strong><br/>Ellian is a land of creativity cloaked in mystery. Craft the equipment you need to venture out to new regions. Meet villages full of adept alchemists or skilled shipwrights, but take care—not everyone trusts that you have the best interests of Ellian at heart.<br/><br/><strong>Rebuild a legendary smiths’ village</strong><br/>Forge a new home in Stal, a former haven for blacksmiths, now in ruin following a mysterious disaster. Revitalize the village to upgrade your own capabilities, and prove to the artisans of Ellian you’re worthy of becoming a master blacksmith.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1906830/extras/Environment_Gif_-_634x356.gif?t=1701795624"> </img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chessarama</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1831830/Chessarama/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1831830/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Chessarama is a collection of original puzzle and strategy games inspired by Chess. It reimagines chess rules and tactics using many different themes. Each game has its own set of rules, visual theme and original handcrafted challenges for you to play!<h2 class="bb_tag">Key Features:</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> Play 8 exclusive chess-inspired games available in Chessarama;<br/></li><li> Puzzle campaigns featuring 100+ levels plus 100+ unique challenges;<br/></li><li> 24 exclusive Chess Figures to unlock and collect;<br/></li><li> Unique art style, with beautiful dioramas;<br/></li><li> Daily and Weekly Challenges;<br/></li><li> Compete against each other on the leaderboards;<br/></li><li> Learn chess movements, tactics and strategies through a modern video game experience;<br/></li><li> Also includes “Classic Chess” for you to put your learnings into practice!</li></ul><h2 class="bb_tag">Many Chess Worlds for You to Explore!</h2><br/>Here are all the original games you will find in Chessarama: (1) Farm Life; (2) Dragon Slayers; (3) Street Soccer; (4) Lady Ronin; (5) Last Stand; (6) Knight Supreme; (7) Pawn Mania; (8) Soccer Chess.<br/><br/>Take a look at some of the Chessarama games:<br/><br/>In <strong>Dragon Slayer</strong>, you need to push your pawn to the end of a path in order to kill the mighty dragon. But it will not be that easy! The dragon attacks the board every time the pawn moves and every undefended piece will die.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1831830/extras/Gif-Dragon.gif?t=1701802466"><br/><br/>In <strong>Lady Ronin</strong>, Chess meets Sokoban. You play with a Ronin (a chess queen) and you <br/>need to eliminate the other pieces in order to get close to the Shogun and kill it. Pieces move like in chess, but push each other like in sokoban.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1831830/extras/Gif-Ronin.gif?t=1701802466"><br/><br/>In <strong>Soccer Chess</strong> you will play a soccer match using chess pieces. You will need to think a few moves ahead if you want to break through the adversary's defenses to score a goal.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1831830/extras/Gif-Soccer.gif?t=1701802466"><br/><br/>This is just some examples about how Chess can be reinvented. Welcome to Chessarama!						</img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arashi: Castles of Sin - Final Cut</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2434420/Arashi_Castles_of_Sin__Final_Cut/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2434420/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take on the role of the deadly assassin Kenshiro as you travel across feudal Japan to defeat the Six Oni of Iga, a bandit group spreading chaos across the land. Through a wide variety of weapons, tools, and techniques, you’ll infiltrate conquered castles and outwit your enemies as you hunt down each Oni. <br/><br/>With your cousin Ayane providing guidance back at base and your loyal wolf Haru on the field, prove yourself as the ultimate warrior and save Japan. <br/><br/><strong>VR’s Award Winning Stealth-Action Experience</strong><br/>Using the innovations of Next-Gen VR hardware, immerse yourself in the ultimate shinobi fantasy. Leap from rooftop to rooftop, hide in shadows and perform lethal sneak attacks, survive impossible odds in sword combat, and vanish from the scene just as quickly as you arrived. Heightened graphical fidelity and carefully tuned controls make each new battle more engaging than the last. <br/><br/><strong>Become an Oni Slayer </strong><br/>Each castle you conquer is capped off with an exciting battle against one of the Six Oni. Each bandit leader is a unique combatant both in style, personality, and abilities, putting your mastery of the sword to the test. Prove yourself against these fearsome foes as you hone your skills with each new encounter. <br/><br/><strong>Haru, a Samurai's Best Friend</strong><br/>Your mission for justice is not one you take alone. With your canine companion Haru by your side, praised for her advanced AI and usefulness, Arashi brings a unique sense of companionship not found in other VR titles. Haru will be an ally you won’t soon forget as you take down opponents together throughout each new dangerous location. <br/><br/><strong>The Arsenal of a Ninja</strong><br/>No assassin is complete without a wide set of tools at their disposal. Customize your arsenal as you see fit before each mission with blades, grenades, mines, arrows, blowguns, pistols, and more! Whether you want to make it through unscathed and unseen, or want to face your enemies head-on with style, your choices are always supported.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Highland Song</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1240060/A_Highland_Song/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Works beautifully on Steam Deck!</h2><i>We're still waiting for Valve to officially verify A Highland Song for Steam Deck, but we've designed it from the ground up to work perfectly there. So if that's your preferred platform, you're in for a treat!</i><h2 class="bb_tag">Moira McKinnon is running away.</h2>To reach the sea, Moira must first cross the Scottish Highlands—a wilderness of paths, peaks, shortcuts, dangers, and song.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/waterfall-jump.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Platforming</h2>Climb peaks to orient yourself and plan your next steps. Spelunk caves, scale cliffs, jump from rock to rock and slide down scree slopes as you make your way forward.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/survival.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Survival</h2>Wind, rain and cold are your enemies. Moira is no superhero, and the Highlands are not to be underestimated. Shelter to survive.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/ascend-peak-shorter.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Navigation</h2>Collect and position 100 map fragments to discover faster routes. The hills are crisscrossed with paths: some well-trodden, others hidden away.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/narrative.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Narrative</h2>Learn the stories and the secrets of the hills, which are filled with lost things, echoes, and memories.<br/><br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/music-run-sunrise.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Rhythm runs</h2>Skip and jump through the valleys to the incredible music of TALISK and Fourth Moon. The landscape itself forms itself around the shape of the music.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/branching-paths.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">Replay</h2>Get ready to make the journey more than once, because a single trip isn't nearly enough to discover the Highlands' deepest secrets.<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/moira-and-deer.png?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Story</h2>Moira McKinnon has never seen the sea. <br/><br/>For fifteen years she’s lived with her mum in a small house on the edge of the Scottish Highlands—then one day she receives a letter from her Uncle Hamish urging her to come to the coast. If she can reach his lighthouse in time, a wonderful surprise will be waiting...<br/> <br/>And so, Moira runs away.<br/><br/>The hills are full of secrets and stories, but what you find will depend on where you go. The narrative is not branching but weaving; a mesh of history, mythology and family secrets. What truths will you discover? <br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/zoom-to-lighthouse.gif?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">The World</h2>In the Highlands, every peak has a story to tell and every valley echoes with song. Giants sleep, ghosts sing, crows carry messages, and eagles lift the dead. <br/><br/>But the Highlands’ crags are unforgiving and its summits are cold—Moira’s trek will not be easy. <br/><br/>Can you help her find a way across this winding wilderness in time?<br/><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1240060/extras/talisk.jpg?t=1701791974"><h2 class="bb_tag">The Music of the Highlands</h2>A Highland Song’s soundtrack is composed by Laurence Chapman alongside two multi-award-winning giants of the Scottish folk scene, TALISK and Fourth Moon. Royalty of the festival circuit, these two bands combine virtuosic instrumental playing with fast, inventive rhythms, to produce new tunes in traditional styles played with beauty, energy and swagger.						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Power</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2680610/Universal_Power/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2680610/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Universal Power is a single/multiplayer game with unique World design, Weapons, Play styles, Animations, Story and more...<br>
You can play Universal Power Alone or with your Friends.<br>
Universal Power has over 7 play styles and many different ways to play.<br>
we will be adding NEW maps, Weapons, modes and fixing bugs so players can have a better more fun experience.<br>
<br>
Gameplay: The gameplay of universal power is a third person warrior With different swords, katanas and many abilities.<br>
in game you can choose your weapons based on how YOU want to play the game.<br/>
you want to play in stealth mode no worry you can Assassinate your enemies from behind.<br/>
you want to go and fight everyone no worries go get the best weapons and fight every one.<br/>
Also you can stop time with your abilities and fight everyone at the same time.<br/>
<br/>
(warnings) Universal Power contains blood Act of violence and killing.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tram Simulator Urban Transit</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2546690/Tram_Simulator_Urban_Transit/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2546690/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Welcome to Tram Simulator Urban Transit - get on aboard! In this game, you take on the role of a tram driver and manager in Angel Shores, the North American-themed city from the popular bus simulator game Bus Simulator 21 Next Stop. Drive 6 unique tram models, each boasting its distinctive style, from cutting-edge, sleek trams to those with a classic, timeless charm through the lively city with its numerous sights. Transport passengers with your trams and drive them to the numerous stops. Plan your own routes, carefully manage your timetables, and expand your tram network.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Home: Look and Find Collector's Edition</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2701630/Sweet_Home_Look_and_Find_Collectors_Edition/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2701630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Avi Games presents an all-new series for newcomers and seasoned hidden-object seekers with Sweet Home: Look and Find!<br>
<br>
Immerse yourself in the comfort and tranquility of home as you relax and enjoy finding objects, solving puzzles, and conquering mini-games in this cozy and clever new game! Take a walk in nature, sit by the pool, and barbecue in the backyard while you hone your skills and complete each challenging level! While you're here, customize your room with decorative items and furnishings, purchase items from a vast inventory, and fill your space with beauty and luxury! Welcome home!<br>
<br>
This is a special Collector's Edition release full of exclusive extras:<br>
<br>
* Stay home and keep the fun going with eight exclusive locations!<br/>
* Download gorgeous wallpapers to beautify your own space!<br/>
* Mellow out with the exclusive music player!<br/>
* Eight bonus and replayable mini-games just for you!						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arms Race 2</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2284800/Arms_Race_2/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2284800/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Feeling bored while waiting? Why not support our development efforts by playing "The Cold War Era"? - <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/10404/The_Cold_War_Era_Bundle/" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/bundle/10404/The_Cold_War_Era_Bundle/</a><br/><br/>Arms Race 2 is a turn-based strategy game based on the events of the Cold War between the Americans and the Soviets, spanning the 1950s through the 1990s. In just a few hours of gameplay, players will immerse themselves in five decades of contention, paranoia, secrecy, proxy wars, and the overarching "us vs. them" mentality.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2284800/extras/banner1.png?t=1701788930"><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1264830/The_Cold_War_Era_2" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1264830/The_Cold_War_Era_2</a><br/><br/>Here's what sets Arms Race 2 apart from other war-based strategy games:<br/><br/>Immerse yourself in a realistic atmosphere that retells the story of the Cold War.<br/>Choose your side and play as either the Americans or the Soviets to rewrite history.<br/>Deploy military and espionage units to support allied governments or transform rebels into revolutionaries in opposing countries.<br/>Establish spy networks to bolster government propaganda campaigns or undermine the opposition's stronghold.<br/>Launch rockets, satellites, and astronauts or cosmonauts into space to astonish the world and prove your superiority.<br/>Devise your own strategies and tactics, forcing your opponent to play by your rules.<br/>Organize pro-government parades or incite riots to plunge countries into chaos.<br/>Experience the technological, nuclear, arms, and space races through historic units, models, and names.<br/>Encounter global consequences from historical international events that impact both superpowers and neutral regions.<br/>Utilize powerful UN decisions to intervene in other countries or protect them from your foe's intervention.<br/>Access a comprehensive database with pictures of influential politicians from both superpowers' governments.<br/>Vote and establish your government with its own specific characteristics, such as politicians' skills and conservative or liberal views.<br/>Experience industrialization, which promotes international cooperation within your alliance and enhances your gaming score.<br/><br/>GAME EXPERIENCE:<br/><br/>Arms Race 2 offers an easy-to-play experience suitable for gamers of all ages and skill levels. In-game tutorials and user-friendly menus provide information on:<br/><br/>Players' influence in each country and worldwide.<br/>Opponents' influence in influenced, neutral, and opposing countries.<br/>Number of military units stationed in each country.<br/>Spy network status and propaganda campaign success.<br/>Player's budget, which can be used to enact your regime.<br/>Nuclear, arms, and space race milestones, which contribute to global influence and firepower.<br/>Score values for each country, used to calculate a player's budget.<br/>Total score as game events unfold.<br/>Political and global consequence points—use them wisely, as they are limited.<br/>Firepower for military and geographic landscape—truly lead an arms race!<br/><br/>WHAT'S NEW?<br/><br/>Arms Race 2 is the sequel to Arms Race - The Cold War Era game, developed and released by Alina Digital. Arms Race 2 incorporates the core AR-TCWE game mechanics and all DLCs. AR2 has been graphically redesigned to provide an improved user interface experience. Additionally, new features have been added to AR2, including highly requested changes to the community's favorite game mechanic, Global Consequences.						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood West</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_steam_text_header.png?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>Weird West legends meet eldritch horror in <strong>BLOOD WEST</strong>, an immersive stealth FPS. Become the Undead Gunslinger, doomed to roam the barren lands until he finds the means to purge their curse and free his soul. No, this isn’t your typical Wild West desperado redemption arc. This is a damnation arc.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_episodes_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Canyons, the Swamp, and the Mountains. Each swarming with abominable monsters and unholy demons, these are open-ended worlds for you to explore freely at your own pace. It will take the player over 20 hours on average to complete all three scenarios, and over 35 if they want to see everything the barren lands have to offer.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_stealth_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/><strong>Blood West</strong> is a stealth FPS inspired by the genre classics such as the Thief series (whose fans will be happy to hear the voice of Stephen Russell, the actor voicing the master-thief Garrett, returning here as the protagonist), S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games, or - from the contemporary catalog - Hunt: Showdown. The gameplay rewards the careful approach: scouting the area, stalking your enemies, and striking from the shadows. Can you figure out a way to clear a fort full of ghouls and monsters without raising an alarm?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_horror_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The Barren Lands present the player with a nightmarish, twisted vision of the Wild West legends. The curse that has befallen the realm has corrupted every living thing, defiled the land itself, while summoning restless spirits and dark entities. In this mixture of gunslinger pulp and Lovecraftian horror, dark occult magick presents just as much of a threat as sudden lead poisoning.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_characters_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>In <strong>Blood West</strong> you will meet many colorful, yet strangely twisted, fully-voiced NPCs. Just as much prisoners of the Barren Lands as you are, they will sometimes share their unusual stories and send you on various missions. Play nice and they might reward you or become your allies. Cross them and risk their wrath.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_secrets_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The game won’t hold your hand. You’ll have to explore the land for yourself (buying a map from a vendor might prove useful!), and figure out your own way to approach quests. As you poke around the three expansive maps, keep an eye out for hidden places and secret stashes. There’s gold in the mountains! Fair warning - it’s probably cursed.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_brutal_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>If sneaking around isn’t exactly your thing, or you feel that you have a power advantage over your enemies, you can always take the head-on approach and meet your enemies guns blazing. <strong>Blood West</strong> comes from the creators of the fan-favorite boomer shooter <strong>POSTAL: Brain Damaged</strong>, so much gratuitous fantasy violence and pixelated blood splatter is to be expected!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_inventory_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>One man’s hell might be another hoarder’s paradise! From simple one-use items like bandages, through medical tinctures, explosives and incendiaries, straight to arcane artifacts that - once slotted - can change the way you play the game, the Barren Lands are just filled with STUFF. There are tons of useful items to discover, and there’s a special player’s stash crate for all those super-rare potions that you’ll hoard and never use.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_weapons_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>A gunslinger without a gun would be just a regular slinger. Where’s the fun in that? <strong>Blood West</strong> makes sure you’ll have plenty of weapons to choose from. Revolvers, rifles, shotguns, carabines - a great variety of firearms, from standard army-issue to those infused with powerful magic, or straight-up possessed. And if you prefer not to cause a ruckus, there’s a wide selection of hand-to-hand combat weapons and archery weapons to pick your favorites from.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1587130/extras/BLOOD_WEST_GIF_skills_EN.gif?t=1701798296"><br/><br/>The RPG-like perk-based progression system in <strong>Blood West</strong> will allow you to highly customize the gameplay experience to your liking. Become a stealthy hunter, a revolver-fanning gunman or a relentless berserker. You will gain experience and progress through the skill tree, while discovering new artifacts in each of the scenarios that will bestow on you additional abilities. Combining skills and load-out creates more possible playstyles than you’d normally be able to explore in one playthrough.<h2 class="bb_tag">Are you ready to take back the frontier from the dark forces of demonic corruption and earn the right to move on to a better world? The Barren Lands call you, Gunslinger!</h2><br/><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/" id="dynamiclink_0" rel="" target="_blank">https://store.steampowered.com/app/1587130/Blood_West/</a> </img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legends of Amberland II: The Song of Trees</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2110840/Legends_of_Amberland_II_The_Song_of_Trees/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2110840/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">Overview:</h2>Legends of Amberland II: The Song of Trees is a classic western RPG inspired by the games from the 90s like Might &amp; Magic, Wizardry, Ultima, the Gold Box series and others. Using the classic first-person perspective, over grid movement, turn-based system to travel in an open world with fast travel options and a quick combat.<br/><br/><br/>You lead a party of 7 adventurers, manually assembled or pre-made, on an epic adventure to fight the evil which lurks in Amberland. It's light, fairy tale, epic, heroic and slightly humorous. It does not take tons of hours to complete or require an endless grind to progress. Basically, it's a love letter from the 90s, the golden era of RPGs.<h2 class="bb_tag">Notable features:</h2><br/>* First person perspective, 90 degree rotation, over grid movement (like in the 90s).<br/>* Turn-based (both combat and exploration).<br/>* Party-based (7 heroes, either predefined or manually assembled upon new game).<br/>* Fast paced combat, especially blazing fast against much weaker enemies.<br/>* Quick travel to reduce backtracking.<br/>* Easy inventory management with separate personal equipment encumbrance system and an infinite magic bag of carrying for items not equipped at the moment.<br/>* Open world with a big overworld to explore.<br/>* Quests (including both main storyline quests and side quests).<br/>* Rich world lore (spanning between all games of the series, but no knowledge of prior games required).<h2 class="bb_tag">Technicalities:</h2>The game was designed to look and feel like one of the old games while working flawlessly on modern machines, especially on very high resolutions. It has very low hardware requirements and should run on even very old machines.<h2 class="bb_tag">About the relation to other games in the series:</h2>The Legends of Amberland titles can be played in any order you wish. They share the same world and lore (historical events) but each has a separate and self-contained story. There might be some mild references to events in the previous titles of the series, but more like a flavor, so it does not hinder the ability to play those in any order.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Dreamlight Valley</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1401590/Disney_Dreamlight_Valley/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Disney Dreamlight Valley is a hybrid between a life-sim and an adventure game rich with quests, exploration, and engaging activities featuring Disney and Pixar friends, both old and new.  <br/><br/>Once an idyllic land, Dreamlight Valley was a place where Disney and Pixar characters lived in harmony—until the Forgetting. Night Thorns grew across the land and severed the wonderful memories tied to this magical place. With nowhere else to go, the hopeless inhabitants of Dreamlight Valley retreated behind locked doors in the Dream Castle.<br/><br/>Now it’s up to you to discover the stories of this world and bring the magic back to Dreamlight Valley!<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Discover the Secrets Of Dreamlight Valley</strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Pillar_600x200_v3.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Dream Castle from the insidious grip of the Forgetting, and unlock the unique Realms of well-loved Disney and Pixar characters, including great queens and kings such as Anna and Simba. Each Realm contains unique challenges with puzzles to solve in the quest to bring friendship back to the Valley.  <br/><br/>You’ll start your adventure in the Valley, but your journey will take you to infinity… and beyond! Explore what lurks in the Forest of Valor and brave the deepest caverns as you take on challenges from iconic Disney and Pixar heroes and villains. Who knows who—or what—you might discover.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Forge friendships with Disney &amp; Pixar characters </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_Garden_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Garden with WALL•E, cook with Remy or kick back and fish with Goofy. What better way to collect, craft, and rebuild the Valley than with a friend! From beautiful princesses to nefarious villains, every Dreamlight Valley resident brings their own story arc, quests, and rewards. Meet up in daily hangouts and make friends with some of your favorite Disney and Pixar characters..<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Restore the Valley to its former glory </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/GIF_House_Slow_600x200.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Free the Valley from the grip of the Forgetting and return Dreamlight Valley to its former greatness by making it your own. In Dreamlight Valley, you can build the perfect neighborhood that is just for you with a fully customizable layout, creative landscaping, and thousands of decorative items. <br/><br/>Will you settle on the Beach next to Moana, or call Buzz Lightyear your next-door neighbor in the Plaza?<h2 class="bb_tag"><h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>Express Your Disney Style </strong></h2></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220614_22043_V_ProductDescriptionGIFsExpress_A_01_ON01_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>Bring out your inner princess, villain, or Disney bounder! Assemble unique outfits and decorate your home with thousands of fantastic items. Using the Touch of Magic tool, you can even create your own designs with Disney- and Pixar-inspired decals! <br/><br/>With the in-game Camera, get ready to snap a sunset selfie with Mirabel, capture a culinary creation with Remy, or simply cherish a moment.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>A Game In Constant Evolution </strong></h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1401590/extras/DDV_220714_22043_V_ProdGIF_Evolution_A_01_ON02_ST_EN__1_.gif?t=1701785134"><br/>New content means that there's always something fresh to explore. Meet new characters in the Valley, check out the latest clothing and furniture collections in Scrooge’s Store, and complete challenging in-game events! Be sure to dream your way back to Dreamlight Valley regularly to discover new adventures!						</img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake Galaxy Online</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2668440/Snake_Galaxy_Online/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2668440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Snake Galaxy Online is the first of many other games that Vivid Unity Games want to bring to Steam. We welcome you to the family and hope you enjoy and have fun with our work.<br>
<br>
Adventure awaits you in Snake Galaxy Online!<br>
<br>
Snake Galaxy Online offers the soul of the classic Snake but fully adapted to modernity. Your mission is to defy the wrath of an intergalactic monster to save your friends. <br>
<br>
Embark on an adventure and cross 3 galaxies with more than 30 planets to explore. Enter gigantic beaches, huge deserts, desolate swamps, labyrinthine mines, and discover their secrets.<br/>
Practice makes a master: Endless and Multiplayer modes are here!<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the extensive Adventure mode, you can practice all your moves while getting prizes in the Endless mode. <br/>
Do you feel ready enough to be called the best Snake Galaxy Online player? Then you will have the chance to prove your worth in the PVP battles of 1vs1 and a Free for All mode that includes four players at the same time!<br/>
<br/>
Customize and be unique<br/>
<br/>
We are all different, why can't a snake be different too? Play any mode to unlock Hats, Skins and Avatars to change your snake's style and make your stay in Snake Galaxy Online a unique experience.<br/>
<br/>
—---------<br/>
<br/>
Snake Galaxy Online es el primero de muchos otros juegos que desde Vivid Unity Games queremos traer a Steam. Te damos la bienvenida a la familia y esperamos que disfrutes y te diviertas con nuestro trabajo.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Below</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2394440/The_Great_Below/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2394440/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong> The Great Below: Unravel the Tapestry of Reality</strong> <br/><br/>Step into a realm of enigmatic intrigue and existential tension in The Great Below, an avant-garde environmental experience that defies the boundaries of conventional horror. Embark on a mind-bending journey as you attempt to escape the haunting loop of a mansion steeped in mystery and malevolence. Will you find your path to salvation, or become ensnared within the labyrinth of your own mind?<br/><br/><strong>Synopsis</strong><br/><br/>Embark on an expedition unlike any other, driven by the clandestine motives of a secret society in pursuit of forbidden knowledge. You are the protagonist, a seeker of The Object - a sacred artifact whispered to bestow unparalleled enlightenment upon its possessor. Lost within the foreboding walls of an uncanny mansion, you must unravel its cryptic enigmas and transcend the boundaries of reason before your consciousness succumbs to the abyss.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2394440/extras/1.gif?t=1701783263"><br/><br/><strong>Unconventional Visual Poetry</strong><br/><br/>The Great Below shatters the conventions of horror gaming, reshaping your perspective through a unique blend of 2D and 3D visual storytelling. Traverse a surrealist dreamscape where camera angles dance with dimensions, forging an immersive experience that challenges your perceptions. The game's distinctive visual style harkens back to the tactile allure of analog textures, invoking a nostalgic homage to the iconic era of the PS1.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2394440/extras/2dmap.gif?t=1701783263"><br/><br/><strong>Strategic Enigma</strong><br/><br/>Survival hinges on your cunning as you navigate The Great Below's intricate web of tension and uncertainty. The mansion itself becomes your ally and adversary, where every corridor and hidden shortcut holds the key to your liberation.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2394440/extras/inventory.gif?t=1701783263"><br/><br/><strong>Unearth the Mythos</strong><br/><br/>Rituals weave the fabric of narrative in The Great Below, conjuring a tapestry of mythology and symbolism that beckons to those who revel in the occult. Plunge into a world where powerful mysticism and arcane secrets entwine, fueling a sense of dread and fascination. Immerse yourself in the experience, as you gradually uncover the deep-rooted lore that binds the mansion's unsettling presence.<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2394440/extras/6.gif?t=1701783263"><br/><br/><strong>Features</strong><br/><br/>- Challenge the conventions of horror with a groundbreaking fusion of camera perspectives and dimension-defying visuals. <br/><br/>- Immerse yourself in an analog-inspired aesthetic that harks back to the iconic era of the PS1, evoking a sense of nostalgia and atmospheric immersion. <br/><br/>- Unravel the threads of ancient rituals and symbolism, piecing together a minimalistic interpretative narrative that melds the uncanny with the mystic.<br/><br/>Embark on a transcendental journey where reality blurs, and consciousness bends. Ascension beckons, daring you to untangle its enigmatic riddles and ascend to a plane beyond mortal comprehension. Will you break free from the mansion's cyclical grasp, or become forever entwined in its eternal embrace?<br/><br/>Dare to ascend.						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walk the Past VR</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2319320/Walk_the_Past_VR/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319320/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Walk The Past VR is a narrated journey through history, created in collaboration with writer Sam Gohra. It allows you to go through detailed reconstructions of events, fortifications and environments during the battle of Cartagena in 1741.<br/><br/>Enjoy the sights, discover the landmarks, and learn about history.<br/><br/>A great effort was directed to the creation of 3D models of the fortifications and scenarios on which the user can move freely. You can take the main tour, guided by 2 narrators and listen to an enthralling and fully voice acted retelling of the battle. Apart from this you will be able to do exploratory activities at your discretion extending your experience. There are also fast travel options to places of interest, for specific experiences.<br/><br/><strong>Non VR mode is also available.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Collect objects scattered all around the locations and find your way by using your compass.</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319320/extras/compasssmall.png?t=1701778765"><br/><br/><strong>Read through beautifully written journals of fallen soldiers .</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319320/extras/readingsmall.png?t=1701778765"><br/><br/><strong>Mark the discovery of landmarks. </strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319320/extras/flagsmall.png?t=1701778765"><br/><br/><strong>We hope you enjoy your journey into the 18th century!</strong><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319320/extras/SanLuissmall.png?t=1701778765"><br/><br/><i>You’ve come a long way, traveller. Crossed vast oceans, sailing against the tides of time. Welcome to the Battle of Cartagena de Indias, 1741.<br/>Come with me. I will show you the beaches and the forests, the Castles and the forts, our first staggering steps in the sand and our final desperate climb.<br/><br/>So - would you care to come to shore?</i><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2319320/extras/BeachCampsmall.png?t=1701778765"> </img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Night Escape</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2463340/Night_Escape/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2463340/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							"Night Escape" is a thrilling and immersive multiplayer game set in a mysterious mansion. Step into a gripping battle for survival as a group of players, with one among them secretly playing the role of a cunning assassin. The objective? Uncover the identity of the killer while solving intricate puzzles and finding keys to unlock doors that lead to your escape.<br>
<br>
As tension fills the air, every decision counts. Engage in strategic gameplay, gather clues, and collaborate with your fellow players to outsmart the assassin before they strike you down. But beware, the assassin is relentless and will stop at nothing to eliminate their targets without being detected.<br>
<br>
Intrigue intensifies as bodies are discovered, triggering intense meetings where players must vote to identify the killer. As a slain player, you return as a ghost, capable of haunting the assassin by collecting keys from fallen bodies or stealing them from the assassin's own pockets. Your mission as a ghost is to disrupt the assassin's plans and protect the remaining innocent players.<br>
<br>
Prepare yourself for an adrenaline-pumping experience filled with suspense, mystery, and deadly encounters. Can you survive the night and unravel the secrets of the mansion, or will the killer reign supreme? It's a race against time, where trust is tested and survival hangs in the balance.						</br></br></br></br></br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Rocket Pudding</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2652110/Christmas_Rocket_Pudding/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2652110/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Control the pudding by accelerating and jumping. The only limit to your speed is how skillfully you can navigate the course!<br/>Features 15 levels, with 3 level modes:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Three lap sprint</li><li>Collect the candy canes</li><li>Blast the snowmen</li></ul>Fun for all ages. Merry Christmas!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OG Puzzlers: Kira Maus</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2692720/OG_Puzzlers_Kira_Maus/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2692720/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>OG Puzzlers: Kira Maus</strong> is an casual puzzel game with cute dog images. You have to assemble a single image from random generated indivdual pieces. <br/>Combine all of the smart singel frames into one big image and unlock the next level.<h2 class="bb_tag"><strong>features:</strong></h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li> 12 Levels<br/></li><li> 4x4 frames<br/></li><li> casual puzzle adventure<br/></li><li> auto saving<br/></li><li> simple mouse control<br/></li><li> 100 steam awards</li></ul> </div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Suika</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2686980/Planet_Suika/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2686980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Take your Suika stacking skills to a new planetary level in the Casual Puzzle Game Planet Suika! Combine smaller planets together to turn them into larger planets. Master the games Physics to combine the planets until you make a big Sun!<br>
<br>
Play the Single Player mode and try to combine two suns. Make sure to combine planets covered in star dust to double your points, use the meteor showers to rack up a high score!						</br></br></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnavody</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2695020/Magnavody/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2695020/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							The Magnavox Odyssey was the world’s first video game console. It was released in 1972 and by the time production stopped several years later it had sold over 350,000 units. In total 28 games were made for the Odyssey. The most famous game from the platform is "Table Tennis" which served as the direct inspiration for Atari's "Pong". <br/><br/>Not only was it the first console but the Odyssey is also a unique piece of hardware. There is no CPU or memory to emulate. Instead the Odyssey is a collection of circuit boards, each controlling a key element of the system such as the ball, the wall and each player's dot. It is a very misunderstood system!<br/><br/>Now you can experience the wonder and strangeness of the Odyssey with Magnavody! <br/><br/>Magnavody is an open source simulator of the Magnavox Odyssey with a focus on accuracy, historical authenticity and fun. Magnavody is a homage to the games on the system in a modern package designed to be played on modern hardware. Your Steam purchase supports future development.<br/><br/>Magnavody has the following features:<br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Emulates the system design of the Magnavox Odyssey (1972) - the unit controllers, cards, spot generators, gate matrix and flip-flops<br/></li><li>Magnavody Table Tennis - A homage to the original 1972 table tennis game<br/></li><li>Controller support designed to best simulate the strange and awkward dial controllers of the original<br/></li><li>Authentic 4:3 mode (see the games as they were originally presented)<br/></li><li>Optional enhanced widescreen (16:9) mode (see the games fill the screen as they were originally designed to do)<br/></li><li>Optional CRT overlays (add static, waves and other retro effects)<br/></li><li>Toggle on screen elements to choose your own level of immersion<br/></li><li>Two player support<br/></li><li>Some quality of life improvements such as "quick load" and "reset controllers" to make it easier to use.</li></ul><br/>Take a trip back in time and live the experience of the very first home video games. Our team includes an historian and great effort has been taken to not just recreate the design but also how it must have felt to be there. Here is just one example; In 1972 a full screen TV was in the aspect 4:3. Technical accuracy requires Magnavody to supply games in 4:3 aspect however we also have crafted a 16:9 aspect mode so modern players can recreate the "full screen" feel of playing the Odyssey. It's these thoughtful design decisions we hope we really transport people back in time to gain a genuine feel for this fascinating console.<br/><br/>With your support the intention is to progressively add more games to Magnavody (however your purchase is for Magnavody as is, there is no guarantee of future releases).<br/><br/>Magnvody is part game/part historical research project. Games for the Odyssey show a glimpse of a different type of console gaming experience, a world where video games mix with table top games, where the action is not just on the screen but in the room with the players. If you are a serious gamer or a game historian or a game developer, this project has a lot to offer.						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amberial Dreams</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/917140/Amberial_Dreams/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/header_alt_assets_2.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/202206_AD_Logo_STEAM.gif?t=1701781377"><br/><br/>Amberial Dreams is an evolving 2D physics-based precision platformer. Control a sphere and its speed through an enchanting universe filled with wonders and wicked levels. <br/><br/>5th game in the series of famous flash games, Amberial Dreams scales everything up whilst keeping true to its success formula, loved by more than 2 million players! Bringing a new engine, an exhaustive level editor and a narrative campaign full of colourful characters, Amberial Dreams is ready to launch in Early Access. <br/><br/>During this year of Early Access we will work closely with the community to add new levels, campaigns, traps, pieces and much more!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/BANNER_Simple_mechanics.png?t=1701781377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/202206_AD_Simple_mechanics_no_text_STEAM.gif?t=1701781377"><br/><br/>Rolling left and right, will you be able to tackle the challenge? <br/>Use the different surfaces to control your momentum, play in null gravity and interact with the many different pieces to finish more than 50 handcrafted levels. New levels and mechanics will also be added throughout Early Access!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/BANNER_Can_you_surpass.png?t=1701781377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/202206_AD_Can_you_surpass_no_text_STEAM.gif?t=1701781377"><br/><br/>Amberial Dreams offers a unique difficulty with wicked levels. Test your skill against pixel perfect levels filled with devilish traps. Only players having mastered the game can hope to finish them. Not to mention finishing the levels while recovering all the collectible moons. We tried... and we could not beat them all. Can you?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/BANNER_A_story_of_dreams_and_nightmare.png?t=1701781377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/202206_AD_dreams_and_nightmares_BANNER_STEAM.gif?t=1701781377"><br/><br/>Follow the story of Amber as she wakes up from her long slumber, alone, to find her former idyllic world transformed to the core. Incarnate her avatar and explore 4 different biomes, each with their own gameplay twists and narrative. Change the world as you progress and uncover hidden secrets. Where are your missing sisters and why did everything change so drastically?<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/BANNER_Design_your_own_level.png?t=1701781377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/GAMEPLAY_design_your_own_levels_no_text.gif?t=1701781377"><br/><br/>We give the players the same tools we used to develop the game.  We wanted to offer you the best experience with the ability to customize every level you have beaten in the campaign or to create your own with dozens of unique pieces. Carefully place portals, deadly moving spikes, gravity rays and so much more to craft your own playfield. You will never run out of possibilities with the addition of new elements throughout Early Access. <br/><br/>Once you are happy with your levels, share them with the world and explore theirs! Thanks to a powerful tagging and research tool, find the levels that you want to play or give the featured ones a try! <br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/BANNER_We_care.png?t=1701781377"><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/917140/extras/202206_Amberial_static_STEAM.png?t=1701781377"><br/><br/><strong>Join our official Discord server!</strong> The community is an essential part of our game, and we want to build it with you!						</img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D PrintMaster Simulator Printer</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2427000/3D_PrintMaster_Simulator_Printer/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2427000/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<h2 class="bb_tag">3D PrintMaster </h2>offers a realistic and in-depth simulation of the exciting world of 3D printing. Start by assembling your first 3D printer from various parts, using tools like wrenches, hexagons, and screws. As you progress, you'll have the opportunity to upgrade your printers, buy better materials, and take on more challenging orders. Manage your workshop effectively to maximize profits and grow your business!<h2 class="bb_tag">Assemble and Upgrade your first Printer</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2427000/extras/build2.gif?t=1701770805"><br/><br/>Assemble and Upgrade: Buy printer parts, assemble printers, and upgrade them to create a powerful and efficient 3D printing workshop.<br/>Realistic Assembly Experience: Use tools like wrenches, hexagons, and screws to put together your 3D printers, ensuring a hands-on and engaging gameplay experience.<h2 class="bb_tag">Watch the most satisfying process of printing your first object</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2427000/extras/print.gif?t=1701770805"><br/><br/>Print and Fulfill Orders: Take on customer orders and print 3D objects, ranging from simple to complex designs. Complete orders on time to build your reputation and earn money.<br/>Material and Printer Management: Purchase and manage different types of plastic materials to unlock better orders and increase your workshop's capabilities.<h2 class="bb_tag">Buy and Unpack Printer Parts</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2427000/extras/boxes.gif?t=1701770805"><br/><br/>Creative Mode: Unleash your creativity in the game's creative mode, where you can access all printer parts and materials to build and design without limitations.<br/>Sell and Trade: Sell old printer parts and materials to make room for new, more advanced equipment, and keep your workshop up-to-date with the latest technology.<br/><br/>Thriving Economy: Navigate a dynamic in-game economy where supply and demand determine the value of your 3D printed creations and materials.<h2 class="bb_tag">Money Money Money 🤑🤑🤑</h2><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2427000/extras/cash.gif?t=1701770805"><br/><br/>In 3D PrintMaster, you'll have the opportunity to experience the thrill of running your very own 3D printing workshop, from assembly to management. With its realistic assembly mechanics, diverse range of printer parts, and dynamic economy, this game is perfect for anyone interested in 3D printing or looking for an immersive and enjoyable simulation experience. Are you ready to become the ultimate 3D PrintMaster?						</img></img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Cricket Mod Creator</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2626650/Real_Cricket_Mod_Creator/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2626650/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Software</h2>
							Real Cricket Mod Creator is an app created by Nautilus Mobile - the creators of the hit mobile-cricket franchise Real Cricket. This app lets you create and customise in-game assets of Real Cricket and publish it straight to the Real Cricket servers. These assets will then be available for download on your favourite game on mobile – Real Cricket<br/><br/><strong>Tournaments:</strong>  Edit and customise more than 50 Tournaments of Real Cricket such that the user can change the name of the tournament and its logo by simply uploading an image.<br/><br/><strong>Teams: </strong> With more than 450 cricket teams on offer, users can customise his favourite team starting with renaming the team to uploading a new logo and some advanced customisation features to edit and customise the team jerseys to your liking.<br/><br/><strong>Player: </strong> Customise your favourite cricketers in the game by simply filtering out the tournaments and teams which they represent and unlocking a host of customisation options starting with changing their name, jersey number, jersey name and advanced customisation options for editing their faces, hand color, shape, hair and size of their head and body.<br/><br/>This app lets you create your own tournaments, teams and players and download it directly to your favourite mobile game – Real Cricket making it one of the few games on mobile which lets you customise everything to your liking and never know boredom ever again!						</div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Bear's Bizarre Adventure</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2264950/Mr_Bears_Bizarre_Adventure/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2264950/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
							Player will act as a bear who master in Chinese blade. He travels around the world and challenging Kungfu masters from various countries:<br/>the guardian warrior at the Inari Shrine, the skeleton king in the dark dungeon and the pirate captain from the Caribbean sea....<br/>We even adapted different music styles for each themed level: traditional Japanese sounds, Shamisen music, Lo-Fi, HipHop, Trap, and Reggae!<br/> <img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2264950/extras/熊先生-歌曲.gif?t=1701766936"><h2 class="bb_tag">Characteristic</h2><ul class="bb_ul"><li>：Base the music rhythm, fight with your opponent,<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2264950/extras/近战.gif?t=1701766936"><br/></img></li><li>Different enemies feature in various attack style. Players can identify the attack direction and beat back accordingly,<br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2264950/extras/远程1.gif?t=1701766936"><br/></img></li><li>During the music highlight, players can use combo hit unlimitedly.</li></ul><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2264950/extras/无限.gif?t=1701766936"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2264950/extras/远景.gif?t=1701766936"> </img></img></img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremely Powerful Capybaras</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2089980/Extremely_Powerful_Capybaras/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<strong>These unique Capybaras will fight for their survival in this chaotic bullet heaven roguelite adventure! Whether you are solo or with a team, face hordes of enemies, collect coins, unlock weapons and skills, and become the mightiest capybaras of all!</strong><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/mighty.png?t=1701767997"><br/><ul class="bb_ul"><li>Unleash the capy-power with a diverse range of capybara heroes, each boasting unique classes, weapons, and combat styles! Whether you're a mighty Warrior or a melodious Bard, prepare to face hordes of enemies in style!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/EPC_CapyHeroes.gif?t=1701767997"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/assemble.png?t=1701767997"><br/></img></img></li><li>Are you a lone capy-warrior or a squad commander? Take on the adventure solo or team up with your capy-comrades through <strong>Online</strong> or Local Co-op for a fur-ocious fight!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/EPC_Arena2BossGif.gif?t=1701767997"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/powers.png?t=1701767997"><br/></img></img></li><li>Every run brings a fresh set of randomized skills and passives! Pick the perfect combo to complement your capy-build and make each run a unique and thrilling experience. Mix, match, and conquer!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/EPC_NewLevelUpGifresized.gif?t=1701767997"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/coins.png?t=1701767997"><br/></img></img></li><li>Earned a hoard of Capy-Coins during your daring runs? Time to give your abilities a capy-boost! Visit the Upgrade Shop to exchange your well-earned coins for powerful ability upgrades. Enhance your gameplay, optimize your strategies, and unleash even greater capy-chaos!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/EPC_AbilityShopGif.gif?t=1701767997"><br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/chill.png?t=1701767997"><br/></img></img></li><li>Before diving into the action, indulge in some capybara-style relaxation by chilling in the hot springs. Savor the calm before the storm, as you and your companions gear up to showcase your Extremely Powerful Capybaras!<br/><br/><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2089980/extras/HotSpringsGif.gif?t=1701767997"/></li></ul> </img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Game Is Easy</title>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2493630/This_Game_Is_Easy/?snr=1_239_new__tab-AllNewReleases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493630/header.jpg" /><br/><div style="text-align: center;"><div class="game_area_description" id="game_area_description">
<h2>About This Game</h2>
<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2493630/extras/1.png?t=1701765925"><br/><br/>The easy adventure game you've been waiting for has finally arrived! In this game, you take on the role of a player travelling through stunning landscapes, solving puzzles and overcoming obstacles to reach the end. You'll meet a fascinating character who will help you on your way, or try to stop you. With stunning graphics, this game will be an unforgettable experience for all players. So get ready for adventure and excitement in this fantastic world!						</img></div></div>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
